Chapter 886: Crying Miniman

Northern Plains, in a certain secluded area, Luo Po valley.

Souls were wailing, thunder roared and lightning struck down. The light of fire shined everywhere, and explosions rang out continuously.

A huge, intense battle was ongoing.

The defending side was Shadow Sect, whose members had resolutely abandoned Lang Ya blessed land and came back, Qin Bai Sheng, Fairy Jiang Yu, Hui Feng Zi, He Lang Zi and others.

Immortal killer move — Soul Suppression!

Qin Bai Sheng grunted, stepping forward in the endless light and fire.

Bam bam bam!

Three intense explosions sounded out, Qin Bai Sheng had forced back three invading Gu Immortals with an overwhelming momentum, giving a feeling of an impenetrable fortress.

'I, the grand Chen Zhen Chi, actually lost three times in a row against a single Gu Immortal, and in one move each time?!' The Gu Immortal from Myriad Dragon Dock, Chen Zhen Chi, stabilized himself with difficulty and looked at Qin Bai Sheng with shock and fury.

'Damn it... it was not easy to organize a wave of offense, and it was actually broken by him so easily.' Bu Fei Yan gritted her teeth as blood seeped out of her lips.

'This soul path killer move is really too strong, who could have expected Qin Bai Sheng's true strength to be so strong! Old Oracle's deduction was really correct, this guy is very likely to be the culprit of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's destruction!' Old Man Tian Long thought.

The group that was attacking Luo Po valley was none other than the group of Gu Immortals from Central Continent's ten great ancient sects.

When their objectives could not be achieved in Snowy Mountain blessed land, Feng Jiu Ge was not discouraged and directed them appropriately, finding many secrets and clues.

After going through Old Oracle's deduction, the group of immortals found the location of Luo Po valley and hurried over.

However, Luo Po valley had already been in Shadow Sect's possession for a long time, and had a powerful defensive Gu formation. While Central Continent's Gu Immortals were being delayed by this, Qin Bai Sheng and the others had retreated from Lang Ya blessed land, coming to reinforce immediately.

Thus, the current situation was formed.

Both sides were in a deadlock.

Central Continent's group wanted to invade Luo Po valley, while Shadow Sect's group was defending their base tightly.

Transformation path killer move — Fragrant Sorcerer Yin Statue Wolf Transformation!

Wind path killer move — Death Wind Flying Blade!

He Lang Zi and Hui Feng Zi saw the Central Continent Gu Immortals suffering setbacks, immediately grasping the opportunity to counterattack incisively.

Fairy Ling Mei and Fairy Ao Xue from Heaven's Envy Manor were no match against the intense attacks, and could only retreat without any power to fight back.

Immortal killer move — Green Jade Song!

At the crucial moment, Feng Jiu Ge took action, using an extraordinary sound path killer move.

He Lang Zi and Hui Feng Zi suffered intense damage and fell back.

Hui Feng Zi retreated back to the defensive Gu formation, spitting out over ten mouthfuls of blood in succession. This blood had changed into a deep green jade color.

He Lang Zi's injuries were even more severe, the fragrant sorcerer yin statue wolf he had transformed into had mostly changed into jade stones, he was extremely shocked: "What immortal killer move is this? It seems to restrain transformation path! I am actually not able to change back to human form. It looks like I have to resolve this injury before I can transform again."

"Feng Jiu Ge!" Qin Bai Sheng shouted furiously, his voice spreading over the whole battlefield.

"Qin Bai Sheng, I underestimated you. Previously I was actually deceived by you, I am far beneath you in terms of acting skills. Fortunately, my side has a wisdom path Gu Immortal and without stinting on the expenditure of lifespan, he was able to successfully deduce the location of this Luo Po valley." Feng Jiu Ge was still dressed in a red and white robe.

His posture was straight, like a spear or sword. Right now, he was speaking with a slight smile, his tone was articulate and extremely graceful.

"Successful deduction, my ass! I have no relation with the destruction of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. But since you came, your life will end here." Qin Bai Sheng slowly closed his eyes and lowered his head.

He placed his hands together in front of his chest, then he grabbed his left palm with his right hand and formed a fist, which he raised high above his head.

When they saw this stance, the expressions of the Central Continent Gu Immortals started changing to that of shock and bewilderment, and they started retreating.

Only Feng Jiu Ge stood on the spot, like he was nailed between heaven and earth, and would not move even if a storm battered him.

He looked at Qin Bai Sheng's stance with bright eyes: "This move, could it be Sword Immortal Bo Qing's five finger fist heart sword?"

"Correct." Qin Bai Sheng replied: "Are you prepared to die?"

Feng Jiu Ge laughed heartily, his expression was one of excitement: "Good, good, wonderful. Sword Immortal Bo Qing is my senior in Spirit Affinity House, he failed in his tribulation and his killer move inheritance also mysteriously disappeared. Spirit Affinity House did not obtain it, but it instead landed in a Northern Plains Gu Immortal's hands. But I have read relevant records in the sect, this five finger fist heart sword is extremely powerful and sharp. It is rumored that back then, Lord Sword Immortal Bo Qing felt the majesty of Heaven and Earth, and the difficulty of ascension, thus he created this move to show his courage and pride of resisting heaven and earth by himself."

"So this move's stance is quite peculiar, the person who uses it must confront heaven and earth, lowering their head and closing their eyes. It seems like an admission of defeat, but they are in truth using all their physical and mental strength to produce and unleash the sharpest attack. The fist above their head shows how incomparably bold Sword Immortal Bo Qing was. As the saying goes, I decide my own fate, not heaven, with a sword at my heart, I advance in sword path."

Feng Jiu Ge was not the least bit nervous in facing the legendary killer move, instead he was speaking with confidence.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals behind him were influenced by this, and the fear in their minds gradually dissipated. This made them have even more admiration of Feng Jiu Ge's temperament.

"Hmph, you know quite a lot, it seems you have a premonition of your defeat and death." Qin Bai Sheng sneered.

Feng Jiu Ge shook his head and smiled brightly: "By fortunate coincidence, I have created a sound path killer move, inspired during a certain time period. During my cultivation journey, I've discovered heaven and earth, faced heaven and earth, and revered heaven and earth, I felt the vastness of nature, felt how minute and weak I was. I named this song 'heaven and earth song'! Heaven and earth is so vast, while humans are so insignificant. This song borrows the strength of heaven and earth, using an incomparable might to suppress all resistance!"

On one side was the vast might of heaven and earth, in accordance with the course of nature and with boundless force, while the other side was about defying heaven's will by oneself, with the will of sword path, pressing forward indomitably.

These two moves were complete opposites of each other.

In the end, would it be heaven and earth song or five finger fist heart sword that emerges victorious?

The tempo of the whole battlefield slowed down for a moment.

Everyone's gazes were on Feng Jiu Ge and Qin Bai Sheng.

Even Qin Bai Sheng showed a peculiar look, and while still having his eyes closed, he spoke: "Oh? Then this fight is going to be truly interesting. Take this, first finger!"

...

Light illuminated Heavenly Court.

Eternal and indestructible.

The giant image in the air, formed by the refinement path Gu formation, was no longer dazzling, its radiance was completely restrained.

"Good, the first stage is finished, all the materials have been processed. The second stage is to draw in heaven's will!" Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord said after he inspected it once.

"Draw in heaven's will..." Fairy Cang Shui mumbled.

Lian Jiu Sheng and Bi Chen Tian also bore serious expressions.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord continued to explain: "Heaven's will is also known as the will of heaven and earth! Humans have will, heaven and earth also has will. Compared to heaven and earth, humans are tiny like ants, lowly like sand, they are basically not worthy of being mentioned. Heaven's will is the most important immortal material to restore fate Gu. Now, it will be an extremely long and arduous process of managing this refinement path Gu formation. Because we need to resist heaven's will, heaven's will is boundless, we cannot let it ruin our minds, otherwise we will suffer extremely severe injuries or even die! Heavenly Court has lost quite a few rank eight Gu Immortals in this process. More preparation may quicken the speed of work, now we will take turns to rest and recover."

"Alright!"

...

Central Continent, Hu Immortal blessed land.

A piece of lamb that was as large as cattle was laid out in front of Fang Yuan, dripping in blood.

Fang Yuan sat on the ground and tore a portion of the meat, and put it in his mouth.

His basin-sized mouth chewed continuously for a moment before swallowing it.

Trickles of blood flowed out from the gaps between his sharp teeth, and seeped out of his lips. Fang Yuan's face, however, showed a satisfied and happy expression.

This lamb was not ordinary meat, but was the meat of a giant horned sheep.

Fang Yuan had captured a live strength path desolate beast, giant horned sheep, previously in Northern Plains, right now he was using eat strength Immortal Gu to devour the meat and increase the strength path dao marks on his body.

"I am a strength path Gu Immortal after all, strength path dao marks are my foundation."

Fang Yuan kept eating while looking back mentally over the defensive battle of Lang Ya blessed land.

In this battle, Fang Yuan had first tested vaguely familiar face, deceiving almost everyone, the effect satisfied him.

Secondly, he used star path killer moves in actual battle.

Star cloud grindstone, star snake rope, six illusion star bodies and position star swap.

Actual battle was vastly different from normal practice. Fang Yuan was able to comprehend an additional layer of understanding regarding these four immortal killer moves through the battle.

Naturally, Star Lord Wan Xiang's star path inheritance did not have just these four killer moves.

However, Fang Yuan could only use these four currently.

Because he only had three star path Immortal Gu - Star Mark, Starlight and Star Shoot. These three Immortal Gu were used in turns as the cores of the four star path killer moves.

Star Lord Wan Xiang had four Immortal Gu but one was destroyed in battle. Thus, only three ended up in Fang Yuan's hands.

"I had thought of using the light of wisdom to deduce some strength path immortal killer moves to make up for my weak points. But these star path killer moves are quite good and can be of use for now, there is no need for me to waste my time and energy."

Through this battle of defense in Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan was able to gain an even more clear understanding of his own battle strength.

"When considering star path killer moves, my battle strength is already firmly at the peak of rank six. Just based on the offensive aspect, with myriad self, my battle strength can match rank seven. But I am still quite far away from being able to fight with veteran rank seven Gu Immortals, and can only try my best to pester and stall them. As for Qin Bai Sheng, I have no hope of matching him, he is a quasi rank eight, an expert like Feng Jiu Ge!"

This battle made Fang Yuan truly recognize the power of Qin Bai Sheng.

Due to this, in the entire battle, Fang Yuan generally did not use his full strength and was basically going with the flow. Only at the last juncture did he display myriad self giant hand.

Under such a situation, being high profile was seeking death.

From start to finish, Fang Yuan had placed some of his attention to controlling Fixed Immortal Travel constantly. Once something went wrong, he was ready to immediately retreat.

"Who is this Qin Bai Sheng? His true strength is actually so great! Hei Cheng, Jiang Yu, Hui Feng Zi, and the others, why are they together? Qin Bai Sheng seems to be their leader, and with Hei Cheng in their group, Hei Lou Lan's revenge is probably hopeless. Now that I think about it, the hidden details regarding Lang Ya blessed land run very deep, there is more than meets the eye."

In the memories of Fang Yuan's previous life, Lang Ya blessed land had resisted seven waves of attacks.

But now, just in this fourth wave, there were signs of not being able to resist.

What was the truth in history? Was it because of influence from Fang Yuan that Lang Ya blessed land's situation had changed?

A thick fog had appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

"Even if I was in perfect condition, when facing Qin Bai Sheng, especially that immortal killer move soul suppression, I simply wouldn't have any strength to strike back. Truly powerless."

Fang Yuan gazed down at his hand, his hand was stained with blood.

Compared to Qin Bai Sheng, Fang Yuan seemed like this giant horned sheep which could only allow itself to be slaughtered by another.

Heaven and earth was vast, nature was boundless. The more one knew, the more they would find out how ignorant they are. The stronger one became, the more they would find how weak they are.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> had an interesting account.

Boundless Forest Samsara was separated from her father, Ren Zu, and could only stay in ordinary abyss.

She was heartbroken, and did not feel happy eating the fruits anymore.

Every day, she would shed tears and weep incessantly, until she got tired and gradually fell asleep.

In a dream of hers, she vaguely heard some extremely soft voices, and felt something small, like an ant was climbing her body.

Immediately, she woke up and sat up, and saw a miniman was climbing on her body.

Because of Boundless Forest Samsara's movement, this miniman's foothold became unstable and it fell to the ground.

"Who are you? There is actually such a small person like you in the world?" Boundless Forest Samsara saw the miniman that was not even the size of her finger, and felt extremely curious, forgetting to cry for a moment.

The miniman looked at the giant Boundless Forest Samsara with a stupefied look, and after the shock, he raised his head and started crying loudly.

"Hey hey hey, little person, I am not crying, what are you crying for?" Boundless Forest Samsara was puzzled.

The miniman spoke while crying: "I am the tallest in my tribe, and I was brave, arrogant and proud because of this. Today, I intended to climb a mountain, but to think that this mountain was really a person. There are actually such giant people like you in the world, this is the first time I've seen someone like you, so I burst into tears!"

Almost every person who explored and grew up, would have such a mental journey.

The more they saw, the more they realized their weaknesses. Sometimes they would sigh at the vastness of the world, and sometimes they would find how far their goal was and to reach their goal, they had to go through an endless journey which they had not considered before. They would feel loss, bewilderment, discouragement, panic, even hopelessness.

Thus, one could understand the miniman crying when it saw Boundless Forest Samsara.

"Thinking back to my previous life, I also was once perplexed and had 'cried'. There are mountains beyond mountains, and experts beyond experts. There are always stronger existences than me, eternal life is too far away, how could my insignificant self achieve it?"

Fang Yuan gazed at his bloody palm and was lost in thought for a while.

After a long time, he suddenly smiled, revealing his sharp fangs.

"Still too weak. Whether it was my previous life or this life, I am like that miniman that wanted to climb the mountain."

"But... my insignificance won't be an excuse to stop chasing after the grandness."

"Only the cowardly and defeated will look for excuses."

"Even if tears are shed and snot flows out, I will continue to climb the mountain, this is the pleasure of life."

As he thought of this, Fang Yuan ripped apart another portion of bloody meat and bit it.

The sharp teeth ruthlessly chewed at the meat, trickles of fresh blood seeped out of his lips.

Chapter 887: Short Break

Half a month later.

In Fang Yuan's dead immortal aperture, two wills were in a fierce struggle.

One will was like specks of starlight, flickering brightly. The other will was illusory, suddenly going in and retreating just as suddenly.

They were a star will and a fake will.

These two wills had already fought for seven minutes. The star will was slowly unable to keep up with the fake will, and was showing signs of losing.

However, with a shift of Fang Yuan's mind, a new portion of will descended from the sky and joined the battle like reinforcements, immediately changing the battle situation.

In the end, the fake will was defeated miserably with only a few fragments of it remaining.

"Fang, Fang Yuan, you... will die... a terrible death..." The fake will could not condense into any form, and used all its strength to curse in a stammering voice.

A curse from such a weak being was simply of no importance.

The star will won, it condensed into Fang Yuan's image and sneered while glancing at Mo Yao's fake will, before it flew to the sky and left the dead immortal aperture.

"I have already made large progress in battles of wills. Now, in a one versus one, although I cannot defeat Mo Yao and am defeated every time, Mo Yao's will also doesn't have an easy time, and recently all her victories are achieved with difficulty."

While Fang Yuan was evaluating himself inwardly, the star will entered his mind and the information received this time appeared in his mind.

Fang Yuan originally had no expectations, but the information this time gave him a slight surprise.

"Spring dream fruit tree?" Fang Yuan's mind jolted.

During her travels in the outside world, Mo Yao had once unexpectedly found a spring dream fruit tree near a nameless hamlet.

At that time, the conceptualization of dream path was very minimal and there were no external manifestation of dream realms, even Heavenly Court's exploration of dream realms was extremely shallow.

Mo Yao only felt the tree was somewhat strange, she did not recognize it, so she engraved it in her mind.

She left this spring dream fruit tree in its place and did not move it.

Spring dream fruit tree was not a desolate plant and looked ordinary, normal Gu Immortals would not be able to find anything wrong. It was only because Mo Yao's investigative killer move was rather unique that she discovered some strange points about the spring dream fruit tree.

But she was only slightly curious, it was not an immortal material after all. Later, because of other matters, she did not visit that hamlet again.

That spring dream fruit tree all along had been left there.

Time brings great changes, so many years had gone by, who knew what had happened to that tree.

Perhaps it was already cut down by mortals, maybe it was destroyed by fire or maybe it was still there.

The possibilities were too many, it was anyone's guess.

"This old hag, Mo Yao, is still hard to deal with! She suppressed this memory in the deepest layers, until she could no longer hide it and I found it. But according to this state, almost all the things she knew have been squeezed out by me."

Fang Yuan suppressed the thought to go and take the spring dream fruit tree.

In fact, he had also obtained another valuable clue earlier.

It was in regards to hibiscus stalactites, this was a genuine immortal material.

However, when he had secretly gone to that place, he discovered the main area was already secretly occupied by Spirit Affinity House.

Fang Yuan thought for a while before deciding not to go.

Therefore, Fang Yuan did not hold much hope in regards to the spring dream fruit tree. Moreover, to retrieve the spring dream fruits, he had to use special dream path methods and also make other preparations.

"If there truly are spring dream fruits, they will be of huge help to me in refining dream path mortal Gu. After all, the materials used in refining dream path Gu worms are truly scarce."

Ever since he got the immortal killer move unravel dream, no matter how busy he was, Fang Yuan would spend some time almost every day to refine dream path mortal Gu.

If he had spring dream fruits, it would be of great help in refining these dream path mortal Gu. Even with a conservative estimation, the efficiency of refining the Gu would multiply by at least times!

The extremely weak Mo Yao's will was left in the dead immortal aperture to slowly recover.

Fang Yuan opened his eyes and left his bed, moving to Dang Hun palace's prison.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was held captive here, he was lying on a stone bed, his eyes vacantly gazing at the ceiling without moving.

Immortal Crane Sect had abandoned him, and this to him was an extremely heavy impact.

After the initial hysterical shouting and wailing, Fang Zheng had turned into this state.

Fang Yuan began to speak.

Even if his voice was filled with ridicule, or belittling and cursing Immortal Crane Sect as well as Lord Sky Crane, Fang Zheng did not respond.

Fang Yuan did not mind and continued to speak for a while before leaving.

Reeducating his little brother required time and could not be done in one step. Fang Yuan had already expected this and also did not lack patience.

Every set interval of time, he would take the initiative to visit Fang Zheng.

In Dang Hun palace, he could completely monitor Fang Zheng's every action from far away. The true intention behind Fang Yuan personally arriving was to let Fang Zheng know he had visited.

Fang Yuan left the area and entered another prison.

Up to this point, Fang Yuan's prisons had already held many prisoners.

Other than Mo Yao's fake will and Gu Yue Fang Zheng, there was Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul, the rank seven featherman Gu Immortal Zheng Ling's soul, and finally, Xue Song Zi's soul, which he had captured in the battle of Lang Ya blessed land.

Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul was already completely searched by Fang Yuan and the only value it had left was the soul itself.

Meanwhile, the souls of Zheng Ling and Xue Song Zi still had great value.

Over these last days after returning from Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan had been constantly soul searching these two.

The gains were considerable, large numbers of mortal Gu recipes, many mortal killer moves, some immortal killer moves, a few Immortal Gu recipes, as well as secret knowledge, many treasure-troves and clues to inheritances.

However, because Zheng Ling was a wind path Gu Immortal and Xue Song Zi was a snow path Gu Immortal, these were not suitable for Fang Yuan's strength path or star path.

Before Fang Yuan got hold of wind path Immortal Gu or snow path Immortal Gu, these things could only increase his accumulation and strengthen his foundation.

One thing worth noting was that Xue Song Zi's soul had been tampered with, and his most recent memories were erased. Thus, Fang Yuan did not know why Xue Song Zi and Hei Cheng were in cahoots with Qin Bai Sheng.

Such a soul path method was extremely profound, making Fang Yuan lost in wonder and unable to do anything.

Naturally, the souls of Zheng Ling and Xue Song Zi were still not completely searched, the future gains were still unknown variables.

As for Lang Ya land spirit's reward, it was indeed extremely bountiful.

Fang Yuan not only received the previously agreed upon rank six Immortal Gu recipe of all-out effort Gu, moreover under Fang Yuan's persistence, Lang Ya land spirit fully imparted the method to relocate a blessed land to Fang Yuan.

These were only two rewards, but they had extremely huge value to Fang Yuan.

There was no need to mention the value of all-out effort Gu's Immortal Gu recipe, speaking instead of the method of relocating a blessed land.

Whether it be Hu Immortal blessed land or Star Form blessed land, both needed to be moved urgently.

But the cost of this method was extraordinary and would inflict huge damage to the blessed land itself, and it required using twelve Immortal Gu at the same time. Lang Ya land spirit had already prepared to relocate Lang Ya blessed land.

After the relocation, he would lend these Immortal Gu to Fang Yuan for Fang Yuan to relocate his blessed lands.

Naturally, the price of borrowing these Gu was very high.

Chapter 888: Entering Eastern Sea

Two months later.

At a certain place in Eastern Sea.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng stood quietly on a cloud, waiting for Shark Demon and others.

The sun was setting now, causing a huge area of clouds with a burning red appearance to the west, even the sea underneath them was dyed red.

Waves after waves appeared in the sea, under such elegant turbulence, the last rays of light shone brightly onto these water droplets, they were bright and red. Together with the burning red looking clouds, a beautiful scene was formed.

"Every time I see such a beautiful sight, I will stop and immerse myself in this atmosphere, sighing at the marvels of nature." Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a deep gaze as he sighed: "Right now, I am someone who has succeeded in immortal ascension, but I can feel that this world is still so grand and majestic, it makes one feel like they are an insignificant insect, having a great sense of inferiority. Comparing mankind to heaven, we are really insignificant. Maybe only rank nine Gu Venerables would have the qualifications to contest with heaven and earth, I have no such hope."

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Brother Tai Bai, don't think too lowly of yourself. Do you remember from \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, that story of the miniman, when we recognize that we are tiny and insignificant, we have to try and get even stronger. We are tiny, but to stop being ignorant and become wise, you will feel pain, because that shows you are growing."

"Xing Xiang Zi, you still have such grand ambitions. Hahaha..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng was stunned for a moment before he laughed as well.

The two were still conversing, when a Gu Immortal emerged from the sea below them.

"Who is this?" Fang Yuan shouted.

"Lords, please calm down, my name is Sha Nan Jiang, I was sent by Lord Shark Demon to invite both of you over." The person smiled as he introduced himself.

Sha Nan Jiang's body rose up, in a few breaths of time, he arrived at Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng's location.

He was a rank six immortal zombie.

His body was strong and muscular, he had a bald head with a copper band on it, he had icy blue eyes and his skin was like old tree bark, his arms and legs were exposed on the outside, his fingers were webbed, his ears looked like fish fins, they were sharp and extended towards the back of his head.

Fang Yuan twiddled his fingers, suddenly asking: "Scenic blue travel immortal zombie body?"

Sha Nan Jiang's mild smile froze, he stared at Fang Yuan as he cupped his fists: "Sir must be the wisdom path Gu Immortal Xing Xiang Zi? Impressive, my scenic blue travel immortal zombie body was self-created, I have just come out of closed cultivation, I have not told anybody. Sir only made a small deduction and actually found out its name."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan chuckled: "I am not a wisdom path Gu Immortal, I mainly cultivate star path, I only secondarily cultivate wisdom path. Earlier, I was just guessing randomly, I was lucky to have been correct."

Fang Yuan was very humble.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng watched at the side, laughing to himself inwardly.

This was the first time Tai Bai Yun Sheng met this Sha Nan Jiang. Thus, the scene earlier occurred.

Sha Nan Jiang used an immortal killer move to sneak over here, when he reached the sea beneath Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, his traces were exposed by Fang Yuan.

This was the probing of Sha Nan Jiang.

But soon, Fang Yuan retaliated and deduced the name of Sha Nan Jiang's immortal zombie body.

When Gu Immortals interact, their strength was the most important thing. After some mutual probing, they could win each other's respect.

Sha Nan Jiang no longer dared to be careless, he showed a serious expression.

He nodded to Fang Yuan, having a respectful expression, before turning his gaze to Tai Bai Yun Sheng: "Please follow me, Lord Shark Demon and the others are already attacking Yu Lu blessed land."

A moment later, the three of them dived into the seawater and saw a door at the bottom of the sea.

This door was circular and had a light color, it looked like porcelain or jade. Chains of water crystal pearls lined the top of the door as they hung, forming a veil and blocking the entrance.

Fang Yuan's eyes showed a look of curiosity.

He would definitely not think that this door that had suddenly appeared was made of jade.

This was the entrance of Yu Lu blessed land, it only showed its outer appearance, but its true purpose was to act as the connection between Yu Lu blessed land and the outside world.

The entrance was extremely significant to small worlds like blessed lands and grotto-heavens.

Once the entrance was closed, the immortal aperture world would become an enclosed small world, isolated from the outside world. If Gu Immortals from outside the immortal aperture wanted to enter, it would be extremely difficult.

One could say, the entrance was the first difficulty to tackle when invading a blessed land.

Back then, Immortal Crane Sect's He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu worked together to attack Fang Yuan's Hu Immortal blessed land. In order to solve the problem of the entrance, they used Fang Zheng and a blood path method to locate it. Only after locating the blessed land did they enter Hu Immortal blessed land.

Qin Bai Sheng and the others invaded Lang Ya blessed land, they also made use of the souls of the hairy man Gu Immortal undercover agents to locate it and enter Lang Ya blessed land.

Thus, even if Fang Yuan did not capture Fang Zheng to use Blood Deity, he would still need to be concerned about the safety of Hu Immortal blessed land and deal with Fang Zheng. In that case, there would be no way of tracking him. Even if they knew the location of Hu Immortal blessed land precisely, even if they could break the space between the two worlds, they could not connect to the inside of the blessed land.

As the three arrived in front of the light jade door, Sha Nan Jiang activated his Gu worms as the crystal veil of the entrance lifted, and the door opened.

"Sirs, please enter." Sha Nan Jiang invited.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng saw this and smiled: "Your alliance has formidable methods, you can already control the entrance."

Sha Nan Jiang smiled lightly: "Sir Tai Bai might not know, ever since the failure two months ago, Lord Shark Demon returned to the Zombie Alliance headquarters and spend a huge sum of contribution points to request for the help of a rank seven wisdom path immortal zombie. Right now, we have already gotten through the round of vanishing immortal essence dissipation rain, and entered deeper within. This entrance was also completely under our alliance's control since a month ago."

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded, they stepped into Yu Lu blessed land.

After entering the blessed land, they did not see Yu Lu blessed land's true appearance, instead they were inside a frozen world that was completely white.

"This is the third round after vanishing immortal essence dissipation rain, it is a battlefield killer move called freezing rain frozen earth. Every hour, there would be intense freezing rain, as well as attacks from snow monsters. Lord Shark Demon and the rest are just up ahead." Sha Nan Jiang introduced.

"Freezing rain frozen earth..." Fang Yuan muttered lightly, he gazed around, showcasing huge interest regarding this battlefield killer move.

He had already eliminated his earlier weakness after gaining several star path techniques.

Be it attack, defense, movement, investigation, or healing, he had no apparent gaps.

Even in terms of investigation, Fang Yuan had an immortal killer move. Not long ago, Sha Nan Jiang was exposed by Fang Yuan, that was because of a star path investigative immortal killer move.

His current battle strength was firmly at the peak of rank six. If he used myriad self, he would reach rank seven battle strength.

What Fang Yuan lacked now was a battlefield killer move.

If he had a battlefield killer move, he could kill a Northern Plains Zombie Alliance immortal zombie secretly, taking over their identity and infiltrating the place.

For this goal, Fang Yuan sought Fairy Li Shan for help, but she rejected him.

Fang Yuan racked his brains over it, he was an astute person, he found another method to take a step back and make an alternative goal, he decided to get into Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's headquarters.

Thus, he used the appearance and identity of an ordinary star path Gu Immortal, Xing Xiang Zi, and came to Eastern Sea with Tai Bai Yun Sheng, intentionally getting close to Shark Demon and the others.

"Brother Tai Bai, we meet again. Hahaha!" A moment later, when everyone met, Shark Demon was extremely enthusiastic.

He patted Tai Bai Yun Sheng's shoulder and directed his gaze towards Fang Yuan: "Sir must be brother Tai Bai's best friend, Xing Xiang Zi? Since you are brother Tai Bai's friend, you are also my friend."

"I am but a wandering lone cultivator, I would not dare to." Fang Yuan smiled humbly.

He wore a large blue robe, his hair was white like snow, but his skin was tender like a baby's skin, he had a poised and sagely appearance. In fact, he looked more appealing than Tai Bai Yun Sheng, one could not help but feel some fondness upon seeing him.

Shark Demon's wife, Su Bai Man, asked: "Don't be so humble, Xing Xiang Zi, I heard that sir has quite an impressive wisdom path attainment level, can we have a demonstration?"

Fang Yuan looked towards her.

Su Bai Man was an immortal zombie, but he could see her former beauty and elegance.

As the saying goes, a beautiful woman leads to a hero's grave. It was no wonder that Shark Demon turned himself into a zombie, sacrificing his immense cultivation prospects to accompany Su Bai Man.

Immediately, Fang Yuan replied to her without hesitation: "Then I will give it a try, please do forgive me if I mess up."

"Just go for it, Sir Xing Xiang Zi. Even if you fail, nobody will blame you." Shark Demon replied.

He had a ruthless and fierce nature, he usually looked at people coldly, but this was the first time he was meeting Fang Yuan, yet he was so warm and enthusiastic. Evidently, he was giving Tai Bai Yun Sheng face.

Or rather, he was giving face towards the man as before Immortal Gu that Tai Bai Yun Sheng had.

Fang Yuan raised his head and observed the surroundings.

This world before him was a land of snow and ice. It was completely white, it indeed was a battlefield killer move, they were often known as quasi-blessed lands.

Fang Yuan activated many wisdom path Gu worms within his immortal aperture, he used several wisdom path investigative killer moves in front of everyone.

But he saw no flaws, the entire battlefield was completely unchanged and intact, he could not finding a point of weakness.

But Fang Yuan was not anxious, even though he had studied very hard over the last two months, becoming proficient with many wisdom path techniques, the battlefield killer move in front of him was not simple, it was created by Fairy Yu Lu.

Fairy Yu Lu was a remarkable person.

She had an impressive origin, being a disciple of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. He was the one who left behind the number one battlefield killer move inheritance in the entire history of humanity!

Fairy Yu Lu's battlefield killer move was certain to be extraordinary.

"Impressive! This battlefield killer move is completely fused with Yu Lu blessed land, it seems that it was created using the dao marks in the blessed land. Such methods are much more advanced than Lang Ya blessed land."

Fang Yuan observed for a long time, he gradually found some interesting points.

Lang Ya land spirit did not dare to setup a battlefield killer move in his blessed land to deal with Qin Bai Sheng, he only used the twelve wave cloud confusion Gu formation to deal with them. Lang Ya land spirit was afraid that the temporary dao marks created in setting up a battlefield killer move would harm the blessed land greatly.

In fact, in the current cultivation world, most Gu Immortals would not dare to use a battlefield killer move in their blessed lands or grotto-heavens.

Once the temporary dao marks made by the battlefield killer move clashed with the dao marks in the immortal aperture small world, the battlefield killer move would fail, and the Gu Immortal would face a backlash. In the worst case scenario, the dao marks will conflict with each other, unleashing terrifying strength that could destroy the blessed land and kill the Gu Immortal on the spot.

This had the same principle with the backlash of refining Gu.

But Fairy Yu Lu was indeed a great expert in battlefield killer moves, she directly countered this weakness by using incredible techniques that were out of Fang Yuan's imagination. She even greatly surpassed a fossil like Lang Ya land spirit in this regard.

Fang Yuan was secretly in admiration and anticipation: "It would be great if I can obtain Fairy Yu Lu's inheritance. Even if I get only one battlefield killer move that suits me, it would be a wonderful thing!"

Chapter 889: Freezing Rain Frozen Earth

Within the battlefield killer move freezing rain frozen earth, Fang Yuan used wisdom path techniques one after another, making continuous deductions.

Freezing rain frozen earth was made using the dao marks inside Yu Lu blessed land, they were not temporary dao marks, this made it very troublesome to deal with.

Shark Demon and the others could not break this battlefield killer move forcefully. If they destroyed it, they would be destroying the dao marks inside Yu Lu blessed land, this would cause irreparable damage to Yu Lu blessed land.

This was the same as saying: Qin Bai Sheng snatched away a portion of the Immortal Gu House, Refinement Cauldron, this cased Lang Ya blessed land to lose a large number of dao marks, it was a devastating loss.

Shark Demon and the others attacked Yu Lu blessed land for the inheritance and resources inside. Furthermore, violently destroying a battlefield killer move required a powerful offensive immortal killer move, that in turn meant that they would expend a huge amount of immortal essence.

Thinking about the costs and benefits, Shark Demon and the others could only try to properly unravel the battlefield killer move freezing rain frozen earth.

Thankfully, this Yu Lu blessed land was ownerless, and it was unknown if there was a land spirit. Fang Yuan had many Gu Immortal guards around him, they gave him a lot of freedom to research and decipher the environment.

Fang Yuan squinted his eyes as starlight shot out of his pupils.

At this moment, in his mind, countless star thoughts were moving about, clashing into each other as he deduced rapidly.

Fang Yuan was putting in all his effort now in deducing freezing rain frozen earth!

Firstly, deducing such a high quality battlefield killer move could give Fang Yuan a lot of new knowledge and inspiration.

Even if Fang Yuan could not obtain a battlefield killer move that suited him, with this knowledge and inspiration, he had a firm foundation to create his own battlefield killer move.

Secondly, the plan for Fang Yuan after entering Eastern Sea was to enter the headquarters of Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

This was the first time he was meeting Shark Demon, he had to display his worth so that Shark Demon would think highly of him, helping to recommend him into Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's headquarters.

As he deduced at a rapid rate, time passed quickly as well.

"Time is almost up, the freezing rain is going to start soon, the snow monsters will form and attack us. How much longer does Sir Xing Xiang Zi need?" A Gu Immortal that came along with Shark Demon asked impatiently.

His name was Bo Dan, a Gu Immortal member of Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

He was not an immortal zombie, but a living person. But he was in difficult straits, and did not have a high status after joining Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

Because he had some wisdom path attainment, he was brought into Yu Lu blessed land by Shark Demon, to join in this invasion.

Before Fang Yuan appeared, Bo Dan was the only pseudo-wisdom path Gu Immortal in the group.

The appearance of Xing Xiang Zi threatened his status and benefits.

If Fang Yuan made a successful deduction, would that not show that Bo Dan was useless?

Seeing that Fang Yuan was not making progress, Bo Dan could not hold it in anymore, he vaguely exerted pressure on Fang Yuan.

The other Gu Immortals were also paying attention to Fang Yuan's performance.

Bo Dan asked the question they had internally.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly, he did not try to protect his face, he said directly: "I am ashamed! This battlefield killer move is very profound, after deducing it for so long, I have only made some minor progress."

This battlefield killer move, freezing rain frozen earth, was indeed worthy of the work of the rank eight great expert, Fairy Yu Lu.

Fang Yuan used many wisdom path techniques in turn, but he made no progress! It was like he was facing a giant barrier, he did not even know where to start.

"Is that so." Su Bai Man sighed, feeling disappointed.

Fang Yuan was unwilling to give up this chance: "Give me a bit more time, I will continue to deduce."

Shark Demon nodded, he said: "Xing Xiang Zi, go ahead and make your deductions, we will block this attack for you."

At the same time, Shark Demon was considering other thoughts internally: "Xing Xiang Zi was highly recommended by Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but now it seems that he is not as amazing as he was said to be. Sigh, last time the battlefield killer move already made me pay a huge price in asking a wisdom path immortal zombie in Zombie Alliance to help. I have already invested a huge sum into Yu Lu blessed land, I need to be thrifty. If this Xing Xiang Zi can really unravel this battlefield killer move, that would be the best outcome."

But now, the other Gu Immortals looked at Fang Yuan with much less expectations.

Bo Dan watched at the side, he laughed to himself internally: "In the previous battlefield killer moves, I could at least find the Gu worms lurking behind it. But this time, I could not even find any clues. I'm curious, how will you find a breakthrough?"

As expected, a moment later, in the sky above this battlefield, a small drizzle of freezing rain started.

These raindrops were like tiny ice needles.

Rather than raining, this was more like the falling of ice needles, piercing the air and shooting towards Fang Yuan and the others.

The Gu Immortals used their defensive techniques.

Bo Dan did not have an Immortal Gu, he was protected by Shark Demon's defensive immortal killer move.

Fang Yuan was also shielded by Shark Demon.

Countless ice needles shot down, but they were blocked by the light barrier, because the needles were moving extremely quickly, they caused sparks to appear on the light barrier.

Fang Yuan willed, using star cloud grindstone and entering it.

He was not going to place his safety in the hands of others.

Seeing Fang Yuan's defensive immortal killer move, the other Gu Immortals' gazes shined, their attitudes changed slightly.

Fang Yuan could use an immortal killer move, he definitely had an Immortal Gu.

A Gu Immortal with Immortal Gu was not to be underestimated in Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world.

Not all Gu Immortals had Immortal Gu. In fact, most rank six Gu Immortals could only use mortal killer moves, they were unable to obtain an Immortal Gu even after much difficulty.

The intensity of the rain increased, as the ice needles slowly turned into stronger ice darts.

The ice darts tore through space, creating shrill and loud sounds.

The Gu Immortals defended together, they placed all their efforts on defense, they were also inwardly counting the expenditure of their immortal essence.

"Eh? This battlefield changed a little after using a new attack, a tiny flaw has appeared and I can make use of it. It is no longer like before when I had no clue at all." Fang Yuan's heart shook, he felt a sense of joy.

He moved quickly, three times as fast as earlier.

At the same time as using mortal killer moves, he also used wisdom path mortal Gu.

These killer moves and mortal Gu hit the air, causing smoke to rise, thunderous explosions, or jade green acid to splatter.

Fang Yuan used all sorts of methods to test this flaw.

But the effect was quite lackluster.

The ice dart rain had turned into an icicle storm.

The Gu Immortals' immortal essence expenditure rose at a rapid speed.

Roar!

With a loud sound, a huge snow monster charged over from the icy rain that filled everyone's vision.

Snow monsters were the prey of snowmen, by eating the flesh and blood of snow monsters, snowmen could breed more rapidly and even gain lifespan.

A thirty feet tall snow monster could battle a rank three Gu Master. Forty feet tall had the strength of a rank four Gu Master. And fifty feet tall had the terrifying power of a rank five Gu Master.

But the snow monster right now was about sixty feet tall.

This was a desolate beast level snow monster, it was not to be underestimated.

"Try not to kill them, even if these snow monsters die in battle, they will revive, they are very persistent." Su Bai Man quickly reminded.

Fang Yuan's heart shook.

"Endlessly reviving snow monsters? How can we fight them like this?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng also had a change in expression.

"Don't worry, once the time is up, these snow monsters will vanish on their own. They will only reappear during the next time the freezing rain appears." Shark Demon explained.

A Gu Immortal to the left of Shark Demon sighed in a worried tone: "This freezing rain frozen earth battlefield killer move already had a hint of resemblance to Reincarnation Battlefield. Fairy Yu Lu was a disciple of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, she might have obtained some insight regarding reincarnation and rebirth."

Grrr!

One after another, snow monsters appeared, they made it very hard for Shark Demon and the others to defend themselves.

The attacks of the snow monsters were very powerful, and they did not lack mobility.

The Gu Immortals did not want to face them directly, they attacked unceasingly, using immortal killer moves to disrupt the charging snow monsters, slowing their speeds and preventing them from getting close.

Fang Yuan's joy intensified.

When the snow monsters appeared, he found out that this battlefield killer move had even more flaws.

"There's hope!" Fang Yuan cheered on himself.

He had only received the wisdom path inheritance for a short amount of time, his wisdom path attainment level was at ordinary level, even though he worked hard without relaxing or slacking off, attainment levels needed accumulation over time.

Calling Fang Yuan a half-baked user was a huge compliment already. He was more like a wisdom path newbie.

But now, this wisdom path newbie was trying to unravel the killer move, freezing rain frozen earth. Using an analogy from Earth, this was like asking an elementary school student to do a senior high school mathematics problem.

Fang Yuan grabbed onto this flaw he found, his hands were moving faster and faster.

Eventually, under his deductions, he found a Gu worm.

This was a mortal Gu, it was coordinated with countless mortal Gu and Immortal Gu to form the battlefield killer move freezing rain frozen earth.

"Go!" Fang Yuan willed and a star snake rope flew out, coiling around this mortal Gu rapidly.

But when Fang Yuan was about to drag this mortal Gu back for research, this mortal Gu self-detonated.

The star snake rope missed its target, it could only return to Fang Yuan's side.

Such movements attracted the attentions of the other Gu Immortals.

Because this mortal Gu was destroyed, the freezing rain became significantly weaker.

"He actually found a flaw?" Bo Dan was shocked, he had once tried to look for flaws during the period of attacking, but he had no gains.

Bo Dan's wisdom path inheritance was too incomplete, it was of low quality and had limited methods.

In contrast, Fang Yuan's inheritance was extremely impressive, it had extraordinary origins. It led to the creation of many powerful wisdom path Gu Immortals, and its last owner was the number one wisdom path Gu Immortal in Northern Plains, Dong Fang Chang Fan.

Even with Fang Yuan's ability, he could find a flaw in the freezing rain frozen earth, this showed how impressive this inheritance truly was.

"Good!" Shark Demon praised.

But just as he said that, the storm above them became three times as fierce!

Swish swish swish!

Rain poured down like a storm, the icicles were sharp and emitted immense pressure on the Gu Immortals who were defending against the attack.

"Xing Xiang Zi, what in the world did you do?" Bo Dan grabbed onto this great opportunity and chided.

Fang Yuan's heart also jumped, he knew that he was too rash. Even if he found a Gu worm that formed the battlefield killer move, he should not have destroyed it at will, otherwise, it would lead to an even stronger resistance and attack.

But soon, Fang Yuan felt joyful again.

After this mortal Gu was destroyed, the battlefield killer move freezing rain frozen earth had two more flaws.

This way, there was more hope in unraveling the battlefield killer move!

Chapter 890: Framing

Soon, using the star thoughts in his mind to make deductions, Fang Yuan found the location of a few more Gu worms.

Their locations could not be found with investigative methods, of course.

"One, two, three, four, a total of four spots. There are Gu worms hiding there, but they are all mortal Gu. They are really hiding well, even with my star path investigative immortal killer move, I could not find them."

With his earlier experience, Fang Yuan did not try and destroy these mortal Gu again.

He remained unmoved, continuing to observe and deduce.

"So close!" Soon, he sighed internally, finding a point of danger.

The mortal Gu that was hiding at that place formed a crucial spot in the battlefield killer move.

In his initial estimations, Fang Yuan found out that by killing this Gu, he would reduce the power of the freezing rain and snow monsters by fifty to sixty percent.

But after further deductions, Fang Yuan obtained new findings: If he really eliminated the Gu, that would result in problems. Even though the current attack would be weaker, the next attack would happen more quickly, and its power will be three times as great!

The current attacks were already very difficult for Shark Demon and the others to defend against.

The freezing rain continued, it expended quite a lot of immortal essence, the immortal zombies were feeling a big headache.

The sixty feet tall snow monsters came one after another, the Gu Immortals did not dare to be careless.

"If the attack becomes thrice as strong, ancient desolate beast level snow monsters might show up!" Fang Yuan was internally shocked, the risk of unraveling this battlefield killer move was too high, if he lost his concentration even once, he would suffer severe consequences.

And this was only against mortal Gu, the mortal Gu that made up the outer layer. If he was dealing with Gu worms inside the inner layer, if Fang Yuan's methods were incorrect, he would face an even fiercer backlash!

Fang Yuan got past the flaws and continued probing the other areas.

Time passed quickly, but Fang Yuan made no progress.

"This is the fourth wave already. Sigh... how much longer do we have to endure?" An immortal zombie sighed, since joining this invasion, the amount of immortal essence that he had already spent was causing him to feel loss.

"In this current situation, no matter how much immortal essence we use, what would be the point if we don't see any results?" Bo Dan provoked.

Shark Demon and the others were feeling frustrated, their attentions were directed towards Fang Yuan.

This was the first time they had met Xing Xiang Zi, they did not know what ability Fang Yuan had in wisdom path. Bo Dan was already useless, now the heavy burden of dismantling the battlefield killer move fell onto this stranger's hands, could they rely on him or not?

"Lord Xing Xiang Zi, since the start, you have been using mortal techniques to probe it. Look at this, even though the circumstances are not critical yet, it is already a tough situation. Why don't you use immortal level wisdom path techniques? Don't worry, according to the rules, the amount of immortal essence that you consume will be compensated to you later, you do not need to worry about the expenditure." Bo Dan said again.

Fang Yuan frowned.

This Bo Dan had ill intentions, he had tried to sow discord time and time again.

Fang Yuan was well aware of the troubles of being an immortal zombie, immortal essence was hard to obtain, he treasured his supply greatly.

But now, there were huge losses but little progress, even if Shark Demon stayed silent and Su Bai Man remained impassive, he could guess the other immortal zombies' frustrations.

Fang Yuan could understand why Bo Dan was targeting him. But understanding was one thing, his provocative acts were akin to stabbing a dagger into Fang Yuan's back.

Immediately, Fang Yuan gave Bo Dan a deep look as he manipulated moving perspective cup Gu, transmitting to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng cooperated with him, speaking: "Bo Dan, why are you so anxious? Lord Shark Demon has already said it, we will endure this wave of attacks and fight for time for Xing Xiang Zi. Now that were are only halfway through this wave, you want to run away already? Or do you think that you have made immense contributions already?"

Bo Dan's expression changed, he said in a tone of one who was wronged: "Why would I dare to, Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng, you have misunderstood me!"

He knew deeply that Tai Bai Yun Sheng was Shark Demon's 'hot favorite', everyone knew of the warm attitude that Shark Demon had towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Furthermore, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had an extraordinarily precious Immortal Gu, it was an impressive healing method, he could not be offended.

"Alright, stop arguing." Shark Demon tried to control the situation as he looked at Fang Yuan: "We have already gone through the first three waves, we can afford to keep going through this fourth wave."

Fang Yuan felt Shark Demon's gaze as his heart sank.

It seems that Shark Demon and the others were not confident in him at all.

How could he allow that to happen?

Fang Yuan knew the importance of a first impression, he wanted to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance with Shark Demon's recommendation. If he failed the first time he tried, Shark Demon's poor impression of him would make things hard in the future. Even if he showed his worth later, the effect would be far worse than now. In contrast, if he succeeded now, even if he failed in the future, in Shark Demon's perspective, it would be reasonable, after all, who would not fail sometimes?

"Based on Shark Demon's tone, it seems that he will not stay for the fifth wave. After all, the issue of cost is important in attacking a blessed land. Forget it!"

Fang Yuan evaluated inwardly, he made up his mind.

He struck suddenly, attacking the Gu worm from earlier.

With a light sound, a Gu worm broke.

"Another Gu worm! Haha." Tai Bai Yun Sheng cooperated as he laughed loudly.

Shark Demon and the others' expressions turned to joy, their morale rose slightly.

Bo Dan kept quiet.

Following Fang Yuan's instructions, Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not let go of him: "How about that, Bo Dan? Regardless of whether a technique is mortal level or immortal level, the only importance is that it works."

Bo Dan nodded, showing a smile: "Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng is right, I was too rash earlier."

He understood the reasoning of backing down, he did not retort, he had given in.

Evidently, it was very hard to deal with people like him who could hold in a grudge.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng continued: "The rest of you may not know, but I have known brother Xing Xiang Zi for a long time, I know how impressive his wisdom path techniques are."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's actions were like a friend trying to speak up for his good friend.

At this time, Fang Yuan pretended to have made huge advancements, he continued: "Hehehe, I finally took down one important area. With this discovery, I have a greater confidence in unraveling this battlefield killer move now!"

"Is that so?" Su Bai Man's eyes shone, she believed a portion of his words.

But soon, the truth spoke for itself.

A immortal zombie shouted: "Quickly look, the freezing rain has weakened, many desolate beast snow monsters are disintegrating on their own!"

The immortals were overjoyed, their gaze towards Fang Yuan changed a lot.

They had only taken Tai Bai Yun Sheng's words with a grain of salt, but after seeing and sensing it for themselves, the immortals' attitudes changed drastically.

"Maybe this Xing Xiang Zi can really unravel the battlefield killer move?"

"Earlier, Bo Dan could do nothing, but once he came, he destroyed two Gu and reduced the power of the battlefield killer move by half."

"It seems that his wisdom path attainment is much higher than Bo Dan. I have to admit, this Northern Plains barbarian has quite the skill."

Everyone's hearts became filled with hope.

Bo Dan smiled on his face, but he was feeling very dark and gloomy inside.

The better Fang Yuan performed, the more it pointed out his inability.

Bo Dan was very discontent, he used his wisdom path techniques and observed the battlefield.

Once he observed it, his heart shook, he felt endless joy.

It turned out that after Fang Yuan destroyed two mortal Gu, and after such a long time, with Bo Dan's skill, he could find two flaws as well.

He deduced in secret, this was his intelligence, he did not want to do anything until he had concrete results, he was biding his time for a counterattack.

Fang Yuan retracted his gaze that was observing Bo Dan, he looked at the battlefield killer move again.

After destroying that mortal Gu, it was as if a veil was lifted, six to seven flaws were exposed in the freezing rain frozen earth battlefield killer move.

But Fang Yuan was not happy at all, he felt very gloomy.

The price of obtain these six to seven flaws was simply too high.

For the time being, Shark Demon and the others were still kept in the dark, but when the next wave of attack comes, they would feel the pain.

Fang Yuan continued to deduce, he had used over ten thousand star thoughts already.

The offense of the battlefield became weaker, Shark Demon and the others let out a breath of turbid air, the pressure of defending was very great, now that they were almost through with the fourth wave of attacks, they felt much less pressure, but they did not relax their alertness.

Fang Yuan had good progress, but he did not act.

He did not even use his probing methods from earlier. He sat in the air as he closed his eyes, showing others the impression that he was deducing with all his effort.

In fact, he was thinking: "This battlefield killer move is used to defend the blessed land, there are benefits and demerits. The biggest drawback is that the battlefield killer move forms a temporary world, it is a pseudo-blessed land. In here, all mortal Gu and mortal killer moves can be used, they are not restricted like in a blessed land. But in total, the benefits outweigh the demerits. These battlefield killer moves can slow down the speed of invaders, up until now, Shark Demon and the others still have yet to even see Yu Lu blessed land's true appearance. Even if they could use mortal killer moves, the invading Gu Immortals still have to expend a lot of immortal essence. Because once this battlefield killer move is activated, its power forces the Gu Immortals to defend themselves, or advance and attack using immortal methods."

"If I can obtain some battlefield killer moves in Yu Lu blessed land and use my own blessed land's dao marks to set up layers and layers of battlefield killer moves, that would be most favorable. When I relocate Star Form blessed land, I can use this method to form layers of defense. Hu Immortal blessed land can also make use of this, in case one day, Hu Immortal blessed land gets attacked, these defensive battlefield killer moves can help me stall for time as I relocate the resources within."

Because they were afraid of interrupting Fang Yuan's deductions, Shark Demon and the others remained silent.

Because of Fang Yuan's earlier performance, they gained some patience now.

What they did not know was, Fang Yuan was actually thinking about other things instead of deducing.

In this place, the most anxious person was not Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was worried about Fang Yuan, or even Shark Demon, it was Bo Dan.

Bo Dan was anxious.

He was not resigned to being suppressed by Xing Xiang Zi, earlier, because there were no flaws, so be it, he was helpless. Now that he found some flaws, there was hope, he tried his best to undergo deductions.

Time continued to pass, but Fang Yuan did not do anything, Bo Dan instead found an area with hidden mortal Gu. If he got rid of this mortal Gu, there would be little harm, and there would be progress in breaking the battlefield killer move.

Bo Dan had some ability after all, if not for that, Shark Demon would not have brought him to attack Yu Lu blessed land.

Having this discovery, Bo Dan was overjoyed, he thought to himself: "Bo Dan, you are really amazing!"

He was quite steady, he did not strike yet, instead he was observing Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was still shutting his eyes, he did not make a move.

Bo Dan waited as he lost his patience, his eyes were darting around.

He had wanted to wait for Fang Yuan to be helpless before he struck, giving a hard slap to Fang Yuan's face. But soon, he thought: What if Xing Xiang Zi also finds this flaw, what would I do?

Thus, he decided to act.

"Lord Shark Demon, I have made progress! Look!!" Bo Dan suddenly spoke, he said this as he moved his hands, destroying the mortal Gu that was hidden.

Shark Demon nodded at him, Bo Dan was a member of Zombie Alliance after all, compared to an outsider like Xing Xiang Zi, Shark Demon was more willing to see Bo Dan's improvement.

Su Bai Man smiled lightly: "With both of their help, it won't be long before we break the battlefield killer move."

But at this time, Fang Yuan opened his eyes, his expression turned very ugly: "Oh no!"

"What is it?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng asked cooperatively.

Fang Yuan said: "This mortal Gu cannot be destroyed, it is like a trap, after destroying it, the battlefield's offensive power will rise!!"

Fang Yuan thumped his chest and stomped his feet, he showed a look of anger and regret, as if he was very upset at the moment.

Chapter 891: Distorting The Truth

"What?" All the immortal zombies heard Fang Yuan's words and were shocked.

"You, you, you, bullshit!" Bo Dan felt a strong sense of humiliation as he burst into anger.

Shark Demon squinted, he looked at Bo Dan and Fang Yuan, his expression turned dark: "What is going on?"

Bo Dan was gritting his teeth from anger, he said: "Lord Shark Demon, I am willing to use my years of reputation as a guarantee, there are no issues with my action just now."

"This Xing Xiang Zi might look like a gentleman!" Bo Dan pointed at Fang Yuan: "But he is a small-minded scoundrel that is jealous of other people's capabilities. He must have seen my superior performance and decided to slander me. Lord Shark Demon and everyone else, please see the truth."

"I am most clear about brother Xing Xiang's abilities! In my opinion, you are the scoundrel!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was extremely angry, he retorted immediately.

"All of you, shut up!" Seeing that the situation was going out of control, Shark Demon shouted, he turned to Fang Yuan: "Xing Xiang Zi, what do you have to say?"

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "I have nothing to say."

Seeing this attitude, Su Bai Man's eyebrows raised.

But Fang Yuan continued: "I have a question however, for Sir Bo Dan."

Fang Yuan was not angry, he had a gentlemanly demeanor, when compared to Bo Dan's hysteric and frenzied state, there was a clear contrast.

Bo Dan saw Fang Yuan's demeanor and felt even more jealousy and hatred, he snorted: "What question do you have?"

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, he stared at Bo Dan as he tried to incite him: "If I ask you, would you dare to answer the truth?"

Bo Dan gritted his teeth, he knew that this was Fang Yuan's trap, but he could no longer back down now, he forced the words out of his throat: "Go ahead and ask!"

Fang Yuan sighed, he showed a look of 'I do not want to have conflict with people, yet people come and find trouble with me', he said: "I will ask you, how many hidden Gu worms are there now in this freezing rain frozen earth battlefield killer move?"

Shark Demon and the others looked tightly at Bo Dan.

Bo Dan's heart jumped, he opened his mouth and wanted to speak, but he only managed to stretch out his tongue and lick his lips.

Fang Yuan's question was like a dagger stabbing directly into Bo Dan's heart!

Bo Dan had only found one spot where there were hidden Gu worms, after deducing, he found that there were no issues and acted to destroy the Gu worm.

Now that this Gu worm was removed, there would definitely be new flaws that were not there before forming.

But if Bo Dan wanted to deduce the location of more hidden Gu worms, he would need time.

Bo Dan had thought of lying, but at the next moment, he denied this stupid idea.

Because this was very easy to verify.

If he said that an area had hidden Gu worms, he could be told to simply attack it to show everyone.

Actions speak louder than words.

Bo Dan was speechless, he clenched his fists subconsciously.

But soon, he understood that he could not lie, he loudly responded: "If you want to seek help from me, I will satisfy you. Give me some time, I will advise you after I finish deducing."

Gu Immortals all had their own shrewdness, after hearing these words, they remained emotionless in appearance, but they were shaking their heads internally.

Bo Dan's pathetic state was imprinted in everyone's minds.

These Gu Immortals were not idiots of course, they understood that Bo Dan spoke without enough confidence. Xing Xiang Zi had exposed Bo Dan simply through a question.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at Bo Dan with some pity, he sighed internally: "With just your ability, you want to compete with Fang Yuan?

Fang Yuan knew that Bo Dan would reply like this, he laughed heartily: "Sir Bo Dan must have deduced only one flaw. But this hidden Gu worm is only a trap. If you continue your deduction and have more patience, you will find more flaws and hidden Gu worms. That way, you might begin to understand how rash your actions were."

"Oh?" Bo Dan's lips twitched, he had thought of a reply, he tried to trouble Fang Yuan: "Then tell everyone how inappropriate my actions were? How did I cause more trouble? What kind of trap was this flaw? Haha, you should answer properly, Lady Su Bai Man has a lie detection method."

This flaw was naturally not a trap.

Fang Yuan could not answer him.

But Fang Yuan had prepared his response as well, he laughed: "My wisdom path inheritance is unique, how can I leak it here? Bo Dan, you made a good scheme, you want to stealthily learn my wisdom path techniques?"

"Utter bullshit!" Bo Dan flew into rage.

Bo Dan spoke rudely, but Fang Yuan was not unhappy, he looked at Shark Demon.

Shark Demon was frowning deeply, he was an observer, watching Fang Yuan and Bo Dan argue their way out.

Fang Yuan understood that Shark Demon was still biased towards Bo Dan from this one glance.

This was nothing strange.

Shark Demon and Bo Dan were members of Zombie Alliance. They had worked together many times and had spent much time together.

As the saying goes, an acquaintance may not sow discord among friends. This was only the first time Fang Yuan had met Shark Demon, he was a stranger. Bo Dan and Shark Demon had a much closer relationship.

Fang Yuan laughed, his expression changed as he looked at Bo Dan with contempt, he said disdainfully: "Foolish clown, I will give you a lesson today. Watch closely!"

Saying so, Fang Yuan's fingers moved like swords, drawing lines in the air.

Starlight flew out of his fingertips, they stopped in the air, being either close or far away from him.

"Here, here, here, and all these other places, they have hidden mortal Gu. If you do not believe me, you can try to attack them yourselves. For example, this point needs a fire path attack to destroy the Gu worm. That point needs an ice path technique to be exposed, before using lightning to destroy the Gu worm. And for this point, if you want to destroy the mortal Gu, you have to wait until the next wave to destroy it."

Fang Yuan spoke quickly as the starlight specks floated in the air, there were eight or nine of them.

The Gu Immortals were all astute, Fang Yuan told them the locations of the hidden Gu worms and the methods to destroy them in detail. He was obviously not afraid of them giving it a try.

Such intense confidence made them believe him without any doubts.

Bo Dan stared with wide opened eyes, he did not know how to rebuke him. He got agitated, he wanted to take action: "I want to see if your words are true."

"Wait!" Fang Yuan held out his hand, stopping Bo Dan.

Bo Dan could not longer back out of this, he showed intense surprise and joy upon hearing that, he showed a cold smile: "Why, Xing Xiang Zi, are you afraid?"

Fang Yuan sighed, giving Bo Dan a glance, he was like an adult looking at a mischievous child, Bo Dan almost jumped in anger.

Fang Yuan spoke: "There are hidden Gu worms here indeed, I am not afraid of anyone probing it. But these areas cannot be damaged. Just like what you did earlier, these are traps that are interconnected, if they are destroyed, it would affect the entire battlefield killer move, not only would my wisdom path deductions become completely obsolete, I would even have to restart from scratch. All these areas that I pointed out have troublesome connections, I am unable to deduce which points are safe and which are not."

After saying that, Fang Yuan turned to the immortal zombie Shark Demon, bowing: "Lord Shark Demon, I am truly sorry, this is because I am not good enough."

Seeing Fang Yuan's humble attitude, it was like a subtle mockery. Bo Dan's eyelids were twitching, he wanted to jump and pull out all of Fang Yuan's white beard, tear his blue robe apart, step on him and grind Fang Yuan's clean, pinkish face into the dirty soil.

But he could not do that, because Shark Demon was returning the bow to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had just spoken and bowed to Shark Demon.

From Shark Demon's perspective, he was the leader of them, he had to have manners.

Furthermore, Xing Xiang Zi was Tai Bai Yun Sheng's good friend, he had introduced the former. Now that Xing Xiang Zi was bowing to Shark Demon, how could Shark Demon not bow back?

Zombie Alliance was in the righteous path, even though the members came from everywhere and a large portion were from the demonic path, once they entered Zombie Alliance, they would have to act like proper members of the righteous path and follow the rules.

Also, after hearing their conversation, Shark Demon had a grasp of the situation.

In his opinion, Xing Xiang Zi's wisdom path attainment was higher than Bo Dan. Such a talent was needed in his future attempts to take down Yu Lu blessed land, he had to bow in return as courtesy.

After that, Shark Demon spoke in a very polite tone: "I am deeply enlightened by Brother Xing Xiang's words, I wonder how we should proceed from here?"

Shark Demon was at rank seven, even though he was an immortal zombie, he was a famous expert in Eastern Sea. He took the initiative to call Xing Xiang Zi 'brother', in everyone's opinion, Shark Demon's attitude was truly very gentle.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "It is all because of my low ability, earlier I had a hint of inspiration and did not want to destroy that Gu worm as it would cause my hard work to go to waste. I was anxious and spoke without consideration. Sigh, the saying goes, a strong dragon cannot suppress a local snake, I am just a weak snake, while everyone here are expert dragons."

Bo Dan was so angry he was breathing roughly, his eyes were bloodshot.

Fang Yuan's words were humble, all of his words were 'in consideration' of Bo Dan's face, but he actually slapped Bo Dan loudly countless times.

This time however, Bo Dan did not retort.

He was extremely angry, but he was also feeling uncertain.

His wisdom path inheritance was very incomplete, it was far inferior to Fang Yuan's. Since Fang Yuan could expose so many flaws here, Bo Dan also knew that he could not match Fang Yuan, he just refused to admit the truth.

"Don't tell me, did I really make a mistake? This mortal Gu was really a trap just like what that damned Xing Xiang Zi said?"

Poor Bo Dan, he was framed by Fang Yuan, but even he himself had fallen into self doubt.

Fang Yuan's peripheral vision was on Bo Dan, he observed all his expressions and reactions.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly and humbly on the outside, but he was laughing coldly internally.

He had wanted to retreat long ago.

The next wave of attacks would be extremely powerful. If they are careless, some of these Gu Immortals might die. Even if they could endure it, their immortal essence expenditure would definitely be severe.

Such severe loss would make the Gu Immortals feel severe distress, but Fang Yuan had no way of dismantling this battlefield killer move.

By then, the Gu Immortals would have wasted so many resources, yet Fang Yuan, who was their hope, would make no progress, it was easy to imagine how unhappy they would be with him.

Thus, Fang Yuan's humbleness was not just to mock Bo Dan on purpose, he was trying to plant a seed in these immortals' minds.

"We have to retreat for sure, but the way we retreat is the question." Fang Yuan, after thinking up to this moment, glanced at Bo Dan, before speaking to Shark Demon: "There is little time until the next wave of attacks, with this change, my earlier efforts have gone to waste. I can only restart and try again, but I will not lie, there is little hope of success, I need even more time than before. Most importantly, this wave of attacks will be extremely powerful, in my opinion, we should retreat now."

The immortals were not willing to give up now, they had already reached this step.

Shark Demon said: "I hope brother Xing Xiang will give it a try."

Thus, Fang Yuan pretended to sit in the air as he shut his eyes.

Soon, the fifth wave of attacks came, the ice needle storm rained down as dozens of snow monsters charged towards the Gu Immortals.

"The wave is much stronger as expected!"

"Let's go! This is just the start, and it is already so tough."

"Bo Dan, I don't know what to say to you."

Bo Dan's expression was dark, he gritted his teeth, his gaze was cold. He could feel the Gu Immortals looking at him, it hurt him more than the ice rain. The Gu Immortals' words were like whips lashing on his soul.

"Xing Xiang Zi! Xing Xiang Zi!!" He shouted internally, chanting this name, it was a pity that this was merely a fake name.

After enduring for a while, Shark Demon saw that Fang Yuan was not making progress, his evaluation of the gains and losses this time had completely turned over, he could only squeeze out the word: "Retreat!"

Chapter 892: Alcohol and Food, Fishing for Sharks

The banquet's atmosphere was very cohesive.

Even though this attack on Yu Lu blessed land caused everyone to end up suffering losses, after they left, Shark Demon still kindly invited Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Fang Yuan to his home as guests.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's man as before Immortal Gu was something Shark Demon needed. Fang Yuan, who was under the identity of Xing Xiang Zi, had deep wisdom path attainment, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man saw his value, especially in their attempt to take down Yu Lu blessed land.

Thus, Shark Demon invited Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, it was not a surprise.

Shark Demon stayed in a place called Shark Sea.

This was a huge sea area, being over three million square kilometers, this Shark Sea was of similar size to the South China Sea on Earth.

That was to say, it was as if the entire South China Sea belonged to Shark Demon alone.

Everything inside the sea area, countless types of sharks, seaweed and aquatic plants, the rocks on the seabed, the huge amount of sea water, all of them were Shark Demon's possession.

Like in Northern Plains, where fertile grasslands were split up between people, in Eastern Sea, sea areas that were rich with resources were also distributed among people.

Even though Shark Demon was an immortal zombie, he had immense strength, he had the ability to control this sea area.

His palace was at the bottom of the sea, at the center of this Shark Sea area.

During the banquet, there were all sorts of food from Eastern Sea, they were delicious and filled with the local flavors.

No matter what the intentions of both sides were, on the surface, this was a very effective banquet, there was a harmonious atmosphere.

Shark Demon enjoyed his delicious wine, even though he was an immortal zombie, with the help of Gu worms, he could temporarily regain his sense of taste.

Soon after, he put down his wine cup, at his will, the top of his majestic and beautiful palace turned transparent.

"Everyone, take a look, these are divine spear sharks, these are shattering teeth golden sharks, and over there are silver scale great treasure sharks... these are all pets that I had nurtured with much effort." Shark Demon pointed, not concealing his proud feelings at all.

Fang Yuan raised his head and looked, only to see that the seawater was dark and dim, the palace lights could only shine for ten meters of distance ahead.

The underwater palace was shining in bright lights, if seen from the outside, it was like a huge oddly shaped jewel that was emitting a warm light.

Fang Yuan had his investigative killer moves, the dark seawater could not obstruct him.

He soon saw the sharks that Shark Demon was referring to.

The divine spear sharks moved around alone, they had a peculiar appearance, the tip of their heads were sharp, they were in the shape of long spears. Their bodies were not covered in smooth shark skin, but had a bony texture.

The divine spear sharks swam around in the sea, charging around with no fear. The spear on their heads was very sharp, while not inhibiting their advancement. Everywhere they went, underwater rocks were smashed as pathways was created by them.

As for the shattering teeth golden sharks, they were the most numerous, two to three hundred formed into one group.

These sharks had very small and sharp teeth, when the shattering teeth golden sharks opened their mouths, Fang Yuan could see that in their mouths, both upper and lower jaws, they had six rows of sharp teeth.

Even though these golden sharks were carnivores, they did not prey on large fish, instead they were like whales, they only ate small fish and prawns. The six rows of teeth formed six tight defenses, separating the sand from fish and prawns. No matter how small the fish were, they could not escape from the golden sharks.

Silver scale great treasure sharks were the largest, they would be around the sizes of small whales from Earth.

This type of treasure shark lived in a family of three or four. Usually, they would move about casually, when food appeared, they would move quickly and hunt.

Even though the silver scale great treasure shark had a huge body, its body did not match the incredible speed it could display.

Once it moved, its speed was extremely fast, it would be like a flash of silver lightning in the depths of the sea!

Silver scale great treasure sharks had the most rogue nature, instead of hunting other fish, they ate other sharks as food.

Of course, if it were the stronger sharks like the divine spear sharks or shattering teeth golden sharks, the treasure sharks would not go after them if they had sufficient food.

"How is it, the fish that I am raising, are they alright?" Shark Demon looked at how Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were dazed, he felt incredibly pleased.

"More than alright. These sharks are all lively and energetic, they were raised well. This sea area has all sorts of creatures living in a well balanced habitat, these sharks all have a lot of Gu worms in them, I even saw one or two desolate beast sharks earlier." Fang Yuan said.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng also sighed, he nodded: "No wonder Eastern Sea is the region with the most abundant resources, this sea area already showcases a lot to me."

Shark Demon raised his head slightly as he laughed.

Su Bai Man was beside him, she smiled: "Please do not praise him so much. My husband's hobby is to raise these sharks in his free time, he particularly enjoys hearing the praise of others towards these sharks."

During the banquet, be it Shark Demon or Su Bai Man, they were much more amicable than in Yu Lu blessed land.

These two could differentiate work from social life, during public occasions, they had to control the situation, thus they were stern and serious, without any hint of carelessness. Privately, they were hospitable and warm, by making jokes at times, they could make other people feel much closer to them.

This couple not only had great battle strength, they also had a lot of experience in human interaction. It was no wonder they could obtain such an important mission like attacking Yu Lu blessed land from Zombie Alliance after much competition.

Even though Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had invested a lot into Yu Lu blessed land, having made a huge loss already, losing a lot of their wealth, if Yu Lu blessed land were to be successfully taken down, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man would receive ten times or even dozens of times as much profits!

Most immortal zombies would not undertake such important missions.

Only Su Bai Man and Shark Demon, these veteran experts, had the foundation to support an immense expenditure in the early stages.

Hearing the praise from Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Shark Demon smiled: "You flatter me, hahaha. Actually, this sea area is only ranked forty-sixth among the list of Eastern Sea's sea areas. Above my sea area, there is the elegant splendorous sea area, the flourishing bumpy sea area, and a Song clan Gu Immortal's, Song Yi Shi's poetic emotion sea area."

"Both of you have not been in Eastern Sea for long, you might not have seen the ten great sea areas in Eastern Sea. These ten sea areas are all incredible. Rainbow Island's rainbow sea area, the seawater is beautiful and in all colors, and yet the colors do not smudge. Boundless forest sea area has trees that are thousands of meters tall growing under the sea, the tree crowns can penetrate the water surface, and the huge number of trees form a huge underwater forest. For the mermen sea area, female mermen[1] are extremely amorous, there are countless mermen living there, they have incredible strength, being one of Eastern Sea's top ten super forces."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard all these as his expression froze, he sighed again: "The world is vast, nature is also vast, Eastern Sea has so many precious resources, and countless talents, we can truly feel how insignificant each of us are."

"Mermen..." Fang Yuan's heart moved, he thought of a certain memory in his previous life.

After eating the food, the banquet was reaching its end, Shark Demon said: "Since this is the first time that both of you are here, I have prepared some small gifts, please do accept them."

This was an obvious way to improve their relationship.

Fang Yuan did not reject him, he wanted to get closer to Shark Demon anyway, he showed a look of joy as he cupped his fists: "Then I will thank Lord Shark Demon in advance."

Shark Demon laughed heartily, he clapped: "Good, I like the forthright nature of Northern Plains Gu Immortals. But for the gifts I prepared, you will have to collect them yourselves."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at each other with a sense of confusion.

Su Bai Man explained while concealing her smile: "Both of you might not know, my husband does not invite guests here very often. But when he does, he would gift them some sharks. The guest would need to catch the sharks themselves, as for how many and what type of sharks they get, that would be decided by the guest's ability."

"So that's it." Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Fang Yuan realized.

"Please start moving. You only have seven minutes, during this period, you need to stay inside the palace, it will be against the rules if you go out." Shark Demon said.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was very interested, these sharks were in top-notch condition, they were very valuable. Even if he could not use them, he could sell them for a huge sum of immortal essence stones.

Moreover, there were sharks that suited him here.

Fang Yuan's was moved, he thought of something: "Isn't this the famous shark fishing banquet from my previous life?"

In his previous life, by the time Fang Yuan came to Eastern Sea, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had already died, the cause was unknown.

This shark sea became someone else's possession.

The Gu Immortal who occupied this place, Zhu Xing Bo, was very hospitable and had a wide network of friendships. While holding a banquet, he also played this game, allowing his guests to fish for sharks in the palace.

It turned out that the origin of this was Shark Demon, Gu Immortal Zhu Xing Bo was only imitating him.

The fishing had started, they had limited time, Fang Yuan resisted his urge to enter the sea to take a look.

There were many groups of sharks swimming around freely near the underwater palace.

"Among these sharks, the ones with the highest value are those that Shark Demon pointed out earlier: Divine spear shark, shattering teeth golden shark, and silver scale great treasure shark. But these sharks do not suit me."

Fang Yuan thought in his mind.

The ones which suited him were blood fiend sharks and star mark sharks. The former was suitable for Hu Immortal blessed land after the blood calamity, the latter suited Star Form blessed land, they could be raised in the most central lake.

However, the quantity of these two types of sharks was far less than the divine spear shark, shattering teeth golden shark, and silver scale great treasure shark.

It was because the ferocity of the blood fiend shark and star mark shark was inferior to the divine spear shark, shattering teeth golden shark, and silver scale great treasure shark.

This underwater palace was Shark Demon's place of residence. During normal times, when Shark Demon had the time, he would toss fresh food and cause the sharks to fight for them. As time passed, this place became the sanctuary of the sharks, the strongest shark groups would stay here.

It was difficult for Fang Yuan to obtain blood fiend sharks and star mark sharks.

He was inside the underwater palace, he could not travel around and capture sharks in the water.

This was only a game, Shark Demon was not generous enough to let others capture sharks in his sea area casually.

Fang Yuan felt some regret, but he had to give up on the blood fiend sharks and star mark sharks.

As for the divine spear sharks, shattering teeth golden sharks, and silver scale great treasure sharks, he did not want them. After two months of accumulation, he already had five to six hundred immortal essence stones, with such wealth, he did not need such a small amount.

How many divine spear sharks, shattering teeth golden sharks, and silver scale great treasure sharks could be obtained in seven minutes?

Fang Yuan was not skilled in capturing beasts, using an immortal killer move to capture beasts was too wasteful, unless he was trying to capture desolate beasts.

[1] Mermen as a race refers to both males and females in this novel Back

Chapter 893: Song Clan's Song Yi Shi

Fang Yuan quickly thought, and decided to help Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to capture cloud line sharks which had a small and exquisite bodies, not only could they move in the sea, they could also fly and survive for a long time, they were suitable for Tai Bai blessed land.

However, cloud line sharks were proficient at hiding, were it not for this, they could not have survived near the sea palace between the three shark groups.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's shark fishing ran into a problem at the very start.

His target was cloud line sharks, but divine spear sharks, shattering teeth golden sharks and silver scale great treasure sharks would not just look on from the side.

Like smoke spreading in the sea, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's methods stirred up these three shark groups.

As far as they were concerned, this sanctuary was their joint territory, and now an anomaly appeared. Like beasts whose territories were invaded, they naturally had to teach these audacious invaders a lesson.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was specialized in healing and was not proficient in fishing, these three shark groups caused great disturbance to him.

After Fang Yuan helped, the disturbances were mostly eliminated. Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt his pressure lifting and immediately sent him a grateful look.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly and nodded to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, not saying anything.

Finally, with Fang Yuan's cooperation, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was able to capture an ideal quantity of cloud line sharks.

"I thank both Lord Shark Demon and Lord Su Bai Man." Tai Bai Yun Sheng had profited, thus he stood up and bowed solemnly to the two.

"You two indeed have a deep relationship." Shark Demon sighed softly.

After chatting for a while, this banquet reached the end, both guests and hosts enjoyed it to the fullest. Shark Demon personally accompanied Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng out of the sea area.

They looked on until the two had shrunk to the size of ants in the horizons. Su Bai Man's gaze flashed as she suddenly spoke: "Dear, what do you think of this Xing Xiang Zi?"

Shark Demon's smile disappeared completely and his gaze turned aloof: "This person seems humble but in fact is arrogant and also has lot of hidden thoughts, he is different from Tai Bai Yun Sheng and is not someone easy to deal with."

He paused for a moment before continuing: "Bo Dan is too useless, he was led around by Xing Xiang Zi from start to finish. Bo Dan is a person on our side, but was embarrassed like that by Xing Xiang Zi. Bo Dan's embarrassment caused me to lose face as well. This Xing Xiang Zi did whatever he wanted since the moment he came, there is ruthlessness behind his gentle appearance, he is no kind person. If I had my previous temperament, I would have already given him a few hard slaps and taught him to be obedient. He would learn that this is Eastern Sea and not Northern Plains!"

Su Bai Man hurriedly consoled: "Dear, calm your anger, this type of person with skill will naturally have arrogance. As for Bo Dan's loss of composure this time, it is also justifiable. Think of it, his private sea area has already been occupied for many years by Blazing Heaven Demoness and she still doesn't have the intention to return it. Bo Dan recently went to beg for it but was instead beaten badly by Blazing Heaven Demoness. Blazing Heaven Demoness is a Northern Plains immortal zombie, thus Bo Dan naturally looks upon Northern Plains Gu Immortals with anger."

"Moreover, he lost his private sea area and is without other means of income, he is in extremely strained circumstances. The reward from attacking Yu Lu blessed land is plentiful and it is his best chance to save himself from poverty. However, Xing Xiang Zi arrived with wisdom path methods better than his, it is unavoidable for Bo Dan to be furious for having his source of income stolen. This is a matter of great importance to him, thus it was also unavoidable for him to lose his usual state of mind."

As he heard this, Shark Demon's eyes brightened, and he looked at Su Bai Man with a smiling expression: "Why are you suddenly speaking about Bo Dan so favorably? Ah... it must be that Bo Dan secretly sent a big gift to you, right?"

Su Bai Man covered her mouth as she laughed: "I cannot hide anything from you. It is not a big gift, just a palm sized medicine ice."

Shark Demon, however, was very surprised: "Although the quantity of this medicine ice is small, it is a genuine rank eight immortal material, where did Bo Dan find this? Heh, he is really spending a lot to protect his role."

Su Bai Man lightly shook her head: "Bo Dan doesn't seem to be eye-catching, but to be able to have this success, he isn't a simple character."

Shark Demon said with a profound voice: "It seems Bo Dan really wants to grasp this opportunity. He might not have much experience in this situation, but even if he is incompetent, he also has some use. Xing Xiang Zi has great capability, but he is an outsider. I definitely want to bring Bo Dan, just to keep this Xing Xiang Zi in check and stop him from being solely dominant in the future. If we let him be proud and insolent because of his talent, what will happen in the future? What if when we are attacking the blessed land, we are trapped by him, what will we do then? We don't understand wisdom path methods, but with Bo Dan, we can make Xing Xiang Zi restrain himself and prevent him from making mischief."

Su Bai Man put her mind at ease, gazing dreamily at this man whom she loved deeply: "My husband really is most capable, Bo Dan and Xing Xiang Zi are playing in your hands, and won't be able to create any trouble."

"Hahaha, dear, don't praise me so much."

Fang Yuan followed Tai Bai Yun Sheng to a nameless island.

This nameless island was the home of Tai Bai Yun Sheng previously.

It was extremely crude, but because of Tai Bai Yun Sheng, it gradually started becoming slightly famous in the circles of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals.

In this invasion of Yu Lu blessed land, Shark Demon had to return in defeat after the difficult round.

To carry out another invasion, they needed time to prepare.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to use this free time to meet the many requests he had received in the past.

One had to say that Landscape as Before, this time path Immortal Gu, was very much sought after.

Something unexpected could happen any time, there would always be some issues appearing from time to time in the sea areas the Gu Immortals managed. Landscape as Before had outstanding effects in this aspect and showed instant results.

"Fang Yuan, how about coming together with me, we can take care of each other on one hand and I can also introduce you to others. With this trip, you can also get familiar with the nearby Gu Immortals." Tai Bai Yun Sheng suggested.

This suggestion was very appropriate, but Fang Yuan already had a plan, as he said to Tai Bai Yun Sheng with a wry smile: "Old Bai, it is better if you don't let others know our relation as much as possible. Because the thing I am about to do might very well implicate you."

"Ah? Wasn't this trip to get a share of Yu Lu blessed land, then join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt something wrong from Fang Yuan's tone, it seemed like he was going to create trouble.

With regards to Fang Yuan's ability to create trouble, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a deep impression of it.

The set up in Imperial Court blessed land and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was destroyed because of Fang Yuan.

Moreover, this was accomplished when Fang Yuan had still been a mortal. Now, he was an immortal zombie, this ability to create trouble had definitely increased sharply.

"Fang Yuan, you shouldn't act recklessly. What are you planning?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng worriedly looked at Fang Yuan.

"My good senior brother, don't worry, I am doing this to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance." Fang Yuan consoled.

"Don't, don't call me senior brother, a skilled person is a teacher, I still don't have enough qualifications to be your senior brother." Tai Bai Yun Sheng hurriedly shook his hand, worriedly inquiring about the details.

Fang Yuan revealed a little: "Old Bai, have you thought about how inappropriate it is for me to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng blinked: "Although you are under the identity of a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, Eastern Sea has had cases of Gu Immortals of other regions joining their local forces. Moreover, this Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance is the main headquarters of the Zombie Alliances over all five regions, it is an enormous force. Other Zombie Alliance branches don't recruit living Gu Immortals, but Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance recruits them. Your identity won't pose a problem."

Fang Yuan shook his head: "Those like Bo Dan who have joined Zombie Alliance are those who are living a miserable life and can barely scrape by. These type of people are at the bottom layer among Gu Immortals. Their positions in Zombie Alliance are even lower than immortal zombies. But I, Xing Xiang Zi, am different. Not mentioning my Immortal Gu, I have strong wisdom path methods which can deduce the battlefield killer move in Yu Lu blessed land. People like me, no matter how we live, we are not likely to join Zombie Alliance. As long as I reveal just a slight intent to do so, I believe other righteous path forces would welcome me warmly."

"Hmm, it is reasonable." Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded: "Joining these forces means losing freedom. Especially to foreign Gu Immortals like us, the monitoring and restrictions are much more strict. Otherwise, why would there be so many lone cultivators?"

"So, for a Gu Immortal like me to join Zombie Alliance, not only should it be my own wish, but it also requires a strong external pressure." Fang Yuan nodded.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes shined brightly, as he asked: "What pressure?"

Fang Yuan smiled before lightly asking a question that made Tai Bai Yun Sheng pale: "Which is the closest super force from here?"

Song clan was a colossus that had occupied Eastern Sea for hundreds of years.

This clan was an existence that was in the top ten even among the many super forces in Eastern Sea.

The official, publicly known number of Gu Immortals in the clan was eighteen. Song clan's first supreme elder, Song Qi Yuan, had already been rank eight for many years, his battle strength was unfathomable.

Song Qi Yuan's son, Song Diao Ling, was a rank seven Gu Immortal with outstanding talent, he was cultured and elegant, and had been publicly recognized as the successor for Song clan's leadership.

But unfortunately, over ten years ago, Song Diao Ling was schemed against and died, leaving behind a daughter.

The daughter's surname was naturally Song and her given name was Yi Shi. She was the only descendant left of Song Qi Yuan's bloodline.

Since a young age, Song Yi Shi was pampered by her grandfather Song Qi Yuan. In any world, some people are naturally born with a silver spoon in their mouths.

In the world where most people were struggling to survive, and most Gu Immortals constantly on their guard, preparing to undergo their next tribulations and calamities, rushing around everywhere to raise their strength and cultivation, Song Yi Shi was just sitting back and enjoying life, all her cultivation resources provided by Song Qi Yuan. She only needed to say the word and her grandfather, Song Qi Yuan, would make sure they were fulfilled.

When Song Yi Shi underwent immortal ascension, Song Qi Yuan personally protected her.

After advancing to a rank six Gu Immortal, Song Qi Yuan sent his granddaughter a big gift — a sea area with an area of four million square kilometers. It was slightly larger than the South China Sea on Earth.

Not only this, this sea area was also extremely rich in resources and was named the poetic emotion sea area. In the rankings of Eastern Sea, it was ranked above Shark Demon's shark sea.

Fang Yuan explored and, in combination with his previous life's memories, made his plan center around this Song Yi Shi.

Chapter 894: Purposely Getting Discovered

After plotting in secret for half a month, Fang Yuan arrived on a small island.

Eastern Sea had many small islands, there were millions or even tens of millions of the islands that Fang Yuan had arrived at.

Most small islands were uninhabited islands, but this small island actually had humans.

There were three fishing villages on the island, the strongest cultivator was only rank three.

Fang Yuan hid his figure, under the blazing sun, he strolled into a nearby fishing village like it was a normal thing to do.

The surrounding people were mostly ordinary mortals. There was occasionally a Gu Master or two on the scene, they were either rank one or two, and were very well respected by the mortals around them.

Fang Yuan's current methods were much stronger than the time when he was in Southern Border.

He moved through the entire village two or three times, but no one could discover him.

"This should be Li clan village." Fang Yuan observed it for a while, combined with his previous life's memories, he verified that this was the place.

This small fishing village was obviously not Li clan village.

But in his previous life, there was a mystical and interesting Gu Immortal who emerged from this place, he was called Li Xiao Yao.

This fishing village was renamed by him, to Li clan village.

Of course, right now, Li Xiao Yao was yet to be born. According to his previous life's memories, Li Xiao Yao would be born in around two hundred years.

After confirming the status of this fishing village, Fang Yuan left and arrived at a cliff beside the sea.

There were countless nests in the cliff, there were hundreds, thousands of birds resting here, they had a strong territorial awareness. Once a Gu Master, or a large life form comes and makes the birds feel threatened, they would assault the invaders together.

Thus, few people in the village came to this place. Occasionally, there were Gu Masters who came to harvest some medicinal herbs or steal some bird eggs.

These birds were very diverse, they were a congregation of over ten different hundred beast groups, they were not the same types of birds.

On this tiny island, there were human Gu Masters, but they were not at the dominant position in this environment.

"According to the \<\<Biography of Li Xiao Yao\>\>, when Li Xiao Yao was still a child, he was often bullied by children who were older than him, he had to hide here out of necessity. Here, he found a hidden cave by accident, he treated this cave as his secret base."

This cliff had all sorts of holes and caves, there was a large number of them.

It was obviously very difficult to locate the cave that Li Xiao Yao found.

"However, since there are bird groups here, Li Xiao Yao could not have gone deep inside. His cave should be at the outer periphery."

Fang Yuan was prepared amply, he searched for a while and chose a hundred targets initially.

By the time it was noon, and the sun started to descend towards the west, Fang Yuan found his true target.

This hole was not big, but even with Xing Xiang Zi's current size, he could not enter. Not to mention Fang Yuan's original eight arm immortal zombie body.

Thankfully, he had change form Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan shrunk his body and squeezed inside.

The cave was moist, by the evening, there was weak lingering sunlight penetrating into it. After moving in the cave for a short while, Fang Yuan came to the deepest part of this cave. The space here was extremely wide.

The sea winds outside the cliff blew into the small holes of the cave, they created a whistling sound of moving wind.

Fang Yuan could not help but think of the \<\<Biography of Li Xiao Yao\>\>, inside, it wrote about Li Xiao Yao's childhood, when he was often bullied, he would hide inside this cave and sob quietly, as he listened to the whistling sound of the wind.

This situation continued for a long time, until one day, fate changed for him as Li Xiao Yao's legendary tale began.

This change in fate was the small hole in a corner of the cave.

Once when Li Xiao Yao was hiding here, he leaned on a corner as he rested. Suddenly, the cave collapsed as he fell, directly into a deep part of the cliff, and he got swept away by the currents in the sea.

This trip, Fang Yuan was trying to replicate Li Xiao Yao's fortuitous encounter in his previous life.

This cliff was like an ant's den, the inside had numerous tunnels and different caves, as if there was a drill that moved in it.

Six hours later, Fang Yuan found the actual route.

He broke the hole in the cave as he moved into it.

When he entered the interior of the cliff, he fell rapidly.

It was pure darkness and moisture, there were all sorts of small life forms like snakes, the largest animal here was a type of lizard, having the size of a normal cat.

All these could not obstruct Fang Yuan.

He quickly got to the bottom of the cliff, as the sound of waves got louder.

At the bottom of the cliff, there was a huge spiral of seawater.

This was the unique undercurrent phenomenon of Eastern Sea.

The seawater in the spiral moved rapidly, there were abundant water vapor and it resembled a giant monster's mouth.

Fang Yuan willed and several Gu worms flew out, stopping here and leaving a marking.

Next, he dived into the spiral with a loud sound.

Once he was in the spiral, a formless force surrounded his body. Even with Fang Yuan's incredible strength, he felt a sense of helplessness as he was 'captured' by the seawater.

Fang Yuan did not struggle, instead he allowed this undercurrent to carry him elsewhere.

This undercurrent was like a formless dragon or python, it created a tunnel of water at the bottom of the sea. The fish groups at the bottom of the sea would swim away from it. Even seaweed and aquatic plants did not grow in their path.

Because they could not grow, they could not endure the long term dragging force of the undercurrents.

Fang Yuan followed this undercurrent as he moved quickly, his current speed was incredible fast, even ordinary movement immortal killer moves could not match his speed!

This was a specialty of the sea's undercurrents.

In Eastern Sea, there was a type of precious map.

The map did not record the islands, nor the surface of the sea, it included the undercurrents in the sea.

Gushes of undercurrents interweaved under the sea, they formed into a natural route for transportation of goods.

In Eastern Sea, some super forces had underwater caravans. These caravans made use of Gu worms to go deep into the sea and use the undercurrents to move rapidly, in a short time, they could travel for ten thousand li, or even a hundred thousand li, to engage in trade.

After about fifteen minutes, Fang Yuan emerged from the other end of this undercurrent.

The endpoint was just like the starting point, it was also a huge seawater spiral.

Fang Yuan jumped out of the spiral, what he saw was a sea of red.

The intense hot air assaulted him.

This was an underwater volcano.

Fang Yuan was currently partway up this underwater volcano.

In the middle of the volcano, there was no seawater entering it.

At the bottom of the volcano, molten magma gushed out from the deep parts of the sea trench, causing countless lives to perish.

And at the top of the volcano, there was a natural underwater hot spring.

Fang Yuan's objective was the underwater hot spring at the top of the volcano.

But Fang Yuan made an estimation, it was not time yet, he decided to explore the place to spend the time.

The lower he went, the hotter it was.

It was pure red in front of him, a type of fire lizard entered Fang Yuan's detection range.

This lizard had shiny smooth scales, it extended its tongue as it ate flying bugs as food.

This type of flying insect originated from the bottom of the volcano, inside the moving molten magma river.

In the magma river, there were bubbles bursting at times as small insects flew out from within.

The fire lizard sprawled on the side of the magma river, seeing that the flying insects had flown out, its tongue shot out at lightning speed as it captured these bugs, it retracted its tongue and swallowed its food.

Fang Yuan observed such a unique habitat for a long time.

Nature was really mysterious, it was displayed in front of Fang Yuan right now.

Fang Yuan observed the fire lizards for a while before paying his attention to the flying insects.

This type of insect was very unique, it was hatched in the magma river, it could endure extremely high temperatures.

After a long time, Fang Yuan had a new discovery: The fire lizard did not succeed in getting its food every time, it would fail consecutively at times.

A portion of the flying insects seemed to have developed some sort of latent talent from the pressure created by the fire lizard.

These flying insects turned into Gu worms during the process of being captured as food. Their speed increased and they managed to evade the lizard's tongue.

This was a form of advancement.

Like a carp jumping through the dragon's gate, turning from a fish into a dragon, its life had been elevated in the most fundamental sense.

After these flying insects became Gu worms, a portion of them took the initiative to land on the lizard and become its accompanying Gu, living together with the lizard.

But these were all fire path mortal Gu, they did not have much value to Fang Yuan.

For the current Fang Yuan, the only interesting thing was this underwater volcano. With it, he had a source to produce Gu worms, he could produce large numbers of fire path and water path Gu worms for a long time.

Mortal Gu only had value to Gu Immortals when they were large enough in quantity.

And finally, Fang Yuan observed this magma river.

This magma river had other life forms, they were a type of fish.

Fang Yuan did not intend to explore further, he did not want to get into trouble by jumping into the magma river either.

The magma river had a high temperature, if Fang Yuan wanted to enter it, he would need to use a defensive immortal killer move. That meant that he would need to consume precious immortal essence.

Nature was mighty, many places had such dangerous environments that even Gu Immortals could not enter for long.

Fang Yuan had been counting the time, when he felt that it was almost time, he traveled up along the volcano, past the point he was at and towards the peak.

By now, he started becoming careful, concealing his traces on purpose.

The young and beautiful Song Yi Shi was one of the six great beauties among Eastern Sea Gu Immortals

Today, Song Yi Shi was in a bad mood.

She was being harassed again.

All these male Gu Immortals who came from everywhere were like annoying flies, they were all around Song Yi Shi, chattering non-stop, they could not even be chased away.

After shrugging off these irritating pursuers, Song Yi Shi came to her personal sea area.

This sea area was called poetic emotion sea, it produced a type of rank four wisdom path Gu worm, emotion poetry Gu. This Gu worm could store emotions and was extremely precious in the minds of mortal Gu Masters.

Song Yi Shi came to the bottom of the sea, going into her underwater volcano palace.

This underwater volcano was inside poetic emotion sea, it was naturally Song Yi Shi's property.

Song Yi Shi was at the peak of the volcano, she had built a beautiful small palace there. She loved the hot spring inside the palace, once in a while, she would go there and take a bath.

She took off her clothes and revealed her peerless body. Her skin was tender and pale, like a freshly peeled egg, her limbs were slender and long, her lips were red and her eyes were sharp, and she had long hair that extended to her waist.

She entered the hot spring and enjoyed herself after shutting her eyes.

Soon, her mood became better, she started to hum a song.

But she did not know that Fang Yuan was lurking close by, observing her every movement.

"It is almost time." Fang Yuan's gaze was eerie as he calculated, he purposely leaked a trace of his aura.

"Who is there?!" Song Yi Shi's expression turned pale, she shouted as her eyes stared at Fang Yuan's hiding spot with much anger.

Chapter 895: Happy About Being Chased Down

"Misunderstanding, this is a misunderstanding!!" Fang Yuan appeared like he was 'forced to'.

Seeing an old man like Xing Xiang Zi appearing in front of her suddenly, Song Yi Shi immediately shrieked. Right now, she was relaxing in the hot spring, completely naked, it was naturally her most vulnerable moment.

If the one that appeared was a female, so be it, but it happened to be a male Gu Immortal.

There should be prudence between sexes!

Song Yi Shi fell into panic.

"I can explain. All this is a big misunderstanding. Please, you must listen to my explanation." Fang Yuan waved his hand, speaking without stop.

At this moment, Song Yi Shi's panic was already surpassed by an intense anger.

"Perverted thief, die!"

Song Yi Shi hid her body in the hot spring, and pointed a finger at Fang Yuan.

Immortal killer move — Stream Veil!

There was an increase of water vapor in the air, two streams of water that were like long sleeves of dancing women, or like thin veils worn by beauties to cover their face, coiled around Fang Yuan from both sides.

Fang Yuan's heart shook.

Song Yi Shi was a water path Gu Immortal, this stream veil was an immortal killer move and it was an exceptional method to capture enemies.

If Fang Yuan was struck by this move, it would be difficult for him to get free.

Not daring to let this stream veil near him, Fang Yuan quickly retreated, starlight shone around him and star snakes moved in the air, facing the stream veil.

Immortal killer move — Star Snake Rope.

Star snakes entangled the stream veil, but stream veil was like water, drowning the star snakes. In just few breaths of time, the star snakes vanished into nothingness.

The stream veil moved towards Fang Yuan again.

"Star snake rope and stream veil are both capturing methods, I didn't think the gap between them would be so huge." Fang Yuan's heart sank. Fortunately, with this small delay, starlight Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture was completely activated, bright light shot out from the Immortal Gu like a rising sun.

Surrounding the starlight Immortal Gu were countless fire path mortal Gu, like tens of thousands of fireflies.

Star path immortal killer move — Star Fire Escape!

Whoosh.

Fang Yuan's whole body burned with deep blue flames, and he soared to the sky like lightning.

"Where are you going?!" Song Yi Shi yelled in a charming voice, as she used the killer move to obstruct Fang Yuan.

Bam!!

A huge explosion erupted at top of underwater volcano.

The seabed shook, torrents rose. The underwater volcano's top part was destroyed for the most part, the natural protective structure was broken, causing endless amounts of seawater to flow inside.

Song Yi Shi was very busy for a while dealing with the flying rocks and the flowing seawater.

She put up a defensive barrier, and quickly wore her clothes, her mind slightly calmed down.

Then without caring about the destruction of the volcano by the seawater, she started flying towards the direction Fang Yuan left in.

"You cannot escape!" Song Yi Shi shouted with clenched teeth.

Fang Yuan's speed, with star fire escape's help, was extremely fast, but because the water was extremely deep, it took a good while to fly out of the sea surface.

In his previous life, the \<\<Biography of Li Xiao Yao\>\> recorded that Li Xiao Yao fell to the bottom of the cliff and entered the undercurrent which took him to the underwater volcano. The bottom of the volcano was too hot, Li Xiao Yao tried to get away from it by moving to the peak of the volcano where he unexpectedly saw Song Yi Shi who was bathing. Song Yi Shi immediately captured him, but after interrogating him, she was instead very pleased.

She had not known there was an extremely hidden undercurrent in the underwater volcano. At this moment, the sea was besieged by strong enemies, Li Xiao Yao's appearance instead gave Song Yi Shi a hope to escape.

Song Yi Shi used this undercurrent to be free from the predicament. While Li Xiao Yao's life had a great turn from here on, Song Yi Shi took him under her wing and guided him on Gu Master cultivation.

The treatment Fang Yuan received was completely different from Li Xiao Yao's.

"Li Xiao Yao was a handsome young boy. Although I am an immortal and also have taken a good appearance, it is one where I am already in my seventies and eighties. Song Yi Shi is young and Song clan is also a colossal force, it would be strange if she did not get angry and chase me down."

Fang Yuan sighed while secretly observing behind him.

When he found Song Yi Shi was chasing him, he gave a light smile, before charging out of the sea surface.

Gu Immortal Yao Ge Pi was one of Song Yi Shi's pursuers, and right now, he was lurking around the poetic emotion sea area.

He looked young, was handsome and charming, and had rank six cultivation. He was a lone cultivator of Eastern Sea.

"Fairy Yi Shi will go bathe in the hot spring of the underwater volcano every once in a while. None of them know this secret, only I am aware of it at present. I will take this chance to have more contact with Fairy Yi Shi. If I can marry her, would I still have to fear not having enough cultivation resources? Hmm? What is going on?!"

Yao Ge Pi gazed at the source of the sound and saw Fang Yuan flying out of the sea with a miserable appearance; a giant wave rose up in the calm sea.

"Looking at his appearance, he seems to be a thief. Do I chase him?" Yao Ge Pi hesitated.

Right at this time, Song Yi Shi also flew out of the sea surface and looked at Fang Yuan's receding figure in the air, shouting in anger: "Perverted thief, don't run, die!!"

"What, perverted thief?!" Yao Ge Pi felt like he had been struck by a lightning, his eyes protruded out till they almost fell off!

"Pervert, perverted thief?"

"What happened to Fairy Yi Shi? That old bastard is actually a daring lecher!! Damn it, kill him!"

Yao Ge Pi roared inwardly, killing intent filling his heart.

"Fairy Yi Shi, don't worry, I, Yao Ge Pi, am here!" The next moment, Yao Ge Pi shouted loudly, stepping forward.

Song Yi Shi was dazed, her original provoked and aggressive air also stilled.

She had just attacked with anger and had not thought much when she shouted furiously, but with Yao Ge Pi's appearance, she could not help but feel panic.

Oh heavens, have mercy!

She was still a young lady, and this was the first time she had experienced a situation like this.

Regarding this matter, she naturally wanted to cover it tightly, it was best if she resolved everything herself, kill Fang Yuan and no one else would know of this matter.

If this matter were to be spread, how would she face others in future?

However, another Gu Immortal appeared now.

She recognized this person, he was one those hateful pursuers, his surname seemed to be Yao?

Song Yi Shi was not too sure.

Yao Ge Pi was even more distressed and anguished the moment he saw Song Yi Shi's panicked expression. He then observed Song Yi Shi's flushed face, red like she had just gone through intercourse, the killing intent inside him increased by dozens of times in an instant!

Actually, nothing had happened, but the imagination of humans was endless, moreover, Yao Ge Pi was a man and a crazed pursuer, he easily interpreted the expression in an entirely dark manner.

Right now, Yao Ge Pi was thinking: This old pervert that is escaping with all his strength has definitely taken huge advantage of her! He might have used some dirty tricks to drug Fairy Yi Shi. He must have approached her, no, he likely kissed her and touched her. Who knows how much Fairy Yi Shi was encroached upon, how much humiliation she suffered!

With such thoughts, the fury in Yao Ge Pi's heart burned so high that it seemed to ignite his whole body, he chased furiously while screaming: "You damned old bastard, old lecher, don't run! You dare to desecrate our Fairy Yi Shi, I am going to skin you alive! I will make you regret everything you did to Fairy Yi Shi!!"

When Song Yi Shi heard this furious scream, her whole body shook and she almost fell down from the air.

Don't scream so loudly, are you trying to let the whole world know? Isn't it best if we quietly, quickly and secretly kill this damned geezer?

Unfortunately, the furious Yao Ge Pi could not hear Song Yi Shi's thoughts.

And this was the first time Song Yi Shi had encountered such a situation, so she lost her composure, she wanted to transmit her voice to say this to Yao Ge Pi, but she was too young and could not speak up no matter what.

How embarrassing was it if she said it outright!

Among these three, the happiest was instead Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had already calculated Song Yi Shi's reaction. Yao Ge Pi's appearance, however, was an unexpected surprise.

'Good, that's good, scream loudly, yes, a bit louder.' Fang Yuan inwardly cheered Yao Ge Pi.

The two Gu Immortals chasing absolutely would not be imagining the strange thoughts in Fang Yuan's mind at this moment.

Fang Yuan wanted to blow the situation up into a huge matter.

Song Yi Shi was a Gu Immortal of a super force, Song clan, she was the apple of Song Qi Yuan's eye, with many pursuers. After this matter blows up, Fang Yuan would have an external pressure to join Zombie Alliance.

However, this conflict was not from swindling money, murdering someone's parents, or a life and death battle.

At most, Fang Yuan had only taken a glance unintentionally.

Song Yi Shi was a young girl with very few experiences, her thoughts were still conservative, naturally, she would feel wronged and furious at having someone see her body for the first time.

This was the natural mentality of young people.

As they got older and more experienced, no matter who they were, they would gain at least some knowledge on sexual life.

So what if he took a glance? Didn't some women wish others would just keep on looking at them? From a certain perspective, did this not prove one's charm?

Two to three hundred years later, Li Xiao Yao also peeked at but nothing happened to him, instead he was protected and hidden.

One big reason was that Song Yi Shi's mentality had already changed.

Later, Li Xiao Yao would have another fortuitous encounter and become a sword path Gu Immortal, and finally, he and Song Yi Shi would become an immortal couple.

Wasn't Song Yi Shi older than Li Xiao Yao by two to three hundred years, she could be said to be a cradle-robber.

"Of course, there is another reason. Two to three hundred years later, Song Qi Yuan's lifespan had been used up and he died. The rank eight Gu Immortal's fall created an enormous change in Eastern Sea's structure. Song clan began to weaken and the enormous wealth Song Yi Shi had was coveted by others. Not only was there pressure from external sources, there was internal strife in the clan as well. Li Xiao Yao, who was taught by Song Yi Shi and accompanied her throughout his mortal Gu Master stage and shared her sufferings, became the most reassuring individual to Song Yi Shi. Later, Li Xiao Yao inherited Sword Immortal Drunken Green Bull's inheritance, and developed methods bringing in new advancements, and became a powerful sword path Gu Immortal, this caused Song Yi Shi to fall for him. The two became an immortal couple, moving around without a set destination, secretively and freely. In the five regions chaotic war, they appeared and worked together to resist rank eight Gu Immortals, becoming a great pillar in blocking Central Continent's offensive."

Fang Yuan fled while thinking leisurely about all sorts of things.

Chapter 896: Freely Leaving After Killing

In the sky, a battle of pursuit was unfolding.

Bam bam bam!

Intense explosions occurred one after another.

Song Yi Shi and Yao Ge Pi attacked non-stop, but because of the distance, and because Fang Yuan was slippery like an eel, he could not be caught, he was displaying an incredible flying attainment.

Even though he was ahead, Fang Yuan, who was pretending to be escaping, was actually slowing his speed, allowing the two pursuers to follow him.

He was a demonic path overlord, in his previous life, even though he did not have particularly great achievements, he had rich life experience, he had undergone many battles, it was something that these two young Gu Immortals behind him could not imagine.

Especially Song Yi Shi, she was too young and had little battle experience. Even though she was using an immortal killer move to chase him, she could not catch up no matter what.

Fang Yuan changed directions often, sometimes he went into the water, sometimes he went into the clouds, he was extremely crafty. Song Yi Shi was extremely angry, she felt like she was not chasing him down, but being played with instead.

As for Yao Ge Pi, he was a lone cultivator, even though he had more experience, he did not have a single Immortal Gu, not to mention any immortal killer moves.

He, who could only use mortal killer moves, was doomed in this battle of pursuit from the start.

He was lagging behind, he could only shout loudly, if Fang Yuan was not purposely slowing down for him, he would have been left in the dust already.

The three traveled quickly through the air, they soon left the poetic emotion sea area.

"What is going on? There are Gu Immortals fighting?"

The noise from their travels earned the attentions of two lone cultivator Gu Immortals from a nearby island.

These two were playing chess, they were quite relaxed.

Hearing the commotion, they raised their heads as they used investigative methods.

"It seems to be Song clan's Fairy Yi Shi, and a young male lone cultivator, they are pursuing someone. This person's aura is not that of Eastern Sea, they are a Northern Plains Gu Immortal."

"Less trouble is better than more trouble, Song Yi Shi is the prized gem of Song Qi Yuan, let's not interfere in this."

"You are right, come, let's continue playing chess."

Fang Yuan looked at this island, he frowned slightly as he turned to another direction, continuing to fly.

Not long later, at web eye sea area.

"What? There is such a lecherous and shameless old bastard in this world! Fairy Yi Shi, I, Chen Zhong Yong, will lend you a hand!"

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, he dodged Chen Zhong Yong's attack as he continued escaping.

Thus, there were three people chasing after him now.

After a certain amount of time, at rumbling thunder sea channel.

"Fairy Yi Shi is pure as jade, she was actually tainted! He deserves death, he deserves death!!" Bi Qing Tian was anguished, he joined in the chase resolutely.

Fifteen minutes later, the commotion caused by them attracted a battle maniac Gu Immortal.

"You are a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, you dare to lay your lecherous hands on our Eastern Sea Goddess? Do you think that we of Eastern Sea can be bullied?" Lei Hong was furious, he spoke without restraint.

Song Yi Shi was getting more and more furious, seeing that Fang Yuan was still escaping, her mood was getting worse.

He had only taken a glance at her, why were these people spouting more and more ridiculous nonsense, like she had lost her virginity to him?

"Stop shouting! Kill him in secret, I will reward you greatly!" Song Yi Shi could not hold it in anymore, she transmitted to them.

These Gu Immortals were not idiots, after hearing this, they went silent.

"Why are they not shouting anymore?" Fang Yuan did not want that to happen, he wanted this matter to blow up, the bigger the commotion the better.

"Since you are shutting up, I will have to do it myself."

Thus, Fang Yuan shouted, defending himself: "Everyone, this is a misunderstanding, I will clarify this matter. I had accidentally entered the depths of poetic emotion sea area's underwater volcano, everyone can investigate this matter, I am speaking the truth."

"Old lecher, you are bullshitting!" Immediately, a Gu Immortal screamed back.

But Fang Yuan ignored him, he yelled: "I am a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, I have just arrived here and wanted to choose an unknown island to reside in. I picked a small island after looking for a long time. Before setting up some arrangements, I wanted to look around the area, I discovered a hidden undercurrent and moved along it, getting into the underwater volcano."

"Lies, you're continuing to lie to us!"

"You did something so shameless, but you are actually defending yourself, trying to pretend to be a gentleman?! Do you think we are so easy to fool?"

The Gu Immortals screamed.

Fang Yuan called out: "Even if I am lying, I would need to make a better excuse, why would I mention the undercurrent? You can go verify this, I will tell you the location of the island. Before I entered the undercurrent, I did not know it would connect to the underwater volcano, either, after I entered the volcano, I found out..."

"Shut up!" Song Yi Shi shouted, she was worried that Fang Yuan might expose some secretive information, she interrupted him: "If you are innocent, stop running, obediently submit and let us investigate. If you are speaking the truth, I, Song Yi Shi, will not kill an innocent person!"

Song Yi Shi had learned something quickly and grew a little, she actually understood that she needed to coax him.

But her tone was too stiff, anyone could tell that she was full of anger and killing intent.

Song Yi Shi was still too pitiful in her acting skills.

Fang Yuan continued to escape, he shouted continuously: "Do you think I am a fool? If I surrender, I will die. I am innocent, I did not even touch a single hair of yours, after I reached the volcano..."

"Shut the hell up!!" Song Yi Shi flew into a rage, her voice was even louder now.

The other male Gu Immortals had furious expressions on the surface, but they were secretly concentrating and were afraid of missing a single word from Fang Yuan's mouth!

Seeing that Fang Yuan was interrupted by Song Yi Shi again, they felt mild regret internally.

But Fang Yuan quickly continued: "The more you do not want me to say it, the more I will say. How can you be so overbearing, I am just a Northern Plains Gu Immortal trying to make a living in Eastern Sea, is it easy for me?! I did not do anything, I only saw a glimpse of you bathing, it was all a misunderstanding!"

Song Yi Shi saw darkness in front of her, she was so angered her heart was going to burst into flames.

She could make the people on her side shut up, but she could not stop Fang Yuan from shouting.

"Hehehe, something so interested has happened." At this time, a lovely laugh could be heard, a female Gu Immortal was approaching.

"It is Seven Seas Snake Woman!" The Gu Immortals that were chasing after Fang Yuan saw this female Gu Immortal and became alert.

Yao Ge Pi was bemoaning internally, everyone else directed their gazes towards Song Yi Shi.

Song Yi Shi's expression was dark, she looked like an ice statue that was emitting immense cold air.

As it turned out, Seven Seas Snake Woman and Song Yi Shi were both publicly known as among the six great beauties among Eastern Sea Gu Immortals. Seven Seas Snake Woman had rank seven cultivation level, she was a demonic path Gu Immortal who had some conflicts with Song Yi Shi, but because of Song Qi Yuan's power, she did not dare to attack Song Yi Shi.

At this moment, she heard such interesting news, she was sure to add in more false details and spread this rumor around!

Song Yi Shi felt like the sky was collapsing.

What was she going to do now? Seven Seas Snake Woman was definitely going to ruin her reputation.

Song Yi Shi felt even more hatred towards Fang Yuan now: "You old lecher, how are you so good at running, even running into Seven Seas Snake Woman?"

What a joke!

This route was specially chosen by Fang Yuan after careful investigation.

The Gu Immortals that they would meet along the way were all found out by Fang Yuan prior to this. Seven Seas Snake Woman was very important in Fang Yuan's current plan.

Even though Seven Seas Snake Woman was a demonic path Gu Immortal, she owned seven sea areas, right now, this sea area was at a crucial moment when a large number of red tide fish were reproducing, she had to stay here to guard it.

Fang Yuan easily obtained this information.

Seven Seas Snake Woman was a beautiful but dangerous woman, she was very ruthless in her actions. The righteous path would often leak details of such people, so that others could be prepared if they were to meet them.

Boom!

With a loud sound, Seven Seas Snake Woman suddenly struck, attacking the pursuers of Fang Yuan.

"Seven Seas Snake Woman, what are you doing?" Lei Hong shouted.

Song Yi Shi and the others were severely interrupted.

"Hehehe, this is such an interesting matter, I definitely have to interfere." Seven Seas Snake Woman had an alluring body, she had a coquettish gaze as she answered.

Lei Hong said solemnly: "I will block Seven Seas Snake Woman, the rest of you continue chasing him."

He had rank seven cultivation level, he was not afraid of Seven Seas Snake Woman, even though his battle strength was lower, he could still stall her for a short time and escape from her.

Seven Seas Snake Woman did not know who Fang Yuan was, she would not exert too much effort. Seeing that Lei Hong was stepping up, she showed a look of disgust as she stopped on the spot: "You again, meddlesome fool, you really like to interfere in people's affairs."

Thus, the other Gu Immortals detoured around Seven Seas Snake Woman, chasing after Fang Yuan again.

Time continued to pass, after a very long time, there were a few more people chasing Fang Yuan, even though he was quite injured, he did not fall into their hands, he was still escaping.

"Damn it!!" Song Yi Shi gritted her teeth, she felt fatigue looking at Fang Yuan's energetic body.

Everything had happened too quickly, and too suddenly.

How did it become like this? Song Yi Shi felt a sense of absurdity within her.

A moment ago, she was still enjoying a carefree life, bathing inside her hot spring as she relaxed herself. But now, she was chasing an enemy endlessly with no way of catching up.

And now, almost all the immortals nearby knew about it.

Song Yi Shi felt tired physically, but even more so mentally.

"It is about time." Fang Yuan looked at the pursuers, he smiled faintly. The execution of this plan was much more effective than he had originally planned.

"Now, it is time to leave."

Thinking of this, a ruthless light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes.

His body shook as he turned into six figures, flying towards six different directions.

Immortal killer move — Six Illusion Star Bodies!

The pursuers shouted out in dismay, they were stunned before splitting up to chase him.

Immortal killer move — Position Star Swap!

Fang Yuan changed his position, appearing in front of Yao Ge Pi.

"Don't think I am afraid of killing!" Fang Yuan called out, using star cloud grindstone.

He had been escaping all this time, why would Yao Ge Pi think that Fang Yuan would act differently and counterattack?

Caught off guard, he was sucked into the star cloud grindstone.

He only had mortal killer moves, how could he defend against the power of Immortal Gu?

When everyone else came to reinforce him and destroyed the star cloud grindstone, Fang Yuan was already holding onto Yao Ge Pi's head!

"Hmph, don't go overboard!" Fang Yuan's ruthlessness was shown, he faced the band of immortals.

The pursuers were only rank six. It was not easy to encounter rank sevens like Lei Hong.

"Yao Ge Pi when all is said and done is a Gu Immortal, he was actually killed in such a short amount of time!"

"Northern Plains barbarians are really exemplary in battle strength."

The immortals were all stunned, they felt a strong sense of wariness internally.

Meanwhile, one of the six illusion star bodies had already flown far away, Fang Yuan used position star swap and changed his true body's position, abruptly and freely leaving!

Chapter 897: Difficult To Own Ge Pi Blessed Land

Three days later, in the world of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, there was a rumor that spread widely.

This involved one of the six great beauties of Eastern Sea, Fairy Yi Shi. When she was bathing, she was defiled by an old lecher who shamelessly planned everything.

Song Yi Shi was Song Qi Yuan's precious gem, she had quite a reputation and many suitors. This matter involved Song clan's reputation as well, once information got out, many Gu Immortals' attentions were attracted.

Soon, Xing Xiang Zi's Northern Plains Gu Immortal identity was found out by other Gu Immortals.

Before Song clan even expressed their attitude, Song Yi Shi's suitors were already hunting down Fang Yuan on a large scale with furious emotions.

At a nameless and ownerless sea area with little resources, the sea was deep and dark, there were few fish.

A wooden door that looked like a blessed land's entrance appeared, and opened with a creak.

A figure walked out from within.

It was Fang Yuan, having Xing Xiang Zi's appearance.

Fang Yuan killed Yao Ge Pi on the spot, after that, he carried Yao Ge Pi's corpse away and escaped.

There were two uses for bodies of Gu Immortals. One was to place them down and form a blessed land, the other was to put them into one's own immortal aperture and obtain their dao marks.

Fang Yuan did not have to think it over, he chose the former.

His immortal aperture was dead, if corpses were put inside his dead aperture, not only would he not get any dao marks, it would cause massive destruction to the land, his body would burst and explode.

Such a situation had been experimented with by immortal zombies, but there had never been any cases of success.

Fang Yuan used his wisdom path methods to contain the immortal aperture and stall for some time, after escaping from the pursuers, he used a stargate to return to Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture, before using Fixed Immortal Travel to teleport himself towards the north-eastern extremity of Eastern Sea.

Finally, he dived into the sea, without anyone's notice, he placed Yao Ge Pi's immortal aperture down at the bottom of the sea.

After the immortal aperture formed into a blessed land, it naturally created disturbances in heaven qi and earth qi.

Two whale desolate beasts were drawn over, but Fang Yuan chased them away.

Fang Yuan first turned into another appearance, before entering Yao Ge Pi's blessed land and meeting with the land spirit.

Yao Ge Pi was a wood path Gu Immortal, he owned Ge Pi blessed land, his land spirit was quite peculiar, it was in the form of a tree, planted at the center of the blessed land with no movement ability.

The tree land spirit told Fang Yuan the ownership condition — a hundred thousand immortal essence stones, large amounts of immortal materials, including many rank seven and rank eight materials, it even wanted the fresh blood of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable!

The condition was too immensely difficult, Fang Yuan, of course, could not satisfy it, he could only leave regrettably.

"Yao Ge Pi is a lone cultivator, he had the weakest background among the pursuers, and had no backers, that was why I killed him, to act as deterrence against the others. Indeed, I deterred Song Yi Shi's group and escaped easily."

"Yao Ge Pi's immortal aperture formed into a separate blessed land, but the land spirit's ownership condition has nothing to do with me, the killer. Instead, it is requesting for lots of cultivation resources, it shows that Yao Ge Pi's greatest obsession is towards wealth. But his desire is simply too insatiable."

Fang Yuan had just left, the blessed land's doors closed.

He looked back and saw that the door was completely shut, he frowned slightly.

"If Yao Ge Pi's obsession had to do with me, with my blood path methods, I could easily handle it. But its ownership condition is simply harder than ascending to heaven."

Not mentioning the hundred thousand immortal essence stones, simply the precious immortal materials were hard to gather. Unless Fang Yuan robbed the ten great ancient sects, or stole that huge amount from Heavenly Court's treasury, simply based on his current state, it would take a lot of good luck for him to gather them all, two to three hundred years would be the minimum amount of time he needed.

But most importantly, it was the final condition that the tree land spirit had — Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's fresh blood!

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable was a wood path rank nine Gu Venerable, Yao Ge Pi also cultivated wood path, it was not strange that he desired Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's blood.

But who was Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable? Even if his fresh blood was preserved by Heavenly Lotus Sect, that was a true rank nine immortal material!

This was a precious material that could refine rank nine Immortal Gu, it was definitely heavily guarded, how could Fang Yuan obtain it?

"This Yao Ge Pi must have gone crazy from poverty, his obsession towards wealth is so intense. In this way, to obtain this blessed land, it seems normal methods will not work, I can only attack forcefully!"

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with cold light.

If this land spirit refused to accept a master, he would destroy it and forcefully take over the blessed land!

Not all blessed lands had land spirits. Some Gu Immortals were killed extremely thoroughly and did not leave behind any obsession, after they died, their blessed land would be without a land spirit.

Yao Ge Pi's blessed land had a land spirit, but the conditions were too absurd, Fang Yuan could only find an alternative and attack forcefully. It was like Shark Demon's group invading Yu Lu blessed land.

"If I can obtain this blessed land, I would have a base in Eastern Sea. But now is not the time to settle this blessed land, I should go and regroup with Shark Demon first."

Fang Yuan scattered some mortal Gu, setting up a Gu formation around him.

Next, he activated Fixed Immortal Travel, leaving this place and going to Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture.

Originally, Fixed Immortal Travel's aura was in the sea, but after Fang Yuan's Gu formation activated, it dissipated.

After the work was done, this set of mortal Gu disintegrated on its own.

Unless a very powerful investigation method was used, no one would be able to find out that there was a blessed land in such an ordinary area.

Fang Yuan came out of Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture, the latter had already started moving, he was flying above the vast sea.

The 'senior and junior' brothers conversed along the way, after a few minutes, they arrived at the sky above Yu Lu blessed land.

Here, there was nobody.

The two waited for a while, soon, Shark Demon led a band of Gu Immortals from Zombie Alliance and flew over.

"Brother Xing Xiang, you are quite famous nowadays." Once he saw Fang Yuan, Shark Demon made a joke.

The other Gu Immortals looked at Fang Yuan with curious glances.

These few days, Fang Yuan had become very famous in the world of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, he had gained quite a reputation.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly, he replied: "Very unlucky, I was very unlucky, please don't laugh at me. I wanted to find an island to rest in, but I found an undercurrent and wanted to explore it, to think I would encounter such a troublesome affair."

"This is not a troublesome affair, it is quite appropriate to call this a romantic affair." Bo Dan laughed loudly, sarcastically saying.

Earlier, Fang Yuan had humiliated him.

But after that, Bo Dan paid a huge price and gave Su Bai Man an expensive gift, thus he joined the invasion of the blessed land again, and he had a fearless attitude.

Fang Yuan gave him a glance, smiling, he did not bother responding to such a person.

He glanced around and saw that other than Shark Demon, Su Bai Man, and Bo Dan, there was only one familiar immortal zombie, Sha Nan Jiang, there were three less people than before.

But Shark Demon was very confident, it seemed that he had made ample preparations before coming.

Everyone went deep into the sea, opening the entrance of Yu Lu blessed land, entering the battlefield killer move freezing rain frozen earth again.

"This time, Xing Xiang Zi, we will mainly be relying on your deductions, Bo Dan will support you." Shark Demon announced politely.

Last time, Fang Yuan performed well, Shark Demon and the others thought that Xing Xiang Zi had a deeper wisdom path attainment level.

"Lord Shark Demon, please rest assured, I will do my best." Fang Yuan expressed his firm attitude.

Bo Dan snorted internally, even though he was displeased, he knew his own abilities, he crossed his arms and watched with a dark gaze.

Facing freezing rain frozen earth again, Fang Yuan's expression became serious as he deduced.

The battlefield killer move, freezing rain frozen earth, had completely recovered, the damage caused by Fang Yuan and the others had been fixed already.

Fang Yuan was not surprised.

Earlier, when Shark Demon and the others attacked the blessed land, the battlefield killer move could also repair itself.

It was unknown whether this was due to Yu Lu blessed land's land spirit, or the arrangements of Fairy Yu Lu.

Speaking of which, Shark Demon and the others had attacked the blessed land for such a long time, but they had not found the land spirit of Yu Lu blessed land yet. Whether the land spirit existed, this was still a mystery.

With his prior experience, Fang Yuan's progress was fast.

He naturally did not destroy the crucial mortal Gu, thus the battlefield did not become stronger compared to the last time.

The ice needle storm rained down, as Shark Demon stepped forward and used his Immortal Gu.

The Immortal Gu's name was Melt Ice, it was an ice path Immortal Gu and could melt even the firmest ice. This Gu was borrowed by Shark Demon specially to deal with freezing rain frozen earth, he paid a huge amount to a certain member of Zombie Alliance.

With this melt ice Immortal Gu, they greatly resisted the freezing rain frozen earth's power, even the desolate beast level snow monsters were obstructed.

Shark Demon and the others felt less pressure, they even expended far less immortal essence than last time.

There was a counter to everything, the strong freezing rain frozen earth was greatly weakened after encountering the melt ice Immortal Gu.

The Gu Master world was like this.

Everything was in balance, strong and weak was relative. There were no invincible Gu worms, there were only invincible Gu Masters.

With melt ice Immortal Gu, Shark Demon could move freely as well.

Fang Yuan also progressed stably.

Even though he was a wisdom path newbie, he had precious experience from last time, after returning, he had revised his methods and improved a lot, he designed many new methods.

This time, Fang Yuan came prepared.

He had to say, Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path inheritance was simply brilliant, using it, Fang Yuan could forcefully find a solution.

The start was the hardest, after Fang Yuan found the first flaw, his progress became faster, he deduced more and more hidden Gu worms.

But during this process, Fang Yuan could feel his lack of experience.

But he was an experienced schemer, he immediately ordered Bo Dan to help.

Even though Bo Dan's wisdom path methods were shallow and few, after Fang Yuan started the deduction, he could also see a portion of the details inside the battlefield killer move, he also had very familiar methods and precise techniques.

Fang Yuan pretended to deduce but he was secretly observing Bo Dan's techniques, he learned a lot of things and his wisdom path attainment was rising.

Eventually, with both of their efforts, freezing rain frozen earth was finally unraveled.

By now, the freezing rain battlefield has unleashed a total of thirty-three attacks, Shark Demon's melt ice Immortal Gu was singlehandedly holding them back.

The huge immortal essence expenditure reduced his joy of passing the difficult round to a great extent.

Chapter 898: Fighting Soul Battlefield

Freezing rain frozen earth disappeared, the world changed.

The original icy world turned into a dark environment, it was like evening, there were dark clouds looming and the poor weather seemed to be indicating a thunderstorm.

Evidently, this was another battlefield killer move.

"Welcome to fighting soul battlefield." A faint female voice resounded in the battlefield

Everyone who was inside the battlefield heard the voice.

Shark Demon's expression changed, he said: "Oh no, this is the infamous fighting soul battlefield! This is troublesome."

Even before he finished his sentence, a sandstorm started blowing as sand and dust were scattered in the sky, soul beasts appeared one after another, from all directions, encircling the Gu Immortals.

Su Bai Man quickly reminded: "Xing Xiang Zi, Bo Dan, you have to act quickly! The number of soul beasts here are endless, the longer we take, the stronger they become. This fighting soul battlefield was a battlefield killer move created by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable after he used one of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's inheritances as a reference. Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's other creations had some mercy in them, they would always leave behind a way to survive. But this battlefield killer move is very different, it contains Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's killing nature, it is the most deadly battlefield killer move among Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's creations!"

Fang Yuan and Bo Dan did not dare to take their time, they used their respective methods and tried to unravel the killer move.

Fang Yuan soon discovered: This fighting soul battlefield was very different from freezing rain frozen earth. The latter had no flaws at all when activated, it was very well balanced, giving others a feeling of not knowing where to start. But this fighting soul battlefield exposed several hiding spots of mortal Gu to Fang Yuan from the start easily.

As time passed, Fang Yuan found more and more hidden spots, they were growing into a huge number, there were thousands or even tens of thousands of them!

The number of Gu worms that formed this battlefield killer move was much higher than Fang Yuan's expectations.

Fang Yuan soon found out, there were no traps like the ones that were in the freezing rain frozen earth battlefield killer move. No matter which hidden spot they destroyed, there was no backlash, and Fang Yuan did not need to restart his deductions.

Thus, very soon, Fang Yuan and Bo Dan started to dismantle these hidden spots rapidly.

However, this fighting soul battlefield's offensive power was several times greater than freezing rain frozen earth.

Freezing rain frozen earth attacked in waves, there was a moment of peace in between each wave of attacks, the Gu Immortals could rest for a while each time.

But this fighting soul battlefield did not stop for a moment after activation, the number of soul beasts continued to increase, soon, desolate beast level soul beasts were formed.

A while later, there were more than ten desolate soul beasts, even ancient desolate soul beasts started appearing.

They did not even last for seven minutes before Shark Demon and the others had to use the incomplete Profound Ice House to escape from the place.

"There are simply too many Gu worms used to create the battlefield killer move, I am ashamed, my methods are too simple, I could only dismantle them one by one." Once they got out of the sea, Bo Dan spoke to Shark Demon without concealing any information, he spoke the truth.

Fang Yuan frowned too: "My methods could only dismantle at most five to six hidden spots each time. I suspect that this fighting soul battlefield's difficulty lies here. The faster we can dismantle it, or the longer we can last under the attacks of the soul beasts, the more likely it is that we can unravel this killer move. To unravel it in itself is not the problematic part."

"In that case, Xing Xiang Zi, according to your deduction, how long do both of you need to dismantle this killer move at your current speed?" Shark Demon asked.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly and shook his head: "I am not sure. I did not manage to see the entire battlefield killer move. There are too many hidden spots, they are numerous like the stars in the sky. And even if I manage to find the tens of thousands of hidden spots, to get rid of them, I will need at least thirty minutes."

Sha Nan Jiang was lost for words: "Thirty minutes? We lasted for seven minutes and there were already ancient desolate soul beasts appearing. Thirty minutes... surely, immemorial desolate soul beasts will appear, and there might be more than one!"

Everyone became quiet.

Su Bai Man spoke heavily: "In that case, we can only ask more people to help out next time. These Gu Immortals will need to have enough wisdom path attainment to dismantle the hidden spots."

Saying so, Su Bai Man and Shark Demon looked at each other, they could see the bitterness in each other's eyes.

There were not many Gu Immortals with wisdom path attainment. Asking them to help would incur a huge cost.

Shark Demon thought for a while, he spoke: "Then we will retreat for now. The next time we are attacking is in thirty days, we will decide on the time at a later date, I will inform you all. Xing Xiang Zi, this is my command token, you can use it to stay in Zombie Alliance's headquarters and avoid the trouble you are facing for now."

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "Thank you for your goodwill, Lord Shark Demon, but I am not willing to waste any time. Merely Song Yi Shi cannot do anything to me. Even though Song clan is a huge force, they cannot control the entirety of Eastern Sea. If I hide and shrink away because of this, I, Xing Xiang Zi, would have cultivated for nothing. Everyone, until next time we meet."

Seeing Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng fly far away, Bo Dan stepped forward and stood beside Shark Demon, he slandered: "This Xing Xiang Zi really does not know what is good for him, he actually refused to accept Lord's goodwill!"

Shark Demon glanced at him, he snorted, saying unhappily: "If you were any more capable, why would I need to treat him like this?"

Bo Dan had a bitter expression: "Oh lord, it was not that I did not put in effort, but my inheritance is too incomplete, there is a limit to what I can do."

Shark Demon waved his hand impatiently.

Bo Dan quickly shut up and lowered his head, leaving.

Su Bai Man got close to Shark Demon, she smiled: "If husband is afraid that Xing Xiang Zi would get into trouble and delay the next invasion, you do not need to worry. Northern Plains Gu Immortals often have higher battle strength than the other four regions, Xing Xiang Zi also has Immortal Gu with him, his battle strength was high enough to kill Yao Ge Pi on the spot, nothing would happen to him."

"Even though he offended Song Yi Shi, the precious gem of Song Qi Yuan, it is precisely because Song clan is a righteous path super force, a large organization with many matters to take care of, that they would not create a huge commotion over such a small matter. But Song clan's reputation was affected, they would definitely want an answer. In a while, Xing Xiang Zi would feel increasing pressure, by then, wouldn't he come to ask us for help?"

"Mm, that is indeed the case, your analysis is very accurate." Shark Demon's expression became calmer, he gently held Su Bai Man's hand.

...

Northern Plains, Luo Po valley.

The battle surrounding Luo Po valley had already been ongoing for over half a month.

Qin Bai Sheng's side had the territorial advantage, Feng Jiu Ge's side was unable to take them down. But Feng Jiu Ge and the others were very determined, they besieged the area without retreating, Qin Bai Sheng's side could only hide inside Luo Po valley for the time being.

"Jiang Yu, how are your injuries?" Qin Bai Sheng went to visit Fairy Jiang Yu.

"In half a day, I will fully recover." Fairy Jiang Yu sat on the bed, shutting her eyes as she healed herself, she replied while multitasking.

Joy flashed across Qin Bai Sheng's face: "That is good. After you recover, we will protect you as you charge out of the encirclement, and go to Northern Plains Zombie Alliance to activate our hidden arrangement."

"What? We are going to use our arrangement in Northern Plains Zombie Alliance? Will it not have a huge impact on the entire crucial plan?" Fairy Jiang Yu was shocked, she asked this.

Qin Bai Sheng said heavily: "It won't. I have already communicated with Old Man Yan Shi, in Shadow Sect's Southern Border headquarters. Sigh... Feng Jiu Ge is really quite the character, his self-created heaven and earth song could match my five finger fist heart sword. My personal reputation is nothing important, but the Immortal Gu that is still being nurtured inside Luo Po valley is important to our crucial plan, it cannot be lost. But now that Luo Po valley is being encircled by these people from Central Continent, we are at a disadvantage in terms of numbers, we can only rely on the ancient soul beasts to defend ourselves. We will eventually fall if this keeps up, we need to regain the initiative!"

These last days, he had fought with Feng Jiu Ge for over dozens of rounds, after exchanging blows countless times, even if they put in all their efforts, they had been unable to determine a winner.

Qin Bai Sheng was concerned about the big picture, he wanted to find a way to get out of this predicament.

But at this time, Feng Jiu Ge's voice came from outside.

Qin Bai Sheng heard it and sneered internally: "After remaining silent for three days, he's finally returned to taunt us again?"

Qin Bai Sheng flew into the air, facing Feng Jiu Ge: "Brother Feng, we have undergone innumerable rounds of battles, we know each other's abilities quite well now. You are an astute person, can't you see that in this current situation, as long as I defend this Luo Po valley, you cannot break in by force!"

Feng Jiu Ge smiled brightly, an intense light of confidence shined in his eyes: "Brother Qin, this time is different. After our countless rounds of battles, I had gained much inspiration. These last three days, I have been in closed cultivation, I used the inspiration to complete an incomplete move that I had created in the past."

"Oh?" Qin Bai Sheng's expression turned serious.

Feng Jiu Ge raised his head slightly, he said loudly: "This time, I would like to ask Brother Qin to critique my submission song!"

Green Jade Song.

Heaven and Earth Song.

Submission Song.

When Feng Jiu Ge sang green jade song, his voice was crisp and sharp, like beads of flawless jade. When he sang heaven and earth song, his voice was grand and magnificent, it made others feel their own insignificance.

But now, Feng Jiu Ge sang submission song, his mouth was closed.

The entire place was silent.

Qin Bai Sheng's expression was both serious and grim, because he 'heard' Feng Jiu Ge's singing voice.

His singing voice was directly resounding in Qin Bai Sheng's mind.

It turns out that this submission song was not heard with one's ears, but in one's mind.

Qin Bai Sheng's heart sank: "This sound path killer move encompasses wisdom path, enslavement path, sound path, and soul path, these four paths, it affects a person's mind. From the moment he closed his mouth, there is already a trace of five finger fist heart sword in it. This Feng Jiu Ge actually obtained this inspiration from me. But it is only at this level, it is not enough to affect my fighting spirit. Eh? Oh no!"

Qin Bai Sheng's reaction was fast, but submission song's effect was even faster.

In Luo Po valley, there were many ancient soul beasts that were guarding the place, under the influence of Feng Jiu Ge's song, they submitted to him, they betrayed Qin Bai Sheng on the spot, becoming the lackeys of the Central Continent Gu Immortals.

Submission song could temporarily cause desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts to change sides, becoming subordinates of the singer!

"Damn it!" He Lang Zi cursed.

They had few people, they needed the ancient soul beasts to bolster their defenses.

But now, most of the ancient soul beasts changed sides, they started attacking Luo Po valley instead, Shadow Sect's side was falling into great danger.

But Qin Bai Sheng was not easy to deal with.

He quickly thought of this and displayed a battlefield killer move.

Feng Jiu Ge and the others, including the ancient soul beasts, were dragged into this battlefield.

There was thick fog in this battlefield, countless souls were flying around.

Dark blue soul beasts gathered and took form, most of them were ordinary soul beasts, but soon, desolate soul beasts appeared, and seemingly before long, ancient soul beasts would appear as well.

The soul beasts that were created in this battlefield fought against the ancient soul beasts that were under Feng Jiu Ge's control.

"Good countermeasure." Feng Jiu Ge stopped singing, he praised: "Using this battlefield killer move to increase your control of the soul beasts and eliminate the advantage of submission song. But your soul taker battlefield is too outdated, even though it was created by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he made it when he was young. Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had once used this killer move to create the even more superior fighting soul battlefield. This soul taker battlefield can only convert the souls of living beings into soul beasts, but fighting soul battlefield can actually produce endless soul beasts."

Feng Jiu Ge was inside the battlefield killer move, but he was not worried, he spoke casually as he critiqued the killer move.

Qin Bai Sheng, however, spoke with a smile: "Future generations enjoy the benefits from the hard work of predecessors. Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable could create the superior fighting soul battlefield because he used the foundation created by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, it is only to be expected. But he was too kind of a person, he weakened Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's killing intent, even though it seems superior, it lost all hope of going a step further."

Saying this, the battlefield changed again.

Feng Jiu Ge's expression changed: "So this is not soul taker battlefield, it is a battlefield killer move that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable created in his later years — Hundred Million Slaughterfield!"

Chapter 899: Twin Polar Sea Strait, Song Jia Dan

Eastern Sea, Song clan's headquarters, Heavy Water blessed land.

"Grandpa, you have to avenge me!" Song Yi Shi charged into the study room, stomping her feet and throwing a tantrum to the rank eight Gu Immortal Song Qi Yuan.

Song Qi Yuan and some rank seven Gu Immortal elders were discussing matters of the clan.

But Song Yi Shi barged in directly like this.

Song Qi Yuan turned around slowly, he showed no anger on his face as he smiled kindly: "My sweet granddaughter, how do you want grandpa to avenge you?"

Song Yi Shi did not find it strange that her grandfather knew about this, in fact, if Song Qi Yuan did not know about it, that would be the strange thing.

Before this young female Gu Immortal came, she had already thought of an answer, she gritted her teeth: "Grandpa, strike directly and capture him alive, I will deal with him after that."

At the same time, she thought inwardly: "I will dig out this old lecher's eyes out first, then I will pull out his tendons and his skin, I will carve out his bones and make his flesh rot, he will be in so much pain, I will make him regret everything that he has done!"

Song Qi Yuan nodded, he did not hesitation, he agreed: "That is a good method, but..."

He dragged his words out, Song Qi Yuan changed the course of the conversation as he showed a difficult expression: "Grandpa has something important to do now, I cannot leave, why don't I get your uncle, Song Xia Qi, to help you?"

Song Yi Shi's eyes shined, she forget her own situation, she thought of something as she asked excitedly: "Grandpa, is it regarding Ascending Heaven Plain?"

Song Qi Yuan did not hide it from her, he admitted: "That's right! Ascending Heaven Plain's exact location has already become an open secret among most Eastern Sea Gu Immortals. In Ascending Heaven Plain, there is Old Eccentric Tian Nan's inheritance. This time, grandpa will lead the clan's Gu Immortals to compete against Cai clan and Ruo Lai clan, to try to obtain Old Eccentric Tian Nan's inheritance."

Old Eccentric Tian Nan, a refinement path supreme grandmaster from the Remote Antiquity Era, he was on par with Old Immortal Kong Jue and Long Hair Ancestor over the course of history.

According to historical records, Old Eccentric Tian Nan had a strange personality, he attempted to refine the immemorial nine heavens and ended up dying after failing.

Even though Song Yi Shi was spoiled since she was young, she understood the bigger picture, she quickly replied: "Go and deal with that, grandpa, make sure you utterly defeat them both! You do not need to worry about my matter, but just uncle Song Xia Qi isn't enough, I want uncle Song Jia Dan to help me once, to deduce the location of that old lecher."

"Haha, my dear granddaughter. Alright, take this token and go to twin polar sea strait, and find your uncle Song Jia Dan." Saying so, Song Qi Yuan tossed a token to her.

Song Yi Shi quickly caught it and showed a joyful expression, she turned around and left, not even saying a word of goodbye.

Twin polar sea strait was covered in a thick layer of fog all year round.

In the air, Song Yi Shi stopped, seeing the fog in front of her, she felt a little troubled, she turned to the middle aged Gu Immortal beside her: "Uncle Xia Qi, how do we get in?"

Song Xia Qi's body was filled with a vigorous aura, he smiled lightly and said: "Didn't your grandfather give you a token? Little Yi Shi, you just need to take out the token and your uncle Jia Dan will sense it."

Song Yi Shi held the token high up in the air.

A moment later, the fog in front of her started to disperse, a small tunnel appeared, it directly connected to the inside of twin polar sea strait.

Song Yi Shi and Song Xia Qi entered the tunnel and stepped into twin polar sea strait, meeting Song Jia Dan.

Song Jia Dan was a wisdom path Gu Immortal that Song clan had specially nurtured.

He stayed on the cliff of twin polar sea strait normally, his upper body was already old and weak, his lower body had been petrified, his legs seemed to have fused with twin polar sea strait.

"Uncle Jia Dan!" Song Yi Shi called out.

Since birth, she had only met the Gu Immortal Song Jia Dan a handful of times, but that did not affect her admiration towards Song Jia Dan.

Song Jia Dan had sacrificed his own freedom for the clan. Ever since he became a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he had sat here, using his special wisdom path inheritance to fuse with the world. Because of this, Song Jia Dan's deductions and schemes were very brilliant. Every time Song clan had important matters, they would ask him to help and deduce their upcoming fortunes.

Right now in the world of Eastern Sea's Gu Immortals, he was publicly recognized as one of the three most capable wisdom path Gu Immortals.

The saying goes: Jia Dan sits in twin polar, Hua An hides in Nan Gong, there is also Dragon Head Tortoise, living inside adversity sea.

Song Jia Dan had already opened his eyes, he looked at Song Yi Shi and Song Xia Qi expressionlessly.

He wanted to smile, but his face was hard like a statue, his muscles were stiff and could show no expression, even if he opened his mouth, he could only speak very slowly and with much difficulty: "Little Shi, cousin Xia Qi, it has been a long time."

"Uncle Jia Dan, I am here to ask you to deduce the location of an enemy. This is his appearance, and the aura that I collected." Song Yi Shi passed two Gu worms to him.

"Let me look at the command token first." Song Jia Dan spoke slowly. Even though he was familiar with Song Yi Shi and Song Xia Qi, he was to be impartial, to make a deduction, he needed to see Song Qi Yuan's command token first.

After checking that the token was authentic, Song Jia Dan opened his mouth, a suction force made both of the Gu worms from Song Yi Shi go into his mouth.

He shut his eyes and started deducing.

A long while later, he opened his eyes, perplexion shined in his eyes: "I could not deduce anything."

"What?" At once, not only Song Xia Qi who was in anticipation, but even Song Yi Shi, who was very confident, showed immense shock.

"Uncle, you are one of the three best wisdom path Gu Immortals in Eastern Sea, how can you fail the deduction?" Song Yi Shi asked.

"Little Shi, don't be anxious." Song Xia Qi's expression turned heavy: "Elder cousin Jia Dan, the other party is only a rank six lone cultivator that came from Northern Plains, with your wisdom path attainment, you could not deduce anything?"

Song Jia Dan was still expressionless, he spoke slowly: "Is it strange that I could not deduce anything? I am merely rank seven, even though I have some fame, that is all flattery by nosy people. In the end, I am but a tiny worm in this vast world, all I can do is to predict some premonitions of impending storms. Compared to the world, I am insignificant like an ant, compared to the grand heroes in this world, I merely control a tiny domain."

Song Xia Qi smiled bitterly: "Cousin, you are still so humble."

Song Jia Dan said: "I am not humble, but as I continue to fuse with this world unceasingly, every time I advance in wisdom path, I can see the glorious view ahead more clearly. The more I learn about the secrets of this world, the more I am aware of my own insignificance. Thus, I am not being humble, I am just being truthful, I am aware of my own status."

Song Yi Shi was discontent: "Even if uncle Jia Dan cannot deduce it, you are still the smartest person, you can surely give a good suggestion."

Song Jia Dan was silent for a while, he said: "There are two possible reasons why I could not deduce it. The first is that the other party is not in Eastern Sea. The second, they have wisdom path techniques that can conceal them from my deductions. Or maybe they could find other wisdom path Gu Immortals to help them evade my deductions."

Song Yi Shi and Song Xia Qi looked at each other.

These two reasons were very far-fetched.

The first reason, if this old lecher Xing Xiang Zi was not in Eastern Sea, where could he be? Right now, the earth tide was over, how could he return to Northern Plains?

The second reason, how could Xing Xiang Zi resist Song Jia Dan's wisdom path attainment? If he had help, this person would need to be at least at Song Jia Dan's level? Was it Nan Gong clan's Gu Immortal Hua An, or Dragon Head Tortoise Immortal in adversity sea who helped him?

"Uncle Jia Dan, deduce it again. Maybe you just happened to fail!" Song Yi Shi requested as she pouted.

Song Jia Dan directly rejected this: "No, the clan has an important mission, we have to obtain Old Eccentric Tian Nan's inheritance. I need to preserve my strength, and prepare my methods, to deduce for this in a few days time."

"Uncle Jia Dan, you did not originally put in all your effort!" Song Yi Shi heard this and said unhappily.

"Alright, you can leave now." Song Jia Dan shut his eyes slowly.

Song Yi Shi was ignored, she gritted her teeth and stomped her feet, helplessly turning around and leaving.

To fight for Ascending Heaven Plain's control, to fight for Old Eccentric Tian Nan's inheritance, it was a project that the clan had been planning for a hundred years. Pursuing Xing Xiang Zi was just her own personal business.

Even though Song Yi Shi was pampered and spoiled, she could see the big picture and cared for the clan's progress, she was not an ignorant fool.

Central Continent, Hu Immortal blessed land, an underground cave.

Fang Yuan was bathed in the light of wisdom, he shut his eyes as the star thoughts in his mind shined, he quietly deduced some important things.

Last time, he used the light of wisdom to deduce the immortal killer moves, star fire escape and projected star thought.

Thus, Fang Yuan currently controlled six star path immortal killer moves in total.

Star cloud grindstone, star snake rope, six illusion star bodies, position star swap, star fire escape and projected star thought.

Among them, star fire escape was a movement killer move, it was used extensively in escaping the chase from Song Yi Shi. As for projected star thought, it was the investigative immortal killer move that Fang Yuan used to expose the immortal zombie Sha Nan Jiang's traces.

These two killer moves were originally incomplete. They were concepts that predecessors of Star Lord Wan Xiang had left behind in the star path inheritance, they had encountered difficulties during the deductions and could not progress to complete the killer moves.

Fang Yuan's star path attainment was only ordinary, normally under such a situation, these incomplete moves would only be useful as reference to him.

But since he had the rank nine wisdom Immortal Gu, he could use the light of wisdom and gain unlimited inspiration, he got over the difficulty of a low star path attainment level, he forcefully completed the killer moves.

"It is a pity, in the short time I had, completing star fire escape and projected star thought was my limit. After all, I have only three star path Immortal Gu now. Of course, most importantly, my star path attainment level is too low. Eh?"

At this time, a moving perspective cup Gu appeared in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

The information in the Gu came from Lang Ya land spirit.

"Lang Ya land spirit has finally completed the relocation of Lang Ya blessed land, he can lend that set of Immortal Gu to me now!"

Fang Yuan was overjoyed.

This time, he purposely returned to Central Continent from Eastern Sea, it was to wait for Lang Ya land spirit's news and to relocate Star Form blessed land.

In Fang Yuan's plans, Star Form blessed land was very important.

Once the truth that he was the culprit of the incident in Northern Plains becomes exposed, he would have to escape for his life.

By then, Hu Immortal blessed land would face disaster. If he was still an immortal zombie and could not produce immortal essence, then Star Form blessed land would be his sole secret base.

However, Hei Lou Lan knew about Star Form blessed land's location. If Hei Lou Lan knew, Fairy Li Shan also knew.

Fang Yuan was a vigilant person, now that he was Star Form blessed land's owner, he naturally had to relocate Star Form blessed land to a place that only he knew.

Chapter 900: Borrowing Gu from Lang Ya Land Spirit

Fang Yuan did not hesitate, he immediately used Fixed Immortal Travel to go to Lang Ya blessed land.

Lang Ya blessed land had already undergone a huge change.

In the vast sea, three continents were facing each other. In the air, there was a fourth continent made from cloud soil.

Because there was an intense battle that destroyed much of the blessed land, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had helped and restored most of it to its original state.

Even though Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not participate in the battle, he helped repair the blessed land after the battle, he earned quite a sum as well.

Of course, because some Immortal Gu that made up Refinement Cauldron were gone, the space in the blessed land shrank. Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not have the power to restore the missing space and everything that was in them.

The twelve cloud buildings had been rebuilt by Lang Ya land spirit, split up across the cloud soil continent. In addition, there were many hairy man Gu Masters surrounding the twelve cloud buildings, reconstructing even more buildings.

"I intend to create twelve cloud cities centered upon the twelve cloud buildings. This cloud soil continent in the sky will become the new living area for elite hairy men." After Lang Ya land spirit saw Fang Yuan, he explained this.

Fang Yuan nodded in agreement.

Because Lang Ya blessed land lost a number of Immortal Gu, the space inside shrunk by a lot. And because there were many hairy men living in the blessed land, they were reaching the limit of the three continents. Thus, in this situation, a new area to allow the hairy men to live and propagate was needed.

But Lang Ya land spirit's next words shocked Fang Yuan.

"Other than this, I have also established Lang Ya Sect! This sect system will use Central Continent as a reference, I will be the sect's first supreme elder, and the hairy man Gu Immortals will be the other supreme elders. My previous self was too foolish, he used these precious Gu Immortals for Gu refinement. Hmph! To fulfill the dominance of hairy men, bloodshed is necessary."

"Next, I will start training these hairy man Gu Immortals, nurturing their battle talents. Once they have sufficient strength to protect themselves, I will send them out of the blessed land, and let them complete all kinds of sect missions."

"Also, under my influence, the three continents in the sea will erupt in war! From among them, three kings will be chosen, and they will create three kingdoms on their respective continents. The kingdoms will fight against each other, and each year, my Lang Ya Sect will pick the most elite hairy men from these three kingdoms, and send the elite hairy men to the continent in the clouds, they will become the foundation of Lang Ya Sect. Furthermore, I will choose a rank five peak stage hairy man Gu Master as the sect leader of Lang Ya Sect!"

The new Lang Ya land spirit was completely different from the previous one, maybe he was affected by the attack of Qin Bai Sheng, but Lang Ya land spirit had decided to undertake a complete reform of Lang Ya blessed land, he used hard-handed methods and had the disposition of a conquering grand emperor.

Different emperors employ different styles of rulership, because of Lang Ya land spirit's change, the hairy men that were living in the lower tiers were undergoing turmoil and difficulties from war, their peaceful and serene lifestyles were not to return.

"Lang Ya land spirit used such a cruel method to choose the most outstanding hairy men. But this method is simply too wasteful."

Fang Yuan felt some pity, there were bound to be large numbers of sacrifices during war.

He felt quite a loss inwardly, he might as well use these hairy men for Gu refinement.

But Fang Yuan would not say these words openly, he could only mutter in his mind.

From Lang Ya land spirit's perspective, hairy men were the most outstanding creatures of all, humans and all other variant humans were underneath them.

Fang Yuan raised hairy men and used them as slaves for Gu refinement. If Lang Ya land spirit knew this, he would not accept it, he might even fall out with Fang Yuan.

Thus, even though Fang Yuan lacked knowledge and experience of raising hairy men, in the previous discussions regarding the compensation of defending Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan did not attempt to request this even though he knew that Lang Ya land spirit had extremely precious knowledge of how to nurture hairy men.

"But at this rate, Lang Ya blessed land would undergo a huge reform, the hairy men would start working hard and their battle strengths will rise drastically. Maybe this happened in my previous life, after such a transformation in Lang Ya blessed land, it managed to endure seven waves of attacks."

"But this Lang Ya blessed land has hidden undercurrents deep beneath the surface, even though two hairy man Gu Immortal traitors were exposed, we can't be sure that there will not be a third or fourth traitor among the rest. The methods of Qin Bai Sheng that can develop traitors to this extent in here are really unimaginable."

Fang Yuan thought about this as he told Lang Ya land spirit his intentions.

Lang Ya land spirit was slightly shocked, he asked again: "Oh? You want to borrow my set of Immortal Gu now and relocate your blessed land? I remember I told you this set of Immortal Gu will not be cheap. Even on the basis that you fought against strong enemies for us, I told you that you will still need to pay two thousand immortal essence stones?"

Fang Yuan took out two thousand immortal essence stones, handing them to the land spirit: "Look, I've prepared them already."

Lang Ya land spirit was greatly shocked, he received the immortal essence stones as he inspected Fang Yuan, his gaze slightly changing.

He knew Fang Yuan's foundation and was very surprised: "This lad only ascended recently, he already has so many immortal essence stones?"

"Back then when he made transactions with my previous self, he had to earn immortal essence stones by deducing Immortal Gu recipes, it showed how poor he was. It seems that these immortal essence stones were mostly borrowed. That is bad if he owes people a huge sum, or even worse, favors."

Lang Ya land spirit shook his head, he did not approve of Fang Yuan's actions.

But he understood why.

He knew that Fang Yuan's crime was simply too absurd. Once it was exposed, he would be in a doomed situation, he would be chased to the ends of the world.

Thus, Fang Yuan had to relocate the blessed land.

But this point was also the main reason why Lang Ya land spirit wanted to gradually take in Fang Yuan and turn him into a lackey.

It was because Fang Yuan was under such a situation, he was faced with enemies everywhere, when he is left without a choice, he would have to join the hairy men, and become a traitor of the humans.

But what Lang Ya land spirit did not know was — he was completely wrong!

These two thousand immortal essence stones were actually Fang Yuan's own savings.

Fang Yuan was rich now, very rich!

He earned one hundred and eighty immortal essence stones from his first transaction of guts Gu with Spirit Affinity House.

After the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, Fang Yuan displayed formidable Gu refinement talent, He Feng Yang personally invited him to go to Immortal Crane Sect and take a look, this was a change in attitude of Immortal Crane Sect towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan owned Hu Immortal blessed land now, he had room to maneuver between Immortal Crane Sect and Spirit Affinity House.

As his situation became much easier, and as he considered the dangers of being chased down, Fang Yuan decided to increase the production of guts Gu.

Once he made this decision, the profits that he earned from guts Gu each month reached a total of three hundred immortal essence stones!

And don't forget, after Fang Yuan took over Star Form blessed land, he even obtained Star Lord Wan Xiang's four sources of revenue. He even went ahead and established the trade of regretful spiders with Western Desert's Xiao clan.

With a total of six sources of revenue, he earned over a thousand immortal essence stones each month!

There were still the dragonfish and eerie fire dragon pythons that had not entered the market yet. If he included these two, Fang Yuan's initial estimation was that his monthly profit would reach a total of one thousand and five hundred!

Two months had already passed since Fang Yuan became the owner of Star Form blessed land.

He naturally had more than two thousand immortal essence stones in his current possession.

Thinking of back then, when he had just become an immortal, he had to calculate every single stone, looking at prices carefully, he even had to think of how to efficiently use half an immortal essence stone. But now he had over a thousand immortal essence stones of profit a month, he had truly progressed greatly and taken a huge step forward.

He took a really huge step, but Lang Ya land spirit did not know about it, even though he was already thinking highly of Fang Yuan, he was still very wrong.

Even though Fang Yuan was an immortal zombie with the lowest cultivation level, his immortal essence stone profits approached the level of rank seven Gu Immortals.

After paying two thousand immortal essence stones, Fang Yuan and Lang Ya land spirit used an information path immortal killer move to form an agreement.

Eventually, Fang Yuan gave the land spirit two Immortal Gu as collateral before he successfully borrowed a set of Immortal Gu used to relocate blessed lands, there were sixteen of them.

Fang Yuan moved without resting, he used Fixed Immortal Travel and returned to Star Form blessed land.

Star Form blessed land had three desolate beast spinefin star dragonfish, Fang Yuan had already seen them before, he did not hesitate, he chose the strongest one.

He first moved around the spinefin star dragonfish, using methods to inspect the dragonfish's size, bone structure, flesh, blood, and other aspects.

After confirming that the spinefin star dragonfish was in a good state, Fang Yuan sat in the air as he shut his eyes while facing the desolate beast.

The spinefin star dragonfish had been tamed since long ago, it obediently floated in the air without moving. Its fish-like eyes that were large as horse carriages shined with some starlight, showing Fang Yuan's reflection from within.

Fang Yuan's was calm, but he gradually started getting excited in his mind.

Countless star thoughts moved like fireflies filling the endless sky, dancing around in the small area of his mind.

These star thoughts split into two portions.

One portion occupied the right part of his mind, forming a three dimensional image of the spinefin star dragonfish.

The other portion was at the left side, forming the image of Star Form blessed land.

After completing this step, Fang Yuan breathed in deeply as he activated his immortal essence, injecting them into the wisdom path Immortal Gu that he had borrowed, and according to the method that the land spirit gave him, he started deducing.

Two lumps of star thoughts flew rapidly, they collided intensely and created a star cloud storm in his mind.

In the storm, countless star thoughts flashed continuously, some joined together while others disintegrated.

One day, two days, three days... in Star Form blessed land, after a total of seven days and six nights, Fang Yuan, who was extremely exhausted, opened his eyes slowly.

One hundred and sixty thousand star thoughts had been used up in his mind. He even spent sixty-six beads of immortal essence to activate the wisdom path Immortal Gu.

After paying such a huge price, Fang Yuan obtained two sets of Gu formation charts.

Among these two Gu formation charts, one was big and one was small.

The bigger Gu formation chart reflected Star Form blessed land, it had eight formation cores. The smaller Gu formation chart reflected the spinefin star dragonfish, there were four formation cores. Each of the formation cores needed a specific Immortal Gu, in total, both Gu formation charts needed twelve Immortal Gu.

Chapter 901: Transplanting Immortal Aperture, Relocating Blessed Land

Fang Yuan started to set up the formation.

In accordance with locations indicated on the Gu formation chart, he found the eight formation cores in Star Form blessed land through Star Form land spirit's guidance, he placed the corresponding Immortal Gu there one by one.

Star Form blessed land had few space path dao marks, the land spirit could not teleport. The eight formation cores were very varied in distance, they were either close by or far away, Fang Yuan spent a lot of time due to this, by the time he finished, he had already spent half a day.

After this step, Fang Yuan, who was vigilant and cautious, inspected these eight formation cores carefully again.

After confirming that there were no issues, Fang Yuan returned to his original spot and placed the chosen spinefin star dragonfish into his own immortal aperture.

Under his orders, Star Form land spirit opened the blessed land's entrance.

Fang Yuan walked out into Earth Abyss.

The blessed land doors were shining with light, but it could only radiate over a small range of land. The inside of Earth Abyss was very dark and silent.

This was a deep part of Earth Abyss, even Ancient Soul Sect, one of the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, had not explored this deeply yet.

But even though there were no humans here, there were countless hidden desolate beasts, and even ancient desolate beasts, it was very dangerous.

There was no time to waste, Fang Yuan let out the spinefin star dragonfish.

The spinefin star dragonfish had the size of an ordinary whale, but it looked like a carp, its body was covered in blue fish scales. There were bones protruding out of its back, along the spine, extending outwards.

Fang Yuan placed the four Immortal Gu on the body of the spinefin star dragonfish in accordance with the smaller Gu formation chart.

One was in its mouth, one was in a particular bone on its back, one was in the left eye, and the last one was in its stomach.

Even though the spinefin star dragonfish was big, it could not compare to Star Form blessed land.

Fang Yuan only took a short while before his arrangements were completed.

He inspected it carefully again, before Fang Yuan confirmed it: The twelve Immortal Gu had been put in place properly.

He started to scatter countless mortal Gu around the area, there were even one or two Immortal Gu that he tossed out, creating a powerful Gu formation.

Next, he was finally at the most crucial moment of relocating the blessed land.

Fang Yuan followed the method closely, he activated the remaining four Immortal Gu.

Star Form blessed land's doors slowly closed, vanishing into thin air.

Fang Yuan's entire body started to glow in a bright yellow light.

Even though the yellow light was bright, it was not painful to look at, it was a very warm color.

After seventeen breaths of time, the light started to fade, they gathered into Fang Yuan's two eyes.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, he willed.

At the next moment, a faint yellow light beam shot out of his right eye, hitting the whale-sized spinefin star dragonfish.

The spinefin star dragonfish's body shook, the small Gu formation that was on its body activated, it shined with a red light.

Under this red light, the spinefin star dragonfish seemed to be wearing red armor.

The entire spinefin star dragonfish was tough like a rock, and did not move, as if it was a statue.

Fang Yuan breathed roughly for some time, next, a yellow light beam shot out of his left eye, directly piercing Star Form blessed land's hidden location.

Under the influence of the light pillar, Star Form blessed land was drawn out, turning into a blue light lump.

The blue light lump was only the size of a large bean, a sharp contrast to the enormous, whale-like spinefin star dragonfish.

The moment that Star Form blessed land was absorbed by this, the green grape immortal essence in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture started to be consumed at a terrifying speed!

Fang Yuan's left eye turned with difficulty, moving the yellow light pillar with it. The yellow light pillar began to slowly move while pulling the blue light lump.

And that spinefin star dragonfish that was now like a stone statue, also moved along with Fang Yuan's right eye, slowly approaching the blessed land.

Rumble, the ground tremored and earth shook.

Roar roar roar, countless ferocious beasts in the darkness roared in panic and fury.

A blessed land's relocation naturally caused intense turbulence in heaven and earth qi. A powerful earthquake was already forming in the depths of the abyss.

Fang Yuan did not care about these trifling details, and poured all his concentration into the spinefin star dragonfish and Star Form blessed land.

An enormous boulder crashed down on his head, but was blocked by his pre-arranged methods.

Fang Yuan was confident he could hold on for some time even if desolate beasts attacked!

He had created an environment that would not allow any disturbance to him for a while.

As if he was moving two large mountains, the two pupils in Fang Yuan's eyes moved slowly. At this moment, both his body and soul were exerting all their strength.

Not much time had passed from when the two lights touched each other.

However, to Fang Yuan, it was like a year had gone by!

The moment when Star Form blessed land and the spinefin star dragonfish touched, Fang Yuan suddenly relaxed, as if he had unloaded an extremely heavy burden.

Fang Yuan's carefully arranged Immortal Gu formations played a crucial role at this moment.

Star Form blessed land was like a wanderer returning home, or a swallow returning to its nest, settling down in the spinefin star dragonfish's body, turning into an immortal aperture inside it!

This was the method Lang Ya land spirit used to relocate blessed lands.

There must be a desolate beast or ancient desolate beast in which the blessed land would be transplanted as an aperture within it.

Afterwards, the desolate beast or ancient desolate beast could bring the immortal aperture wherever they were moved.

However, time was very limited in this transferral process. The desolate beast or ancient desolate beast that held the immortal aperture could not take in any other immortal aperture, and also could not use any Immortal Gu, otherwise it would influence the workings of the Immortal Gu formation on their body.

The specific circumstances were: Fang Yuan could not store this spinefin star dragonfish into his immortal aperture to quickly move it.

At the same time, he also could not use any other Immortal Gu or immortal killer moves to help it.

He could only rely on the spinefin star dragonfish's own physical strength to float and move to another place.

After all, although an immortal aperture was residing inside the spinefin star dragonfish, it was only barely done with the help of the larger and smaller Immortal Gu formations. Even a slight outside influence could cause the Gu formation to collapse, and not only would the relocation of the blessed land fail instantly, the Immortal Gu used could also be destroyed.

But even such a large disadvantage could not conceal the enormous value of this method.

The person who created this relocation method was not Long Hair Ancestor, but was equally famous as Long Hair Ancestor in history.

His name was Old Immortal Kong Jue.

In the long history of Gu Immortals, he was one of the three refinement path supreme grandmasters, a legend of the Remote Antiquity Era.

His research and understanding of apertures and immortal apertures surpassed his time. It was his efforts that allowed those of the ten extreme physiques to advance and become Gu Immortals, forming super grade blessed lands.

Old Immortal Kong Jue named the immortal killer move of relocating blessed lands as the immortal aperture transplantation method.

Up to this point, this was the immortal killer move with the highest number of core Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan had seen.

Nevertheless, this immortal killer move with up to sixteen core Immortal Gu was only an incomplete immortal killer move. Old Immortal Kong Jue's initial thoughts had been to perfectly transplant a Gu Immortal's immortal aperture into a desolate beast or ancient desolate beast's body, unlike the current situation, where they could only rely on the two Gu formations and consume a lot of immortal essence to join the two together with difficulty, and just for a while on top of that.

After Long Hair Ancestor obtained this inheritance of Old Immortal Kong Jue, he also made many attempts to complete it with Old Immortal Kong Jue's research results, but they all ended up in failure.

Under the inspection of the inkman wisdom path Gu Immortal Yi Yan, Long Hair Ancestor discovered this incomplete immortal killer move already had shocking value!

Gu Immortals could use it to relocate the immortal apertures of dead Gu Immortals.

Time passed by, bringing great changes to the world.

Now, countless years later, Fang Yuan was benefiting from this.

"Move, go there." Fang Yuan commanded the spinefin star dragonfish to move.

Because of the disadvantages of the immortal aperture transplantation method, the spinefin star dragonfish's speed was less than half the original speed, and the pressure on the body was huge, as if it was moving with a mountain on its back.

This made the distance the blessed land could be relocated every time limited.

Lang Ya land spirit had moved Lang Ya blessed land, but it should not be far away from the previous location.

This was also one of the reasons Fang Yuan did not move Hu Immortal blessed land.

"Fortunately, Earth Abyss is an extremely good hidden area, it will be a long while in the future before this layer gets exposed and developed. I can use Star Form blessed land as a reliable camp to replenish and recuperate."

"Moreover, I know the disadvantages of the immortal aperture transplantation method, but others don't know. When Hei Lou Lan does not see Star Form blessed land, she might think the blessed land was destroyed. After all, the concept of relocating blessed lands has already surpassed the common knowledge of Gu Immortals!"

Like this, Fang Yuan led the spinefin star dragonfish to move in Earth Abyss.

The path he moved on was naturally according to a elaborately drawn map, which had already gone through large numbers of tests and probing.

He continued to move deep into Earth Abyss, while avoiding many desolate beasts. In the gaps between the territories of desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts, Fang Yuan slowly moved with the spinefin star dragonfish.

Fang Yuan's destination was three layers down from the original location of Star Form blessed land.

However, after going down two layers, Fang Yuan's luck was used up as he ran into a desolate beast one-eyed giant ape.

The one-eyed ape was extremely vigorous and would often wander around in Earth Abyss. When it discovered the spinefin star dragonfish, it excitedly started a chase.

Fang Yuan began a fierce fight with this one-eyed giant ape, strenuously maintaining the safety of the spinefin star dragonfish.

But in the end, Fang Yuan suffered from having no battlefield killer move, and was unable to effectively restrict the one-eyed giant ape's movement, eventually, partway to their location, the one-eyed giant ape heavily injured the spinefin star dragonfish.

The spinefin star dragonfish was extremely weak while carrying the immortal aperture, it was already using all its strength to move and thus did not have any spare energy to strike back.

Fang Yuan finally drove away this damned one-eyed giant ape, but the spinefin star dragonfish had already been injured heavily and could no longer move.

"Fortunately, the Immortal Gu are unharmed, if anything happened to them, wouldn't I have to compensate Lang Ya until I'm bankrupt?!" After Fang Yuan inspected the condition, his heavy mood eased up.

This was good fortune within misfortune.

Since the situation had already turned this way, Fang Yuan could only choose the second-best option, and place Star Form blessed land nearby.

The moment the immortal aperture was removed, the spinefin star dragonfish completely crumbled, turning into a pool of meat and blood, even its beast soul had dispersed.

This was the necessary sacrifice of the immortal aperture transplantation method, and Fang Yuan had already known this.

Even if the spinefin star dragonfish was not injured, when it reached the destination, it would still die from exhaustion.

Star Form blessed land was successfully relocated, hidden in a completely new area.

Everything was worth it!

Chapter 902: Heavily Developing Star Form Blessed Land

Fang Yuan entered Star Form blessed land.

Star Form blessed land's heaven and earth qi were greatly affected by the relocation, intense earthquakes occurred in Star Form blessed land.

Only until Star Form blessed land was placed down and started to absorb the endless amount of earth qi did it stabilize, as the earthquakes ceased.

At this moment, Fang Yuan looked over it, the vast landscape was filled with cracks and crevices, dark smoke rose up from burning flames.

Fang Yuan's heart sank slightly, he sighed deeply.

This was something he had no other way to deal with.

Because to transplant the immortal aperture, he could not interrupt the activation of the two Immortal Gu formations. Thus, even if Fang Yuan had methods involving Immortal Gu, he could not use defensive or protection methods on Star Form blessed land.

Lang Ya land spirit had once told Fang Yuan about this, Lang Ya blessed land's losses were far greater than Fang Yuan's Star Form blessed land.

Thus, ordinarily, the blessed land would not be relocated.

"Where is the land spirit?"

Fang Yuan called out.

Star Form land spirit's eyes were red, he did not understand why his master wanted to move.

Under Star Form land spirit's guidance, Fang Yuan started inspecting Star Form blessed land.

He first had to inspect Star Form blessed land's four sources of revenue, the arrow bamboo forest, broken star lake, meteorite pit, and the star fragment grass fields.

Broken star lake's water was flowing along a huge crack, there were piles of seaweed at the bottom of the lake, there was still some water left inside, it had not dried up completely yet.

Landscape as Before!

Fang Yuan took out the Immortal Gu and poured his immortal essence into it.

Landscape as before Immortal Gu gave off a white light, sweeping over the broken star lake.

Immediately, the ground below broken star lake mended, the lake water filled up and returned to its original state. But the loss of seaweed was still going to affect the production of star river Gu for a period of time in the future.

There was nothing inside the water, only seaweed and aquatic plants were floating around. The original palace below the lake was completely destroyed. Landscape as Before could not restore things like man made buildings.

But the fish groups, insect groups, and Gu groups that were inside this lake did not die from the earthquakes. Fang Yuan had moved them into Hu Immortal blessed land long ago.

Fang Yuan's immortal aperture was a dead land, living beings could not live inside for long.

Afterwards, Fang Yuan went to arrow bamboo forest, meteorite pit, and star fragment grass fields to inspect them.

Out of his expectations, arrow bamboo forest was unharmed. Beside the arrow bamboo forest, there were two long cracks, they narrowly grazed the edge of the forest, it was truly a close call.

The arrow bamboo forest was the biggest plantation in Star Form blessed land, Fang Yuan had already collected most of the resources there and kept them in Hu Immortal blessed land.

To think that arrow bamboo forest dodged this crisis, it was truly a stroke of good luck.

But the meteorite pit and the star fragment grass fields were not so lucky. The meteorite pit suffered huge damage, it was nearly unrecognizable. As for the star fragment grass fields, because of the fire, some had been burned into ashes, at first glance, it was a barren land.

Under the effect of Landscape as Before, the meteorite pit was restored to normal, and even the terrain of the star fragment grass field had been restored.

"Landscape as before Immortal Gu is truly useful, with it, my losses shrunk by at least eighty percent! And since I already moved out most of my resources beforehand, Star Form blessed land only suffered a minor loss in the end, even though there was huge destruction that occurred."

Fang Yuan thought as he looked around, he used Landscape as Before to restore the landscape of Star Form blessed land, but that expended a lot of green grape immortal essence.

He did not repair everything, he left some cracks in the ground as they had been.

He had a stroke of inspiration: "Maybe I can use this chance and turn the cracks in the ground into river channels, creating a network that can spread throughout the entirety of Star Form blessed land. But Star Form blessed land has a unique terrain, as for how I can make this a reality, I will need to use the light of wisdom and think over it."

Next, Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel and went to Lang Ya land spirit, returning the Immortal Gu back to Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit returned the Immortal Gu that had been held as collateral to Fang Yuan as he said: "If you need to relocate anything else, you can find me again."

After all, he had earned a huge sum just now, in a short time, he earned more than two thousand immortal essence stones.

Lang Ya land spirit continued: "If you join my Lang Ya sect, and become a supreme elder, in the future when you relocate your blessed land, I can give you a huge discount when borrowing Immortal Gu!"

"I will think about it." Fang Yuan replied half-heartedly.

He had only wanted to obtain benefits from Lang Ya land spirit, he did not want to be tied together with these hairy men.

Once he joined, he would be unable to go away, he would lose his freedom. He would not make such a stupid decision.

Next, Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel and entered Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture, returning Landscape as Before to him.

In the immortal aperture, Fang Yuan asked about Eastern Sea's information from Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng told him that Song Yi Shi and the others were searching for him all over the place, some people had approached Tai Bai Yun Sheng as a result.

"Looking at the situation, our relationship would be exposed in a short while." Fang Yuan muttered.

"I suggest that you contact Shark Demon and join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance. Relying on Zombie Alliance, you will be able to resolve this." Tai Bai Yun Sheng said.

Fang Yuan was not anxious, his plan was unaffected by external pressure, he shook his head: "It is still not time yet, there are still more than ten days from the next attack on Yu Lu blessed land, let's wait and see."

Hu Immortal blessed land, tens of days later.

Underground cave.

Bathed in the light of wisdom, Fang Yuan opened his eyes, letting out a breath of turbid air.

"I still failed after all." He muttered, standing up slowly.

He was sitting down on a small mushroom stump, he used it as a stool.

But such short stumps were very rare now.

Right now, the underground cave was a huge zhi forest, these lingzhi were very different from before, not only were they tall and thick, they were red in color. This was because of Hu Immortal blessed land's seventh earthly calamity, the blood poison kerria flowers, because of that opportunity, the ordinary zhi forest became a blood zhi forest.

Hu Immortal blessed land's soil was originally not suited for the growth of zhi forests, but now it has become a blood zhi forest, it could grow very well.

But this zhi forest would need one or two hundred years to expand and growing into a true forest, by creating more space and pushing aside the soil and rocks.

Fang Yuan did not have much expectations towards this blood zhi forest, he was not going to invest into it.

These last days, Fang Yuan had neither slept nor rested, he was putting in all his effort into developing Star Form blessed land.

Once his identity was exposed, everyone would know that he was the culprit behind the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Hu Immortal blessed land would have to be given up, Star Form blessed land would become his only base by then.

By that point, if Fang Yuan was still an immortal zombie and had not revived, Star Form blessed land would have an even more important role to Fang Yuan, having immense value and use.

Thus, Fang Yuan's focus had already shifted from Hu Immortal blessed land to Star Form blessed land.

As for the plan of developing Star Form blessed land, Fang Yuan had already thought about it dozens of days ago using the light of wisdom.

According to his earlier inspiration, he would build a huge river system in Star Form blessed land, the actual plan after deducing it properly was grander. The entire water river system would not only be on the ground, he would even encompass the sky into it, he was going to create a huge three dimensional river system.

This made use of Star Form blessed land's unique terrain.

Star Form blessed land had a depression at the center, while having high altitude around the sides, it resembled the shape of a bowl.

If he only built a river system on the ground, all of the water would flow towards the center. But if this was three dimensional, the water from the center would be drawn into the sky, it would flow towards the edges of the blessed land, and form a grand system for water to flow.

As for the way to create rivers in the sky, Fang Yuan had deduced the cheapest and easiest method, that was cloud soil.

Cloud soil was also used by Lang Ya land spirit to forcefully create a cloud continent in the sky of Lang Ya blessed land.

Fang Yuan intended to use the cloud soil to create many river channels, along these rivers, the fertile cloud soil would have countless star fragment grass growing on them.

The soil that the star fragment grass grew in was the cloud soil. Star Lord Wan Xiang had no choice but to plant them in black soil., as he did not have enough financial ability to bulk purchase cloud soil. But Star Form blessed land's environment was very suited for star fragment grass to grow. This caused the growth rates of star fragment grass to be higher in Star Form blessed land than Hu Immortal blessed land!

Fang Yuan's plan was beautiful, but reality was cruel.

Fang Yuan lacked a huge amount of funds, he had just accumulated two thousand immortal essence stones but he had passed them to Lang Ya land spirit. Thus, these days, he could only repair the four sources of revenue in Star Form blessed land.

Arrow bamboo forest had grown to its best condition, emitting a light fog under the use of large amounts of moon well water.

Meteorite pit and broken star lake had been fully restored.

The star fragment grass fields were more troublesome, but after Fang Yuan used the killer move spring star rain several times, they were growing quickly as well.

Ever since he obtained the star path inheritance and gained star shoot Immortal Gu, spring star rain had turned into an immortal killer move, its effect was dozens of times better than before!

As for the dragonfish, eerie fire dragon pythons, regretful spiders, and Dang Hun Mountain inside Hu Immortal blessed land, they were not moved over yet.

Firstly, he needed to develop the place for now, and finalize a proper water flow system before relocating the dragonfish.

Secondly, Star Form blessed land was facing its heavenly tribulation soon!

Why was Star Lord Wan Xiang so anxious to explore Starry Sky grotto-heaven?

It was because the heavenly tribulation was approaching.

He was a rank six Gu Immortal with one heavenly tribulation passed, he was facing the second one soon.

Because he battled with Song Zi Xing and was gravely injured, he lost confidence in surviving the tribulation, he had to expose the secret of Starry Sky grotto-heaven and drag Shi Lei in to explore Starry Sky grotto-heaven together.

Fang Yuan was still hesitating over if he should move all these resources away before the heavenly tribulation struck.

Leaving the underground cave, Fang Yuan returned to Dang Hun palace.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng, who was held captive all along, seemed to have resigned himself to fate, his eyes were hollow as he sat in the prison cell without moving.

Evidently, the truth of Immortal Crane Sect attempting to kill him, and his master Lord Sky Crane trying to possess him were very impactful news towards him.

According to his usual habits, Fang Yuan stood before him and said some words.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng did not move at all, his expression was numb, as if he did not hear a word.

Chapter 903: Joining Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance

Fang Yuan was not anxious, as long as Gu Yue Fang Zheng was eating food, it meant that he had the will to live. As for how to change his mindset, and alter his perspective, so that Fang Zheng would view Fang Yuan more favorably, it was a long process, there was no need to rush.

Afterwards, Fang Yuan came to another secret room and inspected Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul.

He had many souls of immortals now, there was Dong Fang Chang Fan, featherman Gu Immortal Zheng Ling, Snowy Mountain's Xue Song Zi, as well as the Eastern Sea lone cultivator Yao Ge Pi.

These last days, other than developing Star Form blessed land, he had been searching these souls. Currently, he had searched all of their souls already, he gained a lot of benefits.

But what truly made Fang Yuan 'crave for more' was Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul.

Once in a while, Fang Yuan would search his soul.

It was no exception this time.

After the soul search, Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul suddenly spoke: "My memories have been read by you countless times, but recently, when you conduct soul searches, you will always check the memories regarding the dismantling of battlefield killer moves in my soul. It seems that you have encountered an inheritance, or have faced a strong foe that requires you to unravel a battlefield killer move."

Towards Dong Fang Chang Fan's words, Fang Yuan was slightly taken aback, he replied frankly: "That's right. These last days, I have been studying your wisdom path inheritance, especially the details about resolving battlefield killer moves. Combined with my experiences and your memories, I will gain a lot of insight each time."

Soul searching was like reading a book, but one was reading the memories in the soul instead. But like reading a book, there was no way to memorize every single small detail accurately. One thorough soul search was like reading a book from start to finish, you would learn about the contents of the book only. With constant revision, one would learn in-depth about the information, and would obtain more knowledge from it.

Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul smiled: "Have you thought about it, I can actually help you. You re just a wisdom path newbie, no matter how much you revise and read through, the gains that you can have are limited. Meanwhile, my wisdom path attainment is much higher, as long as you give me a body, I will be able to make deductions for you and help you think of solutions. Isn't this a good idea? You can use information path methods to restrict me, I will be your most capable assistant."

"That is a good idea indeed." Fang Yuan nodded, he smiled faintly: "But I will not do that, forget about it. Even after being left with a soul, you are still not giving up, it seems that I have not given you a thorough lesson yet."

Fang Yuan's smile turned into a sinister sneer.

Dozens of Gu worms moved with his will, activating.

"Ah—!" Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul shook intensely, the cell was full of his anguished cries.

This punishment lasted for two hours, the pain in the soul was much more intense than in the body, Dong Fang Chang Fan was definitely taught a good lesson.

Fang Yuan obviously did not waste time there, he left long ago and went to two other secret rooms.

In one room, there was the rank seven featherman Gu Immortal Zheng Ling's soul, in the other room, there was Xue Song Zi's soul.

Even though these two Gu Immortals were not wisdom path Gu Immortals during their lives, they had memories regarding battlefield killer moves as well.

Even though they did not have wisdom path techniques, one was wind path and the other was snow path, they had their own unique methods to deal with battlefield killer moves. These memories were useful as references for Fang Yuan.

What was worth noting was, both their souls had been searched multiple times by Fang Yuan already.

From Xue Song Zi's soul, Fang Yuan learned that he had kept a fortune in Snowy Mountain blessed land. In his mountain peak, there were a number of snowmen, as well as plants related to snow pines there.

But Fang Yuan did not dare to take them.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's capabilities were unfathomable, Fang Yuan did not have much confidence in vaguely familiar face. He could not tell Fairy Li Shan about Xue Song Zi's death either.

Why?

Because Fairy Li Shan and Xue Song Zi were both members of Snowy Mountain, they were allies. After learning that Fang Yuan killed Xue Song Zi, even if Fairy Li Shan did not deal with Fang Yuan, she would have to inform Old Ancestor Xue Hu due to the alliance agreement.

Meanwhile, from Zheng Ling's soul, Fang Yuan also made some gains. He obtained a complete wind path inheritance from Zheng Ling, as well as the immortal killer move heavenly wish, along with precious information regarding the Immortal Gu House, Sacred Feather City, and the green heaven fragment world that the feathermen lived in.

This world was huge, there was a lot of resources inside, after Fang Yuan learned about it, he almost drooled.

Even though he knew about the scenery in the green heaven fragment world, such that Fang Yuan could use Fixed Immortal Travel to get there, but since that place was currently occupied by White Sea Shatuo and other Gu Immortals, it was like a lion's den. Fang Yuan would not take the risk easily.

After coming out from the secret room, Fang Yuan received Tai Bai Yun Sheng's transmission, he said: I have already met up with Shark Demon and the others.

Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel and teleported into Tai Bai Yun Sheng's immortal aperture before coming out of it.

At the next moment, Xing Xiang Zi appeared before Shark Demon and the others.

"Come, let me introduce you, this is the 'world famous' Xing Xiang Zi." Shark Demon laughed as he introduced enthusiastically.

Fang Yuan showed a bitter smile: "Lord Shark Demon, please don't make fun of me... sigh."

Saying so, tiny explosions occurred over Fang Yuan's body, it was as if firecrackers had been ignited on his body.

Fang Yuan's expression did not change, his body shook as hundreds of mortal Gu on his body fell out.

None of these mortal Gu survived, some were torn to shreds from this explosion.

"Hehehe, Xing Xiang Zi, you offended Song clan, this wisdom path mortal killer move cannot conceal your traces." Behind Shark Demon, an elderly Gu Immortal spoke.

Another skinny middle aged female Gu Immortal had an arrogant expression as she said with disdain: "That's right. Right now, among the three most capable wisdom path Gu Immortals in Eastern Sea, one of them is Song clan's Song Jia Dan. If you only have these methods, you will be exposed soon."

The last person was unfamiliar, he wore a golden robe and had a fat body, he looked like a rich person as he smiled and expressed goodwill towards Fang Yuan: "Jia Dan sits in twin polar, Hua An hides in Nan Gong, there is also Dragon Head Tortoise, living inside adversity sea. This refers to the three best wisdom path experts in Eastern Sea. Among them, Song Jia Dan ranks the highest, he sacrificed himself for his clan and fused himself into the world of Eastern Sea itself. As long as it is within Eastern Sea, he can deduce it accurately, this is very scary. Even if sir hides in someone's immortal aperture, you will only delay the timing, you will be found eventually."

Xing Xiang Zi nodded, he cupped his fists towards the three Gu Immortals: "I have been enlightened, thank you for the information."

The mortal Gu that died were his defensive wisdom path methods, to protect him against others' deductions.

But the moment Fang Yuan stepped into Eastern Sea, these defensive measures self-detonated, one could see how skilled Song Jia Dan was from this.

"Alright, brother Xing Xiang, let me introduce you." Shark Demon referred to the elderly Gu Immortal with his hand: "This is the demonic path Gu Immortal Ninth Ghost Finger, he cultivates soul path mainly and wisdom path on the side."

Shark Demon shifted to the arrogant middle aged female Gu Immortal: "This is the wisdom path Gu Immortal Xie Shu Fang, Master Xie."

Finally, he talked about the smiling fat Gu Immortal: "This is 'Big Bag' Lu Tan Xin, he mainly cultivates space path, but he has wisdom path attainment as well."

"It is my honor to meet all three of you." Fang Yuan cupped his fists again, having a humble attitude.

The middle aged female Gu Immortal Xie Shu Fang said coldly: "Meeting you is my misfortune. You offended Song clan, don't think you can escape. Right now, you are still scot-free, that is because Song clan did not go all out to find you, as they are busy fighting for Ascending Heaven Plain and have no time for you. I would advise you to surrender to Song clan, burdening me is one thing, but if you burden everyone and cause our Yu Lu blessed land invasion to be obstructed, you will be doing everyone a disservice."

Her words were very rude, many Gu Immortals heard it and had a change of expression. They were not worried about Xie Shu Fang's words, instead, they were worried that Xing Xiang Zi might feel insulted and create a conflict among themselves, creating internal strife.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression turned grim, while Bo Dan felt secretly joyful seeing that Fang Yuan was insulted.

Fang Yuan gave Xie Shu Fang a look, he thought that this Gu Immortal was probably in the righteous path, resulting in such a poor attitude towards himself.

Fang Yuan was joyful instead of angry, he continued from her words: "Master Xie is right, Song clan is a super force, they have such great influence, how could I defend against them? Thus, I have decided, Lord Shark Demon, I would like your help in joining Zombie Alliance, do you think I can avoid this trouble if I join?"

Xie Shu Fang was stunned, in her impression, Northern Plains Gu Immortals were very rash and arrogant, why was he being so mild?

Shark Demon was the first to react, he laughed loudly: "Of course you can. Brother Xing Xiang is a great talent, joining Zombie Alliance is a good idea. I can assure you, you will join Zombie Alliance smoothly. As long as you did not defile Song Yi Shi, we can back you up in this matter, and support you as we negotiate with Song clan."

"Then I will thank Lord Shark Demon first." Fang Yuan's face was full of helplessness and bitterness: "Don't worry Lord Shark Demon, I had accidentally entered the bottom of the volcano and saw that Fairy Yi Shi bathing, that was the cause of this crisis, sigh..."

Fang Yuan sighed deeply, he showed a look of feeling upset over a great misfortune that he did not intend for.

Bo Dan's expression became very dark.

Shark Demon laughed loudly: "I believe brother Xing Xiang Zi, come, let's go and break that fighting soul battlefield!"

After entering Yu Lu blessed land, everyone entered fighting soul battlefield again.

In a dark and gloomy area, dark clouds were looming as a thunderstorm approached, intense winds blew and a sandstorm was blowing. Soul beasts formed in the sandstorm, they grew in numbers and charged towards Fang Yuan and the others without stopping.

Fang Yuan, Bo Dan, and the others had started deducing the battlefield the moment they entered, they displayed all their methods and techniques.

Because of their earlier probing, they had found out, the key to this round was not traps or difficulty, it was the immense time needed to find all the Gu worms.

Seven minutes later, ancient soul beasts would start to form, it would be best if they dismantled this fighting soul battlefield before seven minutes!

Chapter 904: Star Thought Immortal Gu

This was a race against time!

If Shark Demon and the others could not hold off the soul beasts, then this invasion would end in failure again.

If the Gu Immortals could unravel the battlefield killer move before that, they would obtain victory.

Boom!

Fang Yuan waved his sleeves, a wisdom path mortal killer move was used, he destroyed seven to eight hidden Gu worms.

Earlier, when he targeted this fighting soul battlefield killer move, he could only destroy five to six hidden Gu worms at once. But now, he could destroy seven to eight. This showed that during this time, he had been hiding in Hu Immortal blessed land, practicing and learning to improve his wisdom path techniques.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied: "This kind of self-directed learning is too limited in terms of improvement. To increase my rate of deducing this battlefield killer move, I need Immortal Gu. It is a pity, even though I have a wisdom path Immortal Gu, Unravel Mystery, I cannot use it to deal with battlefield killer moves."

Unravel mystery Immortal Gu's effect was to help a Gu Immortal think and solve puzzles and mysteries. If the battlefield killer move was treated as a puzzle, then unravel mystery Immortal Gu would be very helpful in unraveling battlefield killer moves.

But simply unravel mystery Immortal Gu alone could not do anything to battlefield killer moves.

Fang Yuan used the light of wisdom and intended to use unravel mystery Immortal Gu as the core to deduce a simple immortal killer move that could unravel battlefield killer moves.

But unfortunately, even though Fang Yuan had been trying hard, up until the point when he had to come to Eastern Sea, he did not succeed.

Deducing an immortal killer move was very difficult.

Normally speaking, even if rank eight Gu Immortals wanted to deduce a brand new immortal killer move, they would need to spend years.

And every so often, their foundations would be insufficient, until their deaths, they would not be able to complete the immortal killer move.

Thus, Fang Yuan also had many incomplete immortal killer moves in the inheritances that he had obtained.

Even though Fang Yuan's star path attainment level was ordinary, relying on wisdom Gu, he could completely deduce some incomplete immortal killer moves, that resulted in star fire escape and projected star thought.

But now, he wanted to deduce a brand new wisdom path killer move without any foundation, this was out of Fang Yuan's abilities.

Even with the light of wisdom, his wisdom path attainment level was ordinary, this was his greatest drawback, it was holding him back.

"Actually, unravel mystery Immortal Gu and the unraveling of battlefield killer moves are very closely related. As long as my wisdom path attainment level reaches master level, I will be able to design a new wisdom path immortal killer move specially used to unravel battlefield killer moves."

Fang Yuan had estimated this inwardly long ago.

But now, even though he felt some regret, he was not anxious at all.

Since Shark Demon had promised him publicly to recommend him to Zombie Alliance, there was little chance that he would go back on his words.

Even if this attempt to unravel fighting soul battlefield fails, Fang Yuan would not be implicated.

Fang Yuan would had achieved his goal, that was to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

"In fact, from another perspective, to express my value to Shark Demon, so that it would benefit me, battlefield killer moves like fighting soul battlefield should take as long to deduce as possible."

If he completely deduced these battlefield killer moves, and Yu Lu blessed land was taken down, Fang Yuan would receive little benefits from it. He might as well drag the time out and wait for himself to get stronger, he might get a bigger share of the profits then.

Fang Yuan continued to move his hands, he was calm as he observed the situation secretly with his peripheral vision.

He did not need to observe Bo Dan, he was doing the same, trying his best to deduce, but he could only destroy one hidden Gu worm at once, he made barely any progress towards this situation.

Fang Yuan's focus was on the three new Gu Immortals. They had wisdom path techniques in one way or another, they were invited by Shark Demon for this purpose.

The one closest to Fang Yuan was the elderly Gu Immortal, demonic path Gu Immortal Ninth Ghost Finger.

Right now, he was lowering his head and looking at his hands. His ten fingers were intact, but when he moved his fingers rapidly, only nine fingers could be seen in the silhouettes.

His wisdom path inheritance was very unique, the missing finger represented the 'one in the Great Dao' that fled, it was the most profound heavenly secret.

Ninth Ghost Finger moved his fingers, they danced in the air like phantom spirits, he chanted in an unknown language that no one could understand.

At the same time, all sorts of mortal Gu flew out of his immortal aperture.

These mortal Gu flew into the air and self-detonated, revealing the hidden locations of Gu around the area.

Some mortal Gu only destroyed one spot, while some mortal Gu destroyed seven to eight hidden Gu worms. On average, his speed was slightly slower than Fang Yuan, but his wisdom path attainment level was definitely higher.

Fang Yuan looked at Big Bag Lu Tan Xin.

The title of Big Bag was very interesting, Fang Yuan guessed that since he was a space path Gu Immortal, did Big Bag mean that he had incredibly skilled storage techniques?

But normally speaking, Gu Immortals who mainly cultivate space path have a lot of space path dao marks, their immortal aperture would also be much larger than ordinary Gu Immortals' immortal apertures.

Right now, Lu Tan Xin's eyes had turned into vertical pupils, they were like cat's eyes as he investigated continuously.

His fat hands turned golden and oily, the aura that leaked from it displayed to others that this was a top tier mortal killer move.

Lu Tan Xin first observed for a few breaths of time before striking.

He stretched out a golden hand and aimed at one point, pointing a finger.

This movement seemed to have expended a lot of his energy, soon, he was breathing roughly and panting.

But after each time he pointed, at the corresponding direction, large numbers of hidden Gu worms would be destroyed, turning into golden dust that scattered.

Every strike of Lu Tan Xin's destroyed eight hidden Gu worms.

But his speed was very slow.

His attacks needed investigation beforehand, and he had to take several breaths of time to prepare it, it was very exhausting. The more tired he got, the slower his attacks became.

Thus, in conclusion, Lu Tan Xin was slower than Ninth Ghost Finger.

It could be seen that Shark Demon's evaluation was on point. When Shark Demon introduced Lu Tan Xin, he said that he had wisdom path attainment. When he introduced Ninth Ghost Finger, he said that he cultivated wisdom path on the side. Meanwhile, Shark Demon also placed much focus on Gu Immortal Xie Shu Fang, as a person mainly cultivating wisdom path, she was undoubtedly the most capable among the three.

Fang Yuan looked at Xie Shu Fang next.

As expected!

Xie Shu Fang stood in the air arrogantly, two streams of yellow and white vapor were blowing out of her nose continuously.

The yellow and white streams of vapor moved extremely quickly, they moved a round in the air, destroying up to a hundred hidden mortal Gu.

After destroying these Gu worms, the yellow and white streams became thinner, but when they returned to Xie Shu Fang's nostrils and were breathed out again, they regained their power and become unstoppable again.

Heaviness flashed across Fang Yuan's eyes secretly.

These two streams of yellow and white vapor had incredible power, this was surely an immortal killer move.

The power of an immortal killer move was much greater than the mortal killer moves that Fang Yuan had.

Fang Yuan sighed to himself internally: "My wisdom path attainment level is insufficient, I cannot use unravel mystery Immortal Gu properly, so be it, attainment levels can only normally be accumulated through long periods of time. But if I have star thought Immortal Gu, according to Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path inheritance, I will be able to use at least three wisdom path immortal killer moves to destroy battlefield killer moves. Among them, two are even stronger than this yellow and white vapor, by at least five to six times!"

The wisdom path inheritance from Dong Fang Chang Fan was more refined than the one Xie Shu Fang had.

Fang Yuan wanted to obtain star thought Immortal Gu the most now.

On one hand, he had a huge need for star thoughts. One Fang Yuan stone nest in Hu Immortal blessed land was refining star thought Gu all the time now. If he had star thought Immortal Gu, he would be able to use this stone nest for the production of airsac Gu, increasing its scale and earning more immortal essence stones for Fang Yuan.

On the other hand, star thought Immortal Gu was one of the two cores of the immortal killer move star fog concealment.

Star fog concealment had a similar effect to dark limit Immortal Gu.

It could defend against other people's deductions, making their deductions unclear and inaccurate regarding the truth.

Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path inheritance had many top tier mortal killer moves, Fang Yuan had used them, but facing people like Song Jia Dan, there was no way to defend against his deductions using them.

Once Fang Yuan stepped into Eastern Sea, the mortal Gu that he had used instantly self-detonated, the defensive mortal killer moves collapsed in no time.

Evidently, if Fang Yuan really became a fugitive in the future and was hunted down by everyone, countless people would be deducing his whereabouts. Then, he would need an immortal killer move to protect himself against others' deductions.

It could be seen that mortal killer moves, even if they were top tier, would have no use no matter how many there were.

There was a qualitative difference between immortal and mortal.

"But to refine star thought Immortal Gu, there are many difficulties. Firstly, the issue of funding, I have just spent two thousand immortal essence stones, the money I have on hand currently is limited. Even if I have enough, to purchase all of the immortal materials, I will need enough time and luck. Also, my success dao mark was used up already to refine change form Immortal Gu. Even if I prepare adequately, if I am unlucky, and encounter the failure rate, I would fail to refine star thought Immortal Gu."

"As for other people refining star thought Immortal Gu, the possibility is very small, after all, Dong Fang Chang Fan only self-detonated star thought Immortal Gu not too long ago."

Time passed, seven minutes had gone by already.

In fighting soul battlefield, ancient soul beasts appeared again.

A continuous stream of soul beasts encircled Fang Yuan and the others from all directions.

Compared to the dark swamp of soul beasts, Fang Yuan and the others were like sesame seeds on a pancake!

However, Shark Demon and the others were not desperate, they had intent to fight and anticipation.

That was because Fang Yuan and the others were close to succeeding in dismantling the battlefield killer move.

"All or nothing!" Shark Demon gritted his teeth, he knew that he had to stake it all now, he activated the incomplete Profound Ice House without hesitation.

The incomplete Profound Ice House took in everyone as it rushed out of the soul beast army by charging forward.

It charged unhindered, tearing countless soul beasts to shreds, even the desolate beast level soul beasts could not stop the rampaging Profound Ice House.

Bam bam bam!

Ancient soul beasts had enough strength, they surrounded Profound Ice House and attacked ruthlessly.

Immortal essence was expended intensely, Shark Demon, Su Bai Man and the others' expressions turned pale!

Chapter 905: Pitiful Victory

"Endure, endure it!"

"Success depends on this, we will win if we endure for just a bit more!"

In the incomplete Profound Ice House, everyone was screaming loudly, they lost their composure.

Outside the incomplete Profound Ice House, there were an uncountable number of soul beasts, they were like swamps of ants encircling Profound Ice House in the middle.

"How many hidden spots left?" Shark Demon shouted.

"A hundred and seventy-eight!" Bo Dan immediately reported. Even though he could not destroy the mortal Gu efficiently, at this point, fighting soul battlefield was close to collapsing, soul beasts were no longer being produced, Bo Dan's investigative methods could cover the entire battlefield.

"A hundred and seventy-eight..." Su Bai Man muttered, her expression was ugly, but the light of hope in her eyes shined brightly.

This number of hidden locations seemed easy to deal with.

But in fact, it was very difficult.

Firstly, the core Immortal Gu left were the hardest to deduce and take down.

Secondly, the immortals were now inside Profound Ice House, their methods were restricted, they could not use their methods as freely as before.

The Immortal Gu House had both offense and defense, as well as movement, it was a war fortress with capabilities in all areas, without any apparent weaknesses. The more Gu Immortals inside the Immortal Gu House, and the higher their cultivation levels, the more immortal essence they could provide to the Immortal Gu House, and the more power the Immortal Gu House could unleash!

But there was a flaw in this.

That was that the Gu Immortals could only provide fuel for the Immortal Gu House. The Immortal Gu House's offense, defense, movement, healing, investigation, and others, were decided based on the Immortal Gu House's own Immortal Gu and mortal Gu.

Thus, Fang Yuan, Xie Shu Fang, and the others' methods were obstructed by the Immortal Gu House, they could not be used.

From this perspective, ancient battle formations were much better than Immortal Gu Houses. Even though ancient battle formations had been deemed outdated in history after the emergence of countless Immortal Gu Houses, facts showed that ancient battle formations still had many advantages.

For example, the fighting methods of ancient battle formations were much more flexible than Immortal Gu Houses.

An Immortal Gu House's offense, defense, movement, healing, and investigation abilities were all decided by the Immortal Gu, they could not be changed, their power only depended on how much immortal essence was used, they were inflexible.

But ancient battle formations were different, even though ancient battle formations were also made of Gu formations, the core was the Gu Immortals inside.

The Gu Immortals could use their personal immortal killer moves inside the ancient battle formation.

Just like during the defensive battle of Lang Ya blessed land when Fang Yuan and the hairy man Gu Immortals used the second best ancient battle formation, Heavenly Giant Solor. This silver giant would change its form depending on what killer moves the Gu Immortal used, and the killer move's power would be amplified greatly as well.

In all, if it was an ancient battle formation, the immortals might have already destroyed all of the hidden Gu worms and obtained victory. But because this was an Immortal Gu House, they were restricted.

It was like climbing a mountain, they only had a small flight of stairs in front before they could reach the mountain peak. But just this small distance was an incredible obstacle to them.

In the immortals' perception, time seemed to have slowed down, every second felt like years.

"Are we going to fail again?" Su Bai Man muttered in disappointment, she showed a dark and defeated expression.

But at this time, Xie Shu Fang stood up, she said heavily to Shark Demon: "I can settle all of the remaining hidden Gu worms, but I would need to pay a huge price for my method. If you can give the Immortal Gu inside to me as compensation, I will help."

Shark Demon's expression was ugly, he snorted coldly. Su Bai Man also showed a ruthless and unfriendly gaze.

Xie Shu Fang's actions were likely to be extortion, but at this moment, they had no other ways left, to complete this difficult task, they could only rely on Xie Shu Fang.

But Xie Shu Fang asked for an Immortal Gu as compensation, Immortal Gu were extremely valuable, she was really asking for an exorbitant price.

But after Shark Demon thought about it for a while, he agreed without waiting for too long: "You can only take one Immortal Gu, that is my limit!"

He had undergone an intense competition in Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance to seize the mission for attacking Yu Lu blessed land.

Other than a portion of the benefits that had to be given to Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, the rest would go to Shark Demon and Su Bai Man.

This immortal zombie couple had already invested a huge sum, their foundations were shaken. The Immortal Gu inside Yu Lu blessed land were their property, right now, Xie Shu Fang's request was simply digging away at their fortune!

But one had to say, Shark Demon really had a grand disposition, he knew how to assess the situation and give up some benefits when necessary.

He could actually hold in his anger and agree to Xie Shu Fang's request.

This made Fang Yuan praise him secretly.

Xie Shu Fang saw Shark Demon giving in and did not hesitate, she nodded, smiling: "Sir Shark Demon, I am not a greedy person. But one of the Immortal Gu in the battlefield killer move suits me a lot. I will not dare to ask for more Immortal Gu, I owe you a favor this time."

"Go ahead, Master Xie Shu Fang." Su Bai Man crossed her arms, saying in a cold tone.

This Immortal Gu was not easy to obtain.

Everyone watched with anticipation as Xie Shu Fang's expression turned serious, her aura was growing. At the same time, black and white lights appeared on her body.

The black and white light swirled around, forming into a big ball.

The ball was made of black, white, and grey, it resembled a map and was showing a life-like scene of the battlefield.

In the map, the incomplete Profound Ice House was a white dot in the center, surrounded by darkness, they were all soul beasts. The hidden Gu worms were around the countless soul beasts, they were shining like stars, having very clear locations.

Wisdom path immortal killer move — Distinct Map!

Xie Shu Fang breathed in deeply, she stretched out her finger and pointed at the map.

She used her index finger and thumb to grab onto a hidden spot, by exerting some strength, she squeezed.

The immortals only heard a soft cracking sound, like something had shattered.

Immediately after, Xie Shu Fang's fingers grinded, when she took out her hand, the Gu worms at the hidden spot were destroyed.

At once, the immortals gasped.

Xie Shu Fang's wisdom path killer move could bypass Profound Ice House and attack the outside world, with such precision. The soul beasts outside could do nothing to stop it, it was incredible!

Even Fang Yuan found it eye-opening.

This female immortal, Xie Shu Fang, might have a terrible attitude towards Fang Yuan, but she was called Master Xie by Shark Demon, she truly had some abilities.

Even though Fang Yuan had the advantage in terms of a good wisdom path inheritance and could surpass Bo Dan, Lu Tan Xin and Ninth Ghost Finger, against a wisdom path Gu Immortal like Xie Shu Fang, he was lacking by a lot.

Eventually, Xie Shu Fang used this distinct map killer move and destroyed most of the hidden Gu worms, capturing an Immortal Gu in the process.

When she took out this Immortal Gu from distinct map, the other Gu Immortals were all shocked.

After losing one Immortal Gu, fighting soul battlefield broke down rapidly, the remaining Immortal Gu and mortal Gu disappeared quickly, retreating on their own.

Countless soul beasts growled, as they growled, they attacked relentlessly for the final time.

Profound Ice House was after all an Immortal Gu House, it resisted the soul beasts' frenzied attacks until the end.

Eventually, the soul beast army disintegrated along with the battlefield killer move, Shark Demon and the others finally obtained victory.

But soon, they fell into another battlefield killer move.

"Heavens, how many battlefield killer moves are there in this Yu Lu blessed land?" Bo Dan held his head in desperation.

After the fighting soul battlefield, the immortals went into another new battlefield killer move — Eight Doors Labyrinth.

In this battlefield killer move, the sky and ground were all orange, other than eight huge doors around them, there was nothing else.

But even the best wisdom path Gu Immortal, Xie Shu Fang, showed a difficult expression, she reminded them: "Be careful. This eight doors labyrinth is used specially to trap enemies, even though it does not have the killing nature of fighting soul battlefield, it is harder to deal with."

Nobody had any rebuttal.

Eight doors labyrinth was very famous in history, when Gu Immortals were trapped inside, they would lose their sense of direction to a huge extent.

Furthermore, each of these eight doors would only allow one life form inside.

After entering, the door would disappear.

That was to say, the eight doors before Shark Demon and gang meant that they only had eight chances to explore it.

After entering the door, the Gu Immortals would need to fight alone with any help, there were no other Gu Immortals to help them.

"Rumors says that after entering the door, Gu Immortals will end up in a second area, and make another choice out of eight doors. In the eight doors labyrinth, there are eight areas, each area has eight doors. There is only one correct path however, choosing the wrong path would just be going in circles. This is a classic labyrinth battlefield, it is very powerful at trapping people. Without a wisdom path Gu Immortal skilled at deductions, there is no way to unravel it. Gu Immortals skilled at fighting cannot progress through this, they might even be trapped inside until they die." Xie Shu Fang sighed.

Even though she was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, she was not skilled in deductions.

The immortal killer move distinct map earlier had already exposed her foundation, she was a wisdom path Gu Immortal skilled at investigation and long ranged attacks, she was more of a battle type.

Fang Yuan's wisdom path inheritance was good at deductions, but he did not even have the most basic star thought Immortal Gu. One couldn't cook a meal without the ingredients, this was a very awkward state.

"This is only the first area, we can still retreat." Xie Shu Fang reminded.

In the earlier battlefield killer move, they could probe it. But against eight doors labyrinth, Gu Immortals would be risking their lives to investigate it, they could not even probe it from outside.

"Yu Lu blessed land's battlefield killer moves are getting harder to deal with. We should be close to completely taking it down?" Shark Demon sighed, he wisely chose to retreat.

Using Profound Ice House, the immortals charged out and left Yu Lu blessed land.

This time, even though Shark Demon and the others unraveled fighting soul battlefield, they paid a huge price, it was a pitiful victory.

The one that benefited the most was Xie Shu Fang.

She obtained an Immortal Gu as compensation, she was overjoyed.

Chapter 906: Yellow Spring Sea Area, Undying Kingdom

They had unraveled fighting soul battlefield, but because of the battlefield killer move eight doors labyrinth, Shark Demon and the group had no choice but to temporarily retreat from Yu Lu blessed land.

After parting with the other wisdom path Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng followed Shark Demon and Su Bai Man to shark sea where they were hosted to a banquet.

"Brother Xing Xiang, I wonder how much assurance you have in deciphering eight doors labyrinth?" In the banquet, Shark Demon asked.

Fang Yuan's expression slightly changed as he heavily shook his head: "I am ashamed, I don't have the least bit of assurance."

"Even you don't have any assurance?" Su Bai Man said with disappointment.

Fang Yuan mumbled: "If I could refine a certain wisdom path Immortal Gu, I would have thirty percent assurance. Unfortunately, although I have been trying with all my efforts to gather the immortal materials, I am still far away from the standard to refine Immortal Gu. Refining Immortal Gu is... really hard!"

Shark Demon's eyes slightly brightened at Fang Yuan's words, but soon dimmed.

He had cooperated with Xing Xiang Zi not only once, and knew ins and outs of Fang Yuan; Fang Yuan indeed lacked wisdom path immortal killer moves.

While unraveling the battlefield killer move this time, Shark Demon also learned several things.

Big Bag Lu Tan Xin and the demonic path Gu Immortal Ninth Ghost Finger could not match Fang Yuan in wisdom path methods. There was no need to even mention Bo Dan. Xie Shu Fang, on the contrary, was truly skilled, far surpassing Fang Yuan, but she was a righteous path Gu Immortal and not to mention that she could not fit in with Shark Demon's group, her appetite was too big.

In this trip, Shark Demon and the group did not even get anything, but Xie Shu Fang obtained an Immortal Gu, gaining the biggest profit.

No matter how open-minded Shark Demon was, he felt extreme loss from losing an Immortal Gu.

Although they unraveled fighting soul battlefield, they held a poor impression of Xie Shu Fang, it was only that they suppressed it and did not mention it. With Shark Demon's personality, he would get back at her for this, sooner or later.

Fang Yuan was observing Shark Demon's expression, seeing the latter's eyes brighten before dimming, he sighed and said gently: "I won't hide it from the two of you, my wisdom path inheritance is complete, if I have that wisdom path Immortal Gu, I can use several powerful immortal killer moves and my strength will definitely rise greatly. Even if I can't match Xie Shu Fang, the gap won't be too big."

Shark Demon nodded and talked about other things, not continuing this topic.

Fang Yuan had not fully expressed himself before he was interrupted, but how could Shark Demon not understand Fang Yuan's meaning?

'The hidden implication of Xing Xiang Zi's words is to make me sponsor him in refining that wisdom path Immortal Gu. But I will suffer greatly in this transaction, it is okay if the refinement succeeds, but if it fails, all the investment would be gone to waste, that will just be adding to my misfortunes.'

Shark Demon pondered, and denied the thought of helping Fang Yuan refine Immortal Gu.

In fact, the pressure on him recently was huge.

To invade Yu Lu blessed land, he and Su Bai Man had invested large amounts of energy and wealth, but up to this point, there were few results. On this attempt too, they had paid quite a lot to invite three wisdom path assistants.

Even if Shark Demon and Su Bai Man were veteran experts with deep foundations, their accumulation was showing signs of being exhausted right now.

Refining Immortal Gu might just be sending themselves into a bottomless pit. Unless it was the only choice left, Shark Demon absolutely would not choose this option.

Fang Yuan felt slight regret about Shark Demon's stance, but he had already predicted it and did not feel any disappointment.

He had used up most of his immortal essence stones to relocate the blessed land. With his current financial ability, he required a long time before he could gather enough immortal materials for refining star thought Immortal Gu.

"It doesn't matter that Shark Demon did not take the bait, the main thing is still to join Zombie Alliance." Fang Yuan did not forget his current main goal.

Shark Demon also wanted Fang Yuan to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

The reason?

Because once Fang Yuan joined Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, he would be on Shark Demon and Su Bai Man's side. Like this, with Zombie Alliance's alliance restrictions, Shark Demon could more conveniently and more assuredly use Fang Yuan the next time they attacked Yu Lu blessed land.

This would be of great help to Shark Demon's present development plan.

Helping Xing Xiang Zi was helping himself, so after the shark fishing banquet, Shark Demon brought Fang Yuan to Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's headquarters.

Two days later.

Shark Demon and Fang Yuan were flying quickly.

"This is yellow spring sea area." Shark Demon pointed at the sea below, and introduced.

In fact, there was no need for his indication, as Fang Yuan was already looking at the special sea below him.

The seawater of the yellow spring sea area was yellow in color, like the sea was mixed with dirt and sand. Waves billowed, moving up and down the sea.

But in fact, there was no sand floating on the yellow spring sea area, the seawater by itself had a light yellow color.

"Yellow spring sea area is an extremely special sea area. As you get closer to the center of the sea area, you will find there are no living creatures, this is the largest zombie farming area in the five regions." Shark Demon introduced.

Fang Yuan nodded and used investigative methods, his vision increased sharply, penetrating the sea surface towards the depths.

He saw countless skeletons floating inside the sea, large numbers of zombie fish groups, zombie cuttlefish, jellyfish, sea turtles, and so on, moving in the sea, and constantly fighting each other.

In the seabed lived grayish white decomposed corals which gave off intense stenches that pervaded the surrounding seawater. Strands of seaweed, drifting with the water flow, were deathly pale, like nooses used to hang people.

"Over these two days, we used four undercurrents, and flew for a day and half, going past ten sea areas before we reached this yellow spring sea area where Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's headquarters lies. Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance is indeed the main headquarters of the zombie alliances over the five regions, to be able to grasp such a large territory in Eastern Sea." Fang Yuan sincerely exclaimed.

Shark Demon laughed heartily: "The Zombie Alliance branches in the other four regions are weaker, but this here in Eastern Sea is the headquarters of Zombie Alliance, it is powerful and prosperous, and can surpass other super forces. Brother Xing Xiang, joining this powerful force is a sensible decision!"

Different from Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's Dark Flow Giant City, Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance possessed a public blessed land which they used as their headquarters.

This public blessed land, located in the center of the yellow spring sea area, was known as the 'Undying Kingdom' in the world of Eastern Sea Gu Immortals.

Under Shark Demon's guidance, Fang Yuan smoothly entered Undying Kingdom blessed land.

Unlike Fang Yuan's estimation, Undying Kingdom blessed land was a scene full of life, filled with the twittering of birds and fragrance of flowers.

This formed a stark contrast with the death energy and putrefaction of immortal zombies.

"Since immortal zombies are already among the living dead, their immortal apertures turns into dead lands, how could you raise such a large public blessed land? Could it be from the blessed lands of living Gu Immortals members of Zombie Alliance?" Fang Yuan was puzzled.

Shark Demon laughed: "Xing Xiang Zi, you can be at ease. Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance has never forcibly demanded any living Gu Immortal, that wants to join Zombie Alliance, to offer a part of their immortal aperture. Naturally, Zombie Alliance encourages you to offer part of your blessed land by providing large amounts of rewards. You will see this once you look at the assignments in the inner hall."

"Most of the Undying Kingdom blessed land still came from immortal zombies. Or to put it more accurately, it came from those old Gu Immortals whose lifespan is ending and are planning to turn into immortal zombies to prolong their lives, or for various other reasons. Do you know why this blessed land is called Undying Kingdom? It is because Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance has unique methods to merge pieces of blessed lands to preserve and maintain their vitality."

Fang Yuan's eyes brightened, showing an extremely interested expression.

Shark Demon was observing his expression, and laughed: "Xing Xiang Zi, are you also interested in this method? Hehehe, that's right. Our Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance has already gained some success from countless predecessors' studies and accumulations — on how to maintain the vitality of the immortal aperture while not causing any change to the immortal zombie body."

Fang Yuan's heart thumped loudly, he had always been thinking of how to revive and get rid of his immortal zombie body.

Why?

It was because an immortal zombie's immortal aperture was a dead land and had no potential to progress in cultivation.

However, now, as Fang Yuan heard Shark Demon's words, his thoughts towards reviving had another change.

'The reason I am trying to be free of an immortal zombie body and revive is for my immortal aperture to be full of life and to progress in cultivation. But if I could truly maintain the vitality of the immortal aperture as an immortal zombie, and have the possibility to improve, then wouldn't it be making the best of both worlds?'

To be an immortal zombie was to be among the living dead with no limit to lifespan, and could be considered as another form of longevity.

Fang Yuan was using this advantage to continuously step into the wisdom light halo, greatly improving his capabilities.

But if Fang Yuan revived into a living person, his lifespan would sharply reduce under the light of wisdom and he would only be able to use wisdom Gu for a number of times.

The immortal zombie body had advantages and disadvantages.

But even if Fang Yuan had wisdom Gu, the disadvantages still outweighed the advantages.

Thus, Fang Yuan had been looking for a way to revive all along.

'If I can truly maintain my immortal zombie body and still revive my immortal aperture to advance my cultivation, this would be the best option for me. But right now, it seems that although Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance has made remarkable achievements in this aspect, they are still a great distance from perfecting it. If they truly had this method, Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance would already have been dominating Eastern Sea. The five regions would also not have the current structure.'

After Fang Yuan calmed down, he speculated the truths of Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

"All humans are mortal, they will have a day where their lifespan ends. Brother Xing Xiang, after you join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, you can contribute to the alliance and use these contributions to exchange for this research result." Shark Demon smiled as he patted Fang Yuan's shoulder.

Fang Yuan nodded with a fervent expression on his face, but his mind was calm and knew Shark Demon was simply trying to entice him.

Fang Yuan had joined Northern Plains Zombie Alliance and already understood that to exchange for such a level of research results, the contribution to the alliance must be extremely big.

Shark Demon brought Fang Yuan to the center of the Undying Kingdom.

Over there existed a mountain range carved from skeletons, and on the tens of mountains lay tens of palaces or halls.

Shark Demon led Fang Yuan to a hall.

After a long while, Fang Yuan and Shark Demon walked out of the hall. Fang Yuan now had an identity token and also information path mortal Gu used to transmit all sorts of information to and from Zombie Alliance.

With Shark Demon's guidance, Fang Yuan smoothly became a member of Zombie Alliance.

Chapter 907: Interacting with Song clan

Compared to the first time when Fang Yuan joined Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, it was much easier this time to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

Originally, Fang Yuan was afraid that his identity would get exposed, after all, there were several rank eight immortal zombies guarding Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

Because of this, Fang Yuan had used the light of wisdom in Hu Immortal blessed land and expended a large number of star thoughts to fuse star mark Immortal Gu into the killer move vaguely familiar face.

With Eat Strength, Change Form, and Star Mark, three Immortal Gu as the cores, it was much more realistic when Fang Yuan transformed into a star path Gu Immortal or a star path desolate beast.

But this time, when he joined Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, Fang Yuan did not see a single rank eight Gu Immortal, even the inspection towards his Xing Xiang Zi identity was only a formality.

"The reason for this, other than the busy schedule of rank eight Gu Immortals, should be that Shark Demon has a high status in Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance. Living Gu Immortals cannot become higher-ups of Zombie Alliance, the reason should be because Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance has a huge force, it has enough confidence and foundation." Fang Yuan analyzed secretly.

Seven days later.

Bee sea.

Countless bee groups emerged from the water, landing on the boat flowers floating on the sea.

During May in Eastern Sea, the surface of bee sea would have ripples that carried countless boat flowers that floated over.

These flowers were in vibrant colors, they were as large as small boats, they were like scrolls that spread out in the sea of flowers.

Bee sea was a sea area that was connected to flower sea.

There were large numbers of water bees living in bee sea, this special type of bee could only fly temporarily, they were more skilled at swimming in the sea freely.

During May each year, countless boat flowers would flow along with the waves, arriving at bee sea area, it was the only opportunity for the water bees to collect nectar.

In the air of this sea, Fang Yuan, Shark Demon and the others got into a formation, as they underwent an intense negotiation with Song clan's Gu Immortals.

Eventually, after thirty minutes, the two sides came to an agreement after coming to terms.

Song Yi Shi and the others no longer pursued Xing Xiang Zi's wrongdoings. Even though Xing Xiang Zi did not do it on purpose, it was still a mistake, not only did he have to apologize, he even had to compensate Song Yi Shi six hundred immortal essence stones. Xing Xiang Zi could not pay everything in one go, so he could have six installments for it. He could pay a hundred immortal essence stones first, followed by a hundred and twenty on the second installment, and a hundred and forty immortal essence stones on the third...

According to the agreement, if he were to pay in batches, Fang Yuan would definitely make greater losses.

Thus, after they came to an agreement, Fang Yuan borrowed a sum of immortal essence stones from Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Shark Demon, getting a total of six hundred and passing it to Song Yi Shi.

Song Yi Shi's expression was dark, she received these immortal essence stones as she stared at Fang Yuan angrily, she said coldly: "Apologize!"

Fang Yuan was a person who could give in if needed to, he smiled bitterly and apologized earnestly: "I did not intend to offend Fairy Yi Shi, to have angered a beauty, I truly deserve death, please forgive me!"

"Then why don't you go and die?" Song Yi Shi interjected.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "If I had seen Fairy Yi Shi's body fully, I would deserve to die a thousand deaths. But fairy should know, the mist in the hot spring is thick, you also used an isolation immortal killer move, how could I see anything?"

Song Yi Shi snorted, she was extremely clear of the situation then, she had no defenses set up at the bottom of the volcano, how could she have any immortal killer move. Even if there was mist, Song Yi Shi had gotten rid of them in advance, she did not like to have her vision obstructed.

But Song Yi Shi did not argue against Fang Yuan's bullshit.

Even if this 'lecherous and shameless' old man had seen her entire body, Song Yi Shi had to deny it and refuse to acknowledge it.

The two Gu Immortals from Song clan had a dazed expression, they even secretly pitied this Xing Xiang Zi. Fang Yuan had explained it clearly, the truth was, after this matter was exposed, Song clan had inspected Li clan village thoroughly.

This undercurrent had only been formed in the last few years. And because Song Yi Shi did not inspect the bottom of her volcano clearly, such a loophole was formed.

Xing Xiang Zi only took a look, and because of the thick mist, he could not see anything, but he had to compensate six hundred immortal essence stones, this was simply too much of a price to pay.

In the end, it was all because Song clan was a super force with a large foundation. If Xing Xiang Zi offended anyone else, it would have been fine, but he actually looked at Song Yi Shi, even though she herself was not an issue, she was backed by the first supreme elder of Song clan, Song Qi Yuan!

If not for Shark Demon negotiating in this matter on behalf of Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, if not for Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance being stronger than Song clan, Fang Yuan would not have been able to pay merely six hundred immortal essence stones to settle this matter.

"Xing Xiang Zi, even though this matter is over, I don't want to see you appear in front of me ever again!" Song Yi Shi said harshly before flying away.

The other two Gu Immortals from Song clan had a milder attitude, they cupped their fists politely: "Lord Shark Demon, Lady Su Bai Man, farewell."

"Take care." Shark Demon replied.

At this point, the incident was resolved.

Shark Demon invited Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng to Shark Sea again as guests.

But Fang Yuan rejected him, he told Shark Demon that he wanted to see if there were any lucrative missions in Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance that could make use of his expertise, in order to earn immortal essence stones and settle his debt.

Shark Demon sensed Fang Yuan's 'dejection' and consoled him, saying that Zombie Alliance had a loose structure and would not restrict his freedom.

Fang Yuan's acting was on point, he made Shark Demon believe that he was really a lone cultivator that was very bent on having freedom.

Since Fang Yuan rejected them, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man did not force him. This couple also needed time to prepare for the next invasion of Yu Lu blessed land.

After parting with Shark Demon, Fang Yuan actually took some deduction missions from Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance. He was a vigilant person, he had to finish the act, he would not leave flaws in such details.

Fang Yuan had a mission token, and an information path mortal Gu for communication, it was easy to accept missions, he did not need to head to Undying Kingdom blessed land personally.

In fact, Fang Yuan did not intend to enter Undying Kingdom blessed land personally ever again. After all, there were rank eight immortal zombies staying on guard there, against such great experts, even though Fang Yuan had the killer move vaguely familiar face, he was not confident in it.

"Even though I spent six hundred immortal essence stones, as long as I can get into Northern Plains Zombie Alliance successfully, it will be worth it. Now, I have to wait for Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance to release some missions regarding Northern Plains. For example, information collecting in Northern Plains, or a mission to inspect the Northern Plains branch of Zombie Alliance." Fang Yuan planned.

Fang Yuan's plan was going very smoothly, at this point, he just needed to wait.

Next, Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel and returned to Hu Immortal blessed land. He and Tai Bai Yun Sheng parted ways, he used Landscape as Before to pave the way and make friends in Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world.

Using the light of wisdom, Fang Yuan spent a short amount of time to finish all of the deduction missions that he had taken from Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

If it was in the past, these deduction missions would have taken him much of the month, but now Fang Yuan only used several days.

Fang Yuan was gradually feeling his wisdom path attainment increasing.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, he had undergone turmoil, torture, glory, falling from grace, all of these had turned him into a strategist, he was adept at plotting against people, this made Fang Yuan very compatible with the cultivation of wisdom path.

Furthermore, with a high quality wisdom path inheritance, and the rank nine wisdom Gu, could Fang Yuan's wisdom path not improve drastically?

After completing these missions, Fang Yuan did not turn them in. This speed was too shocking, it was not on the level of attainment that he had revealed to them.

As for the immortal essence stones that Fang Yuan owed Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Shark Demon, he was not worried.

Fang Yuan could choose not to pay back the debt to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, as for Shark Demon, he could return it in a few days time.

Guts Gu had greater demand than supply, it was still selling like hot cakes, his other businesses were also progressing smoothly.

Even though he had caused the four sources of revenue in Star Form blessed land to be damaged when he relocated it, Fang Yuan's monthly profits still reached a thousand immortal essence stones!

But in spite of this, Fang Yuan still lacked money.

Be it the reform in Star Form blessed land, or the refinement of star thought Immortal Gu, they needed funds, huge amounts of funds!

Other than that, there was also the feeding of Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan needed to feed the large number of Immortal Gu that he had. If they died from hunger, his loss would be too great.

Finding lifespan Gu, reeducating Fang Zheng, interrogating the captives, building the fourth Fang Yuan stone nest, improving his immortal killer moves, learning new wisdom path techniques for the next invasion of Yu Lu blessed land, buying Gu worms, buying strength path desolate beasts and desolate plants, buying the experience and knowledge of nurturing hairy men, investigating the spring dream fruit tree... all of these matters were complicated, Fang Yuan needed to settle them.

Even though the immortal zombie body did not require the rest ordinary humans needed, Fang Yuan still felt that he had insufficient time.

Fang Yuan understood his own predicament clearly. One day, the fact that he was the culprit behind the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would be exposed.

He had to use this period of time to grow as much as he could, to get rid of the weaknesses that he had.

Fang Yuan would love to split up his time, or even split himself into two and work. While he was busy with his tasks, Fang Yuan also observed the situation in the outside world.

He put less focus on Western Desert and Southern Border.

Central Continent was still being affected by the Refinement Path Convention's lingering effect.

As for Northern Plains, after Old Ancestor Xue Hu defeated Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, there appeared to be peace and quiet. But Fang Yuan had joined the battle to defend Lang Ya, he knew that Old Lord Can Yang and the other Central Continent investigators were here, thus, even though Northern Plains seemed calm, Fang Yuan could feel the intense undercurrents stirring in the dark.

As for Eastern Sea, the current most popular news was about Song clan and other super forces fighting for the control of Ascending Heaven Plain.

A few days later.

Western Desert.

Fang Yuan changed his appearance and did a transaction with Xiao clan's Gu Immortal.

"These are the goods this time, check them." Fang Yuan took out the regretful spiders.

This time, the Xiao clan Gu Immortal was Xiao Shi Rang, he had a stable personality and was quite wise, he was known as Xiao clan's brains and brawn duo along with Xiao Hu Chi.

Xiao Shi Rang inspected it and nodded in satisfaction: "There are no issues, take this!"

He tossed a sum of immortal essence stones towards Fang Yuan.

But now was different, other than immortal essence stones, there was also a token, and an information path mortal Gu!

This was Xiao clan's transaction token!

Chapter 908: Opportunity After Causing Chaos

"It has been a very good experience doing business with you. Our Xiao clan hopes to continue the transactions of regretful spiders for as long as possible. The token in your hand is Xiao clan's transaction token. Sir, with this token, you are now Xiao clan's trading partner and can enjoy a lot of preferential policies. The details are recorded in the information path mortal Gu. Naturally, you can refuse this token as well." Xiao Shi Rang said.

Fang Yuan accepted this token rather happily.

In fact, he was trading with Xiao clan not only to earn immortal essence stones from selling regretful spiders to Xiao clan, but also for this transaction token.

Among the five regions, Western Desert was the most developed in commerce.

Every super force would issue their respective transaction token. But Xiao clan's transaction token was the one with the most value.

The reason was Xiao clan and Tian clan engaged in business the most among all the super forces in Western Desert, with the highest numbers of trading partners. Fang Yuan wanted to enter Western Desert's market, and it could be easily done with Xiao clan's transaction token, and he could also get along well with other trading partners of Xiao clan.

Naturally, this had its demerits as well.

Xiao clan and Tian clan were the biggest competitors, accepting Xiao clan's transaction token meant being close to Xiao clan, as such, it would be difficult for Fang Yuan to do business with Tian clan and Gu Immortals who possessed Tian clan's transaction token.

"With this transaction token, I can officially engage in the trade of dragonfish and eerie fire dragon pythons. My profit every month will pass one thousand immortal essence stones. When I restore other resources, my earnings every month will be close to two thousand!"

Fang Yuan did not conceal his joy, accepting this token with a smile.

Xiao Shi Rang also smiled.

As far as Xiao Shi Rang was concerned, Fang Yuan was extremely mysterious, ever since Fang Yuan appeared, Xiao clan had repeatedly undertaken investigations, but could not find out Fang Yuan's identity. However, Fang Yuan did not hesitate at all when accepting Xiao clan's transaction token, this action meant being closer to Xiao clan, and Xiao Shi Rang naturally expressed more goodwill.

With the transaction token, Fang Yuan started roaming around Western Desert's Gu Immortal world for the next few days.

The path was clear with the help of transaction token, even if it was the first meeting, Fang Yuan was able to smoothly make several deals involving dragonfish and eerie fire dragon pythons. Most of these deals were short term transactions, and only one or two were long term deals.

But Fang Yuan believed that as time went on and the number of transactions increased, these long term deals would keep on increasing in number and become more stable.

With a joyous mood, Fang Yuan left Western Desert. But when he stepped into Hu Immortal blessed land, he received shocking information.

"What? Song Yi Shi actually flattened that island where Li clan village lived, in a fit of anger?!"

Originally, the competition for Ascending Heaven Plain had gotten more intense, at first, it was only three clans fighting for dominance, but when the situation turned into a stalemate, many other forces and Gu Immortals joined in, looking to get some benefits.

During this course of events, Song Yi Shi ran into a female demonic path Gu Immortal, Seven Seas Snake Woman, who ridiculed and slandered her, saying how her body was only worth six hundred immortal essence stones.

Song Yi Shi's mood sank to the depths, and after returning, in a fit of anger, she went to that nameless island and massacred all the mortals and beasts on the island. She then caused a tsunami and submerged the whole island repeatedly five or six times. Naturally, no one on this nameless island survived.

To others, this was not a matter worth mentioning, thus Fang Yuan's shock would be strange from most people's perspective.

"Now what happens to Li Xiao Yao? Originally, Song Yi Shi and Li Xiao Yao were a famous couple, but now because of me, Song Yi Shi massacred all of Li Xiao Yao's ancestors, isn't that like killing Li Xiao Yao?"

The prominent and powerful Li Xiao Yao from his previous life had no chance to take the limelight in history now.

"Such a pity, I had intended to connect luck with Li Xiao Yao in the future. He was also a rather lucky person." Fang Yuan sighed inwardly, Eastern Sea's future structure had changed considerably because of him.

And how far this change would spread to affect other matters, Fang Yuan also did not know.

Several days later, an event occurred that shocked Fang Yuan even more!

"What, Starry Sky grotto-heaven shattered and countless grotto-heaven fragments are falling down like meteors, causing forces of all sizes and countless Gu Immortals to fight for them?!"

Fang Yuan was speechless.

According to his previous life's memories, the event of Starry Sky grotto-heaven shattering and falling down was supposed to happen hundreds of years later!

How could it have happened so early in this life?

"Is it because of me? I picked up benefits from Star Lord Wan Xiang and Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei, and led to immortal zombie Seven Star Child to awaken from the dream realm, causing Shi Lei to be trapped in the grotto-heaven and having no choice but to request support from Combat Immortal Sect. Seven Star Child had to fight against Combat Immortal Sect, but despite having the territorial advantage, Combat Immortal Sect is a colossal force which made Seven Star Child feel the situation was far from good, deciding to detonate Starry Sky grotto-heaven and drag them down with him?"

Fang Yuan's speculation was completely right.

In fact, it had happened like that.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, Seven Star Child was trapped in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm for a long time without waking up. Although Star Lord Wan Xiang died, Shi Lei inherited this fortune, he did not report to the sect and secretly sneaked in every time the crack opened, and plundered the resources wantonly.

However, in this life, after Fang Yuan awakened Seven Star Child, Shi Lei was faced with disaster, having to run around miserably from Seven Star Child, he had no choice but to give up on maintaining his face, seeking help from Combat Immortal Sect.

In the end, Combat Immortal Sect could not forcibly suppress Seven Star Child.

"Since I cannot have it, you can forget about obtaining it!" With this thought in mind, Seven Star Child detonated Starry Sky grotto-heaven and decisively stopped contesting with Combat Immortal Sect's immortals.

Thus, the grotto-heaven's fragments fell down early to Central Continent's land by two to three hundred years.

Fang Yuan was left lost for words after he heard this news.

"Northern Plains has already been turned into a mess by me, with the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and the destruction of Imperial Court blessed land. Eastern Sea has also changed, Li Xiao Yao is no more. Now, Central Continent is also experiencing a drastic change, Starry Sky grotto-heaven has collapsed before its time. According to this trend, Central Continent and Eastern Sea are going to change beyond all recognition!"

Right now, the whole of Central Continent was shaken because of this event.

Countless Gu Immortals, Gu Masters, super forces and other forces of all sizes were flocking towards the grotto-heaven's fragment worlds.

What Central Continent Refinement Path Convention? It was all thrown to the back of their minds.

Fang Yuan could not help but smile bitterly at this.

Starry Sky grotto-heaven had broken up at a very bad time, if it had collapsed two or three hundred years later, Fang Yuan could have gained considerable benefits.

Because that time was when the five regions chaotic war began and dream realms manifested externally. Champions and warriors emerged endlessly, the old super forces would be busy with their own affairs, it was most beneficial to lone cultivators like Fang Yuan.

However, at present, the five regions chaotic war was yet to start. Central Continent was dominated by Heavenly Court, and the ten great ancient sects firmly controlled the whole of Central Continent.

Fang Yuan could foresee that this initial chaos would only last for a short period of time before the ten great ancient sects took control of the whole situation. The true beneficiaries would no doubt be them and Heavenly Court behind them.

The development of the events went according to Fang Yuan's prediction.

The change in the situation was even quicker than Fang Yuan's estimation! Central Continent's ten great ancient sects stabilized the situation, quickly making an internal agreement and expelling all the other forces and Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan got a deep impression of the colossal forces that were the ten great ancient sects.

"It is quite the pity regarding Starry Sky grotto-heaven, Seven Star Child, and that dream realm." Fang Yuan sighed with regret.

Starry Sky grotto-heaven was one of his long term plans, but now with this unforeseen event, this enormous benefit was missed by him.

However, the next change in events was beyond Fang Yuan's expectations.

A letter from He Feng Yang came to Fang Yuan through hole earth Gu.

In the letter, He Feng Yang, on behalf of Immortal Crane Sect, invited Fang Yuan to explore a fragment world of Starry Sky grotto-heaven!

"Could it be?!" Fang Yuan's gaze brightened sharply, the thought in his mind made him stand up in excitement, and laugh loudly.

After laughing, Fang Yuan mumbled to himself: "I cannot be careless, although the likelihood of it being a trap is rather small, it is better to first investigate before replying..."

Two days later, Fang Yuan came to a mountain valley in Central Continent.

This nameless valley was extremely lacking in supplies and in no way was remarkable, but because a large fragment of Starry Sky grotto-heaven had fallen here, this valley was already surrounded by the allied forces of the ten great ancient sects, making a thousand li around it a forbidden zone.

If other Gu Immortals stepped within this range, they would be killed without mercy!

Fang Yuan also did not dare to move around recklessly. He Feng Yang personally came out to welcome him and led him inside the valley.

There were over ten Gu Immortals, from the ten great ancient sects, guarding inside the valley.

"Kid, don't do anything stupid inside."

"Think about long term consequences, young man."

Seeing He Feng Yang lead Fang Yuan in, other Gu Immortals did not have nice expressions, they either threatened or advised.

"Sir is Fang Yuan?" A white clothed female immortal came out of the group of immortals.

"You are Fairy Bai Qing." Fang Yuan's focused his gaze slightly, as he bowed without changing his expression.

Fairy Bai Qing nodded at Fang Yuan, speaking in a warm tone: "You are the person who my daughter often mentioned. In this contest now over the ownership of the grotto-heaven fragment, I hope you can be merciful, we will definitely repay you in the future."

Fang Yuan had traded guts Gu with Spirit Affinity House many times, but had not seen Fairy Bai Qing once.

But now, as it concerned the safety of her daughter, Feng Jin Huang, Fairy Bai Qing had no choice but to appear personally and request Fang Yuan to give her some face.

Fang Yuan had his own plan, and accepted without any hesitation: "Collaborating with your side has been a pleasant experience, Lady Bai Qing can be at ease."

Fairy Bai Qing nodded in satisfaction.

Many other Gu Immortals snorted coldly.

A cold gaze flashed past He Feng Yang's eyes.

"Go in. The others have already entered, your cultivation is the highest so you are the last one." He Feng Yang said heavily.

Fang Yuan nodded and moved forward.

The scenery inside the valley was peculiar like a mirage, what looked like bushes were waves blue like the sea. The scene did not have boundaries in common with each other, resembling a broken picture that was abruptly put together.

This was naturally not a mirage, but a grotto-heaven fragment world, the entrance was open, allowing it to be explored.

Looking at Fang Yuan moving step by step inside, He Feng Yang could not put his heart at ease and reminded again: "Don't forget that place I told you about, you must occupy it!"

"No worries." Fang Yuan waved his hand without turning back. Under everyone's gazes, his body completely entered the grotto-heaven fragment.

Chapter 909: Advantage of Having Lower Cultivation Level

Fang Yuan looked over, seeing that the lake was shining in reflected light, the lake had a wide surface and was colored in many shades of blue.

Once he entered Starry Sky grotto-heaven fragment world, he had landed in this blue lake.

The lake had a huge surface area, there were several small islands near the center of the lake, growing with vegetation.

Looking even further, beyond the blue lake, there were layers of mountain ridges, they were colored in indigo, gently mixing with the sky.

Fang Yuan stood on the surface of the water like he was standing on the ground.

From the perspective of a mortal Gu Master, this ability to stand on water was very impressive. But it was already as simple as breathing to Fang Yuan now.

Before entering deep into the grotto-heaven fragment, Fang Yuan gave a final look below him.

Only to see that below him, the blue lake cracked suddenly, like a cracked mirror, the surface of this lake was completely broken.

Fang Yuan could see the outside world through this mirror, he saw that nameless valley in Central Continent, as well as the Gu Immortals' figures, they were looking at Fang Yuan with complex gazes.

Fang Yuan sneered internally, he turned around and leaped away from the lake, flying away.

The Gu Immortals from the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent did not know that this was not the first time Fang Yuan had been inside Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

Starry Sky grotto-heaven was very unique, it had seven areas that were isolated, it was not like a normal grotto-heaven.

Evidently, Starry Sky grotto-heaven had many space path dao marks, and they were all very special as well.

There were many desolate beasts in Starry Sky grotto-heaven, there were even ancient desolate beasts, the zombie dragon guarding the eighth star hall, the walking meat tree, they left a deep impression on Fang Yuan.

"But after such intense combat, coupled with Combat Immortal Sect's looting, and Starry Sky grotto-heaven's shattering, there must be very few desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts left in the fragment worlds. Right now, there are two desolate beasts and one desolate plant in this grotto-heaven fragment world."

Fang Yuan flew through the sky as he recalled the information that He Feng Yang had told him.

These two desolate beasts and one desolate plant were a desolate beast dragonfish, hidden essence turtle and nether grass respectively.

As long as one was a Gu Immortal, they knew of dragonfish, they were very commonly used as food for Immortal Gu. The overwhelming majority of mortal Gu could be fed with dragonfish meat if their specific food was of insufficient quantity, and a portion of the food for an Immortal Gu could be substituted with it. Of course, Immortal Gu were unique, their feeding requirements could be very bizarre, the effect of dragonfish was much lower. Furthermore, only desolate beast level dragonfish meat could be used for their food.

"Among desolate beasts, the one with the lowest battle strength has to be the desolate beast dragonfish. According to rumors, dragonfish is not a species that originated normally from the world, it was a species artificially created via food path."

The hidden essence turtle was a rare wisdom path desolate beast. It had weird habits, when it matures, it would stay at one place and stop moving. As time passes, after countless years, moss would grow on its body, it would turn to stone and become a giant false hill. Because it could conceal its aura and could hide itself well, it was hard to find.

Only when it senses a huge danger would it relocate, it would not stop until it finds a resting place in which it is satisfied. After that, it would stop and hide in its shell, enduring the weather, be it wind, rain, snow or so on, once again.

If he could capture this desolate beast, it was much better than killing it.

Hidden essence turtle was a wisdom path desolate beast, it had an inborn connection to wisdom path, it was a spirit beast of wisdom path. It had the natural ability to find a safe place to live in.

Many wisdom path Gu Immortals would use the hidden essence turtle to help them when they encounter difficulties in deductions.

Fang Yuan inherited Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path inheritance, there was also a way to use a freshly killed hidden essence turtle shell to help in deductions.

Evidently, capturing this hidden essence turtle was useful for Gu Immortals. Since it did not move and had strong defenses, Combat Immortal Sect did not attack it hastily.

The nether grass was similar, it was rooted to the ground and could not move, it had little threat as long as one did not get close to it.

A stalk of nether grass was very useful to a soul path Gu Immortal. And because nether grass contained large numbers of soul path dao marks, as time passed, it would influence the surroundings, a wide range surrounding the nether grass would become a breeding ground for soul path Gu worms.

Nether grass had an immense effect to modify the environment of a blessed land or grotto-heaven.

So for the same reason, Combat Immortal Sect did not take this nether grass, keeping it until now. But they did not expect Seven Star Child to be so resolute, he would rather drag everyone down with him, causing Starry Sky grotto-heaven to shatter and fall.

This situation was already out of Combat Immortal Sect's control, the fragment worlds of this Starry Sky grotto-heaven became the point of negotiation for the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, they decided on certain timings and entered to harvest the resources within.

He Feng Yang represented Immortal Crane Sect and before entering the grotto-heaven fragment world, he gave Fang Yuan several missions.

Three of them were regarding the dragonfish, nether grass, and hidden essence turtle.

"If you can capture all three of them alive, that would be best. According to the agreement, you can get one-third of the value of what you obtain." He Feng Yang told Fang Yuan.

Even though Fang Yuan was a subordinate of Immortal Crane Sect on paper, this was not the case, as a person directly involved, He Feng Yang was very aware of this.

Thus, he knew that in order to get him to work hard, he could only arouse Fang Yuan's interest through benefits.

Even though Fang Yuan was only a rank six bottom tier immortal zombie, he had a huge advantage against these three desolate beasts or plants.

Because Fang Yuan not only had his own Immortal Gu, he also had the Immortal Gu that Immortal Crane Sect had specially lent to him.

Having Immortal Gu was a completely different level of battle strength compared to not having Immortal Gu.

Even though the dragonfish, hidden essence turtle, and nether grass were very strong beings, they did not have Immortal Gu.

If they did, they would be walking treasure troves, Gu Immortals would have attacked already, be it Seven Star Child immortal zombie, or Combat Immortal Sect, how could they not strike?

Normally speaking, inside grotto-heavens and blessed lands, there were no wild Immortal Gu.

Because once a wild Immortal Gu was formed, the Gu Immortal would take them away for their own use.

After all, leaving a wild Immortal Gu behind had no benefits to the blessed land, it would instead cause the Gu Immortal's control of the blessed land or grotto-heaven to fall. If the desolate beast rampages, that would be problematic.

Furthermore, Starry Sky grotto-heaven's owner, Seven Star Child, had awoken long ago, as the owner, how could he not know if there were wild Immortal Gu?

Even if Seven Star Child was kept busy and had no time, Starry Sky grotto-heaven was attacked by Combat Immortal Sect, they had searched thoroughly. Unless it was a very special Immortal Gu and could conceal itself well, it would not be there up until this point.

"According to the map, the dragonfish is here in this blue lake, near the small island at the center of the lake."

Fang Yuan flew in the sky, his gaze shined, his greatest interest among the three was in the desolate beast dragonfish.

Of course, dragonfish lived together in large numbers.

Around the desolate beast dragonfish, there were many mortal dragonfish.

These were all an enticing fortune to Fang Yuan.

"To think that I would have my second desolate beast dragonfish so quickly. Hmm, since I can take one third of the gains, I will choose the dragonfish." Fang Yuan thought of this and felt a bit of joy internally.

Meanwhile, on a small island on the blue lake, a group of Gu Masters from Heaven's Envy Manor were looking at the lake in front of them with much annoyance.

There were five people in this group, almost all of them had rank five cultivation, except one young Gu Master who was at rank four peak stage.

This youngster was called Wei Wu Shang, he was the head of the elite disciples that represented Heaven's Envy Manor.

He was infatuated with Fairy Bi Xia and had once fought with Fang Zheng, but lost. Fang Zheng gave him some face and admitted it was a draw. Since he kept his reputation, he had a sense of gratitude towards Fang Zheng, feeling like he owed the latter a favor.

He was originally rank four middle stage, but in this contest for resources, Heaven's Envy Manor took action to specially raise his cultivation level to rank four peak stage.

On one hand, they were training the next generation of disciples, they were the hopes of the future, on the other hand, they were lacking in manpower.

Just now, to explore all the fragments of Starry Sky grotto-heaven, the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent had engaged in fierce competition.

Seven Star Child was very ruthless, he self-detonated Starry Sky grotto-heaven, but he controlled the explosion very well. Almost no Gu Immortals could enter the fragment worlds, only their disciples could enter and explore it.

As has been mentioned before, these grotto-heaven fragment worlds had sparse dao marks, they were torn and broken, like houses that were going to collapse, they could only exist for a period of time.

Meanwhile, Gu Immortals had dao marks, they were like giants. Forcefully entering the fragment worlds was like giants entering a small house, the only result would be the house breaking and all the resources inside being destroyed.

In his past life, Fang Yuan became a blood path Gu Immortal and created the Blood Wing Demon Sect. When Starry Sky grotto-heaven was destroyed, he also directed mortal Gu Masters in the demonic sect to enter the fragment worlds in place of him and search for resources.

But now, why could Fang Yuan enter it?

Speaking of this, he somewhat did not know whether to laugh or cry at the reason.

It was because Fang Yuan had bottom tier cultivation level among Gu Immortals, he had few strength path dao marks in his body, and because of vaguely familiar face, he continued to lose strength path dao marks.

One of the core Immortal Gu of vaguely familiar face was eat strength Immortal Gu. Changing the Gu Immortal's regional aura involved using eat strength in reverse, to expend strength path dao marks.

Even though he had the giant horned sheep and other strength path desolate beasts to increase his number of strength path dao marks, he had been disguising himself a lot recently, after summing up his gains and losses, there was a limit to how many strength path dao marks he could gain.

Thus, Fang Yuan could enter while other Gu Immortals could not.

He had just reached the upper limits of what the fragment world could stand, there were very few people who could be so pitiful in their cultivation level after becoming a Gu Immortal.

Most importantly, because of his identity, Immortal Crane Sect could make use of him.

This was a competition among the ten great ancient sects, if Fang Yuan was not a subsidiary force of Immortal Crane Sect, he would be an outsider Gu Immortal, he would not be allowed to enter by the other sects.

This was the righteous path.

They paid close attention to rules.

They were not like the demonic path, who looked at who had the bigger fist, by competing with force against force, or seeing who was more ruthless and despicable.

The first rule of the demonic path was the absence of rules.

Chapter 910: Grabbing the Dragonfish

"Damn this Ancient Soul Sect, they actually caused a commotion with the desolate beast dragonfish to obstruct us!"

At this moment, on the small island at the center of the lake, the group from Heaven's Envy Manor's was trapped, they could not advance.

In front of them, waves were rumbling, tides were rising, the water was grand and treacherous.

The five Gu Masters from Heaven's Envy Manor frowned tightly, looking at the lake, they felt anger and helplessness.

Through the lake water, they could see vaguely that there was a huge monster swimming around in the depths of the lake.

Each time the tail moved, currents would be created as huge tides surfaced.

In fact, sometimes, its tough fish head would ram into the bottom of the small island.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

Each time the dragonfish attacked, there would be a loud sound, followed by tremors below everyone's feet.

The people from Heaven's Envy Manor were trapped on this small island, looking at the waves in front of them, their faces were pale, they were helpless, there was nothing they could do.

Desolate beast dragonfish were usually peaceful and rarely went into a frenzy.

But earlier, the Gu Masters from Ancient Soul Sect had used some method to make this desolate beast dragonfish go into madness, it was in a berserk and rampaging state, it had lost its mind and natural disposition.

The Gu Masters from Heaven's Envy Manor had the ability to climb mountains and move across bodies of water, but they were only mortals with limited primeval essence. Under the current situation, they could not move at all, it was too dangerous.

"Ancient Soul Sect could actually influence the desolate beast dragonfish, they must have used an immortal technique from the sect! We of Heaven's Envy Manor are also from one of the ten great ancient sects, we cannot lose to Ancient Soul Sect. Elder Zhu Ning, let's use our immortal method as well!"

While they were helpless, a Gu Master from Heaven's Envy Manor couldn't help but suggest this.

Hearing that there was an immortal method, the other Gu Masters showed inspired expressions, light shining in their eyes.

Elder Zhu Ning, who had the method frowned, he sighed bitterly: "If I could use it, I would have done so already, why would I wait until now?"

He told everyone his difficulties.

As it turned out, before this trip, Zhu Ning was called by a supreme elder and was entrusted with an Immortal Gu and some immortal essence.

But this Immortal Gu was used for defense, it would not help in this situation to get rid of the dragonfish.

"The sect gave you an Immortal Gu?"

"What does the Immortal Gu look like, I have never seen one before!"

"Quick, let us see it and broaden our visions."

Zhu Ning's frank admission made everyone intensely curious. At once, they forget about the problem in front of them, they wanted to see the brilliance of the Immortal Gu.

Zhu Ning smiled bitterly again: "I will speak honestly, I only took a hurried glance at this Immortal Gu before lord supreme elder placed it in my body. Right now, I don't even know where the Immortal Gu is in my body, not to mention attempting to retrieve it."

Everyone was very disappointed, they sighed in unison.

Only Wei Wu Shang's eyes shined brightly, he said in admiration: "It would be great if I could obtain an Immortal Gu that belongs to me one day!"

The other four old Gu Masters looked at Wei Wu Shang and either smiled bitterly or shook their heads.

Wei Wu Shang was too young.

Young people liked to dream, this was natural.

But only after many experiences would they understand that dreams and reality were different, like these four old Gu Masters.

Who would not want to have their own Immortal Gu, who would not want to become a high and mighty immortal?

But immortal and mortal were worlds apart. Reality was cruel, countless people lost their youthfulness, countless people's dreams were broken.

How many people could really become immortals?

The leader, Zhu Ning, sighed: "For now, we have no better way, we can only wait. When the dragonfish calms down, we will set off."

"But this way, the other nine sects will get all the good stuff. We will only have leftovers!" A Gu Master asked worriedly.

"What else can we do?" Zhu Ning sighed, but he did not forget to raise the morale: "This is not entirely a bad thing. Let them go and compete first, we can take the chance for now to gather our strength. Even though Immortal Gu are incredibly powerful, they need corresponding immortal essence to activate. Their immortal essence will be limited, let them exhaust their resources in competing with each other, during the later stages, we will have more strength than them."

Once he said that, everyone's expressions changed, their dejected moods recovered slightly.

"However, I have something very important to remind you of." Zhu Ning's had a serious expression: "No matter how much strength we preserve, there are two people we cannot offend. One is Spirit Affinity House's Feng Jin Huang, the other is Immortal Crane Sect's Fang Yuan."

"Why? Feng Jin Huang and Fang Yuan are two geniuses of my generation, but each of them are only single individuals. Right now, us ten sects all have five members each, we all have mysterious immortal methods, why should we be afraid of those two?" Wei Wu Shang was unclear of the truth, he asked somewhat skeptically.

"That is because you do not know the hidden details." Zhu Ning's gaze was heavy, he looked at the surrounding Gu Masters and said: "I learned about this shocking news from the sect before we came. Feng Jin Huang has a noble upbringing, her parents are both Gu Immortals, moreover, they are immensely powerful beings even among Gu Immortals. What shocking immortal methods do you think that such a person would have?"

"So that's it!" Wei Wu Shang was startled.

The others also showed shocked expressions.

Zhu Ning continued: "But compared to Feng Jin Huang, that Fang Yuan is even scarier!"

"Don't tell me his background is even greater than that of Feng Jin Huang?" Someone asked in suspicion.

Zhu Ning frowned: "I am also not sure of the specific details, but the sect had specially told this to me, that Fang Yuan is far scarier than Feng Jin Huang, we should avoid him at all costs, we should not contest with him."

"Even though Fang Yuan is the number one genius of my generation, he's not that scary, right?" Wei Wu Shang was suspicious.

"Don't tell me the immortal method that Immortal Crane Sect gave to him is the strongest among the ten sects?" The other Gu Masters tried to analyze.

Zhu Ning shook his head: "I only know that Immortal Crane Sect sent Fang Yuan here alone, think about it, what does this mean?"

"It seems that Immortal Crane Sect is very confident in Fang Yuan, they believe that with his strength alone, he can deal with all of us!"

"Arrogant! They are looking down on us..."

"Immortal Crane Sect are not fools, the sect also told us to avoid Fang Yuan, there seems to be reasons behind this. We should act according to the sect's warnings."

"That is not necessarily the case, as the saying goes, two fists cannot rival four palms, even if Fang Yuan is the strongest, he would inevitably cause the other sects to collaborate in resistance. The result is still unknown."

The Gu Masters discussed.

They talked one after another.

Some were stable and conservative, some were indignant, some wanted to collaborate with other sects.

Right at this moment, a shrill sound came from the sky.

Everyone frowned, Wei Wu Shang even covered his ears.

The five Gu Masters looked over and saw that in the sky, there was a figure tearing across space.

This person was extremely fast, sonic booms could be heard as they traveled.

In just a breath's time, he flew over from a distance away.

When he was above the small island, he stopped. He went from quick movement to extreme stillness, the five Gu Masters from Heaven's Envy Manor felt this was very abrupt and sudden.

"Who is it? He can fly at such a high altitude!"

"So fast, is this a human or a monster?"

"Looking at the person, it seems to be... Fang Yuan?"

Everyone was shocked and subconsciously had their mouths open.

The gusts of wind blew and entered their mouths, even forcing them to shut their eyes.

This wind was created when Fang Yuan flew over, it was very strong.

Fang Yuan stood in the air as he looked around.

Huge waves, a small island, dragonfish, Gu Masters, he understood everything that was happening in an instant.

He placed his attention on the dragonfish.

There were five Gu Masters on the small island, they were not worth his attention at all.

The wind was only a gust, it came and left swiftly.

The five Gu Masters quickly opened their eyes, looking at Fang Yuan who was in the air, they were very nervous.

"It seems that this dragonfish is rampaging due to the effects of a certain soul path or wisdom path technique." Fang Yuan guessed as he stretched out his hand and made a grabbing motion in front of him.

Boom!

Under everyone's shocked gazes, a strength path giant hand flew out and entered the water grandly.

But the thing was, when the strength path giant hand entered the water, there were no waves that were created.

Instead, the water split apart when the giant hand descended, it was as if the water in the lake was cooperating with Fang Yuan.

This was the strength path Immortal Gu Pulling Water, it had taken effect after being fused into strength path giant hand.

The water in the lake did not obstruct Fang Yuan in capturing the dragonfish, it became an aid instead.

With the dragonfish rampaging and losing its senses, it did not try to escape, it made Fang Yuan's attempting at capturing it easier.

Roar!

The dragonfish opened its mouth, emitting a dragon's roar.

On the two sides of the fish's mouth, there were two long dragon whiskers, they were lashing around like whips.

The entire fish body struggled intensely, but the strength path giant hand was stable like Mount Tai, it did not budge at all, like an iron structure.

Under Fang Yuan's control, the strength path giant hand grabbed and captured the dragonfish, pulling it out of the water.

The five Gu Masters from Heaven's Envy Manor were all dumbfounded, they were shocked and in despair at seeing the process of Fang Yuan capturing the dragonfish and putting it into his own immortal aperture.

After capturing this desolate beast dragonfish, Fang Yuan was not satisfied, he turned towards the ordinary dragonfish.

Dragonfish lived in groups, there were dragonfish all over this lake.

This time, Fang Yuan activated pulling water Immortal Gu, lumps of water was pulled up, countless dragonfish that were inside the water were thrown into his immortal aperture.

The group from Heaven's Envy Manor were staring, still as statues.

They would surely never forget this scene in their lives.

Only until Fang Yuan finished his collection and flew away did these Gu Masters jolt to awareness.

They were all covered in sweat, Wei Wu Shang was sprawled on the ground, sitting with his body limp and in shock.

They had finally understood what their sect meant, and the helplessness they were feeling.

"Dealing with such a person is beyond our abilities."

"Oh heavens, I was trying to collaborate with others to deal with Fang Yuan earlier?!"

"Such overwhelming might, did he become an immortal already?!"

Everyone was scared to pieces.

The dragonfish was gone, they could continue on their journey now.

But the scene earlier was simply too shocking for them, even though they did not move at all and were only looking, the Gu Masters from Heaven's Envy Manor were breathing roughly, they felt extremely fatigued in both body and mind.

Chapter 911: Contest of Dream Realm

"About six hundred thousand ordinary dragonfish, and a desolate beast dragonfish."

Fang Yuan flew rapidly while calculating the profits in his immortal aperture.

The first move he made after coming in this Starry Sky grotto-heaven fragment world gave him a huge harvest.

The only blemish was a lot of ordinary dragonfish had died. Because of the desolate beast dragonfish's rampage, many ordinary dragonfish that normally surrounded the desolate beast dragonfish died miserably.

Otherwise, Fang Yuan's gains would be even greater.

Regardless, Fang Yuan was satisfied.

Back then at Dong Fang tribe's headquarters, he only gained around nine hundred thousand ordinary dragonfish and a desolate beast dragonfish. His current gains already were over half of this. If these were to be added to Hu Immortal blessed land's dragon scale lake, its size would not be enough to contain these dragonfish.

"When the truth of the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building comes to light, I must abandon Hu Immortal blessed land, so there is no need to expand the dragon scale lake. It seems when I return after this, I must remodel Star Form blessed land to raise these dragonfish."

Fang Yuan was looking around his surroundings as he pondered.

He had unlimited primeval essence and also had countless investigative mortal killer moves, there was even a recently obtained investigative immortal killer move — Star Premonition.

Thus, he was not worried that he would miss any good things on his way.

However, Fang Yuan did not find many opportunities to take action.

When Starry Sky grotto-heaven was intact, it was already looted repeatedly by Combat Immortal Sect. Now, among the remaining resources, those that could interest Fang Yuan were already very few. Moreover, he had to hand over two-thirds of all the gains he made in this trip to Immortal Crane Sect, while he himself could only obtain one-third. This greatly impacted Fang Yuan's enthusiasm.

"The ten ancient sects sent the disciples to compete for various resources inside within a limited time - seven days and seven nights. After this time passes, the resources occupied inside will be divided up, next would be time for the ten ancient sects to plunder and develop the resources by themselves. This has nothing to do with me. So now, I only need to get the desolate beast dragonfish, hidden essence turtle and that nether grass. Most of my energy and time should be used to search for that dream realm in the central region!"

When he thought of the dream realm, Fang Yuan's gaze shined and a fire burned inside him.

Before leaving, He Feng Yang had reminded Fang Yuan to occupy the central region as early as possible.

In the center of this fragment world was an external manifestation of a dream realm.

As it involved the prophecy of Great Dream Immortal Venerable, the ten great ancient sects had already begun researching. Moreover, Feng Jin Huang possessed dream wings Immortal Gu, which allowed Spirit Affinity House to firmly occupy the leading position.

More importantly, this dream realm had a huge origin.

It was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm!

Immortal Crane Sect's research of dream realms might be completely behind Spirit Affinity House, but as long as they were able to seize this dream realm, they could contain Spirit Affinity House's momentum, and could rely on this dream realm to make terms and exchange benefits with Spirit Affinity House.

In the entire fragment world, the most precious resource was not desolate beasts or desolate plants, instead it was this small external manifestation of a dream realm!

Thus, before they parted, He Feng Yang specially reminded Fang Yuan of this matter.

But how could he know the excitement inside Fang Yuan?

Fang Yuan might not be like Feng Jin Huang with dream path Immortal Gu, but he had a wisdom path Immortal Gu, Unravel Mystery, and the dream path killer move formed with it as the basis — Unravel Dream!

He Feng Yang inviting Fang Yuan to represent Immortal Crane Sect was simply like opening the door to a thief or bringing a weasel to a chicken coop.

"Immortal Crane Sect does not have enough strength, they had decided to send me now, but this was met with strong resistance from the other nine sects. In the end, although Immortal Crane Sect got what they wished, my entry time was far later than the other nine sects. I must hurry and occupy the central region, after all, undue delay may bring trouble."

Capturing the dragonfish was only done casually on his way, the most important matter was still the external manifestation of the dream realm in the central region.

However, when Fang Yuan reached his destination, someone was already there.

"Fang Yuan, I have been waiting for quite a while." Feng Jin Huang led four other Gu Masters of Spirit Affinity House to protect the magnificent dream realm behind them.

She looked at this trip's strongest competitor. Her skin was snow white, her appearance as pretty as a painting, her smile was beautiful and she looked extremely confident.

Fang Yuan was not anxious, as he replied with a smile as well: "According to the rules set by the ten great sects, for your Spirit Affinity House to completely occupy this area, you need to face the challenges from other sects. Only after winning two out of three challenges can you strip away the opponent's right to occupy this area."

The ten great ancient sects were famous righteous sects of Central Continent, but they also had the same origin — Heavenly Court.

Thus, although they were competing, it was not a cruel slaughter like that of the demonic path, and was much gentler.

Feng Jin Huang shook her head: "Although I have Immortal Gu and immortal essence that mother placed on me, I cannot defeat you. I waited for you to do a transaction."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's brows raised as he said, coldly, "You want to do a transaction with me again? Last time, you scammed me quite heavily at the Refinement Path Convention. The method you gave me for getting rid of the immortal zombie status was actually an ascension of the ten extreme physiques! You still want to do another transaction?"

Feng Jin Huang quickly replied: "This transaction will be mutually beneficial, Fang Yuan, you have also taken quite a lot of benefits from my Spirit Affinity House. You can rest assured that I won't let you suffer losses in this transaction."

"Alright, then speak." Fang Yuan nodded.

Feng Jin Huang immediately gave a suggestion of what to trade, it was actually another method to get rid of the immortal zombie status!

She had completely seen through Fang Yuan's weak point, and did not let go of it.

After confirming that Feng Jin Huang's method was not what he already had, Fang Yuan agreed to this transaction.

Like Feng Jin Huang said, this transaction was mutually beneficial, having benefits to both sides. And if there were benefits, Fang Yuan would naturally take it.

Shortly afterwards, Fang Yuan obtained a completely new method of getting rid of the immortal zombie state and reviving.

This was a transformation path method.

According to Feng Jin Huang's words, Fang Yuan would have to cultivate transformation path and use a transformation path killer move to transform himself into a normal Gu Immortal. Then, he could use everlasting Immortal Gu to make this transformation fixed and unchangeable.

Like this, he could get rid of the immortal zombie status.

This was indeed a practical thought.

Because a lot of Gu Masters or Gu Immortals in their cultivation journeys would face an awkward and tragic situation of not being able to go back to their original shape after transforming too many times.

And this method was the exact opposite, it thoroughly finalized the transformation.

As for this dream realm, it would be occupied by Fang Yuan.

But Feng Jin Huang had three days to explore this external manifestation of a dream realm. Three days later, she had to leave this area.

"This is a dream realm's external manifestation?" Fang Yuan mumbled as he looked ahead of him, as if this was the first time he had seen it, his expression was serious, curious and his gaze revealing some greed and fervent passion.

Every external manifestation of dream realm had a wonderfully beautiful appearance.

This dream realm that was displayed in front of them was like a condensed star cloud, with dark purple light shining in the periphery and countless stars inside.

The whole dream realm gave off a profound, mysterious aura, and also gave indications of danger.

Feng Jin Huang looked on at Fang Yuan's eager expression, coldly snorting inwardly with satisfaction.

She had seen this kind of expression many times.

"Dream realms are good, but it is a pity you don't have dream wings Immortal Gu. This enormous benefit is placed right beside your mouth, but you can't eat it. Maybe in your whole life, you won't understand that feeling of exploring a dream realm. Ah, there is also the huge advancement after a smooth exploration."

Feng Jin Huang did not remind Fang Yuan, if Fang Yuan died in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm, it would be much more beneficial for her.

However, she knew that it was not likely to happen.

Since Immortal Crane Sect sent Fang Yuan, they would have reminded him of the dangers of the dream realm.

Sure enough, Feng Jin Huang waited for a while but only saw Fang Yuan standing on the spot without moving forward, although he had a longing look on his face, he did not take a step beyond the limit.

Feng Jin Huang snorted inwardly before turning towards the other four Gu Masters: "Three days is a limited span of time, I need to explore this dream realm immediately. All of you, protect my physical body, don't make any mistakes."

The Gu Masters quickly replied: "We will use up all our strength and even if we die, we will protect you to the end!"

"Lady Feng Jin Huang, you can enter at ease, if the situation is urgent, we will immediately awaken you."

Feng Jin Huang nodded, and stepped towards the dream realm.

When she was still twenty or so steps away from the dream realm, she had reached her limit. With her current ability, she still could not completely throw herself into the dream realm.

She gave a last look at the distant Fang Yuan, before slowly sitting down cross-legged on the ground, she closed her eyes and activated dream wings Immortal Gu, falling into a deep sleep.

As far as Feng Jin Huang was concerned, the greatest threat to her was the immortal zombie Fang Yuan.

Were Fang Yuan to act against her, those rank five Gu Masters of Spirit Affinity House would simply be incapable of resisting him.

Thus, Feng Jin Huang did not completely rely on these four Gu Masters, what she placed confidence in was the Immortal Gu and abundant immortal essence her mother, Fairy Bai Qing, had placed with her.

"Dream wings Immortal Gu...." Fang Yuan looked at Feng Jin Huang with envy.

Dream wings Immortal Gu could let the user fall into a deep sleep at any time, and attach dream wings to their soul, letting them roam freely in dream realms, allowing them to advance or retreat freely, guaranteeing their safety.

Compared to dream travel Immortal Gu, dream wings Immortal Gu had an advantage, it did not require immortal essence to be activated, thus it was the most suitable for cultivators like Feng Jin Huang who had yet to become Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan already had thoughts of taking action.

But killing Feng Jin Huang and seizing dream wings Immortal Gu was not a practical idea.

Seizing Immortal Gu by itself was an extremely difficult matter. And killing Feng Jin Huang was also not easy, even an idiot would know Feng Jin Huang certainly had large numbers of life protection methods on her.

Most importantly, the current situation had yet to turn to a critical state, there was still space to scheme. Fang Yuan was not a retard, he would not make such a huge mistake.

"This Feng Jin Huang is maturing rapidly. First was the transaction, she handed over all the control of this dream realm to me of her own accord, turning me into a shield, to block other competitors in her place, while she uses dream wings Immortal Gu to wantonly explore the dream realm and plunder benefits. Next, when she saw me have a desire to explore, she did not give me any reminders, waiting to see me make a fool of myself. However, regardless of how talented you are, you would not think that I possess the killer move unravel dream."

Fang Yuan sneered as he let out the desolate beast shark fin wolf from his immortal aperture.

This desolate beast wolf had been violently subdued by him through flicking its penis.

For this exploration of the fragment world, Fang Yuan had already taken it out from Hu Immortal blessed land and brought it with him.

The moment they saw the desolate beast, Spirit Affinity House's four Gu Masters were tongue-tied with shock, they were even about to awaken Feng Jin Huang.

It was Fang Yuan who reminded them: "No need to be anxious, this desolate beast will look after this place. Three days later, if all of you have not left, it will eat you alive."

With this warning, Fang Yuan flew to the sky, quickly leaving the vision of the Gu Masters of Spirit Affinity House.

Chapter 912: Beastman

Fang Yuan landed after flying far away.

He took out a large batch of rockmen from his immortal aperture.

Be it in Hu Immortal blessed land or Star Form blessed land, he raised batches of rockmen.

Fang Yuan took half of them and brought them along, right now, he let them out to be used as helpers.

"We greet lord immortal." The rockmen saw Fang Yuan and paid respects.

Fang Yuan responded with a grunt, his expression was cold and he appeared high and mighty, above the masses.

He gave these rockmen instructions to collect resources before leaving, concealing his figure and returning to the dream realm.

These rockmen were elites, there were many Gu worms on their bodies.

These were all specially arranged by Fang Yuan.

These rockmen were all armed by Fang Yuan, their battle strength were greatly raised, because they moved in groups of ten, even if they encountered groups from other sects, Fang Yuan was not worried that the rockmen would lose.

Or rather, even if the rockmen lost, Fang Yuan would not feel loss.

This was only a facade.

The manifested dream realm was like a small hill's size.

Fang Yuan concealed his figure and carefully went to the back, entering the dream realm.

Last time, Fang Yuan was inside the eighth star hall of Starry Sky grotto-heaven, he was at the border of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm and almost died. After detonating his bat wings, he managed to struggle his way out.

This time, he went in purposely, because he had the killer move unravel dream, his power was much higher, times were different now.

His vision changed.

Fang Yuan entered Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm!

It was night.

Fire was burning, rising to the sky.

Countless brawny beastmen were surrounding a huge fire, dancing around it.

Growl growl growl...

Roar roar roar...

Among these beastmen, some had faces of tigers and human bodies, they opened their mouths and growled angrily. Some had eagle beaks, they shrieked loudly. Some had a leopard's tail growing from their backs, they danced around and moved alongside the lingering shadows.

"This is... the beastman race that got wiped out from existence during the Olden Antiquity Era?" Fang Yuan came back to awareness, he understood the origins of these beastmen.

Beastmen were a type of variant human.

During the Remote Antiquity Era, as well as the Immemorial Antiquity Era, they were one of the strongest variant human races in the world.

Beastmen had incredible battle strength, they worshipped fierce beasts, and adopted their ferocity and ruthlessness.

Especially when they could attract wild transformation path Gu worms to live in them, allowing them to transform into a half-man half-beast state, they would gain a part of the fierce beasts' abilities and strength.

As time passed, humans began to rise up. During the Remote Antiquity Era, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable appeared, leading humans to resist the rule of variant humans, establishing the authority of humans. By the Olden Antiquity Era, three human Demon Venerables appeared, creating wars and exterminating the beastmen race, stabilizing the status of humans as the rulers.

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable was a rank nine Gu Immortal from the Remote Antiquity Era, at that time, humans were fighting with various variant humans, and were fighting to control the world. This is indeed Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan was slightly excited.

He looked around, and found that he was a human boy in this dream.

He was tied up by a rope, the other end of the rope was tightly tied to a tree trunk.

There were over a dozen humans who were tied up like Fang Yuan, they were all young children.

"Oh no! Beastmen are bloodthirsty by nature, they were also known as the man-eating race. History states that the favorite food of beastmen are the flesh and blood of human children. Beastmen tribes all treat surrounding humans as food, they would go out to hunt occasionally. When they succeed in their hunts, they would hold a huge celebration by a bonfire."

Fang Yuan sensed the dangerous situation, he struggled intensely, but the rope was getting tighter.

His body had bloodstains because of the friction with the ropes, intense pain was assaulting his body.

"It is no use, the more you struggle, the more painful it gets."

"We are doomed, we are dead meat!"

"Wuwuwu... I don't want to be eaten."

The surrounding human children saw that Fang Yuan was struggling, some advised him indifferently, while others cried in despair.

Just as the bonfire celebration reached its climax, the beastman leader shouted: "Come, bring up our most delectable food!"

Growl growl growl!

The beastmen raised their heads, shouting.

An elephantman who was six meters tall stood up from his sitting position.

He stretched out his long and powerful trunk as he pulled up the entire tree that held the ropes that tied the children.

The tree trunk was raised high in the air.

The children who were tied up resembled tiny pearls as they screamed in fear, hanging in the air.

The beastmen shouted again, the elephantman who had shown off his might laughed loudly, his trunk loosened and the tree trunk was slammed onto the ground.

The children could not free themselves, they fell as well. Some unlucky children were crushed to death by the tree.

An intense smell of blood spread out.

Some beastmen could not control their bloodthirsty desire, they jumped in and grabbed the children's corpses, putting them into their mouths.

"Delicious!"

"Human children taste tender and delicious, hahaha."

As they spoke, the beastmen showed a sense of wildness and ruthlessness.

The blazing bonfire crackled, the surrounding beastmen stared excitedly with red, wide open eyes, towards these lucky children who survived.

Some were growling, some had uneven fangs, some stretched out their bright red tongues, they licked their lips as they drooled, the amber light of the fire was reflecting in their eyes.

The children screamed out in fright, some had fainted on the spot.

But Fang Yuan found that one girl was expressionless. Even though her body was shivering, and her expression was pale as paper, she bit her lips, she did not make a sound.

"Is it possible that she..." Fang Yuan's heart jumped, he had a flash of inspiration.

Before this inspiration was processed, the beastman leader walked towards Fang Yuan and the others with an intensely ferocious aura, he looked down arrogantly at these weak children.

As the light flickered, lots of children watched with fearful gazes, the beastman leader had a black face and sharp fangs, he spoke slowly: "According to the traditions of our tribe, those that can untie the wind knot grass are people blessed by heaven, they can be spared from death. Those who fail to untie it, hehehe, they can be honored to become the food of us noble beastmen!"

The moment he said that, the beastman leader waved his tail.

From the flickering light, a bright flash occurred.

The ropes were cut, the human children obtained temporary freedom in movement.

Wind knot grass?

Seeing the pile of dried grass that the beastmen brought over, Fang Yuan was curious.

The wind knot grass was like a lantern, a round ball-shaped grass lantern, it was very rare to see in modern times.

There was no wind knot grass in the five regions, this was a type of grass only found in green heaven of the immemorial nine heavens.

Ren Zu's ten children destroyed the immemorial nine heavens, causing fragments of immemorial green heaven to fall into the five regions.

During Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's era, many fragment worlds of the immemorial nine heavens fell into different areas of the five regions.

The beastmen worshipped the heavenly deities, their tribal belief was that whoever could untie the wind knot grass was blessed by the heavens, they were precious beings that could not be harmed.

"That means, as long as I can untie the wind knot grass, I can be spared from death?" Fang Yuan's thoughts moved rapidly.

He had turned into a child after entering this dream realm, he was not even thirteen years old yet, his aperture was not awakened yet, he had no power. To free himself from this predicament, he could only follow the beastman rules and untie wind knot grass alone.

Even though he knew it was a dream realm, it was not favorable to die inside the dream.

This meant he would be consumed by the dream realm.

Each time he got consumed, even though he would not die, his soul would suffer a huge injury.

If his soul got injured too often, it would get weak, when he reached his limits, his soul would break down and dissipate, even if his body was still around, he would die.

This was the danger of exploring dream realms!

Soon, each child received their wind knot grass.

Knowing that this was their only chance at survival, the children opened their eyes wide and used every second they had to try and untie the wind knot grass.

The surrounding beastmen were laughing coldly or grinding their teeth, some were licking their lips or polishing their claws, they surrounded Fang Yuan's group and watched sinisterly.

The human children were in the center, surrounded by countless savage beastmen.

Using the light of the bonfire, the children gathered their concentration and placed their efforts on the grass lanterns.

Fang Yuan observed carefully.

This type of grass lantern was made from all sorts of roots, leaves, and stems, they were intertwined together and formed into a mysterious ball.

"Only in immemorial green heaven would there be winds blowing all year around, at strange directions and angles. Countless plants would be uprooted or shaved until they were bare, these twigs would intertwine in the wind and slowly form into this ball shaped grass lantern."

Because time was limited, the surrounding children were trying to untie their wind knot grass.

Only Fang Yuan did not start immediately, this was the first time he was seeing the wind knot grass, he was assessing it.

His unique demeanor attracted the attention of the beastmen, he even attracted the attention of Feng Jin Huang as well.

Feng Jin Huang was also inside the dream realm, similar to Fang Yuan, she was also a child.

Fang Yuan looked very calm and radiated with confidence, his body was covered in dirt and dust, his gender could not be discerned, Feng Jin Huang had a misunderstanding: "What's going on with this child? Is she Star Constellation Immortal Venerable?"

Roar!

Right at this moment, a tiger headed beastman roared loudly with excitement.

He grabbed a human boy rapidly and threw him into his mouth.

Crack, crack...

He opened his mouth and chewed, eating half of the boy in an instant.

"What are you looking at! He ruined a wind knot grass, he had already failed. It is only natural for me to eat him!" Looking at the surrounding unfriendly gazes, the tiger headed beastman growled, there was the blood and flesh of the boy stuck in the middle of his teeth.

With this stimulation, the surrounding beastmen were stirred up, their eyes shined with ruthlessness as they looked at the remaining children.

"Daddy, daddy, where are you? Quickly come and save me!" A girl broke down, she held the wind knot grass as she cried loudly.

"Damn it, why is my wind knot grass so hard to untie?"

"No, I must succeed. I can do it! I have played with this wind knot grass a lot in the past."

The surrounding beastmen did not want the children to succeed, they got closer and closer.

They had ill intentions, they purposely growled and threatened, or breathed roughly to interrupt the children.

"Scoundrel, get away from me, you stink!" Feng Jin Huang flew into a rage, she shouted at a crocodile tail beastman.

The crocodile tailed beastman growled angrily, it stared at Feng Jin Huang with its bloodshot eyes, it did not expect this food to be so arrogant.

Feng Jin Huang had no fear: "What are you growling for, so annoying, you bastard!"

Bam.

The crocodile tailed beastman erupted, its tail which was tough as iron swept and directly destroyed Feng Jin Huang's skull!

Chapter 913: Dream Wings, Unravel Dream

Once Feng Jin Huang died, her soul flew into the night sky, giggling tenderly.

On the back of her soul, a pair of rainbow colored feather wings unfolded.

It was the manifestation of dream wings Immortal Gu!

"I have dream wings Immortal Gu, I can freely enter and exit the dream realm. Even if I failed this time, I can just wait for the next attempt at the dream realm, and try again." Feng Jin Huang snorted smugly internally.

She had tried earlier, the wind knot grass in her hands had already been ruined by her, the knot was even worse than at the beginning.

But when Feng Jin Huang was about to escape by flapping her wings, an eagle bodied beastman pounced down from the sky.

Feng Jin Huang shrieked in fear, she wanted to dodge.

But the wings that could flap rapidly ordinarily were extremely slow when they tried to move in this dream realm.

Feng Jin Huang had underestimated Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm, it was much more hard to deal with, her soul was crushed by the eagle bodied beastman before she could escape!

With just one hit, Feng Jin Huang's soul was heavily injured.

At the next moment, Feng Jin Huang left the dream realm, her soul returned to her body.

Puff!

She opened her eyes and spat out a mouthful of blood.

The Gu Masters from Spirit Affinity House were shocked, they quickly came over to assist her.

"What a formidable dream realm! If I were to take another hit like that one earlier, I would definitely die inside the dream for real." Feng Jin Huang's eyes were flashing with lingering fear, cold sweat was pouring down her back.

"I was careless! Even though I have dream wings Immortal Gu, against the dream realm of an Immortal Venerable, I am not safe at all. Thankfully, I had prepared a large number of guts Gu and brought it with me. With guts Gu, my soul will recover rapidly. In half a day, I will heal completely." Feng Jin Huang wiped the cold sweat off her forehead as she stopped wasting time, she quickly started healing herself.

In the dream realm, Fang Yuan directed his gaze towards the wind knot grass again.

Feng Jin Huang's earlier performance gave Fang Yuan quite a bit of information.

"This dream realm is not large in scale, this current scene is only the outer layer of the dream realm, this is an Immortal Venerable's dream after all, even with the rank six dream wings Immortal Gu, she could not escape immediately. Now it seems, the crux of this dream realm is the wind knot grass in my hands."

Fang Yuan had a realization.

After he finished his observations, he started to untie the wind knot grass.

He first tried to untie it from the outermost layer.

He felt like he was facing a complex and tangled ball of string. He needed to find the outer tip of the string and pull it out slowly strand by strand.

At the third layer, Fang Yuan could not continue further.

It was a complete mess in front of him, the stalks were intertwined together, he could not untie it manually.

"To untie the wind knot grass without using brute strength, not only would I need confidence and good perception, I need to deduce it with my brain, I also need patience and ample time most importantly, along with some luck."

Fang Yuan sighed to himself inwardly.

He had opened a path in this wind knot grass, but this path was stuck at the third layer.

There was a way out for him now, that was to retreat by two layers and try to untie this from another end.

Other people could only do this as well.

But there was an exception.

Fang Yuan looked around and noticed that the girl he suspected was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had already untied the seventh layer.

The wind knot grass had shrunken in half in her hands.

"Without using any wisdom path Gu worms, using purely her brain power, she reached this stage?" Fang Yuan was shocked.

Even though he had been late at starting to unite the wind knot grass, the difference between them was still too great.

Fang Yuan squinted, he concealed the brilliance shining in his eyes.

In terms of untying ability, Fang Yuan was only at the middle to upper tier among the children.

In terms of progress, he was at the middle to lower tier.

More than half the time had passed already.

Looking at the speed of the children, the only one with any hopes of escaping was the girl who he thought was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

But Fang Yuan had ample confidence, he believed that not only could he succeed, he would even surpass everyone and become the first.

What gave him confidence was none other than the dream path immortal killer move — Unravel Dream!

Unravel dream activated.

The intertwined strands in front of him slowly melted, they untied themselves.

The surrounding beastmen were watching this, especially a snake beastman behind Fang Yuan, it was observing the entire process.

But they did not say anything, or take any action.

This was the mystical power of unravel dream.

It was not an offensive killer move purely, its effect varied according to the dream he was in.

For example, if Fang Yuan was fighting inside a dream realm, unravel dream would be his strongest attacking method. If the dream realm was weak, he could directly disintegrate his enemies.

Right now, the dream realm's rules were for Fang Yuan to untie the wind knot grass. Then, unravel dream's current effect was to help Fang Yuan and untie the wind knot grass.

This untying was according to the set rules, it was not unraveled through brute force.

In the eyes of the surrounding children and the observing beastmen, Fang Yuan was not cheating at all, he was using his brain and successfully untying the third layer of the wind knot grass.

Thus, they did not do anything, even the snake person that wanted to eat Fang Yuan only watched with a slightly surprised expression, it felt that it was somewhat unexpected that Fang Yuan could untie three layers.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

Fang Yuan continued his momentum and did not stop. The wind knot grass in his hands was quickly untied, he reached the center.

At the core of the wind knot grass, there was a seed.

This was the self-defense mechanism of the plants in immemorial green heaven, as well as a way to use the wind for dispersal.

Fang Yuan took out the seed, standing up and raising it high.

"He, he succeeded!"

"This speed is too fast!!"

"I am begging you, help me, okay?"

The surrounding people were stirred up, even the girl who he suspected to be Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gave him a surprised gaze.

"You are free, little thing, I will give you three days to escape for your life, scram now." The leader of the beastman tribe snorted, kicking Fang Yuan and sending him flying.

Fang Yuan's tiny body flew in the air for a distance of more than ten steps before crashing on the ground.

What made Fang Yuan surprised was, even though he felt a little short of breath from getting kicked, he was uninjured.

The beastman leader was strong and powerful, but in terms of physical movements, it had reached the stage of perfect self control.

Since Fang Yuan had untied the wind knot grass, the beastman tribe had to let him go.

Fang Yuan gaze a glance at the little girl, the latter had already gathered her attention to the wind knot grass in her hands.

Fang Yuan hesitated slightly, before turning around and leaving.

He left the bonfire, walking towards the darkness in the forest.

He only took a dozen steps before there was a bright light shining in the darkness.

The more he walked forward, the brighter the light, eventually, all of the darkness in front of him turned into light.

The light faded slowly, and the scene of reality showed itself in front of him.

Fang Yuan realized that not only did he open his eyes, his body had walked for over a dozen steps, away from the manifested dream realm.

Looking back at the dream realm, Fang Yuan frowned deeply, he was very confused: "What is going on? I left the dream realm just like that?"

He thought it over.

This exploration of the dream realm did not fail.

His wisdom path attainment level had risen slightly.

"This should not be! According to the scale of this dream realm, there should be three scenes. I got through the first round, why did I not enter the second round successfully?"

Fang Yuan stood on the spot as he pondered.

The light emitted by the manifested dream realm shined on his face.

He left the dream realm and returned on the same route from which he entered. On the other side of the dream realm, Spirit Affinity House's group was still trying to heal Feng Jin Huang urgently.

Thus, Fang Yuan was not exposed.

But if he could not understand why he left the dream realm, there was a possibility that he might walk towards Spirit Affinity House's direction the next time he left it.

If others found out that Fang Yuan could explore the dream realm, it would be somewhat troublesome.

After a long time, Fang Yuan's tight frown gradually eased.

He walked forwards and let the dream realm engulf him.

His vision changed, Fang Yuan had entered Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm again.

Dark night, bonfire, beastmen, children, wind knot grass, the same scene was unfolding again.

Using unravel dream, Fang Yuan cheated all the way, becoming the first to untie the wind knot grass.

But this time, he did not leave, he walked towards the girl who he thought was Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and tried to help her untie her wind knot grass.

The beastman leader did not object, he said: "Little rascal, you still want to help others? Hehe, you can help her, but if you fail, you will lose your life!"

"It seems my guess is correct." Fang Yuan was overjoyed, he untied the wind knot grass within the time limit and successfully escaped with the girl.

"What? I still left?" Fang Yuan looked back in surprise.

His second attempt still failed. Fang Yuan did not enter the second scene, he was thrown out of the dream realm like the first time.

Dream realms were unpredictable and strange, their rules varied. Because each dream realm was unique, it was hard to accumulate experience in exploring the dream realm. Even though Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories, his advantage was still very small.

"This time, after saving the girl, my wisdom path attainment went up more than last time..." Fang Yuan muttered.

He went into deep contemplation.

According to this situation, there were two possibilities.

One, the girl that he saved was not the real Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Two, he had to save more children, after he hit a certain number, he would enter the second scene.

Before he entered the dream realm for a third time, Fang Yuan rested slightly first.

He took out guts Gu and healed his weakened soul back to its prime.

Even though he had successfully escaped the dream realm and did a successful exploration, his soul was not unharmed, he still expended a lot of it in the dream realm.

Of course, Fang Yuan's soul was far less injured than Feng Jin Huang's.

The former had succeeded, while the latter's exploration failed, this was incomparable.

"Third time!" Fang Yuan spurring himself on inwardly, he entered the dream realm again.

Everything restarted again in the dream.

The moment the wind knot grass was distributed, Fang Yuan used the killer move unravel dream several times and in a few breaths' time, he untied the wind knot grass in his hand.

Fang Yuan grabbed onto the seed as he raised up his right hand, shouting: "I succeeded!"

At once, be it the beastmen or children, they stared with wide open eyes as they looked at Fang Yuan in shock.

The noisy scene turned into creepy silence.

Chapter 914: Huge Growth in Attainment Level

"I will help you!" After Fang Yuan untied his wind knot grass, he went to the child closest to him.

"Hehe, rascal, you still want to help others? Sure! But you..." The beastman leader snickered.

Before he finished his words, he was interrupted by Fang Yuan.

"I know, if I can't save them, I will not leave, you can eat me!" Fang Yuan waved his hand, speaking casually.

"Guh..." The beastman leader choked up on his words, he could not say anything else.

The surrounding children looked at Fang Yuan with hopeful and admiring gazes, as if they were looking at a hero.

"Lad, if you can save them all, I will step down as the leader!" The beastman leader smiled sinisterly.

But soon, he could not smile anymore.

Fang Yuan did not follow the script, he used unravel dream continuously at an incredible pace!

All of the captured children were saved one after another.

If he were to untie the wind knot grass through his own efforts, he would not even be able to save himself.

But after using unravel dream, the difficulty fell immensely.

To make a comparison, this was like playing mahjong, where everyone else was drawing random tiles, while Fang Yuan was changing the tiles to whatever he wanted.

From everyone else's perspective, this sort of cheating behavior looked like Fang Yuan moving his fingers rapidly, no matter which wind knot grass he held, after turning it a few times over, it would be untied rapidly, until the seed was taken out from its centermost position.

So simple.

Simply too easy.

This was the power of the dream path killer move unravel dream!

The children's eyes were shining with tears, they looked at Fang Yuan as their gazes was filled with unparalleled gratitude and adoration.

The beastmen opened their mouths wide, they were dumbfounded, unable to believe this.

"I saved them all, I succeeded." Fang Yuan spoke calmly at the beastman leader.

A moment later, the children understand the situation and erupted into a deafening cheer, some were sobbing out of joy, some were jumping around excitedly.

The beastman leader was speechless, he stared at Fang Yuan with bloodshot eyes. The surrounding beastmen were growling or baring their fangs, they were tempted to strike.

Fang Yuan was not afraid that the beastmen would go back on their words.

In most cases, these tribal beliefs were extremely strict, due to the culture and traditions of the tribe, they had to obey it.

Of course, nothing was certain.

In reality, there was the possibility that the beastman tribe would go back on their words.

But here, it was special, it was a dream realm.

This was not reality!

Indeed, like Fang Yuan had expected, the beastmen were furious and discontent, but they could only watch the food that was in front of them leave.

Passing through the dark forest, Fang Yuan led the group of children away from the beastman tribe, they got far away from the bonfire.

The children gathered around Fang Yuan, they walked together as they fell into silence.

In the darkness, a speck of light expanded, until light filled his vision.

Fang Yuan's soul returned to his body, he opened his eyes.

Taking a look, Fang Yuan showed a surprised expression.

He turned to the manifested dream realm behind him, he was filled with questions: "How can this be? I have already saved all the children, I did this to the limits. How can I still be thrown out of the dream realm, and not enter the second scene?"

Fang Yuan frowned deeply.

"Don't tell me, my guess was wrong? Untying the wind knot grass and saving the children is not the correct method to pass the first scene?"

"What clues did I neglect?"

Fang Yuan thought intensely, he worked his mind to its limits.

Explorations of dream realms were difficult. Even if Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories, and was at the forefront of this generation, but when exploring the dream realm, he had no confidence in succeeding.

Every dream realm was unique.

The method to explore dream realms varied each time, it was hard to accumulate helpful experiences.

Fang Yuan could only guess right now and try every idea he had. He could only persevere and not get frustrated to have a chance of passing the dream realm.

Of course, in Fang Yuan's previous life, there were many instances where people explored dream realms and failed to make any progress for decades.

Fang Yuan felt his head hurting, he had little confidence in his new guesses.

"In that case, I should go elsewhere and subdue the hidden essence turtle."

Fang Yuan had run into a barrier in this dream realm, he would not stubbornly stay in place.

Even though Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm was his main objective, he still definitely was going to obtain the dragonfish, hidden essence turtle, and the desolate plant.

Changing his train of thought, Fang Yuan left this place, heading to another location.

Two hours later, Feng Jin Huang's pale face regained a bit of her rosiness.

She opened her eyes.

In her clear eyes, brilliance radiated.

"Guts Gu is truly helpful towards the healing and recovery of souls, it takes effect so quickly." She was joyful.

Seeing that she was safe, the other four Spirit Affinity House Gu Masters heaved sighs of relief.

They were here as bodyguards, if anything happened to Feng Jin Huang, they would not have a good time when they returned to the sect.

Feng Jin Huang saw the desolate beast shark fin wolf that Fang Yuan left behind, her gaze focused as she asked the Gu Masters around her, after hearing that during her healing period, no other Gu Masters had gotten close, she relaxed slightly.

Finally, she inspected her body and confirmed that she had healed completely, she stood up and faced the dream realm again.

"Earlier, I used dream wings Immortal Gu and it displayed great capabilities while I was obtaining a boost in my refinement path attainment level. But this time, I am facing an Immortal Venerable's dream realm, the difficulty is worlds' apart, I cannot commit my earlier mistake again. Eh? Why does the dream realm look slightly smaller?"

Feng Jin Huang's gaze concentrated, she showed a suspicious look.

Once the dream realm was successfully explored, it would vanish.

Even though Fang Yuan did not succeed, he had gained quite a harvest, his wisdom path attainment level rose.

As the saying goes: Where there are gains, there are losses.

Fang Yuan gained something, the dream realm naturally lost something.

It showed on the surface as the dream realm's size shrinking.

"It did shrink, how did this happen?" Feng Jin Huang confirmed it repeatedly and felt more suspicious: "Is this Immortal Venerable dream realm special? It will shrink as time passes?"

Feng Jin Huang did not suspect anything else.

In this era, people's understanding towards dream realms was still at a primitive and ignorant level.

Furthermore, in Feng Jin Huang's heart, she believed that her unique dream wings Immortal Gu provided superiority and advantages to her in dream path.

Although she was suspicious, she could not verify anything.

Eventually, she shook her head, ignoring the sense of suspicion inside her, she entered the dream realm again.

Just as Feng Jin Huang entered the dream realm, Fang Yuan went to the location of the hidden essence turtle in accordance with He Feng Yang's information.

This wisdom path desolate beast was huge, it was like a mound.

At this moment, the hidden essence turtle's four limbs and head were hidden in its shell, its body was covered and hidden under rocks.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly, he swooped down like an eagle ferociously.

Boom boom boom...

Intense explosions occurred, causing thunderous sounds.

Fang Yuan and the hidden essence turtle fought.

At once, rocks flew, smoke was rising up.

The hidden essence turtle tried to resist at first, but it had no Immortal Gu and was only a desolate beast, not an ancient desolate beast, how could it be the match of Fang Yuan who had rank seven battle strength?

After several rounds, the hidden essence turtle could only hide inside its shell and take a beating.

"This turtle shell is really thick..." Fang Yuan attacked against the hidden essence turtle and felt a little surprised momentarily, he laughed in a helpless tone.

He did not exert his full strength, in fact, he rarely used his Immortal Gu.

He had used myriad self giant hand in many situations already, it would be best if he did not expose it. Who knew if other sects had preparations involving some investigative Immortal Gu?

Fang Yuan needed to conceal his strength as much as possible.

Thus, after the hidden essence turtle hid itself, Fang Yuan did not rush.

He split his focus onto two tasks at once, he made the battle grand and loud while savoring his gains from the dream realm.

As he thought over it, he had countless inspirations that emerged in him.

It was like a door had been opened in front of him, he could see the view outside of the house.

This feeling was incredible amazing, Fang Yuan was drowning in euphoria.

"Earlier, my wisdom path attainment level was extremely ordinary, after all, I only started my wisdom path cultivation recently. But now, my wisdom path attainment level has reached quasi-master level. Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm is simply incredible!"

Such progress, if it was according to normal cultivation, would take him decades of accumulation.

Even though the dream realm was dangerous, each time he succeeded, he would have great gains, it was truly a great leap forward, Fang Yuan saved a lot of time.

"Why is there such thunderous noise?"

Fang Yuan was fighting intensely with the hidden essence turtle, groups of Gu Masters were drawn over to investigate the situation.

"Fang Yuan? How can he be so strong?!"

"No wonder the elders in the sect told us to avoid this monster Fang Yuan!"

"He is simply cheating, this is so unfair to us, how can we compete with this monster?"

Eventually, Fang Yuan spend a day and a night to subdue the hidden essence turtle and send it into his immortal aperture. During this period, many Gu Masters were drawn over, but after doing some investigations, they retreated in fear.

"Thirty-sixth failure..."

Feng Jin Huang opened her eyes in fatigue.

Ever since she was heavily injured, she had become careful, unfortunately, she did not have unravel dream, and had never interacted with wind knot grass previously. She failed a total of thirty-six times, not even untying it correctly once.

Being able to survive in the dream was the most basic requirement for successfully exploring a dream realm.

Failing to untie the wind knot grass meant she could not survive, the explorations failed.

Thus, each time Feng Jin Huang explored the dream realm, the injuries to her soul after failing far surpassed that of Fang Yuan.

She had to spend a lot of time to rest and recover.

Thus, after two days and one night, she only explored it thirty-six times.

"The Immortal Venerable's dream realm is so tough, I have dream wings Immortal Gu but it is still so difficult for me, not to mention others!" Feng Jin Huang looked at the dream realm in front of her with a bitter expression.

She was filled with dejection and frustration, right now, as long as she thought about the appearance of the wind knot grass, this proud young genius would feel like vomiting!

At this moment, Fang Yuan secretly got close to the dream realm.

He had already captured the hidden essence turtle and nether grass, he was going to put his remaining time into the Immortal Venerable's dream realm.

After going through some intense deductions, Fang Yuan had a new idea.

Just as Feng Jin Huang was anguished and dejected, Fang Yuan smiled confidently as he secretly entered the dream realm again.

Chapter 915: The Biggest Winner

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm was displayed in front of Fang Yuan once again.

It was night, a huge fire was burning.

Dancing around the fire were beastmen making beastly shouts and growls one after another.

This was a celebration.

A bloody celebration after hunting.

Fang Yuan calmly looked around him.

He was once again a human child bound tightly. Around him were many other boys and girls in the same situation.

"We are doomed, we are dead meat!"

"Wuwuwu... I don't want to be eaten."

The kids cried, desperate and pale.

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with a sharp light as he suddenly stood up and shouted: "I want wind knot grass!"

The beastman tribe's celebration had just entered a heated stage.

And right at this time, Fang Yuan's voice suddenly pierced into this celebration.

For a moment, the bestial calls paused and all the beastmen looked at Fang Yuan with blood-red eyes.

An enormous pressure was formed, the human children became as silent as cicadas during winter, shivering, some even peed their pants.

Fang Yuan was without any expression, as he shouted once more.

The beastman leader grunted furiously before instructing with surging killing intent: "Give it to him!"

"Little rascal, I will be watching you. As long as you ruin even a small strand, I will use my trunk to roll your tender little body into meat paste." An elephant beastman walked over and handed a ball of wind knot grass to Fang Yuan while threatening him.

Fang Yuan chuckled and glanced at the wind knot grass on his hand before raising his head: "One? How is this enough? Give me one ball of wind knot grass for every human captive there is here. I will untie all the wind knot grass, and save all of them!"

Instantly, shocked sounds came from all around.

Be it the beastmen or the children beside Fang Yuan, they all stared at Fang Yuan with different expressions.

After the momentary shock, the beastmen started laughing loudly.

And the children who had felt hopeful, felt dispirited again, worried and desperate.

Soon, all the wind knot grass were laid in front of Fang Yuan.

The height of the whole wind knot grass pile was several times Fang Yuan's current size.

Were he to use his own strength, it would be impossible to untie all this wind knot grass in the extremely limited time.

Besides Fang Yuan, no one else believed he could succeed.

Under everyone's gazes, Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air and began to disassemble the wind knot grass.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

Unravel dream.

...

This special immortal killer move was created with a wisdom path Immortal Gu, Unravel Mystery, as the core and several supplementary dream path mortal Gu.

Right now, it produced extremely great effects.

However, although unravel mystery Immortal Gu could be used repeatedly, other dream path mortal Gu would be expended after continuous use.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan had never slacked off.

He would take out some time every day to explore his own dream realm and refine dream path mortal Gu.

Little by little, these dream path mortal Gu accumulated and were used at this moment. It was as the saying goes: Opportunities favor those who are prepared.

"I have finally entered the second round of the dream realm!" Fang Yuan felt satisfied inwardly.

This time, he was not thrown out by the dream realm, and succeeded in his hopes of entering the second round of the dream realm.

As it turned out, to pass through the first round of the dream realm, one had to save all the children.

Fang Yuan had tried it before but was actually late by a step.

In the original route of the dream realm, a portion of the children were already killed by the elephantman.

The elephantman brought these children under the beastman leader's instruction, but he intentionally slipped up, smashing the tree trunk to the ground.

The tree trunk easily crushed many bound children, their flesh was fought over by the beastmen and devoured.

Although this did conform to the beastman tribe's traditions, it could be considered to be skirting around them.

The elephantman was a famous warrior of the beastman tribe, the beastman leader and others also put up with this action.

When Fang Yuan was subduing the hidden essence turtle and nether grass, he realized this key point and saved all the human children, finally succeeding and entering the second round.

"After passing the first round, my wisdom path attainment has probably reached master level!"

"A lot of dream path mortal Gu have been expended by repeatedly using the killer move unravel dream, I will need to be more sparing."

"It is a pity that when I followed the information obtained from Mo Yao's will to look for that spring dream fruit tree, it was already cut down by some ignorant mortals half a year ago. Otherwise, with this tree, the amount of dream path mortal Gu with me would be at least ten times the number!"

"The first round should be derived from the memory of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's childhood. Maybe it was a regret of hers. I saved all the children which could be considered as making up for her regret, thus succeeding in passing the first round."

"Now, what will the second round be like?"

Fang Yuan suppressed his churning thoughts and observed his surroundings.

It was a mountain.

In the lonely night sky, few stars shone.

Just like in summer, warm wind blew gently, bringing with it the fragrance of the lush mountain forest.

The gurgling of the brook, the rustling of the leaves and the song of the nightingales mixed together to form sounds of nature that needed no words to adorn them.

Compared the bloody, cruel and vicious first round, this second round was mild as a drizzle and gentle as a breeze.

"Move quickly, what are you being dazed for?"

"As long as we can take six steps over the astrolabe chessboard, we can obtain the legacy of Lord Immortal Venerable!"

"If we can become Lord Immortal Venerable's disciples, we can learn abilities and become experts! At that time, we will avenge our families and kill those damned beastmen."

The surrounding children urged Fang Yuan to move, when they saw him stop.

Fang Yuan immediately understood some conditions to pass the second round.

"There are records of this in history. The first rank nine Gu Immortal in human history is known as Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable. He was very aware of the drawbacks of the clan system, and to initiate a sect system, he set an example himself, setting up astrolabes in many places. As long as someone was able to walk six steps on the astrolabe chessboard, they could become his personal disciple."

Fang Yuan recalled as he followed the surrounding companions towards the peak.

There, he saw the famous astrolabe chessboard.

The astrolabe chessboard was carved on a giant rock with a flat surface.

On the rock were lines that were either horizontal cuts, vertical cuts or diagonal cuts.

Every time the breeze blew, these lines would flash with deep blue starry radiance.

When Fang Yuan approached closer, these starry lines directly passed through his eyes and appeared in his mind.

At the same time, his soul was suddenly being consumed at dozens of times the previous rate!

Many of the children who came with him stopped, unable to go forward, some even fainted on the spot.

Fang Yuan concentrated and walked forward till he reached the giant rock, he then slowly put his palm on the rock surface.

Boom.

His ears buzzed as he hallucinated.

Those thin starry lines suddenly expanded into paths he was walking on. And Fang Yuan's whole body blossomed with starry radiance, becoming a star chess piece, stopping in this web of these starry paths.

Astrolabe chessboard!

Fang Yuan observed, cold sweat filling his head.

He thought for a long while before taking a step hesitatingly.

The next moment, his soul was thrown out of the dream realm and returned to his physical body.

His soul was heavily injured!

One wrong step and everything failed.

Fang Yuan's body swayed, almost falling down to the ground. The injury to his soul was much more severe than Feng Jin Huang's, almost costing him half his life!

"The second round of the dream realm is immensely more dangerous than the first round!"

Fang Yuan revealed a shocked expression before immediately calming down.

"But, I have already passed the first round and received great gains. My wisdom path attainment has indeed already reached master level."

"There is still time, no need to hurry. I will use guts Gu to recuperate first, then slowly explore."

While Fang Yuan was healing his injuries, opposite him, obstructed by the external manifestation of the dream realm, Feng Jin Huang had just finished recovering, she opened her eyes and stood up, intending to try again.

"Eh, why has the dream realm shrunk again?"

"Moreover, it has shrunken much more this time, almost by a third!"

Feng Jin Huang stared with wide open eyes.

Fang Yuan had passed the first round and received huge gains, thus the first round of the dream realm's external manifestation had disappeared.

This portion of the dream realm had already turned into nourishment for Fang Yuan.

"Could it be that someone else has succeeded in exploring the dream realm?" Feng Jin Huang thought of this before laughing lightly to herself, "That is not possible. Mother used the sect's help and already deduced that I possess the only dream path Immortal Gu in Central Continent. It seems this dream realm is truly special, it will gradually shrink with time."

"I need to hurry up!" Feng Jin Huang squinted her eyes as she activated dream wings Immortal Gu.

Her dream wings flapped, bringing her soul into the dream realm.

The moment she entered, Feng Jin Huang felt great joy.

"This is clearly a deeper layer of the dream realm, this is great, I finally don't have to face that damned wind knot grass!" Right now, Feng Jin Huang was jumping with joy in the dream realm.

However, after a while, Feng Jin Huang returned, utterly defeated.

Her injured soul returned to its body, her face extremely pale.

"There is no more wind knot grass, but now there is this even more complex astrolabe chessboard..." She bitterly looked at this dream realm in front of her, the external manifestation releasing all kinds of colors, gorgeous and mysterious.

Grievance and anger filled her, but she had nowhere to vent it.

Feng Jin Huang had gained many benefits from dream realms before, and with the dream wings Immortal Gu in her hands, she had gotten the thought that 'dream realms are just so-so', having a low opinion of the obstacles inside.

Over her life, she had never failed so miserably like this.

She had already spent the last few days facing this dream realm, she had received all sorts of injuries dozens of times, but had not made even the smallest gain!

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, I will remember you..." Feng Jin Huang gritted her teeth, her eyes rolled backwards and she fainted, she finally could not endure the injuries.

Time passed quickly, it was already the last day of the agreement.

All the Gu Masters who had entered the fragment world came out and returned to the sides of their respective sect's Gu Immortals, reporting on their findings.

Soon, all the immortals' gazes gathered on Fang Yuan and He Feng Yang.

In this contest, Immortal Crane Sect without doubt monopolized the lead, not only eating meat, they did not even leave behind soup for others.

In such a situation, Fang Yuan naturally did not want to stay for long.

He completed the handover to He Feng Yang on the spot, and left this valley while keeping his dragonfish.

Fang Yuan remained silent about his gains, he was fully aware that he was the biggest winner in this contest!

Chapter 916: Dual Grandmaster!

Hu Immortal blessed land.

The underground cave was shining with blood red light.

The faint blood red light originated from stalks of blood colored lingzhi in the cave. These blood colored lingzhi grew freely, they were mutated from ordinary lingzhi.

The original zhi forest was not suitable for Hu Immortal blessed land.

But after the blood poison kerria earthly calamity, Hu Immortal blessed land gained some blood path dao marks, the environment of the entire area changed drastically, it was suitable for the growth of some blood path life forms.

Thus, the originally dwindling zhi forest turned into a blood zhi forest, it grew rapidly and became extremely lush.

And earlier, Hu Immortal blessed land had chestnut flowers, poisonous blue degree grass, water chestnut grass, six divine grass, seven colored seven treasure flowers, and milk tea flowers and more growing all over it, but they were all wiped out.

When comparing the two, one could see how merciless heaven was, there was a feeling of great changes over time, there was some profound meaning behind it.

Fang Yuan sat on a giant blood lingzhi.

At this moment, he was slowly opening his eyes, letting out a breath of cloudy air.

Earlier, when he moved about, he used the identity of Xing Xiang Zi, as well as vaguely familiar face to disguise his appearance.

Right now, in Hu Immortal blessed land, he was in his base camp, he did not need to use immortal essence to maintain the transformation path killer move, Fang Yuan was in his original zombie form now.

He had eight arms, his face was green and his eyes were bright red, he was six meters tall with protruding fangs, he was shining with a cold glint among the blood red light.

But at this moment, his eyes were shining with a deep light of wisdom.

This light was the accumulation of time, the crystallization of time and space, it was moving and formed a stark contrast to his evil and ruthless appearance.

Recalling his earlier thoughts, Fang Yuan let out a breath of foggy air, he sighed softly: "The gains this time are simply too much."

He had to admit this point.

Because from this exploration of the dream realm, Fang Yuan's star path and wisdom path attainment reached grandmaster level!

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm not only made Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment level increase, it also raised his star path attainment level.

Fang Yuan was very shocked regarding this.

Grandmaster attainment level!

What did this mean?

After accumulating foundation in both his previous life and current life, Fang Yuan only became a grandmaster in blood path and strength path.

Among them, blood path grandmaster was because Fang Yuan cultivated blood path mainly in his previous life, it was accumulated through time.

As for strength path grandmaster, he had cultivated it on the side in his previous life, while mainly cultivating it this time. Because he had a foundation in his previous life, when he cultivated it this time, with the help of the immortal ascension tribulation, he obtained a chance to learn from heaven and earth. Furthermore, there was Hei Lou Lan's dream realm.

With all these reasons, he managed to accumulate sufficient foundation.

After exerting so much effort in both lives, using more than five hundred years, he only became a grandmaster in two paths.

But this time, he only explored a dream realm of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and spent less than half a month, yet he was already a wisdom path and star path grandmaster!

It was impossible to see his grandmaster attainment level physically, but Fang Yuan knew: His gains were immeasurable! He could even say it was more valuable than Hu Immortal blessed land.

"My gains this time will allow me to grow immensely for this period of time, I can even break out of my predicament!"

Generally speaking, development was the result of accumulation and gradual progress, by growing slowly and steadily, one would achieve success in the end.

But fortuitous encounters and windfalls would allow one to experience explosive growth, jumping out of a stale state and saving huge amounts of time, overturning the situation and obtaining an extraordinary achievement.

Since rebirth, Fang Yuan had been resolving difficulties, he advanced bravely and had many gains, they were extremely helpful to him, allowing him to find solutions.

Liquor worm, Spring Autumn Cicada, blood skull Gu, bone flesh unity Gu, all-out effort Gu, Three Kings blessed land, Hu Immortal blessed land, second aperture Gu, becoming a strength path Gu Immortal and gaining inspiration from nature, as well as wisdom Gu.

Other than these, there were other areas in which he grew and progressed, but they did not overturn his situations.

However, after this trip to Starry Sky grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan had gained a new shocking harvest, that was his dual grandmaster attainment level!

Among which, wisdom Gu was a rank nine Immortal Gu, it had reached an agreement with Fang Yuan, but it was not his, the degree to which he could make use of it was not high.

However, attainment levels were something that belonged entirely to the Gu Immortal themselves.

In Fang Yuan's opinion, dual grandmaster attainment level was more valuable than wisdom Gu itself!

"Since rebirth, this can be considered another situation where I made immense and shocking gains, yet this time the process was very easy, it was unthinkably simple."

Fang Yuan could feel the mysteries of the twists and turns over life in opportunities from this.

He naturally had some guesses, perhaps this was related to Connect Luck?

Speaking of which, ever since he used Connect Luck, Fang Yuan's cultivation journey had become much smoother.

The rise of his attainment levels, especially when they rose to grandmaster attainment level, gave an incredible feeling, he could not describe it!

It was as if Fang Yuan had previously been looking out of the window and seeing a large rock formation, filled with crevices and weeds.

Now, he took a few steps up and could see further and higher.

He could now observe part of the rock formation by looking down, he felt that this part of the formation was as tiny as a pebble beneath his feet now!

When he looked further ahead, he could see more, and understand deeper.

Attainment level, this was something very hard to describe.

What was attainment level?

Even for the developed Gu Master cultivation world, everyone had their own explanations for it, there was no unified description.

Fang Yuan's soul came from Earth.

This difference made him possess a different understanding regarding the phrase attainment level.

"So-called attainment levels are like mathematics problems. By answering many mathematics questions, one can accumulate experience when they get the correct answer, they will eventually understand the crux of them, gaining enlightenment and raising their attainment level. With this level of understanding, they can solve other related mathematics questions easily, and get the right answer. When they encounter very unfamiliar questions, they can also use their existing knowledge to answer a portion of them."

Thus, when Fang Yuan encounters questions in cultivation, because his attainment level rose, he could solve the question to varying degrees.

For example, Fang Yuan's use of wisdom Gu earlier was just superficial, it was a brutish and forced method. Now that he had wisdom path grandmaster attainment level, he gained many inspirations and ideas, he could try to use some supplementary Gu worms to make use of wisdom Gu more efficiently.

Another example was modifying Gu recipes.

Back then, Fang Yuan had tried to modify recipes of memory thought Gu, star thought Gu and malicious thought Gu, but because his wisdom path attainment level was low, he kept failing, he encountered impasses and could not advance.

Afterwards, he successfully modified star thought Gu's recipe, but he was making use of starlight Immortal Gu, it was not because of his own abilities.

Now, Fang Yuan could feel that he could modify these Gu recipes, and they would be even better than before.

Going beyond this, Fang Yuan was even confident that he could perfect incomplete inheritances. Like earlier, Fang Yuan had obtained an incomplete wisdom path inheritance, memory thought Gu, reminiscence Immortal Gu, and multiple mortal killer moves were included. With his grandmaster attainment level now, Fang Yuan could deduce this inheritance to a degree, and even restore it.

Gu recipes could be modified, he could modify killer moves as well. The killer moves myriad self, vaguely familiar face, they were within the range of possible applications.

Also battlefield killer moves, Fang Yuan could not find one after so long, but now he had the foundation needed to create one himself!

Or for example, the construction of Star Form blessed land, earlier, Fang Yuan's plans needed huge amounts of funds. Now, with his wisdom path and star path attainment levels, he could improve this plan and save an immensely large number of immortal essence stones in construction fees! Furthermore, this new plan would be even more ideal and useful than the previous one!

The raising of hairy men, his eight sources of revenue, the use of Gu Immortal souls, the claiming of Ge Pi blessed land, there were many things he could do.

The rise of attainment levels was quite special.

In conclusion, when attainment levels rise, the person experiences growth in all aspects. The Gu Master's cultivation journey would be refreshed, there would be great prospects, their strength would rise up as well!

Time passed quickly.

In terms of the five regions' time, half a month passed.

Two wills were intertwined, battling intensely.

Fang Yuan's will had the complete advantage, he was suppressing Mo Yao's will.

Fang Yuan's will's advantage continued to grow, he could almost toy with Mo Yao's will easily now.

"How can this be, how can your capabilities rise by so much?!" Mo Yao's will screamed in shocked anger.

Before this, Fang Yuan had been using a similar amount of will to fight with Mo Yao's will, they were at best evenly matched, he was even at a disadvantage.

But now, Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment level had reached grandmaster level, he only used one third of the will to defeat Mo Yao's will till she screamed in fear.

From the start of the battle, Fang Yuan was implacably in the lead, suppressing Mo Yao's will and preventing her from doing anything.

"Earlier, I used Mo Yao's will as a training dummy, I learned many techniques by fighting with her will. Now, I am far beyond Mo Yao's will, I can use many techniques naturally and smoothly. Mo Yao's will has lost her value as a training dummy."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan drew back his will.

He placed all his attention on the battlefield killer move in front of him, eight doors labyrinth.

Ten days ago, Fang Yuan left Hu Immortal blessed land, he came to Eastern Sea and joined up with Shark Demon and the rest, exploring Yu Lu blessed land.

The tough barrier back then — Eight Doors Labyrinth, was now resolvable by Fang Yuan, who was a wisdom path grandmaster.

Back then, Fang Yuan had thought that he would need the wisdom path Immortal Gu, Star Thought, to have a chance of dismantling eight doors labyrinth.

But now, he could multitask, deducing the battlefield killer move while secretly sparring with Mo Yao's will.

Most importantly, after tens of days had passed in the blessed land's time, under Fang Yuan's lead, Shark Demon and the others were finally close to unraveling eight doors labyrinth.

"We are about to pass eight doors labyrinth, to think that this Xing Xiang Zi would suddenly become so fierce!"

"Eight doors labyrinth, is this battlefield killer move the final obstacle in Yu Lu blessed land?"

The immortals were secretly excited.

Boom!

With a thunderous sound, eight doors labyrinth was thoroughly unraveled by Fang Yuan.

Yu Lu blessed land's true appearance appeared before all the immortals!

Chapter 917: Unmoving Troops

After dismantling the battlefield killer move eight doors labyrinth, everyone field of vision widened, seeing Yu Lu blessed land's true appearance.

Only to see that there were flashing lights in the sky, they were like traces of silk or streams of water, some were moving slowly, while others were creating dazzling ripples.

Red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue, purple... each light had a bright color. Dazzling light shined on everyone's faces.

Fang Yuan, Shark Demon, and the others did not speak. They looked at this amazing sight as they showed some excitement and amazement.

This Yu Lu blessed land was very different from normal blessed lands!

Ordinary blessed lands had the sky, ground, vegetation, flowers, birds, worms, and fish.

But here, there was nothing.

Yu Lu blessed land was very unique, it was merely a broad space without any concept of sky or ground, there was no living beings, and there were also no resources that Gu Immortals usually accumulated.

"Maybe this uniqueness is the reason why Yu Lu blessed land can set up battlefield killer moves of countless paths." Fang Yuan had a realization.

Normally speaking, there were huge conflicts between battlefield killer moves and blessed lands or grotto-heavens. Few Gu Immortals were capable of setting up battlefield killer moves in their blessed lands or grotto-heavens.

Because battlefield killer moves used Gu worms to engrave dao marks and temporarily create a battlefield.

Meanwhile, grotto-heavens and blessed lands were made of dao marks.

Because the dao marks varied, they conflicted. When Lang Ya blessed land was attacked by Qin Bai Sheng and the others, Lang Ya land spirit did not use a battlefield killer move to resist them. That was because within the blessed land, establishing a battlefield killer move was detrimental to oneself.

But Yu Lu blessed land went against this common sense of the cultivation world.

In Fang Yuan's case, when he attacked Yu Lu blessed land, he had encountered three battlefield killer moves, freezing rain frozen earth, fighting soul battlefield, and eight doors labyrinth.

These three were evidently immortal killer moves from different paths, they would not normally gather in the hands of a single Gu Immortal and become used in their immortal aperture.

But within Yu Lu blessed land, not only were these three used, they did not clash with the blessed land at all, in fact, they seemed to complement each other in a way.

"Fairy Yu Lu was a disciple of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. It is not strange that her immortal aperture blessed land is like this." Su Bai Man looked as she let out a deep breath, saying this.

"Even though there are fewer resources here, if we can learn Fairy Yu Lu's methods and use it in our own immortal apertures, we would be able to use battlefield killer moves in it, that would be a huge gain!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes flashed with brilliance.

At this time, a Gu Immortal who went with them pointed at a direction as he shouted: "Quickly look, Immortal Gu!"

Everyone quickly looked towards the direction the Gu Immortal was pointing.

As expected, they saw a Gu worm that had a special appearance. It was long and slim, like a twig. It had numerous thin golden colored wings, fluttering in the sky.

The entire Gu worm looked like a branch of a long golden willow.

This Gu worm quickly drilled into a nearby flashing light and vanished.

But during this moment it was seen, its Immortal Gu aura was undeniably exposed.

Everyone's gazes became heated, their breathing became rough, but they were not surprised.

There were naturally Immortal Gu in Yu Lu blessed land.

If there were no Immortal Gu, how could those battlefield killer moves earlier be constructed?

Even though Yu Lu blessed land did not have an accumulation of resources, with so many battlefield killer moves, it had to have a good number of Immortal Gu!

Shark Demon raised his head and laughed, breaking the silence.

He was overjoyed.

Even though the main gains had to be given to Zombie Alliance, he was the person who took down the blessed land, he would gain the biggest reward of at least one or two Immortal Gu.

Other than that, by succeeding in taking down Yu Lu blessed land, he would also receive a huge sum of contribution points from Zombie Alliance.

If Shark Demon could find an Immortal Gu that suited him, he would definitely take it for himself.

This was the benefit of being the person in charge.

If he found any mystical Immortal Gu that could help him and his wife revive and get rid of the zombie status, that would be best.

Reviving from being a zombie and becoming human, not only was Fang Yuan working towards it, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man were doing the same.

Seeing Shark Demon laugh, everyone started congratulating him.

Su Bai Man smiled more subtly.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had put in huge investment into the mission of invading Yu Lu blessed land, they had almost used up their savings.

On the surface, it could not be noticed, but Shark Demon and Su Bai Man were facing immense pressure.

Right now, their investment was finally bearing fruit.

As long as they obtained a rank seven Immortal Gu, all of their investments would be essentially paid off.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man were joyous, the weights on their minds had been removed.

"Once Yu Lu blessed land is captured, everyone here will be compensated according to the contributions you have made, you will not be shortchanged." Shark Demon smiled as he spoke seriously.

Everyone nodded, they stepped back and asked Shark Demon and Su Bai Man to go ahead.

With immense benefits in front of them, some Gu Immortals might become rash. Shark Demon's words were both an assurance and threat.

Everyone could understand his underlying meaning.

"Alright, everyone can wait and see." Shark Demon did not refuse, he struck.

He willed and turned into a flash of light, with a swooshing sound, he tore through space and shot out, the direction was towards the golden willow branch-like Immortal Gu earlier.

Everyone saw Shark Demon rapidly approaching the Immortal Gu, but suddenly, there were ripples in space as Shark Demon vanished.

At the next moment, he appeared beside everyone with a shocked expression.

"What happened?" Su Bai Man asked in suspicion.

Shark Demon shook his head, he said in an uncertain tone: "It seems to be another battlefield killer move?"

Next, everyone tried but they could not move out, it attested to Shark Demon's guess.

"This is a space path battlefield killer move, even though it has no offensive power, it is definitely more profound than the previous battlefield killer moves."

"Did all of you notice, every time we get transported back, we would be in our original spots. Our positions would not change at all."

"Such an ability, this has to be the legendary unmoving troops."

The Gu Immortals discussed and eventually came to a consensus.

Battlefield killer move — Unmoving Troops. This was the final battlefield killer move, it obstructed everyone.

This battlefield killer move had a huge origin, it was created by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable personally.

The work of an Immortal Venerable was truly profound.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had a mild and kind temperament, he was vast different from the other nine Gu Immortal Venerables.

He was merciful, he did not like killing since he was young, he often subdued people with kindness, taking down enemies without fighting.

Battlefield killer move unmoving troops, once someone entered this formation with any intent to battle, malicious thoughts, or lust, they would be unable to progress at all, unable to move.

In the past, before Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable became a rank nine Gu Immortal, he used this move to subdue a famous rank seven sound path Gu Immortal, Gao Ming. In that battle, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable did not move, he only used the battlefield immortal killer move unmoving troops, no matter what methods Gao Ming used, he exerted all of his strength and did not even managed to get one step closer to Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable.

This battle made the arrogant Gao Ming lose his temper. He then followed Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, becoming his guard henceforth.

"Since this has to do with wills and thoughts, why don't we shut our minds and temporarily stop thinking." Fang Yuan said.

It was not hard to achieve this.

Gu Immortals mostly had some wisdom path techniques, Fang Yuan was currently disguised as Xing Xiang Zi, he was also partly a wisdom path Gu Immortal.

But everyone's attempts ended in failure.

Some Gu Immortals did not have outstanding wisdom path techniques. During this process of moving forward, their desires and thoughts were stirred up, breaking their thoughtless state.

Only certain Gu Immortals, including Fang Yuan, could achieve a state of having no thoughts.

But the problem came after that!

Without any thoughts, how could one capture any Gu worms?

The body's movement was decided by the thoughts that were generated in the mind.

Without these thoughts, the body would stay still on the ground. In this situation, there was no need for the battlefield killer move, the Gu Immortals themselves could not move.

"Sigh! No wonder back then, Gu Immortal Gao Ming became dejected and willingly submitted to the rank seven Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, becoming his guard."

"To get through this round, it is hard, hard, hard!"

"The worst part is, Yu Lu blessed land is right in front of us, undeniably, this is the final obstacle, but we can only watch here and look on, unable to gain anything!"

"Maybe this arrangement was the intention of Fairy Yu Lu. She purposely let us see hope, luring out our thoughts and desires, it increases the difficulty of taking down this battlefield killer move."

"If we really cannot succeed, we will have to retreat and seek reinforcements." Su Bai Man suggested as she frowned.

Shark Demon looked ahead, becoming silent.

Earlier, he had invited a wisdom path Gu Immortal over, but he lost an Immortal Gu to her, thus he did not at all like this idea.

At the crucial moment, only a person on their own side could be trusted.

Shark Demon looked at Fang Yuan, now that Fang Yuan was part of Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, he was one of them.

Shark Demon asked: "Xing Xiang Zi, do you have any means? If you do, use them, don't worry, your compensation will not be small."

Fang Yuan smiled lightly: "To unravel this battlefield killer move, it can be said to be both easy and difficult."

"Oh? What do you mean?"

Fang Yuan looked around, seeing that he had attracted all of their attentions, he said slowly: "Everyone, do not be scared due to the reputation of unmoving troops. Back then, Gao Ming lost because the battlefield killer move was controlled by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. Right now, we are facing an unmanned battlefield killer move. It is far easier to deal with this one."

"That makes sense."

"Indeed, with a Gu Immortal controlling the battlefield killer move, it could transform and replenish continuously. But a battlefield killer move without any Gu Immortals controlling it is very inflexible."

Everyone saw hope and felt joy after hearing Fang Yuan's words.

But next, Fang Yuan's words threw them into dejection again: "Attacking an unmanned battlefield killer move is relatively simpler. But to me, it is extremely difficult to unravel this current one, there is almost no hope of success."

Everyone's expressions crumbled, they cast somewhat unkind gazes towards Fang Yuan.

One of the Gu Immortals said agitatedly: "Xing Xiang Zi, you talked a lot of crap, just tell us if you're useless. Speaking like this, are you trying to toy with us?"

Fang Yuan laughed as he looked at Shark Demon.

Shark Demon showed no expression on his face, but it was obvious that his mood was currently terrible.

Fang Yuan suddenly stopped his smiling expression, he bowed to Shark Demon as he said solemnly: "Why would I dare to toy with everyone? I am truly restricted by a lack of resources, if I can refine a wisdom path Immortal Gu, I would have great confidence in unraveling the battlefield killer move unmoving troops for sure."

Chapter 918: Blazing Heaven Demoness

Shark sea, underwater palace.

Delicious delicacies filled the table, the aroma of wine pervaded the air, and the lantern lights shined brightly.

In the banquet, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man sat on the main seats, treating two Gu Immortals in the hall with utmost cordiality.

These two Gu Immortals were none other than Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

After they ran into a barrier in Yu Lu blessed land, and knew that staying longer would be of no use, Shark Demon and the group sensibly retreated.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng had originally intended to leave, but were invited over by Shark Demon and Su Bai Man.

This was already the third time Fang Yuan had participated in Shark Demon's shark fishing banquet.

Gulping down the fine wine, Shark Demon put down the wine cup and looked at Fang Yuan, suddenly asking: "Xing Xiang Zi, how much assurance do you truly have in unraveling unmoving troops?"

Fang Yuan thought inwardly: 'The time has come.'

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had been talking about all sorts of irrelevant matters, but he just kept quiet and did not speak about the matter first. Shark Demon finally could not hold it in and spoke about the subject.

Fang Yuan immediately replied: "Lord Shark Demon, you are also aware of how things stand for me. The wisdom path inheritance I inherited is complete. Moreover, recently, I have comprehended many mysteries, thus I could unravel the battlefield killer move eight doors labyrinth. But up until now, I have been suffering from having no relevant wisdom path Immortal Gu, thus my methods are limited and my capabilities insufficient. If I could refine this wisdom path Immortal Gu, I can definitely unravel unmanned unmoving troops."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng, who was beside him, also backed him up: "I have known Brother Xing Xiang for many years, I know he is not someone who exaggerates or speaks empty words. Since he says he has confidence, then he definitely has confidence. I can guarantee this."

Su Bai Man, however, was not satisfied with Tai Bai Yun Sheng's guarantee, as she looked at the person in concern, Fang Yuan, and pursued: "If you have the wisdom path Immortal Gu, can you guarantee you can unravel that battlefield killer move?"

Fang Yuan did not answer directly, instead taking a step back in order to advance further, intentionally giving a bitter smile: "How can I have complete certainty? This matter concerns Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, one of the ten supreme experts in history! If something unexpected happens, it would be normal. But for now at least, based on the part that is shown, I am quite confident of unraveling it if I can have the help of the wisdom path Immortal Gu."

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man glanced at each other, although they were angry at Fang Yuan's slippery words, they were moved as well.

There was no other way.

They had suffered much hardship beforehand.

Previously, they had spent a considerable price to invite other wisdom path Gu Immortals to help, but the outcome was emphatically not ideal, they even lost an Immortal Gu in the end.

As for Xing Xiang Zi....

They had cooperated with him many times now, and knew many details about him. More importantly, Fang Yuan had joined Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, and could be considered a person on the same side.

Thus, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man's first choice was Fang Yuan.

However, financing Fang Yuan to refine Immortal Gu was difficult as well.

The cost of refining Immortal Gu was rather high, while the success rate was too low, and depended on luck.

If luck was good, one could refine successfully in the first attempt. Then everything would be a joyous matter. But this situation was very rare.

If luck was not good, there was a possibility of always failing. At that time, even if there was a huge pile of immortal essence stones, they would just be wasted with no gains.

This was also the reason most Gu Immortals would rather capture wild Immortal Gu than to think of refining Immortal Gu themselves.

Refining Immortal Gu was difficult.

In the present cultivation world, many rank six Gu Immortals did not have even one Immortal Gu on them, and could only use mortal Gu to hold their own.

Fang Yuan was a special case. He had a lot of Immortal Gu, so many that were they to be exposed, perhaps people would not believe it!

However, he had reborn, had fortuitous encounters, taken deadly risks, and faced all sorts of harsh conditions to obtain these Immortal Gu.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man did not know these details, but they were aware of Fang Yuan's intention.

Fang Yuan wanted to rely on them to lend him a hand in refining wisdom path Immortal Gu.

As far as they were concerned, Fang Yuan could not afford this expenditure and had no accumulations to refine Immortal Gu, thus he was making them help him.

If it were any other time, Shark Demon would definitely have scoffed and not even given a thought.

What a joke!

How silly would he be to help others refine Immortal Gu?

However, in the current situation, Shark Demon had to request Fang Yuan's help in unraveling the battlefield killer move.

Right now, Shark Demon had one question on his mind — was Xing Xiang Zi fooling them? Was he using this chance to blackmail them, when even without Immortal Gu, he had the ability to unravel this battlefield killer move?

Fang Yuan saw Shark Demon's hesitation, but did not speak and only drank the wine.

This moment and time was just perfect, Fang Yuan had confidence.

Previously, the timing was wrong, now Yu Lu blessed land was laid out in front of them like a juicy piece of meat dangling in the air, tempting Shark Demon. This had indeed done a great favor to Fang Yuan.

As long as they completely dismantled unmoving troops, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man would gain lots of benefits, obtaining hundreds of times what they had invested!

Naturally, with Fang Yuan's personality, he had already thought of devouring these alone, and backstabbing them.

However, his strength was not enough to beat even just Shark Demon!

Shark Demon was a veteran rank seven immortal zombie, although Fang Yuan had rank seven battle strength, it was not outstanding among rank seven Gu Immortals.

But this was already quite good, after all, Fang Yuan's cultivation was only at the bottom tier of rank six.

Fang Yuan could not defeat even Shark Demon, let alone when there were Su Bai Man and other Gu Immortals as well. As for Zombie Alliance behind Shark Demon, there was even less need to mention them.

For a colossal force like Zombie Alliance, Fang Yuan was just a rat running across the street.

Fang Yuan was rational and calm, and knew his own limits. He had observed and evaluated the situation before he joined this expedition, in order to get a share of the profits and extract the greatest benefits for himself.

When Fang Yuan drank the third cup of wine, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had already finished their secret discussion.

They quickly reached a consensus.

They decided to aid Fang Yuan financially and help him refine wisdom path Immortal Gu.

Even if it was Fang Yuan blackmailing them, they had no choice but to settle for it!

They did not even force Fang Yuan to make an oath or use Gu worms to probe out his true thoughts.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man were, naturally, not foolish.

Besides urgently needing Fang Yuan's help for this final important hurdle, they also had another intention.

That was to improve their relationship with Fang Yuan.

After all, the wisdom path potential Fang Yuan showed was already worth it for them to make an investment.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals were rare, having a friendship with a wisdom path Gu Immortal was very precious.

However, just as Shark Demon was about to reply, there was suddenly a change.

The immense sea shook intensely, thunder crackled, and countless chaotic sea currents pressed on towards the underwater palace.

Immediately, a piercing fire pillar shot down from outside the sea, directly striking at Shark Demon's underwater palace with shocking might.

Rumble!

A loud sound reverberated through the area, and the magnificent underwater palace shined with the radiance of a defensive Gu formation.

However, the light could not last for even a breath of time before it was torn apart by the fire pillar.

In an instant, stones and bricks broke and flew in all directions, the palace turned into ruins, the fire kept on burning and was actually not extinguished by the sea.

The extremely pleasant banquet had now thoroughly ended, as the endless sea water surged in, sweeping away all the furnishings and the delicacies of the banquet, and soon submerged Fang Yuan and the group.

However, the four were all Gu Immortals, and had no problems staying in this depth of the sea.

Shark Demon was an immortal zombie, and did not need to breathe in the sea.

He was dazed for a moment before suddenly standing up and looked at the sky above the sea, shouting in fury: "Such audacity! Who dares to attack my sea area?"

Su Bai Man also stood beside Shark Demon, similarly gazing up, her expression pale.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng glanced at each other, puzzled.

Shark Demon had outstanding strength, and with Su Bai Man accompanying him everywhere, they could advance or retreat easily. Such a duo was already extremely dangerous to provoke, more importantly, there was also Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance behind them.

Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance was the main headquarters of the Zombie Alliances over the five regions. They were a colossal force, a level stronger than even super forces, and could even be called an overlord of the Eastern Sea cultivation world.

Who is it that came to attack Zombie Alliance's Shark Demon?

"Hahaha." Shark Demon had just shouted, when a voice resounded in everyone's ears, "This is only a small appetizer, I am not only going to destroy your palace, I will also beat you lowlife lovers till you can't even stand up!"

The voice was extremely arrogant and domineering, moreover from the voice, it was a female immortal?

"It's her?!" Su Bai Man said, her eyes widened, showing a clearly surprised and grave look.

A bright red figure descended from the sky, pressing down into the sea and towards the four on the seabed.

Fang Yuan gazed above at this female immortal and saw she was descending extremely fast. Her whole body was blazing with fire which swayed in the water. As for her true appearance, it was hidden in the flames and could not be seen clearly.

"This surging aura... a rank eight Gu Immortal!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng blurted.

Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes, adding a sentence inwardly: 'More precisely, this is a rank eight female immortal zombie.'

Immediately, Shark Demon shouted out the female immortal's identity.

"Blazing Heaven Demoness, have you gone crazy? You dare to attack a person belonging to Zombie Alliance like you? You are challenging Zombie Alliance's authority, and will definitely be severely punished."

Blazing Heaven Demoness!

Fang Yuan's eyes brightened, as he recalled that he had heard this name before.

This name was a famous one.

Blazing Heaven Demoness, a rank eight Gu Immortal. She was from Northern Plains, the leader of the Northern Plains Zombie Alliance branch!

After Fang Yuan had infiltrated into Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, he had heard other members mention and talk of her many times, praising and revering Blazing Heaven Demoness' formidable strength and domineering style.

Fang Yuan had not expected to see such a person in this way.

Blazing Heaven Demoness, who was covered in fire, laughed loudly: "Shark Demon, don't talk nonsense. The matter between us is an internal conflict between Zombie Alliance members. Speak! What are you trying to do by stealing my immortal material?"

Su Bai Man was just about to question Blazing Heaven Demoness, but had not expected Blazing Heaven Demoness to blame them first.

Shark Demon shouted: "Nonsense! When did I steal your immortal material? If you want to frame me, go find a better reason! These last days, I have only been paying attention to doing the assignment of Zombie Alliance, invading Yu Lu blessed land, when would I have the time to steal your immortal material? You are just trying to start a quarrel!"

Blazing Heaven Demoness, however, was not flustered, instead confidently laughing: "Hahaha, I came here with a witness. Shark Demon, you won't be able to deny it!"

Shark Demon was so furious that he laughed: "Good, good, let me see what witness you have."

Chapter 919: Angry Bird

In the sea and under the water, the two sides were in a stalemate, it was a tense atmosphere.

A moment ago, Fang Yuan was still enjoying a banquet with Shark Demon and his wife, having a joyous time. But at the next moment, they were attacked, the entire underwater palace of Shark Demon was turned into rubble.

As the saying goes: While a person stays in their house, calamity descends from the sky.

Fang Yuan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng as the latter transmitted: "Blazing Heaven Demoness is a rank eight great expert, she is not someone we can fight."

Fang Yuan nodded inconspicuously, he understood Tai Bai Yun Sheng's intention, that was to sit and watch.

At Gu Immortal level, the higher the rank, the greater the difference between them.

Even if Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Shark Demon, and Su Bai Man collaborated and worked together sincerely, they might not be able to hold off Blazing Heaven Demoness over multiple rounds even if they disregarded the cost.

This was an absolutely powerful foe.

Normally, only rank eight Gu Immortals could fight other rank eights.

Shark Demon also knew this, thus, even though his house was destroyed, he did not dare to fight Blazing Heaven Demoness head on.

With Shark Demon's temper, if his house was destroyed, he would burst into anger and attack. But because it was Blazing Heaven Demoness, a rank eight Gu Immortal, he had to control himself even if he was angry.

He knew he was not a match for the rank eight Gu Immortal, the best way to solve this problem now was to use Zombie Alliance's rules and negotiate with her.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had gone against the rules of Zombie Alliance, she was finding problems with an ally, how could that be allowed? Such blatant attacks are simply giving no regard to Zombie Alliance!

But Blazing Heaven Demoness smiled confidently, like she had already won: "Shark Demon, isn't it simple to justify my actions?"

"Bo Dan, come out!" Blazing Heaven Demoness called.

Gu Immortal Bo Dan stood out from behind Blazing Heaven Demoness.

He lowered his head, his expression was bitter as he bowed deeply: "Lord Shark Demon, Lady Su Bai Man, I was forced against my will!"

Seeing Bo Dan, Shark Demon's expression turned dark.

His wife Su Bai Man also snorted coldly, she had an idea of what Blazing Heaven Demoness' plan was.

As expected, at the next moment, everyone heard Blazing Heaven Demoness scream: "Shark Demon, Su Bai Man, the two of you instructed Bo Dan to steal my rank eight immortal material, medicine ice. I was in closed cultivation and was careless, the two of you actually succeeded. Today, I am here to seek justice!"

As it turned out, Bo Dan was quite pitiful, even though he was alive, he had no choice but to join Zombie Alliance.

Just earlier, his private sea area was taken over by Blazing Heaven Demoness using brute force.

Fang Yuan entered Eastern Sea using Xing Xiang Zi's identity and joined Shark Demon in the invasion of Yu Lu blessed land.

Bo Dan was a half-baked wisdom path Gu Immortal, his skill was lacking, he was schemed against by Fang Yuan.

To protect his status, he had to bribe Su Bai Man and give her the rank eight immortal material medicine ice, so that Su Bai Man would defend him.

But Bo Dan was still too incapable, he and Shark Demon slowly became estranged.

Bo Dan was left with no choice, he attempted to use Zombie Alliance to exert pressure on Blazing Heaven Demoness, so that she would return him his private sea area.

However, he was only rank six, while Blazing Heaven Demoness was a rank eight great expert. As the leader of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, she was a higher-up. Even though Zombie Alliance received Bo Dan's plea and complaint, they dragged out his request and tried to stall for time. How could they offend the powerful Blazing Heaven Demoness for this mere Bo Dan?

Thus, Bo Dan's situation became increasingly pathetic, until Fang Yuan unraveled the battlefield killer move eight doors labyrinth and obtained a huge breakthrough in the invasion of Yu Lu blessed land.

Ever since Shark Demon invaded Yu Lu blessed land, he had been receiving heavy attention.

Seeing that Yu Lu blessed land was about to be taken down, with such great benefits, Blazing Heaven Demoness' greed was stirred.

Even though Blazing Heaven Demoness had incredible cultivation level, she was superior to them and had great strength, but she could not forcefully take over the fruits of the labor of Yu Lu blessed land.

After all, this was Eastern Sea, not Northern Plains.

This was the Zombie Alliance headquarters, not her Northern Plains branch.

Since she was a member of Zombie Alliance, she could not break the rules.

Thus, she sent Bo Dan a message, lying that she would return him his private sea area and would compensate him.

Bo Dan had no long term accommodation, as he was wandering about, he received this news and was overjoyed.

In the end, when he returned, he was forced by Blazing Heaven Demoness to frame Shark Demon and Su Bai Man.

Bo Dan did not dare to offend Blazing Heaven Demoness, but he also did not dare to offend Shark Demon and Su Bai Man. He realized that he had fallen into a trap and was in deep regret, but now that he was in Blazing Heaven Demoness' hands, he had no choice left.

In the end, he was captured by Blazing Heaven Demoness and was brought to attack Shark Demon's underwater palace.

Shark Demon's gaze moved from Bo Dan to Blazing Heaven Demoness.

He knew that Bo Dan was just a minor character, he was not crucial.

This accusation would not hold up against any investigations.

Shark Demon held in the anger inside him as he sneered at Blazing Heaven Demoness: "Blazing Heaven Demoness, just say it if you want to pick the fruits, why must you implicate an innocent person?"

Su Bai Man followed: "Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness, you are a rank eight great expert, aren't your current actions too ugly?"

Blazing Heaven Demoness laughed loudly.

She naturally knew that this excuse was weak.

But that did not matter.

She just needed a cover, just an excuse would do.

This excuse was only used to respond to Zombie Alliance's headquarters, it could not force Shark Demon and his wife to obey her.

To force Shark Demon and his wife, what was needed was not an excuse, but strength.

Thus, she came here personally with overflowing battle intent, she was here to find trouble with them!

"Hahaha..." Blazing Heaven Demoness' laughter stopped, her eyes shined with brilliance as she looked at the sea, suddenly saying: "Three moves."

"What?" Su Bai Man was shocked.

"I will finish you off in three moves. If you can block three moves of mine, I will pretend I was never here." Blazing Heaven Demoness said sternly.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man looked at each other, the former let out a breath of turbid air and agreed: "Alright! Let the four of us experience your power!"

Blazing Heaven Demoness' three moves agreement made Shark Demon see some hope.

Of course, the most important reason was that they were helpless in this situation. He had to agree regardless of his wishes!

Weaklings had no choices in the first place.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng frowned slightly, he did not want to take action, but Shark Demon was crafty, with a few words he directly included Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng on his side, against Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Fang Yuan was calm, showing no change of expression.

Su Bai Man transmitted to them: "If we can survive this ordeal, both of us will owe you a favor, as for compensation, we will pay you a sum that is sure to satisfy you. We hope that both of you can support us!"

"Don't worry, we will do our best." Fang Yuan transmitted in return.

In his mind, he had made his decision, he would just pretend to exert effort, only an idiot would help in such a dangerous and pointless request!

Su Bai Man nodded at Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, showing a hint of gratitude in her gaze.

"I am a wisdom path Gu Immortal, while Tai Bai Yun Sheng is skilled at healing, even if we perform badly later, we have sufficient reasons to justify ourselves." Fang Yuan stood out, standing with Shark Demon and Su Bai Man, facing Blazing Heaven Demoness who was at the surface of the sea.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed internally, standing beside Fang Yuan.

Blazing Heaven Demoness laughed lightly, with a look of nonchalance.

She stretched out her hand, opening her five fingers.

Suddenly.

With a soft sound, an orange-yellow flame appeared in her hand.

Blazing Heaven Demoness moved her fingers, rubbing the orange-yellow flame. This lump of flame was extraordinary, it was very elastic. Blazing Heaven Demoness squeezed it as if she was squeezing a meatball.

After a few breaths of time, the orange-yellow flame gradually formed into the appearance of a bird.

Blazing Heaven Demoness opened her hand as the fire bird jumped up from her palm, flapping its wings and chirping, happily fluttering around Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Blazing Heaven Demoness toyed around with the fire bird, not attacking, as if she had forgotten the agreement of three moves.

But be it Shark Demon, Su Bai Man, Fang Yuan or Tai Bai Yun Sheng, they showed extremely ugly expressions!

This fire bird had a cute appearance, but it was terrifyingly powerful in the eyes of the four Gu Immortals. Once released, it would unleash shocking might. Not just this underwater palace, the rest of this shark sea, countless living beings in a huge surrounding area of water might be exterminated by a single blow.

A rank eight Gu Immortal cannot be blocked by rank six or rank seven Gu Immortals.

The agreement of three moves was just a joke.

Just this one attack, Shark Demon and the rest could not defend against it.

"Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness, may I know what is the name of this move?" Shark Demon asked after a while, he spoke in a dispirited tone with a hint of hoarseness in his voice.

Blazing Heaven Demoness smiled lightly: "Hundreds of years ago, I was careless when cultivating and flames of anger were burning my heart, I almost lost my life. When I was recovering, I had an inspiration and created this rank eight level killer move. I named it — Angry Bird."

"Angry bird?" This joke-like name made Shark Demon feel some shock and also bitterness.

Undeniably, Blazing Heaven Demoness was doing this on purpose.

She wanted to display overwhelming strength to force Shark Demon to surrender.

This was a very crude method, but Blazing Heaven Demoness was too overbearing, she was straightforward and had incredible cultivation level, with her battle strength, it was an effective plan.

With just one move, Fang Yuan and the others had given up.

Only Shark Demon was still hanging on.

He said to the rest of them: "You three, retreat first, I will handle this move."

Before Fang Yuan and the others replied, Shark Demon took one step forward and said: "Angry bird, it is a good move, Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness, please attack!"

Blazing Heaven Demoness was shocked, she squinted as she asked in suspicion: "Are you sure you want to face this move?"

"Let's retreat." Su Bai Man's eyes shined with brilliance, she spoke to Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were surprised.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' move was incredibly powerful, there was no hope even if the four of them collaborated. Right now, Shark Demon was facing her alone, not only did he not want other people's help, even his wife Su Bai Man had such confidence in him!

What was he relying on?

"Alright, I want to see what is giving you courage!" Blazing Heaven Demoness no longer hesitated, at her will, the angry bird tore through the water, shooting towards Shark Demon.

But when it got to the bottom of the sea, a strong aura burst out, contesting Blazing Heaven Demoness equally!

Shark Demon showed a smiling expression, like his plan had succeeded.

Far away, Su Bai Man let out a sigh of relief, she explained to Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng: "Back then, we chose this location to build our underwater palace, we naturally had our reasons."

Chapter 920: Immemorial Desolate Beast, One Finger Flow Shark

A surging, vast aura!

Everyone's gazes were attracted to it.

The sea became turbulent and tides started to rise.

Countless undercurrents formed in the seabed and moved rapidly while intertwined together, like countless giant dragons or pythons.

Undercurrent vortex started forming and continued to increase in numbers sharply!

Soon, the dangerous vortexes numbered to thousands, filling this sea area.

"This is?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was startled.

"Immemorial desolate beast!" Fang Yuan's eyes brightened.

Ordinary wild beasts, hundred beast kings, thousand beast kings, myriad beast kings, beast emperors, desolate beasts, ancient desolate beasts, immemorial desolate beasts...

Among them, immemorial desolate beasts were powerful existences comparable to rank eight Gu Immortals!

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man stared fixedly at the center of this aura — there, the form of the immemorial desolate beast was gradually revealed.

The state of the enemy was unknown, Blazing Heaven Demoness also had no choice but to stop her attacks for the moment, recalling the small fire bird to her side.

The sea tides rose and fell along with the rough waves.

The surface of the sea became dangerous while the undercurrents flowed chaotically inside the sea.

Several breaths later, the mysterious immemorial desolate beast's true appearance was completely revealed.

This formidable immemorial desolate beast was unimaginably small and dainty looking.

It was so small that it was actually the size of an adult's finger.

This was a shark.

An extremely exquisite and cute shark.

The size of an adult's index finger.

Its whole body was shining with silver light. This light was not dazzling but mild, like a silk cloth that gently covered the small shark.

"Such a formidable aura, yet its body is like this..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed, having a strange expression at this sight.

Blazing Heaven Demoness, however, showed a trace of seriousness.

The small shark ignored Fang Yuan, Shark Demon and the rest behind it, from the start, its two eyes had been gazing at Blazing Heaven Demoness, revealing intense enmity.

Shark Demon let out a breath, and transmitted his voice to Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng: "My plan has fortunately succeeded... don't underestimate this small shark. It is a one finger flow shark."

"This is a one finger flow shark?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked surprised and shocked.

Ordinary Gu Immortals would not know of the one finger flow shark, but as a time path Gu Immortal, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had long since heard of its name.

In fact, almost all time path Gu Immortals knew a mnemonic — one finger flow shark, an instance of brilliance. Flowing water and clear voice, heaven is impartial.

It was no exaggeration to say that the one finger flow shark was known widely because of the mnemonic.

It was a rank eight time path desolate beast, bearing extremely large amounts of time path dao marks, thus it could swim in the river of time with its physical body!

"The one finger flow shark normally hides in the river of time and does not reveal itself. The two of us also found its tracks by chance. Later, we intentionally requested for this sea area from Zombie Alliance, and built this shark sea." Shark Demon continued to explain to Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Blazing Heaven Demoness suddenly chuckled: "So it was like that, no wonder you two stopped at no expense to exchange for an immortal killer move of the enslavement path grandmaster, Hundred and Eighty Slaves, from Zombie Alliance — Lower Controls Higher. It was to use this enslavement path killer move to subdue this one finger flow shark, right?"

Enslavement path had always been about enslaving higher beasts to control lower.

For instance, back when Fang Yuan was in Northern Plains, using Wolf King Chang Shan Yin's identity to participate in the contest of the imperial court, he had used myriad beast kings, thousand beast kings and so on to indirectly control the whole wolf army.

After all, one had a limited soul foundation, enslavement path Gu Masters could not directly control all the wild beasts.

The larger the scale of the beast group, the weaker the controlling power of the enslavement path Gu Master would be, the more their soul would have to endure and the less capable they would be in displaying skillful control.

But this was not absolute.

Gu are the essence of heaven and earth, man is the spirit of all living beings.

The wisdom of humans was undoubtedly at the top of all living beings.

In the long history of Gu cultivation, there once appeared an enslavement path grandmaster. He had a rough childhood, being born as a slave, and thus had very meager status. He used all the opportunities he obtained and took risks, continuously maturing and finally climbing to the pinnacle.

He was Hundred and Eighty Slaves.

A generation's genius.

Normal enslavement path methods were to use those of higher status to rule over lower status. But he did the opposite, using beasts of lower status to rule over those of a higher status.

This was not without reason.

For instance, an emperor was the ruler, welding absolute power, sitting high above. But sometimes, when the people are united and of one mind, the emperor would also be trapped by the people's will, and would be forced to do things against their own will.

Facing Blazing Heaven Demoness' speculation, Shark Demon nodded and frankly admitted: "You guessed right, that is the case. I have been constantly managing the shark groups in this sea area, it is to use these shark groups to subdue the one finger flow shark. Unfortunately, my enslavement path attainment is insufficient and I also don't have the Immortal Gu forming the killer move lower controls higher, thus, I haven't succeeded until now."

Hearing this, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not help but glance at each other.

Shark Demon had a huge target, his ambition truly was not small.

He was only a rank seven immortal zombie, but wanted to subdue an immemorial desolate beast.

Those able to advance to Gu Immortals indeed were not simple.

If he truly succeeded and had such an aid, Shark Demon could be considered half a rank eight Gu Immortal. His status would immediately rise, with fame and benefits flowing in rapidly.

Currently, he might not have succeeded, but he had made some achievements.

At the least, after this one finger flow shark appeared, it had not cared about Shark Demon's side, and instead directed all its hatred and anger to Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Shark Demon continued: "Moreover, this one finger flow shark is not only an immemorial desolate beast, it also contains several time path Immortal Gu!"

The intention of his words was to make Blazing Heaven Demoness aware of what she was dealing with and make her retreat.

This was not revealing information.

The one finger flow shark's body was overflowing with the aura of Immortal Gu without being concealed. Even Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng could clearly feel it, let alone the rank eight immortal zombie Blazing Heaven Demoness.

"It is rumored that the river of time is home to countless time path Gu worms. The one finger flow shark can freely move around in the river of time, thus having Immortal Gu is not strange." Tai Bai Yun Sheng whispered to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan thought of Red Lotus Demon Venerable's inheritance.

He had to move deep into the river of time to obtain Red Lotus Demon Venerable's inheritance. Maybe he could rely on the one finger flow shark's ability?

The one finger flow shark was extremely rare, and there were probably not many even in the river of time.

To put it in other words, this was a major opportunity that could not be sought out and only found through chance.

No wonder Shark Demon and Su Bai Man stopped at no expense, spending endless time and energy to obtain the one finger flow shark.

"Hahaha!" Shark Demon's words made Blazing Heaven Demoness laugh loudly, "Listening to what you say makes my urge to strike even stronger. Shark Demon! You want to rely on an outside force to make me retreat? To win without fighting? Hehe, wishful thinking!"

The moment she finished speaking, Blazing Heaven Demoness pointed with her finger.

The small fire bird perched on her shoulder suddenly moved, flying straight towards Shark Demon's direction.

"It's coming!" Shark Demon, Fang Yuan and the rest felt their hearts chill, their whole body turned tense as they became extremely vigilant.

The fire bird seemed harmless but in truth, its power was vast and extraordinary.

However, at this moment!

The one finger flow shark suddenly moved, resembling a silver firefly as it pounced at the fire bird.

The two were extremely fast, and in the blink of an eye, had already collided in the sea!

There was no sound and there was no explosion. The instant they collided, a strange thing occurred.

Both sides, which were extremely fast, suddenly stilled. Turning from extreme speed to extreme stillness, at that instant, the one finger flow shark and the small fire bird seemed to have transformed into a painting.

Such a transformation gave the spectators a feeling of being too abrupt.

Shortly, Fang Yuan and the rest saw the one finger flow shark slowly move, using its exquisite nose to lightly poke the small fire bird.

Afterwards, the one finger flow shark made an extremely elegant motion, its whole body leaped over the small fire bird and continued to swiftly move ahead.

In the blink of an eye, the stillness ended.

The speeds of the one finger flow shark and the small fire bird were restored.

However, the former had already moved past the small fire bird and was charging towards Blazing Heaven Demoness.

While the small fire bird was moving towards Shark Demon and the rest of the group.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man were already extremely alert and when they saw the small bird nearing them, they held their breaths, preparing to contend with it.

Fang Yuan was almost about to pull away and retreat, but right at this moment, the small fire bird suddenly flapped its wings and drew an arc as it turned around, chasing after the one finger flow shark.

"Such nimbleness!" Shark Demon was able to avoid this confrontation, but he was instead pale from shock.

'This small fire bird can move smoothly according to the controller's thoughts, it seems it is not a simple fire path killer move, there are definitely wisdom path methods mixed in it.' Fang Yuan analyzed rapidly.

"That scene just now should be because a certain time path Immortal Gu in the one finger flow shark activated. This Immortal Gu can cause the flow of time in a certain range to become extremely slow. It seemed like the two turned from extreme speed to almost complete stillness, but their speed had actually not changed." Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly said.

Su Bai Man nodded and added: "Not only that. When the one finger flow shark poked the fire bird's body, the Immortal Gu's aura had changed again, it should be the activation of the second time path Immortal Gu, it is just that its effect is unclear."

The moment she finished speaking, the effect showed up.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' expression suddenly changed, because the small fire bird chasing the one finger flow shark, had suddenly detonated.

Boom!

Like a crack of thunder resounded over the area.

Flames accompanied the surging blast, as it ferociously spread everywhere.

In an instant, an immense quantity of sea water evaporated and countless lives were lost.

A hemispherical crater formed over the whole sea.

When the fire bird had detonated, it had already flown out of the sea, but the bottom of the crater had unexpectedly touched the soil of the seabed.

Next, the surrounding seawater surged in to fill the gap.

Swoosh!

Tides surged, and huge waves stirred up in the sea. The soil on the seabed rolled and mixed in with the water, making visibility extremely poor.

Fang Yuan and the rest were in a rather miserable state, they had no choice but to fly out of the sea and float in the sky as they continued to watch the battle.

They saw the one finger flow shark shoot directly towards Blazing Heaven Demoness' face like a silver arrow.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' expression became more focused, how would she dare to take it head-on?

Man is the spirit of all livings beings, this phrase was not false, but when strength, recovery, speed and so on were compared, humans were not outstanding among the endless living beings.

Even after becoming Gu Immortals, they usually could not compare to desolate beasts.

The one finger flow shark was small, but it was an immemorial desolate beast, its small body concealed incomparably frightening brute strength!

Chapter 921: Big Fish Eat Small Fish

The one finger flow shark shot forward.

Blazing Heaven Demoness cultivated fire path, not strength path, she knew it would be hard to resist it head on.

However, she had extremely rich experience, and the sacrifice of the small fire bird had huge value, Fang Yuan and the rest had been able to get some information from it, Blazing Heaven Demoness naturally was not an exception.

Fire path killer move — Five Fingers Blazing Chains!

At that instant, Blazing Heaven Demoness had already made the most sensible decision.

She quickly retreated, while spreading open her right hand, her five fingers turned into five thin flames, they were like whips or chains as they moved to tie up the one finger flow shark.

The five fire chains were just about to coil around the one finger flow shark, when the previous scene occurred.

The time in the area around the one finger flow shark suddenly slowed down to an extreme.

However, as a time path desolate beast, this had lesser restriction on the one finger flow shark with its adapted traits and huge numbers of time path dao marks.

The five fire chains coiled around, but one finger flow shark swayed nimbly, moving through the tiny gaps in an inconceivable way before successfully getting past them.

It then charged towards Blazing Heaven Demoness, directly piercing through her forehead.

The exquisite shark was like a silver arrow as it pierced out of the back of Blazing Heaven Demoness' head!

"Success?" Su Bai Man was shocked as well as happy.

Shark Demon's eyes shined with a ferocious and restless light.

An immortal zombie's body did not have fatal points like normal Gu Immortals, but the head was one of them.

The thought processes of immortal zombies was slow, so they had to rely on wisdom path Gu worms to create thoughts and help them in their thinking.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' head was pierced, although not fatal, it was a serious injury.

'If the four of us can take this chance to attack...' The moment this thought appeared in Shark Demon's mind, the one finger flow shark changed its direction, shooting backwards as it pierced through Blazing Heaven Demoness' chest.

A dark fire burned and in the blink of an eye, the holes in Blazing Heaven Demoness' head and chest had been restored to their former states.

Even Fang Yuan was left speechless at this sight: "Such a formidable killer move, it can actually make the recovery so fast!"

Blazing Heaven Demoness covered her chest as she stared fixedly at the one finger flow shark, in spite of having been heavily injured, she was smiling: "Hehehe, interesting! This has three time path Immortal Gu, one can slow down time, one can speed up time and the last can change the perception of time."

Although she did not know what time path Immortal Gu they were and what were the limits of their power, Blazing Heaven Demoness was able to make some rough conjectures.

When the one finger flow shark collided with the small fire bird and dodged the five fire chains, it had used the first time path Immortal Gu to slow down time.

As for accelerating time, it used it when it poked the fire bird.

The fire bird could not be maintained for long, and a part of it had reached its limits after the one finger flow shark had hit it. The explosion of this part subsequently caused the explosions of the other parts, finally destroying the stable structure of the fire bird, causing the fire bird to explode, which almost dried up the surrounding parts of the sea area.

Finally, when the one finger flow shark pierced through Blazing Heaven Demoness' forehead and chest, it used the last time path Immortal Gu to influence Blazing Heaven Demoness' perception of time, causing her to not be able to dodge and take the attack directly.

Shark Demon's frown not only became deeper, he also felt the situation had turned bad.

The one finger flow shark indeed clearly had the auras of three Immortal Gu.

In just a few moves, Blazing Heaven Demoness had already probed the details of the one finger flow shark.

This was a clear display of this rank eight Gu Immortal's extremely formidable proficiency in fighting.

At the same time, it also showed the superiority of immortal killer moves to Immortal Gu.

Gu worms had one ability, others could often find the details of the Immortal Gu after it was used just once.

However, immortal killer moves were different. They were a combination of countless Gu worms, not only did this conceal the core Immortal Gu, enemies would also find it harder to counter the effect.

Just like Shark Demon expected, as the fight continued, Blazing Heaven Demoness changed her battle tactics.

She split into five or six clones, each was lifelike, the one finger flow shark was tired out rushing this way and that, its offensive was seemingly impressive but it was actually being played by these clones to move around in circles.

"Wild beast are wild beasts in the end, they don't have enough wisdom."

"If it had an investigative Immortal Gu, maybe it could see through these clones, a pity...."

"It looks like the battle situation is set, Blazing Heaven Demoness has already obtained the advantage."

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng secretly conversed, analyzing the battle situation.

It could be said that at this stage, the battle had already lost any suspense.

Regarding the one finger flow shark, its real chance had been during the initial stages. If it could have used this opportunity when Blazing Heaven Demoness was still unaware of its trump cards, it perhaps could have killed her.

But now that Blazing Heaven Demoness had probed out its cards, she had changed her tactics and immediately took over the battle situation.

Unless there was an outside interference, this battle would have only one possible outcome.

'The only outside forces at present are Shark Demon and Su Bai Man. But do they truly have the courage to go against a rank eight expert?' Fang Yuan glanced at the immortal zombie couple and inwardly shook his head as he saw their hesitant looks.

The true chance had been the instant Blazing Heaven Demoness' head was pierced.

But Shark Demon already lost this chance.

Although his name included the word 'demon', he lacked the mentality of taking risk in spite of danger. It could be because he had been part of Zombie Alliance for too long and lost the enthusiasm to fight by himself. It could also be that he had misgivings about dragging down Su Bai Man.

Even Shark Demon and Su Bai Man, as the people involved, were like this. Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, who were just external aid, would be even more unlikely to take this risk.

After secretly communicating for a while, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng made the decision to act according to the circumstances and look to retreat when there was a chance.

"Sirs, please make your moves! We are unable to distinguish the clones of Blazing Heaven Demoness. Sirs, if you have a method, please break this deception for the one finger flow shark and point out the location of the true body of Blazing Heaven Demoness. This will make the situation turn for the better." At this moment, Su Bai Man suddenly transmitted her voice, requesting earnestly.

At the same time, Shark Demon also added: "If you can succeed, we will reward you heavily, you won't regret it!"

Without any consideration, Fang Yuan refused with a bitter smile: "Lady Su Bai Man overestimates us, you two have been rank seven Gu Immortals for many years with plenty of methods and deep foundation, we are unable to match you. Even you two don't have a way to solve this, how can the two of us be of any help?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng, similarly, shook his head: "I only specialize in healing, this matter regarding investigation is beyond my ability."

Su Bai Man did not say anything more while Shark Demon gave a gloomy look at Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng, his expression clearly not pleased.

Fang Yuan snorted inwardly, feeling disdain towards Shark Demon and Su Bai Man.

Honestly speaking, it was not that Blazing Heaven Demoness' method could not be resolved.

But Shark Demon and Su Bai Man did not make a move.

It was because the other party was a rank eight great expert, once they moved to help the one finger flow shark, it definitely meant they would attract Blazing Heaven Demoness' fury and her counterattack.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man feared Blazing Heaven Demoness and did not want to make a move, wanting to preserve some leeway, thus they wanted to make Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng cannon fodder.

How could Fang Yuan be stupid enough to be used by others like this?

Thus, his reply had deep intentions.

Both sides were astute, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man realized Fang Yuan had seen through their plot, so they did not attempt to persuade any further.

"Now it seems the truly terrifying one is still Blazing Heaven Demoness!" Fang Yuan gazed at the distant battlefield, not concealing his fearful expression.

It was rumored that Blazing Heaven Demoness had a great killer move called blazing heaven.

In the past, she had fought with the rank eight Heavenly Lord Bai Zu in Northern Plains over possession of a certain fragment world of the immemorial nine heavens, but in the end she failed, despite being on the verge of success.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was so furious, she used the killer move blazing heaven to directly burn down the whole fragment world, annihilating countless living beings.

If I can't have it, you can also stop dreaming about it!

Heavenly Lord Bai Zu's hard work and plans all turned to dust at the last moment.

Northern Plains Zombie Alliance belonged to the righteous path, Blazing Heaven Demoness, however, blatantly had taken a demonic path action. Thus, after burning down the fragment world, she incited public outrage.

Blazing Heaven Demoness withstood the pressure without any fear, even proclaiming that if anyone continued to make a fuss, she would burn down that person's blessed land.

Since she could even burn down a fragment world of the immemorial nine heavens, burning down a blessed land was clearly a simple matter.

The righteous path choked on their words, as they unexpectedly discovered they could do nothing to this brazen Blazing Heaven Demoness!

At rank eight, one could be an overlord. If they truly shed off all pretenses and started sneak attacking and harassing, any force would feel an incomparable headache.

Helpless.

Even if the other party was an immortal zombie, she was a rank eight great expert after all. Although her battle strength could not match a normal rank eight, it could not be looked down upon and was not someone they could force.

If they went beyond the limit, and Blazing Heaven Demoness decided to attack, these righteous path forces with many assets to take care of would be the ones to suffer.

Those with a bottom line are afraid of those with no bottom line, those who follow the rules are afraid of those who don't.

After this matter, Blazing Heaven Demoness' name spread throughout Northern Plains, Northern Plains Zombie Alliance was able to hold their heads high and no one could bully them. It was only after Blazing Heaven Demoness left Northern Plains to look for fortuitous encounters in Eastern Sea that Northern Plains Zombie Alliance fell back into a predicament.

It could be said that Blazing Heaven Demoness had single-handedly brought Northern Plains Zombie Alliance to power and glory.

Now, Blazing Heaven Demoness was fighting against the one finger flow shark without even using her signature killer moves. She clearly had a lot of spare strength left.

Fang Yuan even had a slight suspicion that Blazing Heaven Demoness had intentionally used the clone technique to try to lure Shark Demon and the rest to attack, thus finding another excuse to make trouble.

Although Shark Demon was not duped, Blazing Heaven Demoness' move had created a rift between Fang Yuan and Shark Demon.

The one finger flow shark, an immemorial desolate beast with three time path Immortal Gu, Blazing Heaven Demoness was not only dealing with it easily, but she had successfully plotted against Shark Demon, Fang Yuan and the rest who were observing the battle.

It was clear that Blazing Heaven Demoness had outstanding battle strength along with skill in strategy.

This type of enemy was extremely hard to deal with.

To put it in other words, Gu Immortals who could slowly climb up from rank one to rank eight were certain to not be idiots, each of them were true experts rich in both wisdom and battle strength.

As the battle progressed, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man's expressions became even more gloomy.

They had already secretly sent requests for reinforcements to Zombie Alliance's headquarters at the start of the battle.

The battle had lasted for so long that those who should have come would have already arrived, but no reinforcements had arrived.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had not arrived rashly, she had already bribed those in charge and made sufficient preparations, which was why Shark Demon and Su Bai Man's requests for reinforcements were ineffective.

Shark Demon even guessed that Blazing Heaven Demoness had already reached an agreement of sharing profits with the highest ranking members of Zombie Alliance.

In an instant, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man's hearts sank to rock bottom, their intent to battle kept lowering and the anger in them gradually dissipated, leaving behind extreme bleakness.

Big fish eat small fish, small fish eat shrimps, this was the normal course of behavior in this world of Gu.

This couple, who had been big fish since the beginning, now became small fish in front of Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Rank eight!

How could they match her?

Let alone when Blazing Heaven Demoness not only had such strength, she also had matching intelligence!

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man simply did not have any hope no matter how hard they struggled.

Sigh...

Shark Demon heaved a long sigh before he suddenly lowered his head: "Enough, Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness, please stop. We are not capable enough, in consideration of Zombie Alliance's situation, it would be better if you lead us to take down Yu Lu blessed land."

"Hehehe, Shark Demon, you know when to advance or retreat, very good." Blazing Heaven Demoness' laughter came from above the battlefield.

Her laughter stopped, and the fake bodies in the battlefield burned until there was nothing remaining.

Without a target to attack, the one finger flow shark stayed dazedly in place, seemingly at a loss on what to do.

Shark Demon heaved another sigh, as he pursed his lips and let out hooting sounds.

The one finger flow shark was pacified, it lightly swung its tail as it dived into the sea again and soon disappeared.

Clearly, it had gone back to the river of time.

Shark Demon's method gave a shock to outsiders like Fang Yuan.

Shark Demon's influence over the one finger flow shark was already quite remarkable. Given some time, he might truly be able to control this immemorial desolate beast.

At that time, the three time path Immortal Gu on the one finger flow shark would naturally fall into Shark Demon's hands.

Blazing Heaven Demoness revealed her true body, she gave a deep look at Shark Demon before turning her gaze towards Fang Yuan.

"You are Xing Xiang Zi?"

"I am."

Blazing Heaven Demoness announced with a forceful tone that allowed no refusal: "From now onwards, I have enlisted you. In the following invasion of Yu Lu blessed land, you must use your full capabilities, I won't allow any slacking!"

Chapter 922: Conclusion of the Hundred Days Battle

Hearing Blazing Heaven Demoness command him so overbearingly, Fang Yuan was not angry at all.

On the contrary, he was somewhat pleased.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man, this couple had put in a lot of effort to attack Yu Lu blessed land. In the end, right before they obtained the fruits of their labor, Blazing Heaven Demoness forcefully took them for herself, they were really pitiful.

Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had put in so much, almost all of their life savings had been invested into it.

After getting robbed by Blazing Heaven Demoness, they were heavily crippled, they lost a great deal.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man died while shark sea was invaded by others, was this part of the cause?

But Fang Yuan did not feel distaste for Blazing Heaven Demoness' actions, he also did not feel pity towards the predicament of Shark Demon and Su Bai Man.

If he had Blazing Heaven Demoness' cultivation level, he might have been more overbearing in his actions.

Big fish eat small fish, this was the rule of the cultivation world, it was bloodthirsty and cruel.

But any person who was older and had more experience would understand — this was the norm, it extended to all parts of nature.

Even before Fang Yuan transmigrated, the human society on Earth was the same.

When benefits were involved, friends would betray each other, brothers would become enemies, this was all too common.

The only difference was, they used excuses to make their actions seem grand and righteous. The truth was, there were people who, on the surface, were virtuous, but in the dark, they were dirty and despicable.

But this was not wrong.

To survive and reproduce was the nature of all living beings.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness' interference created a huge impact that would influence Fang Yuan's plans.

"Blazing Heaven Demoness has high cultivation level, she is also astute and calculative, more difficult to deal with than Shark Demon and Su Bai Man by a hundredfold. But she has quite a lot of wealth, maybe she can subsidize me in refining star thought Immortal Gu? There is also another advantage: Getting close to her would give me a greater chance of returning to Northern Plains Zombie Alliance and entering Earth Trench, in order to get that treasure."

In a breath of time, Fang Yuan had already thought matters through.

The moment Blazing Heaven Demoness finished her words, Fang Yuan cupped his fists, smiling bitterly: "I would not dare to defy Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness' orders. But I have my difficulties. I had just mentioned this to Lord Shark Demon earlier, in order to unravel the final battlefield killer move, I will need to refine a rank six wisdom path Immortal Gu first."

Shark Demon snorted coldly.

Fang Yuan had changed sides rather too quickly.

Su Bai Man thought to herself: This Xing Xiang Zi seemed to be a gentleman ordinarily, but to think that he was without a backbone, he could fawn and bend over to others to curry favor, he had no integrity at all!

Fang Yuan did not care about their thoughts. They were already out of this game. Meanwhile, Fang Yuan, who joined partway, managed to stay.

Seeing Fang Yuan's straightforward gaze, Blazing Heaven Demoness rubbed her chin, she smiled with deep meaning: "You want to refine Immortal Gu... hehehe, this is easy, I will fund you!"

Northern Plains, Luo Po valley.

Another earth-shaking intense battle had just reached its end.

As the battlefield, Luo Po valley was in bad shape, crushed rocks were everywhere, it was as if this was the aftermath of both an earthquake and a hurricane.

The Gu Immortals from Central Continent had various injuries, they were focusing their attentions on Feng Jiu Ge right now.

Admiration, trepidation, confusion, heaviness, fear, complexity, they had a number of different emotions.

"Feng Jiu Ge won again!"

"His opponent is Qin Bai Sheng, but even with his strength, he could not resist Feng Jiu Ge's powerful attacks."

"He has already won seven battles in a row, Qin Bai Sheng is completely at a disadvantage against Feng Jiu Ge."

"The hundred days battle, only after a hundred days did we see its results."

"Honestly speaking, Qin Bai Sheng is immensely strong, but he actually faced off against an even stronger opponent, Feng Jiu Ge!"

Looking at the time, Central Continent's gang had reached Luo Po valley and attacked it for over three months, met with the stubborn resistance of Shadow Sect's Qin Bai Sheng and others.

Hundred days battle!

This was a true hundred days battle.

Under normal circumstances, Gu Immortals would not fight for such a long time.

In terms of scale, there were more than ten Gu Immortals from Central Continent and Northern Plains involved, they were all shining experts. One could say, for the last thousand years in the five regions, there had not been a battle of such scale.

If this was announced, the world would be shaken, commotions would arise, the attentions of innumerable observers would gather on them.

But it was a pity, be it the Central Continent Gu Immortals who were investigating secretly, or the hidden Shadow Sect which sought to remain in the dark, they did not want this battle to be exposed.

Thus, this battle that should have shaken the whole of the five regions remained a secret from start to finish.

Regarding this, the two sides had a sort of tacit understanding.

Ever since the hundred days battle started, the crucial members had always been Feng Jiu Ge and Qin Bai Sheng.

Initially, they were equally matched, it was a stalemate. Qin Bai Sheng, who had the territorial advantage and the battlefield killer move hundred million slaughterfield, showed a slight edge.

But after that, Feng Jiu Ge got stronger as he fought, he displayed his immense talent and ability.

The two sides gradually became even, then Feng Jiu Ge expanded his advantage little by little.

Eventually, in the last few days, Feng Jiu Ge's battle strength had risen after a long period of intense fighting, and finally defeated Qin Bai Sheng.

One or two wins was nothing. But winning seven fights consecutively, it proved that Feng Jiu Ge firmly had obtained the advantage.

The Shadow Sect members slowly retreated to the deepest part of Luo Po valley.

"A desperate foe should not be pursued." Feng Jiu Ge stood proudly at the front, seeing that their enemies had hidden into the valley, he spoke calmly.

His expression was pale, he had over a dozen injuries on him, blood was dripping from the corners of his mouth and his eyebrows.

His originally brimming Gu Immortal aura had weakened to an all time low.

But all these could not obscure the brilliance in his eyes.

Every time he fought Qin Bai Sheng, it was a difficult and dangerous fight. But it was because of these tough fights that Feng Jiu Ge could be polished, like a rock polishing a jade and turning it brighter.

Ever since Feng Jiu Ge joined Spirit Affinity House, he rarely had the chance to engage in such intense fights.

Spirit Affinity House was one of the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, Feng Jiu Ge had a high status and reputation, nobody wanted to find trouble with him.

This battle that went on for a hundred days would make other Gu Immortals feel pain and anguish, but Feng Jiu Ge felt a nostalgic euphoria.

This made him think about the splendid times when he was still in the demonic path.

But, there was a slight regret in his heart.

"Demonic path... using all of my strength to fight... it is a pity, I can no longer return to such an exciting time."

Right now, Feng Jiu Ge had a family, he could not take risks easily. Furthermore, these Gu Immortals behind him were from the other nine sects, their intentions were hard to decipher. If Feng Jiu Ge really got heavily injured after fighting, who knew what actions they would take.

Feng Jiu Ge remembered what his wife, Bai Qing, had instructed him.

After all, back then, Feng Jiu Ge had challenged all ten sects and made them lose their faces. After joining Spirit Affinity House, he had been suppressing the other nine sects without giving them any chance to overturn the situation.

Whenever Feng Jiu Ge spoke, the other immortals had to listen.

After the hundred days battle, Feng Jiu Ge's reputation was already deeply ingrained into everyone's hearts.

Cough cough cough...

After Qin Bai Sheng retreated into the valley, he started to cough uncontrollably.

His expression was pale as paper, each time he coughed, there was blood.

"Your injuries are getting more severe!" Fairy Jiang Yu, who was holding him, said in worry, she was frowning tightly.

"Feng Jiu Ge is too despicable!" He Lang Zi, who had lost an arm, growled angrily: "Even though he is fighting you alone on the surface, he is actually getting his people to act like they are charging ahead, threatening our defenses and forcing you to be distracted. If not for that, why would you lose consecutively?"

Qin Bai Sheng said grimly: "Say no more. Winner takes all, a loss is a loss, there is no need for excuses."

"This Feng Jiu Ge truly has immense talent, using his own understanding, he created his personal sound path killer move and got to this stage. Even as an enemy, I am truly in admiration. Using his own advantages to scheme, plot, and gather superiority, that is the way of fighting, if he did not use these methods, I would have looked down on him."

Saying this, Qin Bai Sheng coughed again, spitting out a huge pool of warm blood.

He gasped weakly, looking around him.

After the hundred days battle, only five were left, Hui Feng Zi, Hei Cheng, Jiang Yu, He Lang Zi, and the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal.

Originally, they had Xue Song Zi, but when they attacked Lang Ya blessed land, he was killed by Fang Yuan.

After leaving Lang Ya blessed land, two hairy man Gu Immortals joined them, but both of them were killed by the Central Continent Gu Immortals in the hundred days battle.

However, the Central Continent Gu Immortals suffered greater losses.

Old Oracle from Ancient Soul Sect, as well as two Gu Immortals from Spirit Butterfly Valley and Combat Immortal Sect had died.

Trying to take advantage of Qin Bai Sheng, how could that be possible?

Even Central Continent's ten great ancient sects had suffered heavy losses.

But at this point, the most crucial member, the pillar of support, Qin Bai Sheng, was heavily injured, Luo Po valley's territorial advantage had been overcome, the remaining five Gu Immortals knew — the hundred days battle had ended, they were the losers!

Qin Bai Sheng tried to improve their mindsets: "Even though we lost the battle, it is not over yet. Feng Jiu Ge's group is not united, they cannot fight us wholeheartedly, I successfully stalled for enough time. We just need to wait for one more night, when that Immortal Gu matures in the valley, we would have achieved our goal. Tomorrow, all five of you will charge out, I will stall these people from Central Continent."

"Lord Qin Bai Sheng!" Everyone was shocked.

Qin Bai Sheng's decision was simply courting death.

This was hard to understand.

From their perspectives, if it was Hui Feng Zi, Hei Cheng or He Lang Zi, they would definitely only care about their own lives when they were in this state. Why would they care about others?

Or, was this a trap?

Hui Feng Zi, Hei Cheng, and He Lang Zi kept their thoughts to themselves, they looked at the three people from Shadow Sect secretly

Qin Bai Sheng, Jiang Yu, and the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal, they were the core of Shadow Sect, the others were just outside reinforcements.

Silence ensued.

Everyone walked to their resting places.

"This will be it. Use this time to rest, tomorrow, your performances will decide whether you succeed in breaking out or not." Qin Bai Sheng waved his hand weakly, dismissing them.

Hei Cheng, Hui Feng Zi, and He Lang Zi, felt very heavy, their gazes was uncertain.

The three wordlessly decided to rest together, they were guarding against the possible betrayal of Shadow Sect.

But late into the night, the three were summoned by Qin Bai Sheng.

Chapter 923: Breaking Out

Late at night, in Luo Po valley.

Qin Bai Sheng and the other five immortals gathered.

Qin Bai Sheng handed an Immortal Gu to the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal openly: "This Immortal Gu is very important, I am entrusting it to you now!"

The black robed Gu Immortal nodded.

He was wrapped in a shroud of obscurity, even up until this point, none of the Gu Immortals outside of Shadow Sect had seen his appearance. They only knew that he had outstanding battle strength, around the upper tier of rank seven.

Qin Bai Sheng turned around, instructing Jiang Yu seriously: "I can die, you can also die. But he is needed for the plan, we cannot lose him!"

Fairy Jiang Yu nodded solemnly in return: "I can only guarantee that before I die, he will not perish!"

Hei Cheng and the others listened in astonishment.

What sort of organization was Shadow Sect? It could make these Gu Immortal disregard losses to themselves, even if they had to sacrifice their lives, they had to complete the mission!

To make Gu Immortals so loyal, it was difficult for even super forces to achieve.

This was an unimaginable matter!

A moment later, the silent Luo Po valley erupted into thunderous explosions.

An intensely loud sound filled the whole valley.

At the same time, there was a shrill warning — "Enemy attack!"

Fairy Ling Mei, who was warning them, retreated continuously.

In front of her, Jiang Yu, Hui Feng Zi, He Lang Zi, Hei Cheng, and the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal attacked jointly!

The enemy was attacking with such force, how could Fairy Ling Mei defend against them, she only had one thought, that was to escape!

Fairy Ling Mei came from Heaven's Envy Manor, she and Fairy Ao Xue had control over the rank seven crescent moon Gu, they could unleash the killer move peerless crescent moon slash if they cooperated.

Peerless crescent moon slash was extremely powerful, it was one of the signature famous killer moves of Heaven's Envy Manor.

Fairy Ao Xue and Fairy Ling Mei had always been together constantly, they were hardly ever separated.

But now, because there were limited people in Central Continent's group, they had to encircle the huge area of Luo Po valley, thus, Ling Mei and Ao Xue had no choice but to split up.

Once Shadow Sect's group burst out, Fairy Ling Mei was caught off guard, she fought alone and fell into an extremely dangerous situation.

"Kill her!" Fairy Jiang Yu who was at the lead of the five Gu Immortals, was bursting with killing intent, her eyes were red and her attacks were fierce.

Even though Fairy Ling Mei was a peerless beauty with grand elegance, none of the five Gu Immortals showed her any mercy because of it.

Their killer moves were used in succession, they would only stop after Fairy Ling Mei was dead.

At the moment between life and death, Fairy Ling Mei resolutely chose to destroy an Immortal Gu, stalling three breaths of time for her.

During this period, Fairy Ling Mei activated a Gu formation, her body vanished amidst the wind and rain, at the next moment, she appeared far away.

"Huff! Huff! Huff!"

Fairy Ling Mei breathed roughly, her face was pale.

She had escaped with her life, her face showed lingering fear, her back was covered in cold sweat.

"So close, so close. I was at the moment between life and death, it is all thanks to this Gu formation!" Fairy Ling Mei felt gratitude inside.

This Gu formation was set up by Gu Immortal Hong Chi Ming after putting in a lot of effort.

Hong Chi Ming came from Wind Cloud Manor, one of the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, he was skilled in Gu formations and was famous in Central Continent.

Gu formations had a point of inferiority to killer moves in that they could not be activated instantly. They took a long time to activate, and were not flexible enough to be used for a wide range of applications in intense battles. However, once they were activated, they would provide a huge advantage, they were often faster than immortal killer moves and expended less resources.

Precisely because of this, Fairy Ling Mei survived.

Seeing that Fairy Ling Mei had escaped, Fairy Jiang Yu sighed internally.

The other four Gu Immortals also showed regretful looks.

Earlier, during the hundred days battle, Ling Mei and Ao Xue had collaborated to unleash peerless crescent moon slash, they were a huge threat to Shadow Sect, almost all the Gu Immortals were injured by this move to varying degrees.

Unfortunately, Shadow Sect initially had the territorial advantage. However, Central Continent took down their Gu formations one by one, and now, the Central Continent Gu Immortals created their own Gu formations, the outer area of Luo Po valley was now their territory.

"Since we can't kill her, we will continue charging out!" Fairy Jiang Yu shouted.

She moved with determination and resolution.

Ling Mei retreated, Central Continent's side immediately had a gap in their defenses.

They needed to break out of this encirclement quickly, the chance was slipping!

"Ling Mei, are you alright?!" Fairy Ao Xue wore a white blouse, she came over quickly, showing shock and anger on her face.

"We won't let you go, die here!" Chen Zhen Chi shouted.

"Isn't it too late now to want to leave?" Bu Fei Yan sneered.

Even though Fairy Ao Xue and Fairy Ling Mei were separated, they were situated quite closely, thus, she could arrive first.

As for Chen Zhen Chi and Bu Fei Yan, they could reach at the same time as Fairy Ao Xue because they had incredible speed.

"Zhen Chi of the nine heavens, followed by Fei Yan... damn it!" Hei Cheng gritted his teeth, feeling great pressure.

Chen Zhen Chi and Bu Fei Yan were two famous flying grandmasters in the current Central Continent Gu Immortal world. 'Zhen Chi of the nine heavens' referred to Myriad Dragon Dock's Chen Zhen Chi, while 'followed by Fei Yan' was speaking about Heavenly Lotus Sect's Bu Fei Yan.

Jiang Yu and the other immortals wanted to break out of this place, their biggest concern were the pursuers excelling in speed like these two.

Seeing the three of them get close, the five immortals on Shadow Sect's side did not even say a thing, they only focused on breaking out.

At this moment, a wall of light appeared, blocking the five immortals.

It was the activation of a Gu formation.

This was the work of Wind Cloud Manor's Hong Chi Ming!

Although Hong Chi Ming was not inside, his voice was heard from within the Gu formation: "Lord Feng Jiu Ge had already predicted that you would break out. Surrender now and we might spare your lives!"

Once he said this, an immensely powerful aura got closer to them like a rushing dragon.

This aura was so grand and magnificent, Shadow Sect's members were familiar with it, it was Feng Jiu Ge, they felt cold sweat breaking out as they showed panic on their faces.

After the hundred days battle, the five immortals knew clearly, even if they worked together, they were not Feng Jiu Ge's match.

Was their attempt at escaping going to fail?

When the five immortals were close to despair, a golden arrow shot over, piercing the wall of light that obstructed them.

Far away, Hong Chi Ming's body shook and jolted, as if he was shocked by electricity, he spat out a mouthful of blood, suffering a heavy injury.

The one who shot the golden arrow was Qin Bai Sheng.

How could he watch as the five immortals failed? Thus, he forcefully moved his wounded body, blocking Ling Mei, Ao Xue, Chen Zhen Chi, and Bu Fei Yan.

The four Central Continent Gu Immortals arrived quickly but also lost quickly.

They did not just lose, they failed completely.

Like Feng Jiu Ge, Qin Bai Sheng was not someone the other Central Continent Gu Immortals could stop.

Qin Bai Sheng did not kill the four immortals from Central Continent, he allowed them to retreat. His attention was primarily focused on Feng Jiu Ge.

Feng Jiu Ge's gaze was shining, he had already understood Qin Bai Sheng's injury.

He smiled with much elegance, saying: "You are all rushing about, it is inappropriate to leave without saying goodbye. If you want to leave, you should at least listen to my parting song, right?"

Immortal killer move — Green Jade Song!

The five immortals on Shadow Sect's side retreated, someone cried out in pain while another grunted.

Green jade song's mysterious power affected the five immortals to an extent. After being hit, their bodies slowly turned into jade, and the area was spreading continuously.

The five immortals were resolute figures, they knew this was a problem and immediately shattered or dug out their contaminated flesh.

At once, blood flowed like a river.

Immortal killer move — Soul Suppression!

At the next moment, Qin Bai Sheng struck, his powerful soul path technique was aimed at Feng Jiu Ge's face, pressuring him.

Feng Jiu Ge's expression changed, he quickly defended himself.

Qin Bai Sheng had two major trump cards, one was the soul path killer move soul suppression, the other was the sword path killer move five finger fist heart sword. Once used, ordinary Gu Immortals could not even endure one hit from him.

Feng Jiu Ge had three trump cards, the first was heaven and earth song, second was green jade song, and third was submission song. Not only were they powerful and grand, they were also profound and mystical.

Feng Jiu Ge's attention was drawn, green jade song halted as the five immortals felt their pressure decreasing, they quickly rushed away for a distance.

Qin Bai Sheng used a metal path killer move again.

Golden chains coiled around Feng Jiu Ge's limbs, tying him up tightly.

Feng Jiu Ge was not frightened.

During the hundred days battle, the two had learned a lot about each other. Qin Bai Sheng's metal path killer move had little effect on Feng Jiu Ge.

The golden chains were much more effective against Chen Zhen Chi and others. Against Feng Jiu Ge, he only needed a breath of time before shattering them.

But at this moment, Qin Bai Sheng showed a wry smile on his face: "I'll let you see the true secret within Luo Po valley now."

Saying this, he used his method and activated something.

Countless mystical lights shot out from the valley, one of them hit Feng Jiu Ge.

"This is?!" Feng Jiu Ge shattered the golden chains, but because this used up his time, he could not dodge the mystical light and was immobilized.

"The power of space path!"

"How can this be so strong?"

Not far away, the two fairies, Ling Mei and Ao Xue, were also hit by the mystical light, their expressions changed as they gasped.

As for Chen Zhen Chi and Bu Fei Yan, they were extremely fast, they dodged the mystical light.

Qin Bai Sheng did not care about them, his main goal was to restrict Feng Jiu Ge. Right now, half of his goal had been achieved.

"Don't struggle. This light is harmless!" Feng Jiu Ge understood at once, he shouted as he reminded them.

Ao Xue and Ling Mei were uncertain, but at the next moment, they saw that Feng Jiu Ge stopped resisting and was dragged into a deep part of Luo Po valley by the mystical light.

Qin Bai Sheng's smile became wider, he approached a mystical light and was dragged into the valley as well.

Ao Xue and Ling Mei looked at each other, they gritted their teeth, deciding to believe Feng Jiu Ge, they stopped resisting as they entered the valley as well.

This change of events was out of everyone's expectations.

They were only stunned for a moment before Chen Zhen Chi reacted and shouted at the Shadow Sect immortals: "Take them down first!"

This was a wise decision.

Seeing that they were about to break out, the five Shadow Sect immortals were held back by Chen Zhen Chi and Bu Fei Yan.

Next, Hong Chi Ming, Old Lord Can Yang, and Old Man Tian Long arrived, engaging in fierce combat.

One side fought desperately to leave, while the other side desperately prevented their escape.

"Ah, someone save me!" Hei Cheng shouted, he was the weakest here, he was hit by a move and had been detached from the main party.

"Ignore him, protect our main target, continue to break out!" Fairy Jiang Yu shouted, she heartlessly abandoned Hei Cheng, protecting the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal with all her effort.

At the same time.

Deep within Luo Po valley, in a mysterious place.

"Where is this?" Ao Xue and Ling Mei looked around in shock and suspicion.

"So this was it." Feng Jiu Ge who had entered before them had already retracted his gaze: "This is actually a hidden Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable true inheritance!"

Chapter 924: Discarding this Ruined Body to Exchange for a Clear Breeze

In the mystical area, light shined warmly, there were no mountains or rivers, neither wind nor land, it was completely blank.

"That is true." Once Feng Jiu Ge spoke, Qin Bai Sheng appeared in front of him, looking at the three immortals from Central Continent, he smiled deeply: "If not for Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's arrangement, how could I lure brother Feng here?"

Indeed.

Even though Qin Bai Sheng was very powerful, he was still at a loss against a one in a thousand years monster like Feng Jiu Ge.

Especially when Qin Bai Sheng's two trump cards were not for trapping enemies, they were for killing.

To temporarily trap Feng Jiu Ge, he had to activate the arrangements that Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had personally set up in the past.

"This really is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance?" Fairy Ling Mei asked in a heated tone.

Since ancient times, in the long history of Gu cultivators, there were countless geniuses and heroes. But if these people were akin to shining stars in the sky, then the ten rank nine Gu Immortals were each like the sun, they were bright and dazzling, spreading their radiance over the whole world.

Every generation's venerable, be it an Immortal Venerable or a Demon Venerable, was at the peak of that era, they dominated the world and were invincible, unparalleled in their time.

Among them, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was also a legend. He excelled in space path and had unparalleled stealing abilities. He even cultivated transformation path simultaneously and was skilled at disguises, before he was rank nine, he could transform into all sorts of people and use their identities to achieve his unspeakable motives, he even caused huge commotions over the world, sending it into chaos.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable also had a close relationship with Long Hair Ancestor. The failure to refine space escape Gu became Long Hair Ancestor's obsession after death, it had become a legend.

Such a person, his inheritance, was actually before them!

Be it Ling Mei or Ao Xue, these two fairies who had icy hearts felt excited, their hearts were burning with ambition.

But Feng Jiu Ge quickly discouraged them: "Don't even think about it. Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance is not something you can obtain."

Ling Mei and Ao Xue's expressions changed.

That's right, there was still Feng Jiu Ge and Qin Bai Sheng here, with these two experts around, how could Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance become theirs?

At once, Ling Mei and Ao Xue felt great disappointment.

Feng Jiu Ge's back was facing them, he stood in front of them but understood their emotions, he continued: "You misunderstand my words. Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance has a strict requirement, both of you do not fulfill it, I do not fulfill it, and even brother Qin also has no chance of inheriting it."

Ling Mei and Ao Xue were shocked, one of them asked: "There is such a thing?"

Qin Bai Sheng laughed loudly: "Brother Feng really knows a lot about Thieving Heaven's true inheritance. It seems the rumors are true, Spirit Affinity House indeed possesses one of the true inheritances of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable. They have been researching it for a long time, a pity there have been no gains."

Feng Jiu Ge's eyes shined with brilliance, he stared at Qin Bai Sheng, admitting: "To think that brother Qin knows so much about Central Continent's details despite living in Northern Plains. That is true, my sect controls a true inheritance of Thieving Heaven and have been researching it for many years, we have learned some things after these years."

Ling Mei and Ao Xue looked at each other, they were unwilling to give up, Fairy Ling Mei asked: "May I ask Lord Feng Jiu Ge, what is the criteria to inherit it, maybe we can achieve it, who knows."

Feng Jiu Ge's gaze had been fixed on Qin Bai Sheng, he did not dare to be careless.

He said: "Do you know Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's origin? He is not a person of the five regions, he is from the outside world, an otherworldly demon. Thus, the inheritances that he left behind only have one requirement towards the inheritor, they have to be an otherworldly demon! I am obviously not one, brother Qin cannot be one, otherwise he would have inherited it long ago, why would he wait until now? Are you two otherworldly demons?"

Before Ling Mei and Ao Xue replied, Qin Bai Sheng flicked his sleeves and laughed, he denied the possibility: "Impossible! All the Gu Immortals in the hundred days battle are not otherworldly demons. If not, why would I let any of you in here?"

"Otherworldly demons? They really exist? Since the start of my life, I have never seen one."

"Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was actually an otherworldly demon?"

Ling Mei and Ao Xue were taken aback.

Feng Jiu Ge nodded: "Even though otherworldly demons are rare, they exist. Since they come from beyond our world, then outside of the five regions and nine heavens, there are bound to be other worlds. Unfortunately, no one has ever ventured out of the Gu world."

Ling Mei and Ao Xue looked at each other, they asked again:

"Other than the five regions, there are really other worlds outside?"

"Even if we cannot achieve this condition, the inheritance is fixed in place, while we humans are alive, don't tell me that even with Lord Feng Jiu Ge's power, you cannot take it forcefully?"

They were unwilling to give up.

This was a Thieving Heaven true inheritance!

The experts could take the meat while they could have some soup, the two female immortals were not greedy for more, they just wanted to have a share of the loot.

Qin Bai Sheng sneered: "Wishful thinking! Back then, even after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable became rank nine, he still returned empty-handed after encountering a Thieving Heaven true inheritance. Not only did he get nothing, he even suffered a loss and ended up in a pathetic state. Hehehe... if not for that, why would Giant Sun Immortal Venerable hate otherworldly demons to this extent. The two of you think you can obtain this true inheritance?"

"There was such a thing?"

"This is too absurd. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable is also a rank nine Gu Immortal, he could not even take one of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's true inheritances even after he died?"

Ling Mei and Ao Xue stared with their beautiful eyes wide open, they half-believed and half-doubted this.

Feng Jiu Ge did not refute it, he said solemnly: "Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's space path attainment was unfathomably deep, it surpasses the imagination of people. There is a theory: Because he was an otherworldly demon, when he became a space path Gu Immortal, a special type of space path dao mark was produced. These dao marks originate from another world, they are foreign to the five regions and nine heavens. The space we are in now, it seems ordinary, but it had already transcended the Gu world, it is not within the five regions and nine heavens. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable wanted to obtain the true inheritance, but he was afraid of the implications, thus he failed and suffered a loss, unable to do anything about it."

Ling Mei and Ao Xue gasped in shock.

The two of them were too inexperienced compared to Feng Jiu Ge and Qin Bai Sheng, this was the first time they had heard about such secrets regarding the venerables.

At once, Ling Mei and Ao Xue felt their horizons expanding.

But soon, they became worried and anxious.

"Not even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could do anything to this mystical space, how can we get out?"

"Don't worry, as long as we do not move, in fifteen minutes, we will be teleported out." Feng Jiu Ge replied confidently.

If it were other Gu Immortals who landed here, they would use their methods to investigate. In that case, they would be in trouble. The time that they were trapped would be extended.

But Spirit Affinity House possessed one of Thieving Heaven's true inheritances, and Feng Jiu Ge was a higher-up in Spirit Affinity House, he knew the proper way to leave this true inheritance.

But at this moment, Qin Bai Sheng raised his head and laughed: "Feng Jiu Ge! Since I took great pains to lure you in here, how can I let you leave? Stay here for good."

Saying this, Qin Bai Sheng struck.

His powerful aura burst into the air.

Ling Mei and Ao Xue acted like they were facing a strong foe.

Feng Jiu Ge quickly said: "Don't move! In this place, it might seem like we are close to each other, but we are actually very far away from each other. He is trying to lure you to attack, once you do, this place will change and target whoever attacks. The stronger the attack, the greater the backlash from this place, and the longer you will be trapped. Do not fall into his trap!"

Feng Jiu Ge was very aware regarding this Thieving Heaven true inheritance.

He was clear about the terrifying power of this mystical space. Even though he was proud and powerful, he did not dare to act rashly.

Ling Mei and Ao Xue chose to believe Feng Jiu Ge, they held in their impulse and did not attack.

But Qin Bai Sheng showed a weird smile: "Brother Feng is very confident, but it is a pity that your sect has not researched deeply enough into Thieving Heaven's true inheritances. I wonder what you will do against my next action?"

He spoke calmly as he activated the Gu worms in his body, his aura burst out and reached its peak.

"What is he trying to do?" Feng Jiu Ge felt something amiss, he focused himself, his gaze was like lightning, looking at Qin Bai Sheng fixedly.

But at the next moment, Qin Bai Sheng's action was something out of the Central Continent immortals' expectations.

They only heard Qin Bai Sheng recite —

Even after experiencing fifty-four tribulations, the sky is still filled with tribulation clouds.

The soul light in my chest pressures everyone, the sword qi in my fist dominates Northern Plains.

Four hundred years passed rapidly, how can there be life without death?

Discarding this ruined body to exchange for a clear breeze, I will sweep the heavens for countless light years!

His voice was clear and loud, he spoke with a calm expression, his gaze showed a sign of expectation towards the future.

After finishing this poem, he smiled lightly at Feng Jiu Ge.

Next, he shut his eyes, all signs of life leaving his body!

Feng Jiu Ge frowned tightly, even during the hundred days battle, he did not show such an expression.

At this moment, Qin Bai Sheng had actually ended his own life!!

At the next moment, a clear breeze started from within Qin Bai Sheng's body.

Behind Feng Jiu Ge, Ling Mei and Ao Xue's expressions changed, their voices were trembling from fear, they screamed: "Winds of assimilation!"

As it turned out, in order to stop Feng Jiu Ge, Qin Bai Sheng had given up his own life, making the ultimate sacrifice.

His method was ruthless, he directly destroyed his own immortal aperture.

Once the immortal aperture was destroyed, without other immortal apertures to hold it, winds of assimilation started blowing.

Winds of assimilation were extraordinary, they assimilated everything, even rank eight Gu Immortals had to avoid them at all costs.

And in this mystical true inheritance space, if five finger fist heart sword or heaven and earth song were used, it would only be like a pebble tossed into a lake.

At this moment, winds of assimilation blew, even though it was a clear breeze, the entire mystical space started shaking, it was as if water on a lake was boiled, there were ripples forming in the space unceasingly.

Feng Jiu Ge had a solemn expression.

Against Qin Bai Sheng's resolute attack, he had to face it with all of his ability, if he was careless, he would die.

Behind him, Ling Mei and Ao Xue had activated their Gu worms, protecting their bodies.

Even Feng Jiu Ge had to activate his Immortal Gu, of course they had to do the same.

Leaving the mystical space was another issue now. They had to survive this crisis first.

Otherwise, it would be a pointless thing to worry about!

Chapter 925: Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance

Two flowers blossomed, each branching in different directions.

Ignoring the situation of Qin Bai Sheng sacrificing himself to create the winds of assimilation and trap Feng Jiu Ge, Ling Mei, and Ao Xue in a dangerous situation for now.

Looking instead at Jiang Yu and the other immortals breaking out.

They were about to escape, but Hei Cheng was hit by a killer move and fell.

His face was pale as he shouted for help.

However, they were all escaping for their lives, every second was important, at the crucial moment, any hesitation would mean the difference between life and death.

The immortals ignored him, they only raised their own speeds to the limits.

Fairy Jiang Yu was even more heartless, she directly told them to abandon him, disregarding Hei Cheng's life or death.

They were so close to escaping, freedom was right in front of them. Hei Cheng was lagging behind, couldn't he be useful in stalling the Central Continent Gu Immortals? However, he controlled the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison, after Hei Cheng died, it might end up in the Central Continent Gu Immortals' hands.

That was a slight pity to Jiang Yu and the others.

But it was only slightly regretful, compared to the Immortal Gu House, their own lives were more important.

"Hehehe, you can all continue playing around. I'm out of here." While they were breaking out, Hui Feng Zi laughed loudly.

Immortal killer move — Wind Escape!

His speed rose sharply, in a few breaths of time, he was way ahead of Jiang Yu and the others.

Seeing Jiang Yu and the others' fiery gazes, Hui Feng Zi flew even faster.

"Cooperate with me!" Hong Chi Ming shouted.

Gu formations at the outer area activated, giving off bright light.

After the hundred days battle, the Central Continent Gu Immortals had gained some coordination.

"Where are you going?" Chen Zhen Chi and Bu Fei Yan moved out, using a Gu formation at the periphery to chase and block Hui Feng Zi.

Hui Feng Zi was known as the fastest in Northern Plains, he came and went like the wind, Central Continent Gu Immortals had to admit that.

Just Chen Zhen Chi or Bu Fei Yan alone could not stop Hui Feng Zi. But now, they were cooperating with much coordination.

At once, no matter how Hui Feng Zi maneuvered, he could not shake off Chen and Bu, his speed gradually fell as he failed his escape.

"He deserves it!" Jiang Yu and the others felt gratified, they turned towards another direction and tried to escape from the side.

"Go down." Old Lord Can Yang snorted in anger, using his signature life chasing fire.

Hong Chi Ming followed up with another attack, beating the dog while it was down.

Hei Cheng's body was burning in flames, he screamed in pain as he fell from the sky.

With a loud crash, he landed on the ground, he spat out a mouthful of blood as countless vines grew from the ground, tying him up firmly.

At once, Hei Cheng was trapped, while Hui Feng Zi was obstructed, Hong Chi Ming left Hei Cheng as he chased He Lang Zi.

He activated his killer move, mercilessly attacking He Lang Zi.

He Lang Zi had to use his transformation path killer move, turning into the lightning flash giant wolf to resist it.

Fairy Jiang Yu and the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal were not far away, they were obstructed by Old Man Tian Long and Old Lord Can Yang.

They did not waste time in trash talking, the four immortals engaged in fierce combat.

At once, winds surged and thunderous explosions occurred.

The four immortals displayed their might, they shook the surroundings as intense air currents were created, mountains rocks crumbled and broke.

Old Lord Can Yang was a famous rank seven Gu Immortal, when Dong Fang Chang Fan had been pretending to be dead, he had fought Unfettered Scholar, Fang Yuan, Pi Shui Han alone, he had excellent battle strength.

Old Man Tian Long's strength was similar to Old Lord Can Yang. The former was a supreme elder of Black Heaven Temple. He was sent here by Black Heaven Temple for the secret purpose of countering the sound path Gu Immortal Feng Jiu Ge.

Looking at Shadow Sect, the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal was indeed powerful, but Fairy Jiang Yu was weaker.

After more than ten rounds of fighting, Old Man Tian Long and Old Lord Can Yang had the upper hand, they obtained a good chance to strike.

Immortal killer move — Life Chasing Fire!

"Oh no!" Fairy Jiang Yu was shocked, she wanted to dodge but it was too late.

"Stand back, let me deal with it." At the crucial moment, the mysterious black robed Gu Immortal used his method, replacing Fairy Jiang Yu and using his body to block the life chasing fire.

"Oh? Strange!" Old Lord Can Yang was slightly shocked.

The mysterious black robed Gu Immortal was hit by the life chasing fire, but he was completely intact it was as if nothing had happened.

"Sneaky fellow, show us your true appearance!" Old Man Tian Long shouted, his hands clapped together as blades flew out from the sky.

The mysterious black robed Gu Immortal blocked them as his robe was torn, his appearance was exposed to everyone.

Old Lord Can Yang was stunned: "You have the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance physique!"

One of the ten extreme physiques — Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance!

"Why are you afraid, he is merely an immortal zombie." Old Man Tian Long howled repeatedly, his attacks becoming fiercer.

The mysterious black robed Gu Immortal's true identity was a rank seven immortal zombie. Different from other immortal zombies, he had a special identity, he had one of the ten extreme physiques, Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance, and had turned into an immortal zombie.

"Hmph! Since you found out, there is no point in hiding this anymore." The mysterious black robed Gu Immortal tore off his black robe, pouncing at Old Lord Can Yang.

Old Lord Can Yang was a fire path Gu Immortal, he was countered by the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance physique, he had the disadvantage.

Old Man Tian Long wanted to help, but Fairy Jiang Yu risked her life to block him.

"Quickly go!" Fairy Jiang Yu screamed.

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie angrily snorted, forcing back Old Lord Can Yang, he did not look back, he flew out of Luo Po valley, successfully escaping.

"Where are you going?" Old Lord Can Yang roared, wanting to chase him, but Fairy Jiang Yu, who was bathed in blood, managed to block him miraculously.

"It seems that you have given up on living! Is this immortal zombie your lover, is he worth your sacrifice?" Old Man Tian Long's expression was cold, he descended from the sky and his hand hit Fairy Jiang Yu's back firmly.

Boom!

Fairy Jiang Yu was at her wits' end, she could not defend herself, her chest was shattered as a huge hole appeared, one could see through it.

Her beautiful eyes turned hollow, her purple dress fluttered in the sky, like a butterfly slowly landing on the ground.

Ten breaths of time later, Fairy Jiang Yu's corpse landed on the ground, her bones and tendons were broken, her flesh turned into pulp.

Fairy Jiang Yu died!

At this point, Shadow Sect no longer had a chance.

Old Lord Can Yang and Old Man Tian Long were free now, they could deal with He Lang Zi and Hui Feng Zi.

Hong Chi Ming's focus was on restricting Hei Cheng.

A moment later, He Lang Zi screamed in a deafening tone, the giant wolf that he had turned into was cut into two. His corpse turned into a human body, blood flowed as his internal organs were torn, he died a terrible death.

Hei Cheng was left without a choice, he reluctantly activated the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison.

Even though the Immortal Gu House was powerful, it needed to expend a huge amount of immortal essence. After the hundred days battle, Hei Cheng was already bankrupt, he did not have much immortal essence left.

There was insufficient immortal essence to activate the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison, it had less than one percent of its full power, Hong Chi Ming used his Gu formation to trap it.

Fifteen minutes later, Hui Feng Zi lost as well.

He was extremely fast and slippery, but after the hundred days battle, everyone knew each other's abilities, he did not have any special techniques left, and the Central Continent Gu Immortals had an extremely tight defensive ring, like an impenetrable net. Hui Feng Zi was like a fish that was caught in a net, even though he struggled intensely, he was bound to lose.

"Don't kill me, I surrender." At the moment before death, Hui Feng Zi surrendered with a pale expression.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals looked at each other, expressing their joy.

Death was truly a terrifying thing.

A wise man submits to circumstances, the Central Continent Gu Immortals understood why Hui Feng Zi surrendered.

"Don't play tricks!"

"Hand over your Immortal Gu!"

The Central Continent Gu Immortals did not relax, they surrounded Hui Feng Zi tightly.

Hui Feng Zi did not have any chances left, he sighed deeply as he handed over his Immortal Gu.

Without his Immortal Gu, he was like a tiger without its claws and teeth, his threat level dropped.

Only until he was completely under control and his life and death was at their whim did the Central Continent Gu Immortals breathe out deeply in relief.

Focusing their minds, they started to deal with the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison.

Hui Feng Zi's surrender gave the Central Continent Gu Immortals hope.

The hundred days battle expended a huge amount of their immortal essence, the Central Continent Gu Immortals suffered great losses, their pressure was immense. After capturing Hui Feng Zi, the Immortal Gu they obtained were enough to recoup their losses. If they could obtain the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison as well, they would earn a huge profit from this.

Seven minutes later, Dark Prison was taken down by the Central Continent immortals.

But unexpectedly...

"Where is Hei Cheng?"

"So decisive! He abandoned this Immortal Gu House immediately and escaped."

"While we were capturing Hui Feng Zi, he secretly dug underground and escaped, he really managed to deceive us!"

"Hmph, a coward who is afraid of death, a person who is barely surviving, he is not worth considering."

At this point, the escape attempt of Shadow Sect's side had ended, the battle was over and the dust had settled.

Qin Bai Sheng, Fairy Jiang Yu were sacrificed, He Lang Zi died, Hui Feng Zi surrendered, the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie had escaped with the crucial Immortal Gu, Hei Cheng, who had the lowest battle strength, abandoned the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison and escaped.

A few months ago, these people attacked Lang Ya blessed land with overwhelming might. Over a hundred days later, they were either dead, injured, had surrendered, or escaped. Even the powerful Qin Bai Sheng was sacrificed inside Luo Po valley.

This showed the cruelty of the Gu cultivation world. Even at Gu Immortal level, they were not free from danger, one could still die easily.

More than ten days later, a figure emerged in Earth Trench.

Earth Trench was under the control of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, it was guarded by Dark Flow Giant City.

But this mysterious figure could enter and leave easily, he did not attract any suspicion.

After entering Earth Trench, the mysterious figure was familiar with Earth Trench's terrain as he moved rapidly, taking a shortcut and entering deep into it.

A few days later, a giant graveyard appeared before the mysterious figure's vision.

"I am finally here." The mysterious figure finally showed his appearance.

It was the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie who had escaped from Luo Po valley!

As it turned out, Shadow Sect's backup plan was hidden here. Back then when Central Continent's group attacked Luo Po valley, Qin Bai Sheng and Jiang Yu had thought of breaking out and coming here to use their trump card and resolve the crisis in Luo Po valley.

But this trump card was extremely important, if it was used abruptly, it could disrupt Shadow Sect's plan, Qin Bai Sheng and the others were hesitant.

When they had resolved to use it, the battle had already become very intense, they had no chance to do it anymore. They tried it forcefully, but only sacrificed the hairy man Gu Immortals in vain.

Now, Luo Po valley was taken over by Central Continent's group, the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie did not come here thinking of revenge, and activating Shadow Sect's backup plan. He wanted to hide himself, and place the crucial Immortal Gu here for safekeeping.

This Immortal Gu was related to Shadow Sect's crucial plan, it could not be lost. For this, Qin Bai Sheng and Jiang Yu had sacrificed their lives.

"Just a bit more time, we just need a bit more time..." The Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie felt anger and melancholy, he carried the Immortal Gu and entered deep into the graveyard.

This was the graveyard of immortal zombies. He was an immortal zombie, it was too easy to disguise as a member.

However, just when the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie thought that his ordeal was over, and that he was safe, a figure appeared.

"Interesting... to think that I would meet a ten extreme physique immortal zombie here." The person looked at the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie, evaluating with an interested tone, his rank eight aura was emanating.

At this moment, the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie felt like he had fallen into an icy abyss, his heart was filled with despair.

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu? Why is he here!"

Chapter 926: Refining Star Thought Immortal Gu

Hu Immortal blessed land, underground cave.

The blood zhi forest had already spread out to an area of over thirty thousand square meters.

At the center of the blood zhi forest, the blood lingzhi shined with a dark red light, but currently the light of wisdom had already overpowered it.

At this moment, Fang Yuan was bathed in the wisdom light halo as he sat and concentrated.

His expression was calm, he was like a statue, but his mind was working rapidly, countless thoughts were created and destroyed, they crashed into one another like a meteor shower, or the eruption of a volcano.

He grunted.

Fang Yuan's body shook, he slowly opened his eyes.

His mind which was undergoing a storm made of thoughts had returned to a peaceful state.

He frowned, thinking deeply.

Two streams of blood slowly flowed down from his nose.

The immortal zombie body's blood was pale green, there was no warmth at all, it was icy cold.

Fang Yuan indifferently cleaned up his nosebleed, he evaluated: "It seems that the Gu formation that I newly created still has many flaws."

Ever since he had become a wisdom path grandmaster, he had obtained countless inspirations. As for how to use wisdom Gu more efficiently, he had many new ideas.

This Gu formation was created by him not too long ago.

Not long ago, he had a low wisdom path attainment level and could only use the light of wisdom directly. Now, with this Gu formation, he could intensify the rate at which his thoughts collided.

Even though it could not raise the effect of his deductions, it could save him a lot of time.

Wisdom Gu was rank nine, while Fang Yuan was merely a rank six immortal zombie, it was already very difficult for him to use the light of wisdom. This Gu formation could be considered a significant breakthrough.

Furthermore, this Gu formation was not in its original state, it had been modified several times.

The first few versions had all sorts of flaws, once, the Gu formation even exploded inside Fang Yuan's body.

When he used it this time, Fang Yuan withstood the backlash of the Gu formation and suffered a minor injury.

"The Gu formation still needs to be modified... but, that is not key. Now, the difficult problem is the modification of the star thought Immortal Gu recipe."

Fang Yuan frowned even deeper.

A few days ago, Blazing Heaven Demoness had recruited Fang Yuan, he used this chance to request the refinement of star thought Immortal Gu to her.

Both sides came to an agreement, Blazing Heaven Demoness was very generous about funding Fang Yuan. She provided the materials to refine star thought Immortal Gu for him, dispatching Bo Dan to send them over.

These immortal materials were very precious. Not only were they expensive, if Fang Yuan had to collect them himself, he would need to expend a lot of time.

Only Blazing Heaven Demoness, using her rank eight cultivation level, her Zombie Alliance status, and her deep foundations could gather three sets of these immortal materials in such a small amount of time.

Fang Yuan was well prepared, he naturally got to refining Gu.

But he had tried three times consecutively and failed them all.

Fang Yuan was mentally prepared in regards to failing.

After all, he did not have the success dao mark from the Refinement Path Convention this time, he could only rely on his own skills and luck.

Relying on skill was easily understood, but why did he have to rely on luck?

Looking at the example of star thought Immortal Gu, during the refinement process, there was a step that needed two immortal materials. He needed a portion of pale flame white bones, and a portion of green beetle water lotuses.

The former was a fire path immortal material, the latter was a water path immortal material.

At this step, the two immortal materials have to be processed at the same time, fusing water and fire, to create a clear liquid.

But this step was very difficult.

There were fire path dao marks on the pale flame white bone, and water path dao marks on the green beetle water lotus. To process them and form the clear liquid, the fire path dao marks and the water path dao marks have to be equal in number. Even if they were not equal, the difference had to be very small. That was the only way the fire and water could cancel out each other, if one side was higher, more than the range allowed, the liquid would be extremely murky.

This sort of murky liquid could not be used.

But the liquid could not be stored for long, it needed to be refined right before use. Fang Yuan did not have a time path Immortal Gu to seal the state of the liquid. Thus, Fang Yuan had to create the liquid while refining Immortal Gu.

And the difference in dao marks was extremely subtle. Even if Fang Yuan focused all his attention and used his best methods, he could not inspect all of them, he could only estimate.

Fang Yuan was not a fire path or water path Gu Immortal, he was already reaching the limits of his investigative abilities.

Thus, the Immortal Gu recipe strictly stated the age of the green beetle water lotuses, as well as the amount of pale flame white bones.

But even so, even among green beetle water lotuses of the same age, they would have different water path dao marks on them due to the environment that they were in. If the pale flame white bones were damaged, there would also be fewer dao marks on them.

All of the Gu refinement materials met the Immortal Gu recipe's requirements after Fang Yuan checked them meticulously.

But when they were used in practice, there was bound to be failure.

To refine the clear liquid, there was luck involved in it.

The entire Immortal Gu refinement process had many such examples like the fusing of water and fire.

Succeeding once or twice was not difficult. The difficult thing was to succeed every single time.

Thus, the success rate of refining Immortal Gu was extremely low.

Many Gu Immortal went bankrupt trying to refine an Immortal Gu without success.

Immortal Gu were a huge boost to the Gu Immortal in all aspects.

Because of the existence of heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, Gu Immortals had an even more intense desire in regards to Immortal Gu.

But in the history of Gu cultivation, there were countless instances of Immortal Gu refinement failing, these painful experiences landed countless people in terrible straits.

At present, many rank six Gu Immortals did not even have a single Immortal Gu.

Gu Immortals would rather attempt to capture wild Immortal Gu than take a risk and refine Immortal Gu themselves.

Of course, there was another reason, refinement path attainment levels differed between Gu Immortals. Many Gu Immortals did not have the confidence to refine Immortal Gu themselves.

Especially when it came to Immortal Gu with higher ranks, Gu Immortals would have even less confidence in refining them.

In the past, even two venerables, Giant Sun and Thieving Heaven, had to ask Long Hair Ancestor to help them refine Immortal Gu and Immortal Gu Houses.

Fang Yuan was modifying the Immortal Gu recipe in this aspect.

When he became a wisdom path grandmaster, his star path attainment also rose to grandmaster level. This gave him the ability to modify the Immortal Gu recipe of Star Thought.

Including this current deduction, he had already modified many aspects of the original Immortal Gu recipe.

Eleven processes that were similar to this water and fire fusion had been taken out, they were replaced with more stable steps with higher success rates.

"Looking at the time, Blazing Heaven Demoness is about to send me the fourth set of Gu refinement immortal materials."

With Blazing Heaven Demoness' funding, Fang Yuan's financial difficulties had been alleviated. Blazing Heaven Demoness had been wanting to attack Yu Lu blessed land, she was generous in allowing Fang Yuan to refine star thought Immortal Gu, she would not stop until he succeeded.

But she was not easy to fool.

If Fang Yuan wanted to use the excuse of failure to cheat Blazing Heaven Demoness and get the Gu refinement immortal materials, he would not succeed.

Even though Blazing Heaven Demoness agreed to fund Fang Yuan, they had made an agreement: All of the funded immortal materials would become Fang Yuan's debt towards her. Whether he succeeded or not in refining the Immortal Gu, he would need to pay her back later. The longer he dragged this on, the more interest Blazing Heaven Demoness would receive. If Fang Yuan successfully refines the Immortal Gu but fails to return her the sum in a hundred years, then Blazing Heaven Demoness would be allowed to take an Immortal Gu from Fang Yuan as compensation.

If it were Shark Demon who gave this condition, Fang Yuan would not agree to it, he would propose one that suited his interests more.

But this was the demanding and domineering Blazing Heaven Demoness, Fang Yuan also needed to refine star thought Immortal Gu as soon as possible, he could only agree to it.

Thus, it was in no way suitable to cheat Blazing Heaven Demoness' funding.

Fang Yuan failed three times, the losses were all on him, he already owed Blazing Heaven Demoness a huge debt.

Fang Yuan could clearly discern some of Blazing Heaven Demoness' plans.

Even if Fang Yuan could not repay his debt, with the wisdom path attainment that he displayed, Blazing Heaven Demoness could make use of it and force Fang Yuan to work for her.

After all, wisdom path Gu Immortals were very rare. Those with Fang Yuan's level of attainment were extremely useful subordinates.

If Fang Yuan succeeded in refining star thought Immortal Gu, Blazing Heaven Demoness would be even happier. Because this would allow her to take down Yu Lu blessed land.

The conclusion was that Blazing Heaven Demoness would only earn from this regardless of what happens.

After failing three times, the pressure was all on Fang Yuan.

"According to my current situation, I can only do seven refinement attempts. Now, I have already failed three times, I have four chances left. In terms of refining Gu, I have already reached the limits. I can only work harder in terms of luck."

Fang Yuan thought it over.

He had connect luck Immortal Gu, he could forcefully link to other people's luck and boost his own luck.

But there was a drawback with this.

Even though Fang Yuan had Connect Luck, he did not have Break Luck along with it.

He could only connect, but not break.

If the target of his luck connection became unlucky, Fang Yuan would be implicated.

Thus, Fang Yuan had chosen several targets earlier, these people had extremely powerful luck, they were moreover unceasing and would not fade or become bad over time.

But these people were very rare, in the entirety of the five regions, looking over his previous life, there were only so many of them.

Fang Yuan calculated: "The remaining ones have not been born yet. Among them, Song Yi Shi had already killed the ancestor of Li Xiao Yao on the nameless island, there is no way he can be born now. The soonest and best target can only be Fairy Black Moon."

Fairy Black Moon was very incredible.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, she was the current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House. She was one of the most outstanding characters in Spirit Affinity House.

Her status was similar to Mo Yao in the past, or even higher.

This was because in the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, there was a great era of turmoil. The five regions were in unprecedented chaos, the appearance of dream realms broke the balance of the different forces, a new Gu cultivation path, dream path, was produced, everything hinted towards the emergence of Great Dream Immortal Venerable.

In this great era, heroes emerged, conquerors surfaced, capable people were everywhere, dragons and snakes rampaged all while Fairy Black Moon remained as the representative of Spirit Affinity House, one of the ten great ancient sects, she had incredible talent, it was surely first-rate in the five regions.

Furthermore, Fairy Black Moon led the Central Continent Gu Immortals to attack Imperial Court blessed land, she had outstanding achievements and incredible battle strength, her methods were also profound.

Ever since Fairy Black Moon emerged, she grew stronger with each battle, turning disaster into fortune, her luck had been very strong.

She was indeed an ideal target for Fang Yuan's luck connection.

Chapter 927: Fang Yuan's Opportunity

"Unfortunately, Fairy Black Moon wore a mask and had a mysterious status, I do not know her true identity. In my previous life, she was like a rising sun, she was dazzling and bright, there was no biography on her. Maybe she is still an ordinary disciple in Spirit Affinity House, or maybe she is the descendant of a Gu Immortal. In short, I have too little information, there is nothing I can search for about her."

Since he could not find Fairy Black Moon, he could only look for other, inferior targets.

These people were also very famous characters.

But they only had strong luck for a period of time, it was not long lasting. Several of them had large fluctuations, some even had great misfortune after a period of good luck, dying in the process.

"If I use Connect Luck on them, my luck can become very strong in the short run, I can surely refine star thought Immortal Gu successfully. But I do not have Break Luck, when they become unlucky, so will I. Sacrificing the long term prospects for such small temporary gains, is it really worth it?" Fang Yuan was hesitant.

If he had break luck Immortal Gu, this was not a problem for him.

But whether he could obtain Break Luck in the future, Fang Yuan had no confidence in that.

He was never a person who would do something in which he had no assurance of the outcome.

Placing his hopes of success on pure chance, Fang Yuan would not do that.

He was indeed willing to gamble and take risks, but he was actually very careful and meticulous at the same time. If not for that, he would not have gotten so far.

Several days later, Blazing Heaven Demoness sent over sufficient immortal materials for him to refine Gu again.

But Fang Yuan was no longer in the mood to refine Gu.

He had just heard some shocking news.

Not long ago, Northern Plains Zombie Alliance was infiltrated by Old Ancestor Xue Hu. The latter went deep into Earth Trench and secretly ransacked many precious Immortal Gu and immortal materials.

If Old Ancestor Xue Hu was not exposed, Zombie Alliance could only let this matter go.

But the problem was, an intense battle caused Old Ancestor Xue Hu's tracks to be exposed, Zombie Alliance had to make a response to this.

Zombie Alliance was huge, it spanned across five regions, their territory had just been infiltrated and looted casually, how could they allow it?

If they did not punish such wrongdoers, Zombie Alliance's reputation would suffer, their authority would be undermined and many forces would look down on them, how could they hold their ground in the Gu Immortal world and compete with other forces?

Any organization's face represented a certain extent of benefits.

Moreover, just now, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was found in the immortal zombie graveyard.

This greatly provoked all the Zombie Alliance immortal zombies, they burst into anger.

Immortal zombies had a lot of dao marks in their bodies, they were excellent Gu refinement materials. But an immortal zombie's immortal aperture was dead, thus, they held their own bodies in high regard, this was the last bit of pride they had.

Therefore, immortal zombies placed much more importance on their bodies than ordinary Gu Immortals.

The immortal zombie graveyard was a place in Zombie Alliance that could not be defiled.

But their sanctuary was ravaged by Old Ancestor Xue Hu, could they ignore this?

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu went overboard. This violates the bottom line of Zombie Alliance, it seems that he is taking a risk to refine Immortal Gu Fortune Rivalling Heaven. He actually became a thief and personally stole immortal zombie bodies." Fang Yuan assessed.

He thought about his previous life.

In those five hundred years, this did not happen.

"In my past life, Ma Hong Yun was alive and well, Old Ancestor Xue Hu did not obtain him, of course he could not refine Immortal Gu Fortune Rivalling Heaven. It seems that now, because of my rebirth, everything is changing as my influence grows, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was implicated by me."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's plight was a good thing to Fang Yuan.

In Dark Flow Giant City, Yin Liu Gong, Dragon Commander Ye Cha, and Huang Quan Weng, these three rank seven immortal zombies were standing guard. How could they be Old Ancestor Xue Hu's match, after it happened, they could only watch as he flew away.

This matter could not be ignored, the three immortal zombies could only seek help from Zombie Alliance's headquarters.

Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance flew into a rage, they sent three rank eight immortal zombies, along with ten rank seven immortal zombies out to punish Old Ancestor Xue Hu and protect their reputation.

Among these three immortal zombies, one was Blazing Heaven Demoness, it was necessary for her to go.

Why?

Because Blazing Heaven Demoness was the leader of the Northern Plains Zombie Alliance branch.

She was supposed to be guarding Dark Flow Giant City.

Once this happened, Blazing Heaven Demoness who was in Eastern Sea had to bear responsibility. When a mishap happened to Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, she had to return and fulfill her duty.

Once Blazing Heaven Demoness leaves, the mission of taking down Yu Lu blessed land returns to Shark Demon and Su Bai Man.

Fate worked in mysterious ways, it really caught people off guard and went beyond anyone's expectations.

Originally, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had no more hope, but because of Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Zombie Alliance had to focus on protecting its reputation. Thus, Blazing Heaven Demoness had to return to Northern Plains, and the ones left that were most suited to invade Yu Lu blessed land were Shark Demon and Su Bai Man.

Ever since Blazing Heaven Demoness forcefully took over the mission of Yu Lu blessed land, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man had been having a hard time, everyone avoided them like the plague. But now, the situation was reversed, after all, there was only one final round in Yu Lu blessed land, Shark Demon and Su Bai Man would prosper soon. With this change in circumstances, many Gu Immortals came over to befriend them, to repair the cracks in their relationships that was created earlier. Shark Demon and Su Bai Man were sighing over the mysterious twists and turns in life.

Fang Yuan had no time to care about their feelings.

Shark Demon was angry at Fang Yuan for turning to Blazing Heaven Demoness so quickly, in this invasion, he did not even invite Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Fang Yuan did not give a hoot.

Invading Yu Lu blessed land would give him only a small portion of the rewards, it was far less important than refining star thought Immortal Gu.

And refining star thought Immortal Gu was only the icing on the cake, it was less important than getting into Northern Plains Zombie Alliance.

After all, since long ago, Fang Yuan had been wanting the inheritance in Northern Plains Zombie Alliance. That was the inheritance of an immortal zombie great expert, it would be extremely helpful to Fang Yuan in reviving from his zombie state. In his previous life, Northern Plains Zombie Alliance obtained this inheritance and gained a huge boost in strength, surpassing Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance for a period of time!

Fang Yuan tried to disguise as immortal zombie Sha Huang, in an attempt to make his way into Earth Trench and obtain the inheritance.

It was a pity he failed.

Feng Jiu Ge and the others ruined his plans.

Left with no choice, Fang Yuan had to give up on it. There were many twists and turns along the way, he joined the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention, he invaded Yu Lu blessed land, and even obtained two or three ways to revive from his immortal zombie body. However, his initial goal was still not achieved.

Now, it was the best chance for him to make his way into Northern Plains Zombie Alliance.

Before Fang Yuan had even made any request, Blazing Heaven Demoness had already requested Fang Yuan to go back to Northern Plains with her.

In the letter, Blazing Heaven Demoness' attitude was still domineering as ever, and the reason she gave was also valid and enticing.

Northern Plains Zombie Alliance was the base of Blazing Heaven Demoness, she had many immortal materials kept there, she could give Fang Yuan more attempts at refining star thought Immortal Gu over there.

Or perhaps she was worried about letting Fang Yuan stay in Eastern Sea.

After all, the five regions' regional walls were hard to pass.

The higher the cultivation level, the harder it is to pass, the difficulty multiplied by several times!

A hundred years ago, Blazing Heaven Demoness came to Eastern Sea from Northern Plains, most of her wealth was expended as she even got heavily injured, she only recovered after recuperating for eight years.

Now, facing a strong foe like Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Blazing Heaven Demoness was uncertain of how much time it would take to settle.

Keeping Fang Yuan by her side was more assuring.

At the same time, the wisdom path Gu Immortal Xing Xiang Zi might provide Blazing Heaven Demoness some help when dealing with Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

All in all, the chance that Fang Yuan had been trying to create and was waiting for had arrived.

It was all thanks to Old Ancestor Xue Hu getting discovered!

Towards Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Fang Yuan even felt a hint of gratitude.

Several days later.

Northern Plains, in the deepest parts of Luo Po valley.

The atmosphere was tense.

The five Gu Immortals from Central Continent had solemn expressions as they looked at this inconspicuous place.

After the battle had ended, only two people from Shadow Sect escaped.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals who had come to Northern Plains in secret and were very confident had suffered heavy losses, only five were left now.

"To think that a Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable true inheritance was hidden deep within Luo Po valley!" Bu Fei Yan sighed.

These last days, they had taken control of Luo Po valley and while being vigilant, they made every attempt to save Feng Jiu Ge, Ling Mei, and Ao Xue.

In the end, they confirmed the existence of the Thieving Heaven true inheritance, but they could not enter.

"It is a pity that my sect has no understanding regarding the Thieving Heaven true inheritances. It is too difficult to enter, we cannot break in for at least two to three years." Hong Chi Ming said.

He was the most skilled in Gu formations among the five here.

Now that Ancient Soul Sect's Old Oracle had died, Hong Chi Ming was most suited to speak in this situation.

Not mentioning three years, the Central Continent immortals could not even wait for three months. In fact, it had been very risky to stay in Luo Po valley these last days.

After all, two Gu Immortals had escaped, what if they lured over other people, and attacked again.

"Actually, even if we know how to get in, we might not be able to save them. This is the arrangement of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable after all."

"Lord Feng Jiu Ge is so strong, yet he is still trapped inside without any commotion. It seems that it is very dangerous inside, if we go in, we might not survive."

"Qin Bai Sheng had planned meticulously to trap Feng Jiu Ge in there. If we go to save him rashly, perhaps..."

The Central Continent Gu Immortals spoke, their words contained deep meaning, their gazes were flickering uncertainly.

The ten great ancient sects of Central Continent were all under Heavenly Court, but they did not coexist in harmony, they had incessant conflicts.

If Feng Jiu Ge, a one in a thousand years genius, were to die here, the other nine sects would heave sighs of relief.

As for Ao Xue and Ling Mei, they had Immortal Gu, if they died here, Heaven's Envy Manor would lose its signature killer move — Peerless Crescent Moon Slash. This was no small loss even to Heaven's Envy Manor which had a deep foundation.

The enemy had left, the age-old inner conflicts between the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent had finally started to vaguely show themselves in these five immortals.

"We infiltrated Northern Plains to investigate the truth behind the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Even though we took down Luo Po valley, Old Oracle has died and Feng Jiu Ge is trapped, we can only stop here now."

"That's right, after this battle, we have all suffered huge losses, we need to rest and recuperate now."

"In my opinion, we should hand over the information of what happened, and the fruits of our investigation over to our sects, that is the most important thing."

"That makes sense, don't forget, we have captured Hui Feng Zi and the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison. These gains are all extremely valuable, we need to handle them appropriately."

As they conversed, the Central Continent five immortals silently smiled internally.

Why would they save Feng Jiu Ge?

Save him so that he could suppress them? Save him so that he could get a share of the loot?

But they were in the righteous path, they needed to act on the surface, and not give others excuses to target them.

Now that they had made enough excuses for themselves, the five Central Continent immortals agreed on one thing — to return to Central Continent as soon as possible!

Chapter 928: Luck Path Backlash

After passing the regional wall, the group from Eastern Sea finally reached Northern Plains.

"I am finally back." Fang Yuan sighed. He was disguised as Xing Xiang Zi, as he stepped on the grassland, his wistful sigh was not just an act.

In front of him, Blazing Heaven Demoness' gaze flickered as she muttered softly: "Yes, I'm finally back."

She was more deeply moved than Fang Yuan.

Even though Fang Yuan was a Northern Plains Gu Immortal, he only became an immortal in Northern Plains, he was born in Southern Border.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness was born and bred a person of Northern Plains, after a hundred years, she was finally back.

The five regions had varying terrains. Eastern Sea had endless mystical sea areas, Northern Plains was mostly flat and had countless grasslands, plains, and mounds.

Right now, Blazing Heaven Demoness had stepped into an infertile grassland, the yellow-brown soil only had a trace of greenery.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness felt a strong sense of familiarity inside her.

Apart from Fang Yuan and Blazing Heaven Demoness, the other Gu Immortals frowned slightly. They were Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, they felt curiosity yet unfamiliarity towards Northern Plains. Going from their homeland to another region, they felt a sense of ostracism inside them, they felt out of place from the environment that they were in.

Among them, there were two immortal zombies with the strongest auras, they were both rank eight.

These Gu Immortals from Eastern Sea were almost all immortal zombies, there were barely any living Gu Immortals. Including Fang Yuan and Blazing Heaven Demoness, there was a total of three rank eights, six rank sevens, and four rank sixes.

They were a powerful group, they had strength in numbers!

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's actions had truly angered Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance, it sent out such a huge group to Northern Plains just to take revenge.

However, all of the Gu Immortals were injured now. The rank six Gu Immortals were lightly injured, the rank sevens had more severe injuries and were in pathetic states, while the three rank eight Gu Immortals were weak and had damaged bodies, some were missing arms while others were missing legs. Their bodies were swaying in the breeze, as if about to fall over at any time.

The edges of the five regions had regional walls. The one surrounding Northern Plains was the licorice regional wall, and the one around Eastern Sea was the blue water regional wall.

Because of the existence of regional walls, the five regions were isolated.

Furthermore, the regional walls were bigger obstructions against stronger life forms.

The difficulty of a rank eight Gu Immortal passing a regional wall was innumerable times as hard as a rank six Gu Immortal!

The Eastern Sea immortal zombies had to go from Eastern Sea to Northern Plains, they had to pass two regional walls, the three rank eights were heavily injured, while four of the rank seven immortal zombies died in the regional walls. In contrast, the rank six Gu Immortals faced less pressure.

Among all of them, Fang Yuan had the easiest time.

He had the lowest cultivation level, at the bottom of rank six, at the same time, he was also a Northern Plains Gu Immortal.

When he entered Northern Plains from Eastern Sea, the Eastern Sea regional wall rejected him and pushed him out, while the Northern Plains regional wall welcomed him and drew him in.

Using the same logic, among the three rank eight immortal zombies, Blazing Heaven Demoness had the lightest injuries.

Like travelers from afar returning home, Fang Yuan and Blazing Heaven Demoness received the warm welcome of Northern Plains.

"If not for the giant Gu formation in Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's headquarters, we would have to sacrifice at least one rank eight immortal zombie, and half of the rank sevens."

Fang Yuan observed silently, at the same time, he inwardly praised Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's deep foundations.

Before they left, dozens of immortal zombies in the Zombie Alliance headquarters activated a Gu formation, causing an earth tide.

Once in a while, an earth tide would generate in Eastern Sea.

Drawing the force of the earth from deep within the sea trenches, a grand force would move the seawater and create an earth tide.

An earth tide was extremely powerful, it could easily whip up giant tsunamis. When an earth tide rushes at the regional wall, the regional wall would become thinner as a result, thus, every year during the earth tides, many Gu Immortals from other regions would enter Eastern Sea.

When Fang Yuan and the others set off, the earth tides were over already.

To think that in Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance's headquarters, there was a method to create an artificial earth tide, weakening a portion of the Eastern Sea regional wall for a short period of time.

If not for this, Fang Yuan and the others would have suffered greater injuries.

"What do we do now?" After resting for a while, a rank eight immortal zombie broke the silence.

The other Gu Immortals were focusing their gazes on Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was the leader of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, among the three rank eight immortal zombies, she was the strongest in terms of battle strength, thus, she was primarily directing the group in this mission.

Blazing Heaven Demoness did not hesitate, she smiled: "According to a reliable source, Old Ancestor Xue Hu has already returned to Snowy Mountain blessed land. We should not rush there, we should rest and recuperate, and recover our battle strength, that is the best course of action."

The immortal zombies nodded in agreement, there were no objections.

They had just passed the regional walls, their battle strength had dropped to the lowest point, they needed to recover now.

Blazing Heaven Demoness did not even go back to Dark Flow Giant City, she chose a hidden and secluded spot.

The Eastern Sea Gu Immortals went into hiding as they recuperated.

This was the same course of action as taken by the Central Continent Gu Immortals when they came.

There was no other choice, the cost of passing the regional walls was too high.

In Snowy Mountain blessed land, snow was falling.

Three main peaks with countless branch peaks were situated, like a colossal frost giant that was standing straight.

Among them, the first main peak was tall and big, it was the residence of Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

Right now, in a certain room on the first main peak, a giant Gu formation was flickering with golden lights.

Outside the Gu formation, there was an old man.

It was Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

But at this moment, it was not him controlling the Gu formation, it was a female immortal.

This female immortal looked like she was in her late twenties, she had a beautiful appearance and elegant disposition, it was the second leader of Snowy Mountain, Lady Wan Shou.

Lady Wan Shou was Old Ancestor Xue Hu's wife, she looked much younger than Old Ancestor Xue Hu, but she was in fact much older than him.

Lady Wan Shou once had a fortuitous encounter and obtained the inheritance of Gu Immortal Wang Jiu, not only did she obtain a few lifespan Gu, she also obtained many lifespan extension methods.

These lifespan extension methods all had drawbacks compared to lifespan Gu.

But lifespan Gu were extremely hard to find, Lady Wan Shou's lifespan extension methods were very popular with other Gu Immortals.

During Lady Wan Shou's early days, many Gu Immortals had approached her, paying a huge price for her to extend their lifespans.

In time, Lady Wan Shou helped more and more Gu Immortals, she had extended more than a thousand years worth of lifespan. Not only did she receive countless cultivation resources, her strength also rose drastically, she built a strong network and was very popular.

Many Gu Immortals needed her services, they naturally did not dare to offend her, they promoted her as her reputation soared far and wide.

Lady Wan Shou was not only skilled at extending lifespan, she was also a refinement path quasi-great grandmaster, she was known in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world as one of the 'four refinement path experts'.

Quasi-great grandmaster, she was only a step away from great grandmaster level.

In terms of refinement path, Fang Yuan could not compare to Lady Wan Shou at all. As for Old Ancestor Xue Hu, he was an ice and snow path expert, he was also inferior in refinement path.

Thus, whenever Old Ancestor Xue Hu wanted to refine Gu, he would ask Lady Wan Shou to do it.

But now, Lady Wan Shou was using this refinement path Gu formation not to refine Gu, but to temper an immortal material.

This immortal material was dug out by Old Ancestor Xue Hu from deep in Earth Trench, inside the deepest part of the Zombie Alliance immortal zombie graveyard.

It was palm sized and was shining in purple-gold light, it was like a rock.

The refinement path Gu formation shined brightly and made great rumbling noises.

A while later, the Gu formation settled down, and the light also dissipated. The mysterious purple-gold rock that had turned completely red now cooled down quickly, it went back to its previous state.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu looked at Lady Wan Shou with an expectant gaze, he was asking her wordlessly.

Lady Wan Shou frowned slightly, she shook her head.

"Even you cannot tell what this mysterious purple-gold rock is?" Old Ancestor Xue Hu was surprised.

"This immortal material is truly extraordinary, I have already used my Gu formation to its limits, but I could not refine it. This is the first time I've seen such a situation, I need to research it carefully."

After saying this, Lady Wan Shou changed the topic: "Dear, you were too careless. It would have been fine if you were not exposed when stealing immortal zombies. But now that you have exceeded Zombie Alliance's bottom line, they are sure to take revenge, you need to be careful."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu nodded, he said heavily: "This time, I was overconfident. My original plan was progressing smoothly, I almost looted the entire immortal zombie graveyard, but suddenly, a Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie appeared. This is a superb immortal material for refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu, I got too excited and tried to capture him. To think he had already set up a Gu formation in the graveyard, I was careless and could not conceal the sound of the battle, thus Northern Plains Zombie Alliance was alerted."

"Oh..." Old Ancestor Xue Hu sighed deeply: "Now that I think about it, it was likely the interference of fortune rivalling heaven Immortal."

Lady Wan Shou said in a heavy tone: "Fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu is rank eight, it is to be expected that you were influenced. This is the core Immortal Gu of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. When I was refining Gu recently, I have been failing a lot too, it is likely the effect of fortune rivalling heaven Gu. But dear, just now, you have obtained a large number of immortal zombie bodies, the rate of immortal material collection was raised drastically. As long as we can refine fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, all of this would be worth it."

Ever since Old Ancestor Xue Hu bought Ma Hong Yun, he had been using the latter as the main material to refine the rank eight fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu.

This matter was not advantageous to Ma Hong Yun, thus, Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Lady Wan Shou faced the backlash of fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu.

Not only them, many Gu Immortals of Snowy Mountain blessed land had received Old Ancestor Xue Hu's orders to collect immortal materials, but they constantly faced bad luck and many mishaps happened to them.

Actually, previously, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had already experienced a backlash from luck path.

That was when Fairy Li Shan had just obtained Miniscule Mountain, it attracted the attack of Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu. But fighting both of them alone, Old Ancestor Xue Hu forced them to retreat.

Luck path was not invincible by any means, Old Ancestor Xue Hu used his immense strength to resist the backlash of luck path.

Just now, it was a near guaranteed success that he would steal the immortal zombie bodies, but due to the luck path backlash, he became careless, and the matter was blown up.

"The more difficulties we face in refining fortune rivalling heaven Gu, the more we can see the power of this Immortal Gu, and the more determined I am to refine it! Don't worry, I have already placed Dark Flow Giant City under close supervision, if anything happens, I will know immediately. We will resist whoever comes here, I want to see if Zombie Alliance can really invest so much into this."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu laughed, he displayed the dominance and ambition of a demonic path overlord.

Chapter 929: Plotting Against Old Ancestor Xue Hu

The huge Dark Flow Giant City was situation in a desolate land.

Darkness loomed over it, the giant city was like a slumbering beast, quietly lurking.

Ever since Old Ancestor Xue Hu had ransacked the immortal zombie graveyard, Dragon Commander Ye Cha and the other two leaders had closed the entirety of Dark Flow Giant City, showing a defensive stance.

Dark Flow Giant City was focusing on defense, no matter how other forces tried to probe it, they could only obtain a bit of information.

When night came, Blazing Heaven Demoness led the other Eastern Sea immortal zombies and secretly returned to Dark Flow Giant City.

"Subordinates Yin Liu Gong, Dragon Commander Ye Cha and Huang Quan Weng welcome leader and both lords, greetings to everyone." The three currently in charge of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance paid respects, they could not conceal the uneasiness and agitation in their expressions.

"Get up. You were facing Old Ancestor Xue Hu, it was not your fault." Blazing Heaven Demoness said first.

Yin Liu Gong and the others sighed in relief, their worries were eased.

Their lives had been very difficult these last few days.

On one hand, they were waiting for the reinforcements from Zombie Alliance's headquarters, but at the same time, they were worried about their responsibility towards this matter in terms of negligence.

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu was too arrogant, he has to pay the price, we of Zombie Alliance are not to be trifled with." Another rank eight immortal zombie said.

The surrounding immortal zombies looked at him in admiration, they quickly voiced out their agreement.

This rank eight immortal zombie was known as Corpse Detonation King, he was most skilled at using the smallest cost to ignite immortal zombie bodies and cause terrifying explosions.

He had a bad temper and was ruthless, when he passed the regional wall, he wantonly attacked allies who disagreed with him and killed them. Among the four rank seven immortal zombies that died, three were dead because of him. Their corpses were blown to bits, completely shattered, they created a huge explosion in the regional wall which allowed Corpse Detonation King to advance forward.

"Leader, when are we counterattacking?"

"When we attack, please let me be the vanguard!"

Yin Liu Gong and Huang Quan Weng saw the reinforcements from Eastern Sea and felt a strong sense of enthusiasm, they requested to help.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was not anxious, she said leisurely: "This matter is very important, let's go look at the crime scene first, we need to collect evidence there."

"That's right, looking at these traces, we might be able to estimate some of Old Ancestor Xue Hu's methods." Another rank eight immortal zombie, Pu Wan Dao, nodded in agreement.

Even though they were greater in numbers, they were all immortal zombies, compared to living Gu Immortals, they had many drawbacks.

Most importantly, the other party was not an ordinary person, they could not pressure him easily.

This was someone who could fight both Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu alone and force them back, he was a fearsome character, the publicly recognized number one demonic path Gu Immortal in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world!

Next, the immortal zombies moved without pause, secretly going to Earth Trench and analyzing the battlefield.

The battlefield was well preserved by Yin Liu Gong and the others.

The immortal zombie graveyard was a mess, the surface was covered in large amounts of frost, some crevices even had some fire burning in them.

Everyone displayed their abilities as they investigated.

Fang Yuan was among them, but his mind was wandering.

He gazed around, but his mind was elsewhere. He was looking for the treasure, but this treasure was not inside the immortal zombie graveyard, it was far deeper in Earth Trench.

"How can I obtain this treasure without anyone else knowing? I have a feeling this inheritance will surely be of huge help to me. Perhaps I will have to rely on it to get rid of my immortal zombie body and revive."

Fang Yuan was becoming more excited about it.

But currently it was a pity that he was unable to leave the group, he could only follow them as they left Earth Trench, returning to Dark Flow Giant City.

After observing the battlefield, the immortal zombies' expressions turned very ugly.

Even Corpse Detonation King and Pu Wan Dao had grim expressions.

Even though they did not engage in battle personally, just looking at the traces left behind, they could estimate Old Ancestor Xue Hu's immense power.

But this made everyone feel that there was something strange, it was the person who could fight Old Ancestor Xue Hu to this extent.

"Who is this person? With rank seven cultivation level, he had outstanding battle strength, even already having set up a Gu formation in the graveyard itself. They seem to be an immortal zombie as well, but why do I not have their details in my list of names?" Blazing Heaven Demoness frowned deeply, she asked Yin Liu Gong and the others.

Yin Liu Gong, Dragon Commander Ye Cha, and Huang Quan Weng smiled bitterly, they admitted blame in unison: "We have failed our duties, we were kept in the dark and did not know that there was such a person hiding in Earth Trench."

Blazing Heaven Demoness snorted coldly, her expression turned cold: "Investigate, investigate thoroughly. I feel that this is not so simple! Old Ancestor Xue Hu's appearance here can be explained. He needs to refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu but is lacking in immortal materials. But why did that mysterious immortal zombie appear in our Northern Plains Zombie Alliance graveyard? Looking at this situation, he had been here for a long time already!"

"No need to investigate." At this time, the rank eight Gu Immortal Corpse Detonation King interjected: "This person is a member of Zombie Alliance. We are here now to rescue him."

Beside him, Pu Wan Dao added: "Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness, and everyone from Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, do forgive us. This person is not ordinary, he is a ten extreme immortal zombie with outstanding battle strength. Because he is on a secret mission from Zombie Alliance, for his safety, he was kept hidden. Zombie Alliance's headquarters has sent down a top priority order, we have to work together to rescue this Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie."

"It was like this?" The immortal zombies showed looks of shock.

Yin Liu Gong and the other two were slightly taken aback before their expressions turned grim.

Dragon Commander Ye Cha cupped his fists at the people from Eastern Sea: "I wonder what secret mission this Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie was on, that he had to come to the highly important immortal zombie graveyard in our Northern Plains Zombie Alliance."

Corpse Detonation King replied coldly: "This is not something you are qualified to know."

"Alright." Blazing Heaven Demoness stood up, she tried to ease the situation: "Our enemy now is Old Ancestor Xue Hu. Since that immortal zombie is one of us, we will save him as well."

Yin Liu Gong and the others nodded in agreement.

Fang Yuan watched coldly from the side.

This secret was kept from even Blazing Heaven Demoness. She was, after all, a Northern Plains immortal zombie, even though she had been in Eastern Sea for a long time, she was still isolated from the true core of Zombie Alliance.

At the same time, Fang Yuan realized something.

Zombie Alliance sent out so many people not only to teach Old Ancestor Xue Hu a lesson, but they most importantly wanted to save this Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie.

Fang Yuan saw this interesting situation as he laughed internally: "Hehe, if this Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie was sent by Zombie Alliance's headquarters secretly as a spy to check on the Northern Plains branch, that would be amusing! Earlier, Dragon Commander Ye Cha was probably trying to ask about this."

"Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness, you are indeed a valuable member of our Zombie Alliance. If everyone else had your awareness and understanding, why would we have to worry about Zombie Alliance's goal of becoming the overlord of the five regions? Hahaha!" Corpse Detonation King laughed loudly.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was kept in the dark, she only learned about the true mission now.

But she was a shrewd person, she did not show any displeasure, instead she said: "Next, let us talk about how we will teach Old Ancestor Xue Hu a lesson and also save the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie."

Corpse Detonation King immediately said: "The Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie's body has an abundance of fire path and lightning path dao marks, he is extremely suited to be used to refine Gu. We should not waste time, we should just approach him directly."

"Going right at him is just an act of a boor." Blazing Heaven Demoness rebuked, not giving Corpse Detonation King any face.

Corpse Detonation King stared as he was about to say something, but Pu Wan Dao also supported Blazing Heaven Demoness: "That is right, the other party captured the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie, he has a hostage. If we go there openly, even if we suppress Old Ancestor Xue Hu, he will use the hostage to threaten us, we will be restricted and all our advantages would be lost."

"Then we will sneak into Snowy Mountain blessed land and save the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie!" Corpse Detonation King said again.

Blazing Heaven Demoness snorted: "Outside Dark Flow Giant City, there are countless hidden investigators, some must come from Snowy Mountain blessed land. With just this, we can see how alert Old Ancestor Xue Hu is, Snowy Mountain blessed land is sure to be heavily guarded. It is not realistic to sneak in, it is like surrendering ourselves to them. Of course! Corpse Detonation King, you are incredibly powerful and have amazing skills, if you want to, you can go yourself. I am sure that with your strength, you will succeed."

"You!" Corpse Detonation King was lost for words, he showed an ashamed and angry expression.

"Then, in your opinion, what shall we do?" Pu Wan Dao placed his hand on Corpse Detonation King's shoulder as he asked Blazing Heaven Demoness with a sharp gaze.

Blazing Heaven Demoness smiled proudly: "Even though Old Ancestor Xue Hu is strong, and Snowy Mountain blessed land is heavily guarded, it cannot conceal his greatest weakness."

Someone asked: "Oh? What weakness?"

Blazing Heaven Demoness looked around as she said: "Fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan had no interest in dealing with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, when the immortal zombies were discussing about schemes excitedly, he was thinking about how to get to the treasure deep inside Earth Trench.

After an exchange of words, Blazing Heaven Demoness regained control as the first in command.

The immortal zombies planned and arranged their roles. Blazing Heaven Demoness did not let Fang Yuan go with them, she gave him one mission only, that was to continue refining star thought Immortal Gu.

She even gave Fang Yuan a token, it provided him the highest representation of her authority.

With this token, Fang Yuan could freely enter or exit Dark Flow Giant City, as well as the resource points that were controlled by Northern Plains Zombie Alliance. He could even enter the storage and use the precious immortal materials that were accumulated inside.

As long as they were used to refine Immortal Gu, he just had to register what he took.

The terms were relaxed and in his favor, Fang Yuan could not help but be surprised by this.

"Does Blazing Heaven Demoness still want to take down Yu Lu blessed land? That is not possible. Not mentioning how long it would take to solve this issue with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, now that Shark Demon and Su Bai Man have started invading it again, they are sure to make use of their time and invite wisdom path Gu Immortals to help regardless of the cost."

"But once I have star thought Immortal Gu, together with my wisdom path attainment level, I can deduce many things. Maybe Blazing Heaven Demoness wants to make use of my ability in this regard to deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu?"

Chapter 930: Creating a Chance to Enter Earth Trench

Boom!

There was a loud sound, but the power of the explosion, on the contrary, was not big.

The endless starlight flickered leisurely in the secret room, like fluttering butterflies.

Looking at such a beautiful scene, Fang Yuan's expression was very unsightly.

"Failed again. This time, the refinement of star thought Immortal Gu did not even progress to one-third..." Fang Yuan exhaled and waved his sleeve, immediately, everything was cleared, the starlight disappeared without a trace and the large secret room once again recovered its tranquility.

This was a secret room in Northern Plains Zombie Alliance.

Fang Yuan had obtained enough immortal materials here, thus, he made another attempt at refinement, but tasted the bitterness of failure once again.

"Despite using immortal killer move time assist luck before refining every time, the effect is not much. In terms of Connect Luck, there are no suitable targets. Forget it, I have already showed enough efforts on the surface, now I should try to enter deep into Earth Trench and get that inheritance."

Fang Yuan naturally wanted to get the inheritance as soon as possible, but in many matters, haste was waste.

If he did not refine star thought Immortal Gu and just tried to go into Earth Trench hurriedly, it would no doubt be exposing his intentions.

It would be easily seen through, this naturally could not be allowed.

Although Fang Yuan entered Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, the current problem was he did not have freedom and was strictly guarded by two immortal zombies.

Fang Yuan understood that he was being monitored.

After all, he had failed many times in refining the Immortal Gu and owed Blazing Heaven Demoness a huge amount.

If he was not monitored and ran away, what would she do?

Even though when they had set the agreement, Blazing Heaven Demoness had used information path methods and both sides were restricted by immortal killer moves.

But at Blazing Heaven Demoness' level, as the saying goes, 'the more aged and experienced a person is, the less recklessness they have, the more knowledge they have, the more careful they are.' Who could be certain if Fang Yuan did not have a way to break the restrictions?

And Fang Yuan indeed did!

His previous life's memories gave him knowledge of many methods that could break immortal level restrictions of information path. But he did not have relevant Immortal Gu, so at present, he did not have the ability to break the restrictions.

Moreover, he sincerely wanted to refine star thought Immortal Gu, thus he was cooperating with Blazing Heaven Demoness.

But now, his even more wanted to secretly take that inheritance.

During these last days in Dark Flow Giant City, Fang Yuan tried refining star thought Immortal Gu to make Blazing Heaven Demoness feel at ease, while secretly gathering information and making preparations for when he made a move.

Compared to previously, Dark Flow Giant City had already opened its city gates, resuming its dealings with the outside world. The immortal zombies' morale gradually started rising and they were in high spirits.

Blazing Heaven Demoness led the experts to deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu, using a rather intelligent strategy.

She did not attack directly, instead exploiting Old Ancestor Xue Hu's greatest weakness.

What was Old Ancestor Xue Hu's greatest weakness?

Almost all Northern Plains Gu Immortals knew.

That was fortune rivalling heaven Gu!

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was wholeheartedly trying to refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu, but he severely lacked immortal materials, even though he already had Ma Hong Yun, the main material, this concerned rank eight Immortal Gu, he needed to prepare many sets of materials and do everything to maximize the possibility of success. Thus, his requirements towards immortal materials were extremely huge.

Those demonic path Gu Immortals of Snowy Mountain blessed land were already endlessly at work from Old Ancestor Xue Hu, they were in constant torment in order to find the materials.

Even Old Ancestor Xue Hu let go of his status, and personally sneaked into the immortal zombie graveyard in Earth Trench, like a two-bit thief.

This showed Old Ancestor Xue Hu's extreme desire towards immortal materials.

Blazing Heaven Demoness used this point to actively deploy and transfer experts to deal with those demonic path Gu Immortals of Snowy Mountain blessed land in particular, using ambushes, plots, wrecking plans and various other strategies.

These demonic path Gu Immortals already had enough pain as it was when gathering immortal materials, now that they suffered the backlash of luck path, the immortal zombies had a high success rate every time they moved against them.

As these attempts continued to succeed many times, Snowy Mountain blessed land's morale unavoidably fell, while Zombie Alliance's morale gradually rose, sweeping away the previous dejectedness.

Fang Yuan opened the door to the secret room with an ashen expression.

Two rank six immortal zombies were standing guard at the entrance.

Seeing Fang Yuan, an immortal zombie called Doctor Yin Xuan immediately bowed: "Sir, you have come out. I wonder if this refinement...."

Fang Yuan gave a grunt, waving his hand in irritation: "Don't bother me!"

Saying this, he walked away.

"Hmph, who does he thinks he is, to be so arrogant in our base!" The other immortal zombie, Landlord Lei Yu's eyes flickered with ominous light as he looked at Fang Yuan's receding figure.

However, Doctor Yin Xuan did not care about being ignored, brightly smiling as he followed closely behind Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan walked ahead, taking a left turn and then a right, arriving in front of a hall.

This was the biggest immortal material warehouse in Dark Flow Giant City, and was personally watched by an immortal zombie.

Seeing Fang Yuan as well as Doctor Yin Xuan and Landlord Lei Yu, the immortal zombie in charge familiarly nodded towards them, knowing Fang Yuan was here to get immortal materials; he handed an information path Gu worm to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan held the Gu worm, and pretended to inspect the immortal material list inside, while plotting inwardly.

'Blazing Heaven Demoness, Corpse Detonation King and Pu Wan Dao have already left Dark Flow Giant City two days ago to target the demonic path Gu Immortals of Snowy Mountain blessed land, and have not returned until now. This is an opportunity, I need to take advantage of it...'

Right at this time, the immortal zombie managing the warehouse enthusiastically spoke: "Sir Xing Xiang Zi, you can take any immortal materials you want. Leader has already informed us, and you only need to register the items. You don't need to have any worries."

Who knew that right as he finished speaking, Fang Yuan stared at him with a fierce look: "What worries would I have? Why would I have any worries? I am good!"

Fang Yuan looked like a mess with his hair and clothes in disorder, and also very agitated.

One look at this appearance, and the managing immortal zombie knew Fang Yuan must have failed the refinement.

This immortal zombie was dazed for a moment before thinking: 'Serves me right, why do I have to shoot my mouth off. Whether his refinement succeeds or fails, what has it got to do with me?'

At once, he kept quiet to prevent any further issues.

However, Fang Yuan was not willing to let go.

He crushed the information path Gu worm, and walked away with his head low and hands behind his back.

He was grumbling: "Damn it, why is it still not working, why is it always a failure! I have already failed four times, why is it like this, why..."

Doctor Yin Xuan and Landlord Lei Yu looked at each other, and both sensibly stayed away from Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan, however, became more restless and started swearing while clenching his fists, his words were extremely vulgar and occasionally, he mumbled incomprehensible words.

Doctor Yin Xuan tried his best to differentiate them but he could only make out some fragmented contents.

"Do I really have to use that method?"

"No, the price is too high..."

"Damn it, this damned Immortal Gu, why am I not succeeding?!"

Fang Yuan revealed hesitation, seemingly having to make an extremely difficult decision.

His eyes were very red, giving the impression of a gambler who had already lost most of his assets but decided to go all in to win back the losses.

"Screw it, I will stake it all!"

"This time, it will definitely succeed, definitely."

"Right, it will succeed!"

The three immortal zombies watched on indifferently, and as they looked on at Fang Yuan's restlessness, the disdain and hate in their heart disappeared slightly, replaced by a trace of pity.

Many Gu Immortals had faced such a situation.

To refine an Immortal Gu, they paid a huge price, but they end up making no gains and might even lose all their wealth.

It was like stepping on a road of no return, looking at the dozens of years of accumulation and even hundreds of years of resources go to waste, it was unavoidable for them to become irrational and chase after success, unable to turn back, walking further and further on the road of failure.

Fang Yuan suddenly stopped and turned around, looking at Doctor Yin Xuan and Landlord Lei Yu.

"I have decided, you two pack up and follow me into Earth Trench!"

Fang Yuan's words gave a huge shock to the three immortal zombies.

"Entering Earth Trench?" Doctor Yin Xuan's expression changed.

Earth Trench was a dangerous place with ferocious beasts roaming around and perilous terrain, who knew how many lives have been buried there.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had ordered them to monitor Fang Yuan, naturally it also meant they had to guard him. Hearing Fang Yuan suddenly speak of entering Earth Trench, how could Doctor Yin Xuan agree?

Landlord Lei Yu also did not agree, saying firmly: "We will gather any immortal materials you require, sir, you don't need to take the risk."

"What do you understand, huh?" Fang Yuan raised his voice, his gaze revealing an arrogant look.

"Both of us have received leader's command to ensure your safety, sir. Sir, if you enter Earth Trench and something happens, how can we explain it to leader? Please don't make it difficult for us." Doctor Yin Xuan gave a bitter smile, requesting earnestly.

Why would Fang Yuan care about his sincerity, he raised his arm and roared: "What does your difficulty have to do with me? I only care about refining Gu, I only know I need earth shell snail star night mucus!"

"Earth shell snail star night mucus? Sir, please hold on, I will check." Doctor Yin Xuan immediately said.

He also had information path Gu worms on him which contained the records of most of the immortal materials in Zombie Alliance.

Soon, Doctor Yin Xuan showed a joyous look as he retracted his consciousness: "Earth shell snail mucus is the fluid left behind by the desolate beast earth shell snail as it slowly crawls on the ground. We have it, we have it. Currently, in warehouse number six, there are two to three in stock, will they be enough? If they are not, we will immediately issue a task and summon immortal zombies to gather them."

Fang Yuan bellowed furiously, scolding while pointing at Doctor Yin Xuan's nose: "Have you become deaf or is there a hole in your brain? Didn't you hear what I said?! Earth shell snail star night mucus. Star. Night. Mucus! Not ordinary mucus, do you understand?!"

He then hurriedly continued: "Earth shell snail mucus needs to be sealed and stored within ten breaths of time, otherwise the fluid will dry up and lose its effect. Star night mucus is produced by using my special methods to process the ordinary mucus on the spot! The processing requires seven breaths of time, and even if the processing is complete and star night mucus is produced, its sealing process is complicated and needs to be finished within three breaths. So I need to enter Earth Trench, can you do it without me? If you can do it, I will eat my hat!"

"Uh..." For a moment, Doctor Yin Xuan and the others choked on their words, unable to retort to Fang Yuan's scolding.

Chapter 931: Finally Entering Earth Trench

Earth shell snails lived in the depths of Earth Trench, or rather, they could only live there.

According to what Fang Yuan said, to collect the star night mucus, he would need to enter deep into Earth Trench and find an earth shell snail, trailing behind it as the snail moves, processing the mucus on the spot.

After processing it, he had to collect the star night mucus in a very short amount of time.

There was great difficulty in this, and it was very dangerous.

Earth shell snails had mild temperaments, it was not hard to get near them, one could even stand on their backs and attack them lightly, this desolate beast would not get angry.

The danger came from the fact that Earth Trench did not only contain earth shell snails.

The deeper one went into Earth Trench, the more fierce beasts, mysterious plants and wild Gu worms would show up.

Earth Trench was unfathomably deep, the place where the earth shell snails lived was a huge distance from the surface. Around the earth shell snail, there were many powerful beasts that formed into groups of desolate beasts, even ancient desolate beasts were not rare.

These fierce beasts and plants were the biggest threat.

"I definitely have to go into Earth Trench. Since Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness wants you two to protect me, then I will rely on you. Even if you die, I must live, do you understand?" Fang Yuan ordered them in a matter-of-fact tone.

Landlord Lei Yu and Doctor Yin Xuan gritted their teeth in anger, but they could do nothing to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan used Blazing Heaven Demoness' name, these two immortal zombies had no choice.

The two discussed for a while before Doctor Yin Xuan said with a gloomy face to Fang Yuan: "This is very important, I have to report to Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness first, we cannot decide this ourselves!"

In the end, the key obstacle was still Blazing Heaven Demoness.

But this was something Fang Yuan had expected.

Thus, he waved his sleeves, urging them: "Then go!"

He was not afraid of Blazing Heaven Demoness' investigation.

The truth was, star night mucus was a real thing.

This was one of the gains that Fang Yuan had recently when modifying the star thought Immortal Gu recipe.

Star night mucus was a personal innovation by Fang Yuan, it had a lot of potential and had a variety of uses. Not only could it be used for star thought Immortal Gu, it could also be used for the refinement of other star path Immortal Gu, it was an easy to gather rank six immortal material that also had a lot of use.

"If I can find a suitable habitat for earth shell snails, I can make use of it to produce star night mucus continuously. This immortal material would be a monopoly if I sold it in treasure yellow heaven, I can definitely sell it for a good price. In the short run, its value and profit would rival guts Gu."

Fang Yuan evaluated.

But in the long run, the star night mucus' method of production would be deciphered by others, they would even mimic him.

After all, processing immortal materials was not like producing guts Gu, in the hands of refinement path and wisdom path Gu Immortals, it could be easily deciphered. He could not keep a monopoly for long.

Doctor Yin Xuan stayed and accompanied Fang Yuan. The unlucky fellow, Landlord Lei Yu, carried a sense of heaviness and uneasiness as he went to a certain Gu formation in Dark Flow Giant City, using an information path Gu formation to transmit the information to Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Fang Yuan was not worried that Blazing Heaven Demoness would stop him.

In fact, Fang Yuan was rather confident that she would agree to it.

After all, refining star thought Immortal Gu would be of great help to Blazing Heaven Demoness as well. Fang Yuan still owed her a huge debt, if she did not want him to die, she might even send other immortal zombies to protect him.

Of course, there would not be many immortal zombies protecting him.

Right now, Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's attention was on the demonic path Gu Immortals of Snowy Mountain blessed land, to assault them and prevent them from obtaining Gu refinement immortal materials, so that Old Ancestor Xue Hu would suffer.

"If Blazing Heaven Demoness really did that, it would be in my favor. Entering deep into Earth Trench, the more people there are, the safer it is. By the time I get to the inheritance, I can shrug them off. If there are few people, I can shrug them off more easily."

As Fang Yuan had expected, in the end, Blazing Heaven Demoness agreed with his idea and arranged for five immortal zombies to accompany him.

Among them, two were rank seven, and three were rank six. This was slightly beyond Fang Yuan's expectations, he could see Blazing Heaven Demoness' sincerity from this.

Three days later, the five immortal zombies gathered.

They waited for two more days, as the immortal zombies borrowed some Immortal Gu for this mission.

As the locals, no one was more familiar with Earth Trench than them.

After making ample preparations, the group set off.

What was worth noting was, not only did Northern Plains have an Earth Trench, in fact, the five regions all had an Earth Trench.

The ground was split open into giant ravines, some Earth Trenches stretched on for millions of li, some were tens of thousand of kilometers deep, some were immeasurably deep, in the Gu Master world, it was one of the most magnificent wonders of nature.

The Earth Trench in Zombie Alliance was closely guarded by them. When Blazing Heaven Demoness was not in Northern Plains, Yin Liu Gong, Dragon Commander Ye Cha, and Huang Quan Weng, the three rank seven immortal zombies, would send at least one person to guard the entrance of Earth Trench.

Earth Trench was full of resources, there were many desolate beasts, in the past, when Dark Flow Giant City was built here, it was to occupy this rich resource point.

Everyone knew that Northern Plains has the least amount of cultivation resources compared to the other four regions. But in Earth Trench, there was a huge area of rich resources. The only drawback was, there were powerful desolate plants and desolate beasts inside, they were numerous.

Normally, only super forces could occupy the Earth Trench resource point.

Northern Plains Zombie Alliance was like this, the Demon Expelling Sect in Central Continent was the same. Demon Expelling Sect was a super force, having three Gu Immortals standing guard in it, it controlled the Earth Trench known as An Zu Earth Trench, it was very famous in Central Continent.

By night time, Fang Yuan and the others went through the entrance of Earth Trench.

Fang Yuan had planned for a long time, he was not going to sneak in stealthily. He was surrounded by five immortal zombies, he was going in boldly and openly.

The giant trench was like a giant beast with a bloodthirsty mouth, it slowly opened its mouth in the deep darkness.

Fang Yuan and the others went inside, as their view of the trench gradually enlarged, dozens of times, hundreds of times.

After they flew down for several minutes, the interior of the Earth Trench was already wide enough to fit seventy or eighty Dark Flow Giant Cities.

The eerie darkness shined with twinkling glimmers of light.

The cliffs on the two sides were smooth and bare, there was only a sparse amount of needle shaped plants that were stuck there like sesame seeds.

Nobody knew how deep this Earth Trench was.

Even the immortal zombies who were in control of this place for many years had never explored to the bottom of the Earth Trench.

Even though the Earth Trench was full of resources, there was also an unbelievable number of desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts. Northern Plains Zombie Alliance did not have the strength, even though they exerted all their efforts, they only controlled the territory up to about one hundred and sixty kilometers from the surface.

In this current world, even though humans had been the overlords for a long time, they were not able to gain control over every area in nature.

Compared to the majesty of nature, humans were very insignificant and small.

The profound mysteries of heaven and earth were endless, they were deeply hidden. Even Immortal Venerables and Demon Venerables were merely at the peaks of one or two paths, being able to observe the rules of the world.

Humans were far from understanding the mysteries of heaven and earth, there was a long road ahead of them.

As the group moved deeper, Earth Trench became wider and it showed just how small Fang Yuan and the rest were.

Here, they were already around a hundred kilometers from the surface. Mountains could not fill up this Earth Trench, it was shrouded in boundless darkness, devouring everything.

Everyone was very quiet.

Fang Yuan looked around without making a sound, he observed the immortal zombies secretly using his peripheral vision.

Five immortal zombie guards, two rank seven, three rank six.

Among them, the rank seven immortal zombies were Dragon Commander Ye Cha and Granny Yuan.

Among the three rank sixes, there was Doctor Yin Xuan and Landlord Lei Yu, as well as an enslavement path immortal zombie, called Lin Da Niao.

In the last five days, Fang Yuan had obtained some of their information, he was not clueless about them.

Among the two rank seven immortal zombies, the leader was Dragon Commander Ye Cha.

He was one of the three vice-leaders of Dark Flow Giant City, and also the strongest person in this trip. What was worth mentioning was that he used his own immortal aperture to raise large numbers of yaksha octopuses, gaining a reputation because of them.

Immortal zombies had dead apertures, but Dragon Commander Ye Cha was able to raise large amounts of yaksha octopuses, this was something others found puzzling, and many immortal zombies were curious.

The other rank seven immortal zombie was Granny Yuan, skilled in defense.

Doctor Yin Xuan, as his title suggested, was a healing Gu Immortal. He could not compare to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but in regards to healing immortal zombies, he had quite the skill.

Landlord Lei Yu was skilled in attacking, his attacks were grand and powerful.

The final person, the immortal zombie Lin Da Niao, he was skilled in controlling birds, he was an enslavement path immortal zombie.

From this, one could see that Blazing Heaven Demoness had put in some effort in arranging these people to protect Fang Yuan.

Granny Yuan could provide him defense, while Doctor Yin Xuan could help Fang Yuan recover from injuries at a crucial moment, saving his life. If they were attacked by desolate beasts and were unable to win, Lin Da Niao could sacrifice the bird groups that he had, providing enough time to allow the immortals to make an escape.

The deeper they went, the wider Earth Trench became.

There was a lot of space between the two cliffs on the sides, birds could move very freely here.

At this moment, birds were flying out of Lin Da Niao's immortal aperture, flying around the place.

Enslavement path had its conveniences, ever since they entered Earth Trench, Lin Da Niao was in charge of the investigation aspect.

"The inheritance is that way, but I cannot go there directly, it would seem like I have an objective and they would be suspicious." Fang Yuan did not do anything suspicious, he was very patient.

After some traveling, Lin Da Niao suddenly said: "There is a yaksha octopus in front and towards the left, it is injured."

Dragon Commander Ye Cha's expression did not change: "Ignore it, we will detour around it."

Fang Yuan's group of six was very powerful, a rank six yaksha octopus was surely inferior to them.

But this trip was to find earth shell snails and gather immortal materials, that was their objective.

By that point, they were sure to go through many battles, they should save their immortal essence for now.

Earth shell snails lived deep in Earth Trench, they moved very slowly and did not have fixed locations, they were very hard to trace.

The stronger the beast, the more they would have a sense of territory.

In an extremely deep part of Earth Trench, all sorts of fierce beasts and plants owned their respective territories.

But earth shell snails were a rare species that could move between territories without attracting the animosity of the desolate beasts.

Maybe it was because of the earth shell snail's gentle nature, it let the other strong living beings know that it was harmless.

But Fang Yuan and the others would not receive treatment like the earth shell snail.

Thus, there were bound to be battles.

Chapter 932: Yaksha Octopuses, Mouth Earthworm

Without speaking, Fang Yuan and the other immortal zombies had already traveled more than a hundred and thirty kilometers down into Earth Trench.

Even though they avoided battles, they still engaged in sixteen fights, both big and small.

The immortal zombies were more or less injured to an extent.

"We can't go any deeper." Dragon Commander Ye Cha said: "At this depth, we are already at the range of the earth shell snail's habitat, let's look around."

Northern Plains Zombie Alliance only managed to explore one hundred and sixty kilometers into Earth Trench.

Right now, they were still around thirty kilometers from that limit, but the lower they went, the more dangerous it became, desolate beasts were everywhere, and Fang Yuan's group would face even more difficulties than now.

No immortal zombie objected to Dragon Commander Ye Cha's suggestion.

After choosing a direction, everyone flew quietly.

Maybe it was because Fang Yuan had used time assist luck before this trip and raised his luck for a period of time. But in any case, not long after, he encountered an earth shell snail.

"Great." Fang Yuan showed an overjoyed expression.

"Don't be anxious, check the surroundings first, make sure there are no dangers lurking around." Dragon Commander Ye Cha was very patient.

The immortals used their methods to thoroughly investigate, in this area, there was a sizable group of yaksha octopuses guarding their territory.

"To process the snail mucus, I will need to use starlight, it will definitely alert these yaksha octopuses." Fang Yuan showed a difficult expression as he looked at Dragon Commander Ye Cha.

Everyone's expressions sank.

"Why didn't you say that earlier?" Landlord Lei Yu asked unhappily.

"Maybe there is a way to conceal this disturbance..." Doctor Yin Xuan said.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "That is not possible, I also want to conceal our disturbance, but that is beyond my ability. I cannot reveal my actual method, but in short, we should get rid of these yaksha octopuses first."

Fang Yuan's attitude was firm and his reason was valid.

The other immortal zombies looked at each other, in the end, Dragon Commander Ye Cha relented: "Then we will fight this group of yaksha octopuses before Xing Xiang Zi starts."

This time, Dragon Commander Ye Cha did the scouting personally.

There were eight desolate beast octopuses in this group, among them was an octopus king, having rank seven Gu Immortal battle strength.

"Lin Da Niao will be in charge of the surroundings, mobilizing the bird groups to encircle the octopus group."

"Granny Yuan will draw their attention and distract them."

"Landlord Lei Yu and I will attack these octopuses."

"As for Doctor Yin Xuan, you will stand guard outside in case of emergencies."

Dragon Commander Ye Cha quickly arranged matters, Fang Yuan did not have to do anything.

The yaksha octopuses were truly unfortunate, the immortal zombies stealthily approached them, scheming against this unknowing group. Thus, once they fought, the yaksha octopus group suffered a huge blow and fell into panic.

The immortal zombies quickly gained an advantage as they built upon their superiority.

Soon, the battle reached its end as the octopuses were killed, only two were left.

At this time, Dragon Commander Ye Cha said to Fang Yuan: "Xing Xiang Zi, go ahead and attack."

Fang Yuan's gaze shone, he slowly went into battle.

Immortal killer move — Star Snake Rope.

He first trapped the yaksha octopus that was in better condition, before using six illusion star bodies to encircle the other one.

Swish swish swish...

Starlight shone brightly, Fang Yuan attacked non-stop, he quickly killed this yaksha octopus which was already close to dying.

Next, he turned around and targeted the final one remaining.

The yaksha octopus was half man and half beast. Its upper body was a muscular man with bulging muscles and dark skin that was tough as steel. Its lower body was made of dozens of tentacles, in place of legs.

This final yaksha octopus was in a good condition, it fought valiantly, engaging in a fierce battle with Fang Yuan, as it slowly fell into a deadlock with him.

Fang Yuan used star cloud grindstone to defend himself while waiting for a chance to attack time and time again, until he finally cut off all of the yaksha octopus' tentacles.

When he was fighting, the other immortal zombies watched without doing anything.

At most, Lin Da Niao manipulated the bird groups to prevent the yaksha octopus which was trying to escape from leaving, allowing Fang Yuan to catch up and continue fighting it.

Fang Yuan had a lot of patience, he slowly injured the yaksha octopus, dark and cold blood flowed out from its injuries.

"Alright, you can stop." Eventually, Dragon Commander Ye Cha did not want to wait anymore, he personally struck and captured this yaksha octopus himself.

The first few were all killed because they could not afford to go easy on the group initially.

This octopus was captured by Dragon Commander Ye Cha, he was preparing to raise it inside his immortal aperture.

Now, all the immortal zombies understood Fang Yuan's battle strength.

Fang Yuan only showed his star path battle strength, but even so, he was an expert among rank sixes. Landlord Lei Yu, who was unhappy towards Fang Yuan became silent.

He estimated that if he fought Fang Yuan alone, he might not be able to win.

In the Gu Immortal world, strength ruled above all, even if Landlord Lei Yu was unhappy, he could not show it on the surface.

Next, Fang Yuan started collecting star night mucus.

He requested the immortal zombies to stay back and not use any investigative methods to steal his personal technique.

The immortal zombies were naturally unhappy, they scolded Fang Yuan internally for being so small-minded, but they had to agree to his request.

When processing the mucus, the starlight caused quite a disturbance.

Soon, the earth shell snail stopped moving, its entire body curled into its shell.

The moment it sensed danger, the earth shell snail would react like this.

Its shell was very thick, even though it was only a desolate beast, most rank six Gu Immortals could do nothing to it. Even rank seven Gu Immortals would need to exert a lot of effort to break its shell.

Furthermore, the earth shell snail was large like a whale, and heavy like a mountain, once it entered its shell, it could be for a year or two. If there was a huge commotion outside, it would stay inside for even longer.

If it was moved away from the habitat of earth shell snails, even if it was still in Earth Trench, even if it was outside of it by a few kilometers, the earth shell snail would die immediately.

Thus, the immortal zombies could only give up on this one and find others.

In Earth Trench, there were more than yaksha octopuses.

There were bat desolate beasts, wall climbing demon apes, and desolate plants like earth milk grass.

On their later journey, they met with three earth shell snails.

Among which, Fang Yuan made good use of two of them and collected a lot of star night mucus. The final one however, moved towards the territory of an ancient desolate beast red flame snake.

This monster had dark path, fire path, and earth path dao marks on it, it was hard to deal with and was an expert in digging holes, it could move quickly between the walls of Earth Trench.

Once they fought, the commotion would be unconcealable, thus, Fang Yuan and the others had to give up.

Under Fang Yuan's intentional guidance, the immortal zombies got closer to his destination.

"We've discovered a large number of yaksha octopuses ahead! Stop moving forward, there are a lot of them, the initial estimation is thirty!" Lin Da Niao suddenly reported anxiously.

"Then we will leave this place and go in another direction." Dragon Commander Ye Cha immediately ordered.

Thirty desolate beasts, that was the battle strength of thirty rank six Gu Immortals. Such a massive group would surely have at least three ancient desolate beast yaksha octopuses commanding it.

Even though Fang Yuan was unwilling, he could not object to it publicly, he could only memorize this place for now.

The immortal zombies took a detour towards the south-east direction.

Soon, they found a fourth earth shell snail.

This snail looked quite old, it was carrying a yellow shell, its white body moved slowly on the walls of Earth Trench, at an extremely slow pace.

"We're finally lucky." After investigating, Lin Da Niao laughed: "This area has little danger, Sir Xing Xiang Zi can go ahead and collect the mucus."

Fang Yuan nodded without speaking, observing intently.

Suddenly, his eyes shined, he saw the danger in this place.

This place seemed safe, but it was full of earth path dao marks, once someone got close, they would be pulled towards the wall.

The heavier the body, the stronger the force of attraction.

"Desolate beasts have huge bodies and incredible mass. Once they come here, they would be unable to move and would starve to death. The earth shell snail is heavy like a mountain, but this earth shell snail can still move slowly. It seems that this snail is not old, it is an ancient desolate beast earth shell snail!"

Realizing this, Fang Yuan had an idea.

He flew over, purposely acting like he was sucked over, as he screamed.

"Oh no, it is the gravity soil zone!"

"This should only appear after a hundred and sixty kilometers in depth, it is actually here as well."

"Be careful! This gravity soil zone often has mouth earthworms hidden in ambush!"

At once, the immortal zombies shouted in shock.

The closer he was to the gravity soil zone, the more Fang Yuan felt the suction force getting stronger and his speed increased.'

With a loud thud, Fang Yuan crashed into the wall, his legs were deeply stuck in the wall as he showed a terrified expression.

Immortal killer move — Star Fire Escape!

Fang Yuan used his movement killer move.

Immediately, his body was covered in star fire as he flew.

"Don't fly!" Dragon Commander Ye Cha roared.

But it was too late.

With a loud bang, a huge mouth earthworm emerged from the soil.

The earth shell snail immediately shrunk into its shell, turning motionless.

Huge amounts of rocks were pushed away, the mouth earthworm opened its mouth, it could swallow four or five earth shell snails at once.

Fang Yuan screamed: "Someone save me!"

Once he said that, the mouth earthworm swallowed him.

"Be careful! The mouth earthworm is full of sharp teeth, they are incomparably sharp!"

"Hang in there, we will definitely rescue you!!"

The immortal zombies were panicking, they moved at once.

If anything happened to Fang Yuan, how would they explain themselves to Blazing Heaven Demoness?

They attacked fiercely, forcing the mouth earthworm back into the gravity soil zone immediately.

This mystical ancient desolate beast had a huge body when hunting for food. Once it ate, its body would shrink rapidly like a leaking balloon. The teeth inside it would rotate endlessly, grinding its prey into meat paste and blood.

But once Fang Yuan went inside, he used a star path killer move and stopped the body from shrinking.

Next, he activated Fixed Immortal Travel.

He had memorized the place nearby earlier, in three breaths of time, Fixed Immortal Travel teleported him away and he escaped from this dangerous spot.

But Dragon Commander Ye Cha and the others still thought that Fang Yuan was inside the mouth earthworm, they were attacking it furiously.

Even though Fang Yuan got away from the immortal zombies, the disturbance from Fixed Immortal Travel had attracted the huge group of yaksha octopuses.

Fang Yuan smiled, turning into a yaksha octopus and attacking furiously.

A moment later, he successfully lured the angry yaksha octopuses towards Dragon Commander Ye Cha and the others.

Dragon Commander Ye Cha and the others were unable to discern Fang Yuan's transformation, they thought the yaksha octopuses were fighting among themselves and were chasing away the weakest members.

They sighed over their bad luck but because Xing Xiang Zi was still inside the mouth earthworm, they could not leave.

Thus, the yaksha octopuses, the Northern Plains immortal zombies, and the mouth earthworm engaged in a chaotic battle.

Chapter 933: Wild Immortal Gu, Traces of Gu Formation

In the chaotic battle, Fang Yuan managed to escape.

When he returned to the place where the yaksha octopuses were, about half of them were still left.

He tried the same thing again, luring the remaining yaksha octopuses away.

"Oh no! Another ancient yaksha octopus, and ten desolate beast octopuses. They seemed to have moved out together!" Dragon Commander Ye Cha was stuck in the chaotic battle, seeing the octopus reinforcements, he cried out in bitterness.

What grudges did they have, what vengeance was it?

The other immortal zombies also bemoaned their terrible luck, what was going on?!

But they had other choice than to save Xing Xiang Zi first.

"Hold on!" Dragon Commander Ye Cha shouted, he did not stint on his immortal essence, he used them extensively.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had immense authority, the immortal zombies did not dare to defy her orders, they could only endure in the chaotic battle.

Thankfully, this mouth earthworm did not hide in the gravity soil zone, it was in a frenzy and its huge body lashed around, creating powerful sonic booms.

The immortal zombie did not dare to take the hits, they could only attack from afar, the damage accumulated slowly as the mouth earthworm's skin was damaged.

Originally, the situation was quite simple.

Even though the mouth earthworm was an ancient desolate beast, it was not the match of Dragon Commander Ye Cha and the others.

But with the yaksha octopus group, it became a three way battle.

They restricted each other and fought randomly, the scene became very chaotic.

The yaksha octopuses were the greatest in number, they encircled the immortal zombies and the mouth earthworm, forming a tight layer.

"Xing Xiang Zi, you must survive!" Landlord Lei Yu shouted.

Even though he was unhappy with Fang Yuan, the moment he thought that Fang Yuan could die from this, he burst out in cold sweat.

Fang Yuan's safety was a huge issue weighing on the immortal zombies.

During this period, the perpetrator, Fang Yuan was secretly sneaking into the territory of the yaksha octopuses.

Groups of yaksha octopuses lived in the two sides of the cliff walls.

The cliff wall in front of him had a huge protrusion. This yaksha octopus group made a hole in this protrusion and made it their home.

Fang Yuan sneaked inside, drilling into a bigger entrance.

The entrance of the hole was very big, it was for the yaksha octopuses to enter and exit. Desolate beast level yaksha octopuses were very big, not to mention the ancient desolate beast yaksha octopus kings.

Fang Yuan entered the hole and a thick smell of oil assailed him.

The hole extended in front of him, he looked ahead and only saw darkness.

But Fang Yuan's investigative methods were very rich, this darkness could not obstruct him.

He stretched out his hand and touched the walls.

The surface of the hole's walls were full of black oil, they were thick and sticky.

Why would the dry cave have black oil?

This was due to the yaksha octopus' habits.

Yaksha octopuses were a type of fierce beast that liked to hunt for prey in the black oil of Earth Trench. Therefore, their bodies would often have sticky black oil stuck to them.

When they enter or exit the caves, the black oil would spread from their bodies to the walls of the caves.

The oily smell that Fang Yuan smelt was due to this black oil.

In the black oil, there were lots of weeds and needle wood, they were rooted into the walls and the black oil provided them sufficient nutrients.

Guru guru...

When Fang Yuan touched the black oil and wiped along it, bubbles started appearing on the sticky black oil surface on the wall.

Next, dozens of tiny worms that were smaller than fingers flew out from the bubbles.

They were alerted by Fang Yuan's actions and flew out, but they quickly went back into the black oil.

The black oil was like glue, it was very sticky and stuck to the walls tightly. Inside, there was rotting vegetation as well as large numbers of insects.

The insects were of such a massive scale, there were bound to be wild Gu worms in them.

Fang Yuan only gave them a glance and realized that there were at least four wild Gu worms around him. Two were earth path Gu worms, one was dark path, and one was water path.

Of course, these were mortal Gu, Fang Yuan had no interest in taking them.

"Dragon Commander Ye Cha is able to raise large numbers of yaksha octopuses, is his immortal aperture mimicking this environment?" Fang Yuan's mind wandered as he thought about this.

Fang Yuan was also very curious about Dragon Commander Ye Cha's cultivation secret.

Since an immortal zombie's immortal aperture was dead and filled with death energy, it could not be used to support living beings.

How did Dragon Commander Ye Cha do it?

Perhaps it was possible to learn the secrets of Dragon Commander Ye Cha by researching this environment, but now was not the time, Fang Yuan discarded these thoughts and moved on.

Several minutes later.

Howl——!

This was the final growl before the fierce beast died.

But this growl was only heard in a small area before it vanished.

The killer was Fang Yuan.

He used his Gu worms to prevent the sound from spreading.

This was deep into the yaksha octopus' cave, not only was the black oil seven to eight inches thick, some fierce beasts were even living here in the crevices.

These wild beasts mostly consisted of black stomach hounds.

Black stomach hounds ate rotting meat and bones. The yaksha octopus only consumed the fresh blood and meat of their prey, they did not eat the bones and rotting meat.

These black stomach hounds would eat the leftovers from the yaksha octopuses, the yaksha octopuses were happy with this, they had a free cleaner to tidy up the cave.

This was one of the wonders of nature, living beings could coexist in harmony.

When Fang Yuan found out the relationship between the black stomach hounds and the yaksha octopuses, he turned into a black stomach hound and ventured in.

It was a pity that these black stomach hounds divided their own territories and had a stronger territorial awareness than the yaksha octopuses.

Fang Yuan was fiercely attacked by the black stomach hounds, it would have been easier to just fight in his human form.

If this cave was divided into two, the upper half and the lower half, then Fang Yuan's current position was already in the lower half, past the upper half.

Even so, the clues to the inheritance had not appeared yet.

At every interval, there would be a fork in the path. All of the yaksha octopuses went to their homes through these paths, they were interconnected. In the ground, these countless holes formed widely connected and accessible paths.

Fang Yuan continued moving forward.

He found some yaksha octopuses that were guarding the cave.

These octopuses were only desolate beasts, Fang Yuan could take them down if he used his real battle strength.

But Fang Yuan got past them, he did not want to waste time in fighting with them.

He could use mortal Gu to conceal the traces when killing the black stomach hounds. But when dealing with desolate beasts, he needed a battlefield killer move to conceal the traces and commotion.

He lured most of the yaksha octopuses out.

But there was still an ancient yaksha octopus king, and numerous desolate beast yaksha octopuses.

If the yaksha octopus king was alerted, it would be terrible.

Time continued to pass, but he still found no clues, Fang Yuan was getting more anxious.

If he missed this chance, he would have to plan a lot for the next visit.

Even though he had Fixed Immortal Travel, he could not use it in Dark Flow Giant City blatantly. The activation of Fixed Immortal Travel caused quite a disturbance after all.

Within the investigative range of Gu Immortals, it was not just some light effects, the aura of Immortal Gu was like a fire burning in the night sky.

And at this time, Fang Yuan had to refine Gu in Dark Flow Giant City, Blazing Heaven Demoness would not let him leave her sights.

Fixed Immortal Travel could not be exposed.

Once it was exposed, many secrets would be exposed, the whole world would know that Fang Yuan was the person who toppled Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Fang Yuan did not know that the Central Continent Gu Immortals had already left by now.

"If there is no other way, I can only give up. Time is limited, once the battle ends and the mouth earthworm is dissected, if Dragon Commander Ye Cha and the others do not find me inside, I will not be able to explain it."

Fang Yuan evaluated.

Time was limited. He had about fifteen minutes.

Now, most of the time was already wasted, but he had no gains.

Fang Yuan had to use his time well, he raised his speed.

Eventually, he came to the deepest part of the cave.

Here, there was a yaksha octopus king resting.

Its snores were loud as thunder — evidently, it was sleeping.

"Immortal Gu aura!" Fang Yuan's heart jumped.

He felt the aura of a wild Immortal Gu in this yaksha octopus king.

As it turned out, this cave had existed for a long time, and this yaksha octopus king was the oldest. As a long time passed, among the Gu worms living in its body, one had emerged as a wild Immortal Gu.

The joy in his heart vanished as Fang Yuan felt glad.

Thankfully, he had not lured out this yaksha octopus king earlier.

If this yaksha octopus king appeared, the immortal zombies would definitely go crazy and try to capture the wild Immortal Gu, they would enter a frenzy.

But after finding this Immortal Gu, whether they succeeded or not, they would come to the cave and investigate.

"Perhaps this is how the Northern Plains Zombie Alliance found this inheritance in my previous life?" Fang Yuan had a flash of inspiration.

After hesitating, Fang Yuan decided to take a gamble.

He turned into a black stomach hound and carefully got close to the yaksha octopus king.

If this yaksha octopus king's wild Immortal Gu could expose Fang Yuan's identity, that would be trouble.

But this possibility was not big.

Fang Yuan decided to risk it.

"The cave is huge with many tunnels, but this is the deepest part of the cave, it is most likely to be here."

At this time, the yaksha octopus king's tentacles which were wrapped up loosened, it opened its eyes as its topaz-like pupils looked at Fang Yuan who has transformed into the black stomach hound.

Fang Yuan did not sense anything, he got past the yaksha octopus king and went behind it as if it was normal.

Behind the yaksha octopus king, there was a pile of white bones, there were some rotting meat left in them.

The octopus king shut its eyes, continuing to sleep.

Fang Yuan's mind was energized: "It is here! There are dao marks exposed here, these are traces of a Gu formation..."

Countless Gu worms in his immortal aperture were activated, immortal essence was expended rapidly as this Gu formation was unraveled.

Soon, Fang Yuan found that this space path giant Gu formation only showed a trace of a flaw because it had not been repaired for a long time.

"Very possibly, the treasure that I have been looking for is in this giant Gu formation. But to unravel this Gu formation, I have to activate Gu worms, the disturbance is huge. I can only take a risk..."

Fang Yuan made up his mind, he picked up a piece of bone and left the yaksha octopus king.

He quickly returned and when he reached a certain place, he used his Immortal Gu and directly attacked a close by desolate beast yaksha octopus.

The intense battle erupted as the yaksha octopuses that were defending their homes charged over.

Fang Yuan fought as he retreated, when he reached the exit, he activated Fixed Immortal Travel.

In three breaths of time, he teleported to the deepest area of the cave.

At this time, the yaksha octopus king was still at the exit of the cave, Fang Yuan fought against time as he unraveled this space path Gu formation.

After the yaksha octopuses fought for some time, they did not see any enemies and gradually calmed down, returning to the cave.

They moved quickly in the cave, Fang Yuan's time was limited.

The worse thing was, when he started unraveling it, Fang Yuan could feel the profoundness and complexity of this huge Gu formation.

To completely deduce it, he would need months to do so!

Chapter 934: Sea of Immortal Material Remains

Such an enormous Gu formation required at least several months to be unraveled.

It would require about a month just to pry an opening.

Fang Yuan's hands moved very fast, countless Gu worms fluttered all around, unraveling the Gu formation. At the same time, his ears quivered frequently as he activated his investigative methods to the limit, the yaksha octopus king was already on its way.

Time waits for no man.

Strive for every second!

"This is it." Fang Yuan's eyes suddenly brightened as the air in front of him started emitting a hazy glow.

Beyond the hazy glow, he saw a trace of the enormous Gu formation.

Although his sight was blurry, he could vaguely see the scenery inside the formation.

The yaksha octopus king had already returned.

Time was up, he had to retreat.

In this short amount of time, being able to peep into the scenery inside the Gu formation was already the limits of Fang Yuan's ability.

If Fang Yuan did not reach grandmaster level in wisdom path, he would not have been able to do this.

This was enough.

Fang Yuan relaxed, and immediately retreated.

The ancient desolate beast yaksha octopus king was moving like an underground subway train in the cave. The surrounding slippery black oil from Earth Trench allowed it to move like a fish in water.

Fang Yuan had almost bumped into it.

This yaksha octopus king returned to its place, and gazed around first of all.

It felt there was something off.

When Fang Yuan analyzed the Gu formation, many different kinds of auras were left behind, the wild beast's intuition made the yaksha octopus king feel something wrong.

It frowned deeply, and more than ten of its enormous and tough tentacles carried it nimbly as it patrolled around the nest.

However, it could not discover anything missing even after a while, while the previous unknown auras already had begun dissipating. The yaksha octopus king only then slowly calmed down, lying down on its nest again.

It was just that it did not sleep, its eyes were slightly closed but a small crack was opened.

From time to time, its ears would quiver from the slightest breeze in the cave as it tried to listen to any unknown sounds.

Fang Yuan's worries finally dissipated, he cautiously retreated, even retreating to the upper half of the octopus nest.

This yaksha octopus king seemed to have the highest status as it had stayed behind to guard the nest. If it felt any strong danger, who is to say it might not call back the other yaksha octopuses fighting outside.

At that time, not to mention whether the Northern Plains immortal zombies would feel suspicious and be attracted to the disturbance, Fang Yuan's movements in the octopus nest would be extremely restricted.

"This place should be okay." After a while, Fang Yuan carefully selected an inconspicuous corner among the several underground burrows.

He hesitated for a moment, but still decided to activate Fixed Immortal Travel.

Although that enormous Gu formation was arranged by some predecessor, when Fang Yuan deciphered it earlier, he found out that it had become an unmanned formation and had been unmanaged for many years. The risk of rashly going in was not high.

To find a method of reviving from the immortal zombie state, this was a risk he needed to take.

After all, as time passed, Fang Yuan's predicament would become more dangerous.

Who could say if the matter of him wrecking Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would be exposed at the next moment? At that time, the whole world would hunt him down. He would definitely not be able to protect Hu Immortal blessed land, and Star Form blessed land would be his only base.

In such a situation, the earlier he got rid of his immortal zombie body, the more beneficial it would be. After all, a living immortal aperture world could be brought with him, more safe and convenient than Hu Immortal blessed land or Star Form blessed land.

Moreover, living Gu Immortal immortal apertures could produce immortal essence in set intervals of time, which was extremely helpful to Fang Yuan's financial situation and battle strength!

The Immortal Gu was activated, green light blossomed.

The next moment, Fang Yuan disappeared from his place, appearing inside the giant Gu formation.

Just outside the Gu formation was the yaksha octopus king. But because of the isolation effect of the Gu formation, it was unaware of anything.

"I am finally in here." Fang Yuan was extremely vigilant, he quickly looked around him, this was indeed the place which he had inspected earlier.

Rashly charging into a Gu formation was very dangerous, and it was normal to be attacked by the Gu formation.

However, Fang Yuan did not suffer any attacks, this further proved that the Gu formation was not managed by anyone.

He exhaled a breath of relief, but was still extremely vigilant.

Unmanned Gu formations could still function. Perhaps the core of the Gu formation had the will left behind by the Gu Immortal.

It could be like Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, where Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had left behind his will.

This was an giant formation using mainly space path methods, thus creating a special space.

This huge space had a yellow sky and a ground paved with purple sand.

The purple sand seemed to be extremely fertile, as dense amounts of vegetation covered Fang Yuan's sight, like a tropical rainforest.

"Scribe grass, nutrient peaches, immortal beans, blood tide flowers..." With just a brief glance, Fang Yuan could make out dozens of immortal materials.

Even a person as stoic as him was shocked.

Although most of these immortal materials were rank six level, along with a few of rank seven, their quantity was truly shocking.

"These immortal materials come from five regions, and are not limited to Earth Trench and Northern Plains. What background did the great expert immortal zombie that created this place have?"

To gather such an enormous scale of immortal materials, how much manpower and material resources would it require?

Moreover, immortal materials were not grass growing along the sides of a road, the gathering of immortal materials often resulted in bloodshed and was tied together with fighting. If the gatherer's strength was not up to par, they simply would not be able to get the materials.

There was also the five regions' regional walls.

The stronger one was, the higher the cultivation of the Gu Immortal, the more difficult it would be for them to pass through a regional wall.

"Could it be..." Fang Yuan's thoughts churned as he made a guess.

He had thought this was a great expert immortal zombie inheritance, but now it seemed such huge handiwork could not be possibly achieved by one person, it would at least require an organization.

And this organization must be huge.

Because a small sized organization with two or three Gu Immortals simply could not have such large assets and energy to spare!

Looking over it again, there were countless immortal materials everywhere he looked, such a sight caused Fang Yuan's heart to thump in excitement.

"Such enormous wealth is simply unimaginable! It is enough for me to attempt refining Immortal Gu dozens of times, even hundreds of times! Maybe in my previous life, Northern Plains Zombie Alliance was able to rise up because of these enormous cultivation resources, even suppressing Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance."

This was almost like a warehouse, with so much immortal materials piled up.

The total value was hard to estimate, Fang Yuan only knew this value was enormous, very enormous.

If he had to accumulate this much with his current two thousand immortal essence stones per month earnings, he might not be able to succeed even in a thousand years.

After all, he also had to calculate cultivation expenditures.

As Gu Immortal's cultivation became higher, the calamities and tribulations would become more terrifying.

"But compared to these countless immortal materials, this enormous Gu formation has even higher value!" Fang Yuan's eyes twinkled.

He had a huge ambition and was very experienced, as he came back to awareness, he realized the preciousness of this enormous Gu formation!

In this Gu formation, the countless immortal materials from the five regions were able to exist mutually without interfering with each other.

"Fortunately, I did not rashly take down this Gu formation, otherwise it would be too late for regret. With this Gu formation, I could plant countless types of immortal materials, it is easier to use than an immortal aperture!"

Fang Yuan could not help but praise the great expert immortal zombie that arranged this.

An Immortal zombie's immortal aperture was already dead, this predecessor was able to arrange such a Gu formation which replaced the use of immortal apertures to a certain extent.

"However, this Gu formation has low defense and also can't be moved, it is far from being convenient and safe like immortal apertures. Hmm... this purple sand seems to be rather strange."

Fang Yuan bent down and grabbed a large amount of purple sand.

The sand was extremely fine. Some flowed down the gaps in Fang Yuan's fingers and sprinkled down like fine grains of crystal. While falling down, they drifted haphazardly while emitting fluorescent light.

"But what I want to find is the method of reviving, where is it?" Fang Yuan threw away the purple sand as he thought of his main objective.

He was not in a hurry to gather the immortal materials, and started to gently fly around, searching the area.

Time gradually passed, the joyous look on Fang Yuan's face slowly disappeared as his feeling of unease intensified.

"Something is not right!" He suddenly stopped and looked down at the endless immortal materials.

After inspecting once more, he found what was wrong.

"It is too peaceful. There is not a trace of wind or sound, it is more quiet than even my dead aperture."

"There are also many other areas that feels fishy. Like the immortal beans, they grow in spring water, but are actually growing on the purple sand here. There are also the nutrient peaches, which are usually accompanied by snake-tail monkey groups. Every type of immortal material has a harsh living environment. But here, there are only these immortal material plants, and there is not even an insect."

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with cold light.

He landed on the ground and tried to pick up a strand of scribe grass.

The next moment, Fang Yuan's body shook.

When the scribe grass was on the purple sand, it was safe and sound, but the moment Fang Yuan picked it up, it withered and turned into fine purple sand.

And the sand was the same as the purple sand below Fang Yuan's feet!

"What is going on?" Fang Yuan narrowed his eyes, and tried to pick other immortal materials.

The result was the same, the moment the immortal materials left the sand, they turned into purple sand.

All of these immortal materials had a problem, they were unusable!

"Strange! Strange!! The reason immortal materials are called immortal materials is because they contain plenty of dao marks on them. When these immortal materials wither and turn into purple sand, their dao marks should have been destroyed, but there is not even a slight disturbance from this..."

A chill emerged from the depths of Fang Yuan's heart.

The immortal materials were in such a state, as for an immortal zombie body which contained dao marks, could it be regarded as a type of immortal material, would it also be absorbed into this enormous field of purple sand?

Looking at this vast amount of immortal materials, flowers and trees, Fang Yuan felt like he was looking at the remains of corpses!

From another perspective, this was a sea of immortal material remains!

The unease inside him kept on intensifying.

Fang Yuan immediately flew to the sky, maintaining some distance with the purple sand.

He gazed at the sky.

"There is definitely something strange about this Gu formation, it is probably not enough to just maintain distance from the purple sand. This change in immortal materials should definitely be related to the whole Gu formation. Before I know of what's going on, it is better to quickly find the method to revive from the immortal zombie state and leave as soon as possible!"

Chapter 935: Surprising Gains

Swoosh—!

Fang Yuan was like an arrow as he flew in the air, creating huge air currents.

Below him, there were countless immortal materials, but he did not even look at them. These 'dead' immortal materials were worthless.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's gaze focused.

On the flat ground below, he saw a desolate beast.

This desolate beast was large like a small hill, it was sprawled on the ground and did not move, it was a hidden essence turtle.

Fang Yuan was not unfamiliar with this desolate beast, not long ago, he had captured one inside a fragment world of Central Continent's Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

Lowering his flying speed, Fang Yuan's body turned as he flew towards the hidden essence turtle.

When he got close, he realized this this was a hidden essence turtle that had died long ago.

It was sprawled on the ground, its head lowered, half of it was buried into the soft purple sand.

The hidden essence turtle's state was as if the spine below its neck was broken, its four limbs were extremely relaxed and loose.

But before it died, it had a calm expression, or rather, a peaceful expression, Fang Yuan felt some suspicion.

"Among the countless 'dead' immortal materials, there is a desolate beast corpse huh..."

Fang Yuan tried to collect the hidden essence turtle's body.

A moment later, his heart sank, he saw that a fragment of the hard turtle shell had turned into purple sand in his hands, scattering with the wind.

Fang Yuan's gaze flickered, after a few breaths' time, he left this place, exploring in the sky again.

Soon, he saw a second desolate beast.

This was an earth chief.

It had a humanoid body and a snake tail, its face resembled a bat, and its nose was pointed up. It had large ears and a black body covered in fleshy armor.

Around its chest were fifty to sixty fleshy whips, each over twenty meters in length. There were suction organs on the surface of the fleshy whips, covering them entirely.

At the front of each fleshy whip was a chrysanthemum-like orifice which could shoot out a white milky fluid at the crucial moment, the fluid had very high corrosiveness and contained extremely large numbers of parasitic worms, which could drill into the pores of victims and wreak havoc from inside the body.

The earth chief corpse was well preserved.

But when Fang Yuan tried to collect the corpse, the same thing happened again.

Fang Yuan no longer felt surprised, he muttered: "Hidden essence turtles are a desolate beast from Central Continent, and earth chiefs mostly appear in Northern Plains..."

Leaving this place, he continued exploring.

Fang Yuan quickly made a new discovery.

"Sandalwood sacred elephants, and three of them!" Fang Yuan gasped.

Sandalwood sacred elephants were much more valuable than hidden essence turtles and desolate beast earth chiefs.

Because it was an ancient desolate beast, a mature sandalwood sacred elephant had rank seven Gu Immortal battle strength.

Long ago, during the auction held by Qin Bai Sheng that involved the whole of Northern Plains, someone bid a sandalwood sacred elephant egg and attracted a huge commotion.

in the current five regions, sandalwood sacred elephants were very rare, they were barely seen.

But now, in front of Fang Yuan, were three sandalwood sacred elephant corpses.

Next, Fang Yuan found even more desolate beast and ancient desolate beast corpses. They were all lying on the ground, surrounded by red, purple, or green plant immortal materials.

Moon howling heavenly wolf, star desolate hound, golden sand dark stallion, ice spike divine ape, white hoof ink horse, nine palace crane, iron crown eagle, dragonfish, sharp tusk boar... Those that flew, those that ran, those that swam, all of them were present, it was like a creepy display of specimens.

The more he flew towards the center, the more corpses he found, the numbers were stunning!

Northern Plains' coiling mountain goat king, Southern Border's phoenix feather lava crocodile, Central Continent's diamond bear, Eastern Sea's grand smoke sea turtle, desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts from all five regions were all over the place.

"Eh? This is a ruin bat." Fang Yuan slowed his speed unknowingly.

This ruin bat was a rare space path desolate beast, it was inferior to the immemorial desolate beast ruin bat that Fang Yuan had seen back in Tai Qiu.

"Half moon qilin!" Fang Yuan's body froze.

Right now in Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, there was a living half moon qilin, it was raised like a treasure by the entire alliance.

"This ancient desolate beast, it seems to be... remnant heavenly dog?" Fang Yuan checked it over and over and obtained an answer.

He had never seen a remnant heavenly dog personally, he had only read about its descriptions in records. This ancient desolate beast only existed in white heaven.

The more he saw, the more Fang Yuan became desensitized.

His knowledge was very vast, but he did not recognize many of the ancient desolate plants and desolate beasts here.

"The space here is so vast, I've already flown for so long, yet even with my speed, I have not seen the edge of the Gu formation."

This was out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

He had tried to deduce this huge Gu formation earlier, and realized that it was a giant space path Gu formation.

Fang Yuan had estimated the size of this place, but now it seems, his initial estimation far underestimated the power of the Gu formation.

"It seems that my deductions and estimations did not reach the core of this Gu formation."

"Who is the person who made this? This is unheard of! So many immortal materials, this is truly an uncountable sum! Is it the work of an Immortal Venerable or Demon Venerable?"

Fang Yuan guessed internally.

Even rank eight Gu Immortals did not have such power to create this singlehandedly.

Because the five regions' regional walls prevented most rank eight Gu Immortals from traveling to other regions.

This was also why, even with the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Central Continent's ten great ancient sects only sent rank six and seven Gu Immortals over.

Of course, once a person is rank nine and invincible in the world, the five region's regional walls can no longer obstruct them.

"If it is not a rank nine venerable, then this must be the work of a super organization. This organization spans across all five regions, that is the only way they can collect the immortal materials."

Even though there was treasure yellow heaven and Gu Immortals could use it to trade, at this scale, treasure yellow heaven could not possibly be the site of transaction.

Because such transactions would have unprecedented scale, it would definitely be recorded down in history.

But Fang Yuan knew that there were no such records.

Even though he was deep into the Gu formation and had explored it for a long time, the longer he stayed, the more the mysteriousness around him thickened.

Fang Yuan did not know much about this place.

In his previous life, he had invaded Hu Immortal blessed land, but he did not step into this place.

This was only something he had heard of in his previous life.

Northern Plains Zombie Alliance suddenly became strong, even surpassing the headquarters in Eastern Sea. The explanation that they gave was that there was an inheritance here in Earth Trench.

They said that an immortal zombie great expert had left behind a revival method for immortal zombies. Because of this, many of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's members turned back into humans, and countless lone cultivator immortal zombies came to join them, allowing Northern Plains Zombie Alliance to develop in size.

But soon after, the good prospects did not last, Northern Plains Zombie Alliance was destroyed by Ma Hong Yun forcefully.

Fang Yuan was unfamiliar with this place, but everything he saw made him extremely curious.

"The direction that I am going should be correct, because the immortal materials that I am seeing are getting rarer. Who is the person who arranged this? It is simply terrifying, perhaps even Heavenly Court would not be able to achieve this?"

Heavenly Court was an organization in Central Continent, it held control over Central Continent and had less power and forces in the other four regions.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, all sorts of monsters showed up, Fang Yuan was aware of this.

Or rather, every super force had its own way to develop. Heavenly Court's method was to grasp Central Continent and openly be the supreme force.

"If the one who arranged this is an organization, then this organization has to span across all five regions, while being hidden and mysterious. Eh? That place is..."

Fang Yuan saw a shade of purple in front of him.

This was a desolate land.

Soft purple sand was all around him, the sea of immortal materials was nowhere to be seen.

This desolate landscape of sand was a giant circle, it was at least two square kilometers in area!

There was no wind or sound, it was deathly silent.

Fang Yuan was shocked internally: "This is the central part of the Gu formation, it seems that a terrifying explosion had occurred here!"

It was this explosion that created the two square kilometers of desolate land. There should have been a sea of immortal materials here originally, but now there was nothing left.

As he gradually got close to the edge of the desolate land, a bright light in the sand attracted Fang Yuan's attention.

Fang Yuan landed and saw that there were thin wings piercing into the sand.

These were not the wings of birds, there were no feathers, they were half transparent, they should be the wings of cicadas or dragonflies.

And these cicada-like wings emitted an aura that made Fang Yuan gulp.

An immemorial desolate beast aura!

Even though it was just the remains, it was the real deal, this was shocking!

These cicada wings were extremely tattered, but they shone like a gem under light. From time to time, under sufficient lighting, they gave off a dark golden glow.

"This light is that of dao marks of metal path, these cicada wings should have belonged to something that had a terrifying foundation in dao marks! Only with a dao mark foundation that was at quasi-rank nine would there be visible dao marks that could be seen with the naked eyes. That is the light of dao marks!"

"Wait, maybe this is... the wings of the tiger-striped honey bee!"

Fang Yuan had a flash of inspiration, he made a guess.

This guess made his heart shudder.

Tiger-striped honey bees were a living being recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Each of these honey bees was the size of a leopard with patterns on their body resembling tiger stripes, golden with black stripes on top. They were extremely powerful, Verdant Great Sun could not even beat one of them. The honey wine that they create is sweet and delectable, it is extremely delicious and among the highest quality in the world."

"If the bees are at the size of leopards, the wings are at just the right size." Fang Yuan thought about this and smiled bitterly.

He was uncertain.

His past experiences and knowledge were very shallow when compared to what appeared in this place, he knew little.

He tried to take out these bee wings.

But something shocking happened!

The bee wings left the purple sand and were undamaged, they did not turn into purple sand like the other immortal materials.

At once, Fang Yuan was overjoyed and surprised!

This was from the body of an immemorial desolate beast, a rank eight Gu refinement immortal material!

It could even give out dao mark light.

Thus, more accurately speaking, this was quasi-rank nine immortal material!

Chapter 936: Multi-layered Gu Formation

Fang Yuan held in his excitement.

The immortal material in his hands was of very high quality, even in his previous life, he had never owned such a specimen.

Quasi-rank nine immortal material, it had so many dao marks that it shined with bright light, observable with the naked eye.

Fang Yuan was not a grandmaster in refinement path, but he knew something, the reason why immortal materials could be used to refine Immortal Gu was because the immortal materials themselves contain a lot of dao marks.

Man is the spirit of all beings, Gu are the essence of heaven and earth.

Gu worms were the vessels of the Great Dao, why did they contain power? That was because the tiny Gu worm contained dao marks.

Dao marks were the traces of the Great Dao of heaven and earth, precisely because of this, activating Gu worms would result in many magical effects.

The more dao marks in a Gu worm, the higher their rank would be, and the more powerful and profound their abilities would be.

Refining an Immortal Gu was to gather the dao marks in countless mortal Gu and immortal materials, using the ones needed for the refinement.

Now, Fang Yuan's immortal material had many dao marks, in theory, it could be used to refine a rank eight Immortal Gu!

In fact, he only needed to use a tiny fragment of it to refine a rank six Immortal Gu.

The dao marks in a rank eight Immortal Gu were tens of thousands of times that of a rank six Immortal Gu.

"Of course, this bee wing that resembles a tiger-striped honey bee mainly contains metal path dao marks. If I am trying to refine a metal path Immortal Gu, this would be very useful. Unfortunately, this has no use if I want to refine star thought Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan collected this precious immortal material properly.

He could not use it now, but he might need it in the future.

Even if he did not, this was such a precious immortal material, it would create a huge commotion in treasure yellow heaven, there was no need to worry that it would not be sold.

"I've finally had some gains after entering this Gu formation."

Fang Yuan's mind started to think deeply.

He was not rushing towards the center, he was starting to explore this desolate land of purple sand.

As expected, a moment later, he had another discovery while flying!

In the purple sand, there was a white veil that resembled a handkerchief that attracted his gaze.

He quickly descended, feeling joy after inspecting it.

The aura could not be fake, this was another rank eight immortal material!

But the quality was slightly lower than the bee wing earlier, there was no light from dao marks.

Fang Yuan held it in his hands, the immortal material did not disintegrate after leaving the purple sand.

"It seems that immortal materials of this level are no longer affected by the power of the purple sand."

Fang Yuan squeezed it, this immortal material was very soft, it could be molded into different forms.

"So this is not a veil, but a piece of... cloud?"

Fang Yuan observed carefully, feeling surprised.

This was like a fragment of a cloud, but it contained a huge amount of cloud path dao marks.

"Is this..." Fang Yuan's felt excitement, he activated his Gu worms and spat out a mouthful of water vapor.

When this immortal material was covered in water vapor, it became lighter and floated out of Fang Yuan's hands, it rose into the sky and turned into a tiny cloud in the form of a phoenix. The phoenix's wings moved slowly, as the cloud danced in the air.

Fang Yuan's body shook, he was overjoyed: "As expected! This is a fragment of the immemorial desolate beast cloud phoenix's body!!"

Fang Yuan's heart was pounding.

This cloud phoenix was not a lifeform from the five regions, it was a mystical creature that only existed in white heaven of the immemorial nine heavens.

It was not born with a phoenix bloodline, instead it was an ancient cloud that would not face destruction even after ten thousand years in white heaven. After having a phoenix's aura or blood transmitted and spread through it, the cloud would slowly turn into a living being.

Thus, its body was very special, it was neither made of flesh and blood nor clouds.

The cloud phoenix fragment that Fang Yuan obtained was less than a fraction of a fraction of the cloud phoenix's true body, but the cloud path dao marks inside could be used to refine a rank six Immortal Gu at least ten times as the main material!

The discovery of the cloud phoenix affirmed Fang Yuan's earlier guess.

He continued exploring, not long after, he circulated entirely around the purple desert, he had huge gains.

Counting his gains, he had a total of eighteen of such immortal materials, the dao mark varieties covered the majority of Gu paths. Among which, three materials had a lot of star path or wisdom path dao marks, they were very helpful in refining star thought Immortal Gu.

One could say that with these three immortal materials, Fang Yuan could forget about Blazing Heaven Demoness and refine the Gu himself.

Of course, because of the change in immortal materials, the recipe of star thought Immortal Gu would have to change as well. But Fang Yuan was not afraid of this, he could use the light of wisdom to easily do it, he was also a wisdom path grandmaster now, it was not difficult to deduce!

"Even though the immortal materials that I collected are incredibly precious, they are only a small part of the corpses' bodies. The Gu Immortal who created this place, they actually used so many precious immortal materials, are they trying to refine a rank nine Immortal Gu?"

Fang Yuan could not help but guess.

In the process of collecting immortal materials, he started to realize something.

This desolate land of purple sand once had an incredibly profound refinement path Gu formation.

Combined with these fragmented immortal materials, it was likely that the Gu Immortal had a grand ambition, they were trying to refine an immensely powerful Immortal Gu.

But it was a pity, the Gu refinement failed and a huge explosion occurred.

Not only was the refinement path Gu formation destroyed, with only debris left, most of the Gu refinement immortal materials were destroyed, only these fragments remained.

"Regardless of who it is, or what organization it is, they are most likely dead from the explosion. If not for that, this Gu formation would not be left unmaintained for such a long time. The immortal material fragments here would not be scattered everywhere without anyone taking them."

Even though the immortal materials were just remnants after the explosion, they were very valuable.

With rank eight and quasi-rank nine immortal materials involved, even rank eight Gu Immortals would be moved.

If Old Ancestor Xue Hu knew that Fang Yuan had such a large number of precious immortal materials, he would forget about his face and come to find trouble with Fang Yuan in a hurry.

In order to refine the rank eight fortune rivalling heaven Immortal Gu, Old Ancestor Xue Hu was already going bankrupt trying to find the supplementary immortal materials, even though he had Ma Hong Yun as the main material.

If not for that, he would not thrown away his face as a rank eight great expert and have gone to Zombie Alliance's graveyard to steal immortal zombie corpses in place of the materials.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's worry eased slightly.

Since this mysterious and powerful Gu Immortal, or Gu Immortal organization, was gone, this trip was much less dangerous now.

Fang Yuan looked around, he saw that there was something new in the desolate land of purple sand.

"Sigh... in the endless depths of history, who knows how many truths of the past has been buried, how many incredible people died inconspicuously without anyone knowing."

The commotion stirred up by them fades eventually, legends disappear.

Getting rid of these thoughts, Fang Yuan came to the center of the desolate land of purple sand.

This was the only area he had not explored yet in this entire desolate land.

Even though he obtained many immortal materials, Fang Yuan was still slightly disappointed — in his previous life, rumors said that there was a way to get rid of his immortal zombie body and revive, but why has he not found it yet?

Fang Yuan's intuition was: At the central area of this desolate land, it should be the center of the Gu formation as well, if it was not here, then Fang Yuan would never find it elsewhere.

Looking around, at the center of the desolate land, there was only small fragmented purple sand.

This was the center of the explosion, the purple sand was much finer than outside.

There were no immortal materials.

He looked around, there were nothing.

But under Fang Yuan's investigative methods, he made a discovery of some remnants of the Gu formation deep under the purple sand.

"This is indeed the central control area of the entire place!"

"What an amazing person, this is actually a multi-layered Gu formation, having such an incredible design, this must be the work of a formation path great grandmaster!"

Fang Yuan inspected as he felt shock internally.

It turned out that the entire space was mainly focused on using the refinement path Gu formation, but what originally built this space, including the space path formation, was only a supplementary formation outside the refinement path Gu formation.

Other than the space path Gu formation, Fang Yuan also found many defensive Gu formations, some food path Gu formations, and some phantom path Gu formations.

Food path throughout history had never been widely spread, it was even rarer today.

Fang Yuan did not understand much about it, but he had heard that food path was specialized in feeding Gu worms.

"The food path supplementary Gu formation here should be used to feed these Gu worms. After all, a Gu formation needs countless Gu worms to work together in combination."

"There are still two or three food path Gu formations in use here. It is hard to imagine that after the great explosion, the Gu formation here is still working."

"Maybe that is the reason why the outermost space path Gu formation is still functioning."

This discovered unraveled one mystery for Fang Yuan.

"Eh? This is... a phantom path Gu formation?" As he continued to observe, Fang Yuan made a new discovery.

This phantom path Gu formation was already destroyed, but there were two or three mortal Gu left, buried deep in the purple sand, they are not moving and were barely alive, using the food path Gu formation to maintain their lives.

Fang Yuan had even less knowledge regarding phantom path.

But during the battle of Tai Qiu, Dong Fang Chang Fan had once used a ruin bat corpse to set up a huge phantom formation.

If not for that, Fang Yuan would not have recognized this Gu formation immediately.

"The phantom formation turns the entire Gu formation into a phantom and prevents outside attacks from destroying the Gu formation. Maybe this is the reason why the Gu formation survived the great explosion."

"Refinement path Gu Immortals with such attainment levels have their own refinement path Gu formations, and also many supplementary Gu formations on top of the refinement path Gu formation. Using these Gu formations, the refinement path Gu worms will be twice as effective for half the effort, they would save a lot of time and energy. For example, Snowy Mountain blessed land has an exquisite refinement path Gu formation, it is known as the best formation for refinement path in Northern Plains' demonic path. It is said that this Gu formation is also a multi-layered Gu formation, using a total of twelve different Gu formations." Fang Yuan's thoughts churned.

He could set up some refinement path Gu formations as well.

But these Gu formations were very superficial, after all, they had to do with his formation path attainment.

Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level was very low.

A person has limited energy, and even more limited time, Fang Yuan had some accomplishments in certain aspects, he naturally had areas where he was inferior to other people.

Chapter 937: Life-and-death Immortal Aperture!

The Gu formation in Snowy Mountain blessed land was not set up by Old Ancestor Xue Hu.

He was a rank eight great expert, but he could not set up such a Gu formation.

To set up this Gu formation, Old Ancestor Xue Hu personally went to ask the number one formation path Gu Immortal in Northern Plains, Sun Ming Lu, for help. Sun Ming Lu was a righteous path Gu Immortal, he had a firm personality and refused to cooperate, Old Ancestor Xue Hu knew that he could not be forceful, he put down his status and asked him for help numerous times.

After seven invitations, in which Old Ancestor Xue Hu talked about Lady Wan Shou at the final time, Sun Ming Lu finally was convinced.

Even though Sun Ming Lu was someone with extremely firm will, he treasured love and loyalty. Old Ancestor Xue Hu was setting up the refinement path Gu formation for his beloved wife, their love touched him, therefore he helped.

This matter caused a huge commotion in the Northern Plains Gu Immortal world back then.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, Sun Ming Lu fought intensely with the Central Continent Gu Immortals, he set up a Gu formation that prevented the Central Continent Gu Immortals from advancing. Eventually, the Gu formation was broken, and Sun Ming Lu died.

After he died, someone made a biography of him. Inside \<\<Biography of Sun Ming Lu\>\>, the matter about Old Ancestor Xue Hu's invitation was recorded clearly.

"According to my deduction using this Gu formation's remains, it has at least thirty layers! The twelve layered Gu formation that Sun Ming Lu made caused him to become the publicly recognized number one formation path Gu Immortal in Northern Plains. Then the Gu Immortal who made this arrangement here must be a great grandmaster. Or rather, they could even be a supreme grandmaster!"

Supreme grandmaster!

The attainment level above great grandmaster, a transcendent realm.

For example, the three supreme grandmasters in refinement path: Long Hair Ancestor, Old Eccentric Tian Nan, and Old Immortal Kong Jue. All three of them were unprecedented and unique, they had achievements that could not be surpassed.

"Food path Gu formation, phantom path Gu formation, metal path Gu formation, strength path Gu formation..." Fang Yuan's eyes shined brightly, his gaze pierced past the purple sand and looked into all the traces of the Gu formations.

His heart gradually sank.

He had not forgotten his original goal.

Looking at the situation, there was little hope of obtaining a revival method.

These Gu formations were all near the brink of destruction, mortal Gu inside were barely alive, there were zero Immortal Gu left. Maybe because the strong received the greatest burden, the explosion destroyed all of the Immortal Gu. Or maybe it was because the two or three food path Gu formations could not feed the Immortal Gu, and as time passed, they all starved to death.

Eventually, Fang Yuan found a wisdom path Gu formation that was extremely tattered at the deepest level.

This was the seventh wisdom path Gu formation that he had discovered.

The Gu formation was so fragmented that Fang Yuan bore no hope.

But he took a glance and realized that there was an unexpected gain in this Gu formation!

There were some thoughts left behind in this tattered Gu formation.

These thoughts were in a state of complete rest, it was probably the effect of this wisdom path Gu formation.

Since there were thoughts, they could interact.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, he mustered his strength and started to deduce this wisdom path Gu formation.

He was very careful, this wisdom path Gu formation was like a building that was going to collapse, Fang Yuan needed to act very meticulously.

Thankfully, he was a wisdom path grandmaster already, he had a high attainment level.

A moment later, he deciphered this relatively simple wisdom path Gu formation, and successfully invaded it, controlling this delicate Gu formation.

Next, he sent out thoughts into the Gu formation and started to interact with the thoughts that were at rest.

...

"After using up more than eighty years, this Gu formation is finally complete! In the next few hundred years, or even thousands of years, I will be refining Gu here. Heh, I became an immortal zombie, even though I am not restricted by lifespan, my mind is no longer as agile. Thus, I asked 'Yellow' to add in this small Gu formation and store my thoughts so that they can help me think."

...

"This Gu formation is too useful, not only can it help me refine Gu, it can also conceal us from the perception of heaven's will. Using only two hundred years, I successfully refined eight soul path Immortal Gu, among which six are rank seven, and two are rank eight."

...

"Every year, they send me lots of immortal materials. I would never have imagined this day where I would not be able to use up my immortal materials! I have countless immortal materials, this is so blissful. I should start to attempt those incomplete Immortal Gu recipes."

...

"An unexpected surprise occurred today when refining Gu! I tried to complete the Immortal Gu recipe of devour soul Immortal Gu, but in the end I refined an Immortal Gu with an unknown effect. Even though it is also a soul path Immortal Gu, I will let the others do the work of testing its effect."

...

"My Gu refinement failed! Three of my defensive Gu formations were destroyed, even my main refinement path Gu formation was damaged. That liar in treasure yellow heaven, that unscrupulous merchant! He dared to use a tampered immortal material to deceive me!! I will tear out his tendons and pull out his skin to vent my hatred!"

...

"That unscrupulous merchant was already punished, 'Azure' is really amazing. These days, 'Yellow' arrived and repaired all of the Gu formations. I can refine Gu again."

...

"'Purple' came to inform me to be careful. 'Azure' has met with trouble. It turns out that the unscrupulous merchant Gu Immortal who deceived me was a pawn of Heavenly Court. Fate! It still exists, Red Lotus Demon Venerable did not manage to destroy it thoroughly. It is the assistant of accursed heaven! It will be destroyed one day!"

...

"'Azure's' problem is getting more and more serious. Sacrificing any one of us seven is a huge loss to all of us. Sigh, I harmed him, but he has already made up his mind. Maybe I can try that now... before leaving, he took that soul path Immortal Gu, so that Immortal Gu's effect is like this... I hope it can help him out."

...

"'Azure' failed, his state is so pitiful, he is only one step from complete annihilation. 'Yellow' barely managed to preserve his life, but his injuries cannot be healed, it can only be fixed through time. This would take at least hundreds or thousands of years. Our greatest battle strength has been lost!"

...

"'Azure's' failure made me realize something fully, our previous methods will not work. We are all born with flaws, heaven and earth will not tolerate our existence. As 'Green', I must comprehend the profound meaning of life and death, nobody is more suited for this mission than me. We can only restart if I can find a way to truly revive and obtain an immortal aperture that is full of vitality."

...

At this point, Fang Yuan's heart shook, he showed some excitement on his face.

"Currently, it seems that this is a strong and mysterious organization. The members refer to each other with codenames, among which are Yellow, Green, Purple, Azure... if they have a total of seven members, they probably use the colors of the rainbow — red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue, purple? Hmm... I will call this organization 'Seven Rainbows' for now."

Fang Yuan paused in his speculations, he continued to send his thoughts into the Gu formation, interacting with the motionless thoughts inside the Gu formation.

The following thoughts were missing a huge chunk, they were no longer as closely connected as the previous ones, it seems that each thought was made after a long period of time.

...

"My attempt succeeded, today, I found another revival method, but to me, what significance does such an ordinary revival method have? I do not need it."

...

"'Blue' obtained a Gu Immortal inheritance, it was left behind by Old Immortal Kong Jue in Central Continent. He had researched deeply into the ten extreme physiques, I have great gains from this, no, I have immense gains!"

...

"'Yellow' and 'Purple' worked together and obtained an inheritance of Limitless Demon Venerable. Hahaha, truly worthy of Limitless Demon Venerable, his achievements in rule path are unprecedented and might never be surpassed, even I am vastly inferior!"

...

"Limitless Demon Venerable is correct, there is life in death, and death in life, life and death can be interchanged! Except that under normal circumstances, turning from life to death is a natural process, it flows smoothly. But to turn from death to life, it would be extremely difficult, like traveling upstream. Meanwhile, immortal zombies are stuck between life and death, they are the manifestation of the profound mysteries of life and death."

"Life has its advantages, death has its uses. An immortal zombie's immortal aperture might be a dead aperture, but it is safe from calamities and tribulations. This is a huge advantage of death!"

"Limitless Demon Venerable's direction is correct, I should move forward in this aspect. I am sure to make shocking achievements!"

...

"I succeeded! This is an unimaginable result!!"

"Limitless Demon Venerable was incredibly talented, actually, he was only some steps away from success. An immortal zombie's dead aperture is extremely precious, it has many uses. Hehehe, if this result is exposed, the entire Gu Immortal world would be shaken! Even I myself was shocked immensely..."

Next, Fang Yuan got more and more stunned as his eyes burst with shining light, his expression visibly changed.

According to these thoughts, when a Gu Immortal cultivates, they should first turn into an immortal zombie and obtain a dead immortal aperture! Next, they would revive, obtaining a life-and-death immortal aperture.

This immortal aperture has two layers, one layer is of life, and the other layer is of death, life and death are able to coexist with each other and are interchangeable. It would be an immense help to the Gu Immortal in terms of cultivating or undergoing tribulations!

Ordinary Gu Immortal who are alive were filled with vitality and cannot control death.

Ordinary immortal zombies have death energy emanating in their dead apertures, they have death without life, they could only contain the mysteries of death.

The former had too much vitality, with such immense fortune, heaven would seek balance. Thus, every once in a while, there would be heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, to create losses to the Gu Immortal.

The latter was full of death energy and had no calamities or tribulations, but would slowly disintegrate and could not contain cultivation resources.

The immortal aperture that Fang Yuan obtained when ascending had already disintegrated by more than half.

In time, it would completely disappear, the entire immortal aperture would vanish. By then, Fang Yuan would only have his mortal dead aperture left.

"But according to this cultivation method contained in the thoughts, I can use the dead aperture as the core and fuse life and death during the process of revival, condensing them into one aperture, and form the life-and-death immortal aperture, to control life and death to a certain degree!"

"With this life-and-death immortal aperture, the power of the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities I face from now on would be halved! Most importantly, the dao marks I obtain would not be reduced at all."

Fang Yuan was greatly moved.

Any Gu Immortal would be moved.

"If this method really works, then it would truly shock the entire Gu Immortal world, it would not be an exaggeration to say that the entire world would go into chaos!"

Chapter 938: Successfully Returning to the City

With a whooshing sound.

At a nook of the yaksha octopuses' cave, a green light shined brightly as the surrounding darkness was repelled.

As the jade green light faded, a figure appeared at the place which was previously empty.

It was Fang Yuan, having just come out of the space created by the Gu formation.

He had used fixed immortal travel Immortal Gu.

And this place had been specially arranged earlier, when he explored the yaksha octopuses' underground cave.

He had set up many mortal Gu here, forming a simple and crude Gu formation.

There was nothing that could be done about it, Fang Yuan's formation path attainment was very low, he could only use Gu formations of this level.

The Gu formation could only conceal most of the disturbance, but Fixed Immortal Travel was, after all, an Immortal Gu, when Fang Yuan appeared, this mortal Gu formation immediately broke apart, some aura leaked out.

Fang Yuan quickly used his methods to get rid of these traces.

But soon, he heard the growling of desolate beasts as well as the movement of the yaksha octopuses in the cave.

"The surrounding yaksha octopuses are back already?"

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light.

He took action rapidly, eliminating the Immortal Gu aura before the yaksha octopuses returned, and quickly left.

The yaksha octopuses felt the aura of the Immortal Gu and were stirred up, but when they arrived, there were no traces remaining. The octopuses searched around and saw nothing, their uncertainty gradually vanished, they turned around and left.

If they were Gu Immortals, they would not be so easy to fool.

Desolate beasts lacked intelligence, thus Fang Yuan could easily deal with them.

Before long, he returned to the battlefield with the mouth earthworm, it was a messy scene.

Most of the yaksha octopuses had retreated, while the Northern Plains immortal zombies were nowhere to be found.

A huge gorge, like a long scar along the Earth Trench, was displayed in front of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's lips curled up, he smiled silently.

He knew that this gorge was dug by the mouth earthworm.

Mouth earthworms were creatures that primarily lived under the surface.

They stayed there most of the time, only coming to the surface when hunting for food. After devouring the prey rapidly, they would dig back under the soil and stop moving.

At the same time, their bodies would shrink at a shocking rate, turning from gigantic fat masses to being like bamboo poles.

At this time, the thick meat in their bodies would squeeze together tightly. The unique apparatus in their flesh — countless sharp bony teeth, would rotate and grind the prey into flesh and blood.

"This mouth earthworm swallowed me, but I used Fixed Immortal Travel inside its body to escape. It failed to hunt its prey, it would definitely rage and fight with the Northern Plains immortal zombies. The mouth earthworm is not their match, it does not have wisdom, it is bound to lose. But this wild beast has the instincts to escape, and it is very good at it. Once it is injured to an extent, it would dig into the soil and escape from the battle."

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with eerie light.

If not for this, he would not have chosen to use the mouth earthworm to escape from the immortal zombies' sights.

Previously in Dark Flow Giant City, he had obtained information about Dragon Commander Ye Cha and the others, he knew that they did not have an effective way to deal with the underground mouth earthworm.

Their investigative methods could not bypass the abundant earth path dao marks on the mouth earthworm, thus Fang Yuan dared to use fixed immortal travel Immortal Gu inside its body.

Thus, even though there were many individuals among the Northern Plains immortal zombies, and they had great battle strength, they could not do anything to this mouth earthworm for a period of time.

Especially when the mouth earthworm did not want to fight, and was using all its efforts to escape.

Battle strength did not mean everything.

For example, Old Ancestor Xue Hu with rank eight cultivation level could fight against both Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and force them to retreat, he had incredible battle strength. But to create the Gu formation, he still needed to ask Sun Ming Lu seven times.

Even rank nine venerables were like this.

In the history of Gu Immortals, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had asked Long Hair Ancestor to refine Gu for them.

There were all sorts of paths in Gu cultivation, that meant that specialists tackled their own fields, even if a person cultivates a path to rank nine, they would still be lacking proficiency in other areas.

After all, there was a limit to their energy.

Unless they had a lot of time, or a certain degree of fortuitous encounters.

The mouth earthworm escaped, while the Northern Plains immortal zombies chased, the traces of battle extended along the way.

During this journey, many things could be seen: pits created from explosions, blood inside the gorges, most likely the mouth earthworm's blood. Other than that, there were also many pieces of the corpses of Earth Trench's creatures that were drawn into the chaos.

In order to live, the mouth earthworm was going all out, this helped Fang Yuan conceal his traces to a large extent.

One side chased, while the other escaped, this extended battlefield had been formed.

Seeing the intense fighting along the way, Fang Yuan smiled lightly.

"In order to escape, the mouth earthworm must have panicked and led the Northern Plains immortal zombies to the territories of other fierce beasts. Good, the more chaotic this scene is, the more advantageous for me. This is just like what I had calculated earlier."

Next, Fang Yuan followed along the traces of battle and flew rapidly, his body submerging into the darkness.

The Northern Plains immortal zombies were flying dejectedly.

Their injuries were not light, they were in pathetic states, with ashen expressions.

"What can we do? Xing Xiang Zi died, how can we explain this to Lady Blazing Heaven Demoness?"

"Sigh, we did our best. Assaulting the mouth earthworm along the way, we went through the territories of five fierce beasts, among which three are ancient desolate beasts! Keep in mind, this is the Earth Trench! I have never acted so crazy before."

"Unfortunately, our efforts were in vain, this mouth earthworm fell into the acid bog, it had completely dissolved. Xing Xiang Zi was not spared, there's no way we can sacrifice our lives for him, right."

"In my opinion, Xing Xiang Zi was too careless. Acting so careless in Earth Trench, he was simply courting death!"

The immortal zombies spoke quietly, only the leader, Dragon Commander Ye Cha, was silent.

He had the highest status among these people, he was the leader, he held the biggest responsibility towards Xing Xiang Zi's demise.

Thinking about Blazing Heaven Demoness, Dragon Commander Ye Cha's heart felt extremely heavy.

"Everyone, we finally meet again." Fang Yuan turned into Xing Xiang Zi, appearing in front of the immortal zombies.

"Eh?" At once, the Northern Plains immortal zombies were stunned.

"Xing Xiang Zi?!" Doctor Yin Xuan called out, his gaze was full of joy.

The other immortal zombies were the same, even Landlord Lei Yu looked at Fang Yuan feeling that it was very pleasing to see this old man!

"How did you escape?" An immortal zombie asked.

This question was in everyone's minds.

Several gazes were all focused on Fang Yuan's face.

Fang Yuan was prepared for this, he gave his explanation: "Alas! When I was trapped inside the mouth earthworm's stomach, the surrounding flesh squeezed me, and numerous teeth started rotating. In that dangerous state, I used my Immortal Gu for an immortal killer move, sealing myself into star ice. This is my strongest defensive move, it was able to block the teeth. But there was a drawback, I could not move at all, not just my body, but my thoughts as well, therefore I could not think. The star ice would only exist for a short period of time, but I believed that everyone would save me. All I had to do was to wait until the star ice melted, and when I regained my freedom, I found that I was buried under some rubble!"

"So that's it!" Doctor Yin Xuan realized.

"Xing Xiang Zi must have fell out when we were chasing the mouth earthworm and fighting in the chaotic battle, creating wounds that tore its flesh open."

"So close, so close!"

"Xing Xiang Zi, you were really lucky."

The immortal zombies did not have any suspicions.

Dragon Commander Ye Cha heaved a sigh of relief: "That is good, do you still need to collect star night mucus?"

Fang Yuan's face changed, he showed a hesitant expression, saying: "Forget it! I was unlucky now, let's go back and rest first, we will talk about it later."

The immortal zombies glanced at each other, secretly laughing inside about Xing Xiang Zi's timidness.

But after such an intense battle, their bodies were in bad shape as well, thus everyone agreed to return to Dark Flow Giant City and rest.

As for the remaining star night mucus, that was a problem for later.

A few days later.

Dark Flow Giant City.

In the secret room, the refinement path Gu formation was shining with a dazzling light.

The light shined on Fang Yuan's face, but now, his mind was elsewhere.

"Possible, this is totally possible!" Fang Yuan said internally.

He was using the Gu formation to process the Gu refinement materials on the surface, but he was actually inside his dead aperture, controlling Gu worms to do an experiment.

He was very vigilant, even though he obtained a revival method in Earth Trench, it had a dubious origin, Fang Yuan had to experiment on it and test if it was usable.

The results all proved that this revival method was usable!

Fang Yuan was excited and deeply moved.

Looking back over the past, Fang Yuan had been collecting revival methods ever since Imperial Court blessed land was destroyed, facing many difficulties.

The first revival method he collected, of time path — that was to use man as before Immortal Gu with time anchor Immortal Gu to revive himself.

But though this method might have great potential, it was only a conjecture, to complete it, he needed to cooperate with Shark Demon and invest an immense amount of time and resources into it.

Next, Fang Yuan found the possession method from Dong Fang Chang Fan's soul, using this, he could achieve the target of getting rid of his immortal zombie state.

But if he used this method, not only would there be questions on whether the body would suit his soul, and the aptitude of the body, but the second aperture that Fang Yuan had put in so much effort to obtain would be gone for good.

Following that, Fang Yuan obtained a method of using a ten extreme physique immortal ascension to get rid of the immortal zombie state from Feng Jin Huang at the Refinement Path Convention.

This method was even less plausible, it was suited for mortal Gu Masters. Fang Yuan was already an immortal zombie, he would need to use his first mortal aperture to undergo immortal ascension, he did not have one of the ten extreme physiques either, he had insufficient aptitude. Even though he had blood skull Gu, he already had dao marks in his body, he could not use mortal Gu to raise his aptitude.

Finally, in the Starry Sky grotto-heaven fragment world, Feng Jin Huang told Fang Yuan another revival method.

Using theory involving transformation path, in combination with everlasting Gu, he could achieve a permanent transformation, that was the same as revival.

But what was the way to refine everlasting Gu? Fang Yuan did not know.

If someone else had everlasting Immortal Gu, the situation would be even worse.

Fang Yuan did not excel greatly in transformation path either.

These methods, even though they could succeed, they all had drawbacks and could not be achieved easily.

But as the saying goes, one determined to work hard would not be disappointed, after so much turmoil and difficulties, Fang Yuan finally found the best and most suitable method for himself inside Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's Earth Trench!

Chapter 939: Dual Ten Extreme Physique Rank Nine Demon Venerable?

Since the creator had yet to name the method, Fang Yuan gave it a tentative name: life-and-death immortal aperture revival method.

The true value of this method was absolutely priceless!

If it were to be leaked out to the public, the whole cultivation world would be shaken and the current situation of the world would change. Countless Gu Immortals, even the secluded rank eights, would start researching it immediately with their full efforts and attempt to use the method.

Once a large portion of Gu Immortals obtain this method, from then on, the number of Gu Immortals in all the five regions would start to increase explosively and in unprecedented fashion.

Because the life-and-death immortal aperture contained the mysteries of both life and death, it could reduce the might of heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities. And the extent of that reduction was as high as an entire fifty percent!

What did that imply?

The cultivation journeys of Gu Immortals had two difficulties that they had to pass.

One was that of limited lifespan and the other was the presence of calamities and tribulations.

Increasing cultivation level could not increase lifespan, thus Gu Immortals could only seek out other methods to prolong their lifespans by all means possible.

Ignoring that for the time being.

Right now, calamities and tribulations were to be emphasised.

Gu Immortal would face calamities and tribulations once in a while. Heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities were like blades of an executioner hanging over the heads of Gu Immortals.

During times of peace, most Gu Immortals would die as a result of calamities and tribulations. Countless records within history and practical examples and experiences in real life served to remind Gu Immortals time and time again about how terrifying and fatal these threats were!

Calamities and tribulations were unpredictable and their power was not equal, instead the difficulty increased gradually.

Gu Immortals needed to work hard in their cultivation and raise their strength continuously to have a chance of passing the tribulations.

And cultivation was not simply a theoretical matter, resources for cultivation were required, like immortal materials, Immortal Gu, immortal killer moves, Immortal Gu Houses and so on.

An immortal aperture was the best place to cultivate and harvest immortal materials.

Because the environment of the immortal aperture was special, it had many dao marks and could grow relevant immortal materials that were suitable for the Gu Immortal, in accordance with their situation. Moreover, time flowed much faster in the immortal aperture when compared to the five regions, thus the immortal materials could be harvested more frequently and provide higher gains overall.

There was another reason as well, nurturing cultivation resources in the immortal aperture could be done much more safely and they could be carried around with the person conveniently.

It was quite dangerous to place immortal materials outside.

Not only could they be easily seized by others, there could also be overbearing experts like Blazing Heaven Demoness who would even attempt to destroy them if they were unable to obtain them.

However, the problem was that every heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity would result in heavy negative repercussions on the immortal aperture.

It was already not a simple matter for Gu Immortals to pass calamities and tribulations. To prevent damage to the entirety of their immortal aperture was nearly impossible.

The cultivation resources that were stored in the immortal aperture would often be destroyed to a large extent.

Gu Immortals would have to once again accumulate the cultivation resources to continue their cultivation, there were even some who might have to start all over from scratch.

If that happened, a vicious cycle would be formed.

Accumulating cultivation resources, cultivating, increasing in strength, passing tribulations... re-accumulating resources, cultivating, increasing in strength slowly, passing even tougher tribulations...

The calamities and tribulations would become stronger and stronger, while their resources would need to be accumulated all over again each time, greatly delaying the growth of the strength of the Gu Immortal. The strength of many Gu Immortals might be insufficient for keeping up with the required speed, their growth might even sometimes be stagnant, so how could they cope with the even more terrifying calamities and tribulations?

Thus, since ancient times, countless Gu Immortals had lost everything to heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities and perished.

Hu Immortal was a typical example.

She had passed four earthly calamities, but at the fifth calamity, she encountered a blue charm lightning shadow and died due to it. Her obsession turned into the land spirit of Hu Immortal blessed land, which was finally obtained by Fang Yuan.

Of course, there was a method to reduce the threat, that was to move out the cultivation resources in advance.

Previously, Fang Yuan had done this.

But in fact, very few Gu Immortals would do such a thing.

They were obviously not foolish, so what was the reason?

The reason was because of the targeting natures of heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities. For instance, a wood path Gu Immortal who moved out all their wood path resources before facing a calamity or tribulation may instead end up attracting a fire path calamity or tribulation.

After passing the tribulation, the immortal aperture would be greatly affected, gaining many fire path dao marks, which would cause changes in the environment and temperature.

When the wood path Gu Immortal brings back all the previously moved out cultivation resources, many of those resources would not be suitable to be cultivated in this completely new environment.

On the contrary, if the wood path resources were kept in the blessed land and attracted a wood path tribulation, the immortal aperture's wood path dao marks would increase, although there would be losses, the environment of the immortal aperture would become even more ideal.

Countless examples of success and failure, countless summaries of the experiences of predecessors proved one thing clearly — keeping the resources when facing a tribulation was wiser than moving them away, and was even more beneficial for the Gu Immortal's cultivation journey.

Fang Yuan had previously moved out his resources, which led to a blood path calamity that was essentially unsuitable for the growth of the previous resources.

However, Hu Immortal blessed land was not compatible with his path, so this was not a big problem.

Later on, when Tai Bai Yun Sheng faced the calamity in his immortal aperture, he chose to keep his resources even when aware of how severe the loss could be. It was because the immortal aperture that was undergoing an earthly calamity was his most essential foundation.

Only after understanding this kind of information could one truly realize the terrifying value of the life-and-death immortal aperture method!

Although Gu Immortals were high and mighty above the masses, calamities and tribulations hung above their head, they had to cultivate endlessly, and make huge progress at every phase of their cultivation, and had to keep on making more progress, only then could they continue to survive.

But if they had a life-and-death immortal aperture, everything would be different.

It directly reduced the power of calamities and tribulations by fifty percent!

With the sharp decrease in the power of calamities and tribulations, the loss of their cultivation resources would be less, while there would be no drop in the number of dao marks gained, this was enough to benefit the cycle for the Gu Immortal's cultivation.

Accumulating cultivation resources, cultivating, increasing in strength, passing tribulations... on top the original foundation, one can continue to accumulate resources, cultivating even quicker, experiencing a greater increase in strength, and passing a slightly stronger tribulation...

With just a living immortal aperture, the calamities and tribulations would keep on growing stronger; Gu Immortals could barely endure them as it was, and as their cultivation increased, it would be even more difficult for them to advance.

And if they only had a dead immortal aperture, the immortal aperture would continue to crumble, resources could not be accumulated quickly and there was no hope of progress, it was simply a doomed ending.

However, a life-and-death immortal aperture created a cycle that allowed the Gu Immortal's strength to snowball and accumulate, and have increasingly greater assurance in passing future tribulations!

Undoubtedly, this was an accomplishment that surpassed the current era!

It could change the whole Gu Immortal world, the entire world would be revolutionized, the history of Gu Masters would be changed henceforth.

It might seem to be simply a revival method, but it contained such monstrous power!

More accurately speaking, it was no longer just a simple revival method, it was a method of cultivation.

This technique that had improved upon the foundation of Limitless Demon Venerable's concept was, without doubt, much more superior than the methods of cultivation that had been passed down for countless years!

Such a grand feat, in the context of Earth's history, was like the invention of steam engine, electricity and calculator, they had incredibly significant importance!

The traditional Gu Master cultivation methods were passed down from Ren Zu's era, and there were almost no changes done to it since.

If the life-and-death immortal aperture method was publicized, it would be akin to the theory of general relativity of Einstein which 'overthrew' Newton's first law!

If it were other Gu Immortals, they might find it hard to accept this for a period of time, even thinking that this was an unrealistic fantasy, it might even be considered sacrilegious!

After all, immortal zombies had low status, while this method placed much importance on their dead immortal apertures and instead held them in high regard.

But Fang Yuan's own soul was from Earth, he had an open mind, the authority of the traditional way of Gu cultivation had not been deeply ingrained into his mind.

At this moment, his mind was filled with exclamations of praise!

"The methods of humans continue to progress over time, history continues to be written. Gu cultivation can fully be regarded as another form of science, it continues to advance and develop with time."

"In the past, in ancient times, there were indeed countless wise and capable geniuses who had glorious and brilliant accomplishments. But those of future generations stand on these shoulders of their predecessors, using their foundations, they are able to have even more brilliant and splendid accomplishments."

Like this mysterious great expert immortal zombie who invented the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method, they had stood on Old Immortal Kong Jue's shoulders, they used Limitless Demon Venerable's accomplishments in rule path and combined them with their own talents before they were finally able to create this improved cultivation method.

Fang Yuan continued to ponder.

The more he thought about it, the more he realized the profundity and brilliance of this revival method.

During this short period of time, Fang Yuan could only scratch the surface of this brilliant technique, but he could not comprehend the essence and origin of this brilliance.

He knew that following this method was the right course and the result would also be ideal for him.

But he did not know what principles were involved in this method.

The explanation for the life-and-death immortal aperture could be said to be simple, but the principles involved in it were something Fang Yuan could still not understand.

The contents of the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method were not simple, they were very complex.

Because it subdivided every Gu cultivation path into different revival methods, different Gu worms needed to be refined accordingly.

For instance, Fang Yuan cultivated strength path, he needed a large amount of exert strength Gu, countless disappointment Gu, and many other types of supplementary Gu worms to finally create a multi-layered Gu formation.

Fang Yuan carefully thought over these ideas, feeling that they were rather interesting.

When mortals started cultivating, hope Gu was needed to awaken their aperture. This method, however, required disappointment Gu and exert strength Gu.

Without hope, how could there be disappointment?

Without disappointment, where would hope come from?

Disappointment and hope, these two concepts stood as opposites to each other but they coexisted together.

It was just like the concept of life and death. If one was gone, the other also lacked the significance for a concept of it to be formed.

Fang Yuan planned inwardly: "Disappointment Gu and exert strength Gu are merely mortal Gu, so they are not difficult to gather. There are also corresponding Gu recipes here, I can order the hairy men to refine them day in and day out. Even if the amount required is large, I can complete it within three months. Once completed, I can immediately start my revival and obtain a life-and-death immortal aperture! Except that..."

Except that the life-and-death immortal aperture that would be obtained in this way was somewhat unsatisfactory.

Because Fang Yuan's strength path immortal aperture was already mostly disintegrated. Using just the remaining dead immortal aperture as the base, the newly formed life-and-death immortal aperture would naturally be inferior. Be it the size, the environment or its foundation, they would all be lacking.

When Fang Yuan had been forced to ascend in Northern Plains, the foundation for his immortal aperture was not high in the first place, its size was three and a half thousand square kilometers and the rate of time was sixteen times that of the outside world.

A low grade blessed land has a size of two thousand square kilometers at the maximum, it can draw in a small tributary of the river of time and create over ten beads of immortal essence, while being a land of few resources.

A medium grade blessed land can have a size of two thousand and seven hundred square kilometers to four thousand square kilometers, draw in a slightly bigger tributary of the river of time, create over twenty beads of immortal essence and have plentiful resources.

Fang Yuan's previous strength path immortal aperture was only a medium grade blessed land. Now, if he used his currently shrunken blessed land to revive, it will definitely be a low grade blessed land, and it was very likely for it to be low grade even among low grades.

Without doubt, this would be unfavorable to Fang Yuan's future cultivation.

However, there was a segment of content about the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method which excited Fang Yuan greatly.

During the refinement process, he could use other strength path immortal zombies' corpses as immortal materials and refine them in a Gu formation. This would increase the grade of the life-and-death immortal aperture created, his low grade blessed land could return to medium grade, and as long as there were sufficient strength path immortal zombies, he might even be able to raise his blessed land to high grade!

When immortal zombies die, their aperture would completely dissipate and the dao marks in the aperture would stay in the immortal zombie body. Thus, immortal zombie bodies were rich with dao marks and were special kinds of immortal materials. If not for this, Old Ancestor Xue Hu would not have shamelessly sneaked into the immortal zombie graveyard to steal the corpses.

At the final part of this segment, it was clearly recorded —

If one could obtain a Great Strength True Martial Physique immortal zombie body and used it during the revival process, the life-and-death immortal aperture created would surpass that of a high grade blessed land and become a super grade blessed land!

And after the immortal zombie revives, they would possess the Great Strength True Martial Physique!!

Because Hei Lou Lan had advanced into an immortal with the Great Strength True Martial Physique and possessed a super grade blessed land, Fang Yuan understood many things regarding it.

"A super grade blessed lands has a vast space of over six thousand seven hundred square kilometers. Every year, the amount of immortal essence it produces would surpass fifty beads! The rate of time is even faster, thus precious resources can be obtained in extremely short intervals! Furthermore, the Great Strength True Martial Physique can increase my battle strength by several times!" Fang Yuan's heart thumped with excitement.

From this point, one could also discern that the life-and-death immortal aperture method was an excellent method to raise a Gu Immortal's aptitude!

The ten extreme physiques...

They had extremely great power, but their flaws were even bigger!

Because time flowed faster, calamities and tribulations came quicker and more frequently, their might becoming increasingly terrifying! For the cultivation of Gu Immortals, this was a big taboo!

One could find out from history that none of the ten supreme venerables had one of the ten extreme physiques. Even among rank eight Gu Immortals, it was extremely rare for someone to possess one of the ten extreme physiques.

In short, a person with one of the ten extreme physiques could be unrivaled among those of the same rank and could even fight against those that exceeded their rank, but they did not have the potential to grow and simply could not live for long under the barrage of calamities and tribulations.

However, this huge flaw did not exist to Fang Yuan!

There was only one reason for that — he possessed the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method.

And a life-and-death immortal aperture reduced the might of calamities and tribulations by half!

This lowered the danger to a completely acceptable level and formed a much more beneficial cycle.

"I can at most obtain a high grade blessed land by gathering ordinary strength path immortal zombie bodies. But if I can gather the body of an immortal zombie of one of the ten extreme physiques, I can possess the Great Strength True Martial Physique and own a super grade blessed land, moreover the calamities and tribulations would have their might reduced by half. As long as I have enough time to cultivate, my strength will continue to grow, and I would have a chance at vying for that supreme throne of rank nine!"

Fang Yuan's eyes burned with the flames of passion.

Rank nine venerables were invincible in the world, this was a publicly recognized fact. If since ancient times, there has been not been a ten extreme physique venerable, did that imply that they would be the strongest even among the rank nine venerables?

In this world, the greatest in strength in all of history?

"I also have my first mortal aperture. If my revival goes smoothly, I can use this method again to cultivate time path and change my first mortal aperture to a super grade blessed land. At that time, not only will I have the Great Strength True Martial Physique, I will also have the Desolate Ancient Moon Physique!"

Dual Ten Extreme Physique!

And with time, a dual ten extreme physique venerable?

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan almost shed tears.

In the five hundred years of his previous life and in this life, he had wandered from place to place, enduring many hardships and taking risks amidst life and death. Finally, now, at this moment, he found a hopeful path that could lead him to the grand ambition of immortality!

Eternal life seemed to be an illusory goal, but if one did not have sufficient strength, then it was a target that was impossible to pursue to begin with.

"Strength path immortal zombies are already few in numbers, since I have joined Zombie Alliance, I am unable to target the alliance members. Great Strength True Martial Physique immortal zombie, where can I find one? Hmph. Right now, there is only one optimal target — Hei Lou Lan!!"

At that instant, Fang Yuan's eyes shined with a ferocious light.

"Although I cooperated with you to escape from Imperial Court blessed land and have obtained many benefits later on, having a rather pleasant experience, for the ambition that I seek, you have to be sacrificed."

A faint smile appeared on Fang Yuan's face.

Ruthless.

Callous!

Chapter 940: Fang Yuan's Plans

Since he obtained the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method, Fang Yuan naturally wanted to make as much use of it as he could.

Regardless of whether it was in his previous life or now, cultivation aptitude was always a big regret for Fang Yuan. Now that he could fix this, Fang Yuan was extremely happy to do so.

Most importantly, the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method for the ten extreme physiques was too enticing, the advantage it gave towards cultivating was too great.

However, it was extremely difficult to obtain a Great Strength True Martial immortal zombie.

Firstly, the ten extreme physiques were very rarely seen. Even if they appeared, they could not cultivate easily.

There were even fewer of those with the Great Strength True Martial physique that cultivated to Gu Immortal level.

And on this basis, those who turned into immortal zombies and still had their bodies intact might simply be nonexistent!

Fang Yuan checked historical records and his memories, but there were no clues.

Thus, Hei Lou Lan was his easiest target, and also the most appropriate and realistic one.

Or rather, she was his only target.

But the problems in front of Fang Yuan were not few.

Firstly, Hei Lou Lan herself was a formidable person, she had both brains and brawn, in his previous life, she left her own mark in history. Such a person was not easy to deal with, she could risk her fight and battle all out while also scheming deeply, she could not be messed with casually.

Secondly, Hei Lou Lan was not alone, she had the rank seven Fairy Li Shan supporting her. They had a close relationship, they would not turn on each other. To deal with Hei Lou Lan, Fang Yuan would also have to deal with Fairy Li Shan.

Thirdly, Fairy Li Shan, Hei Lou Lan, and Fang Yuan had an alliance agreement.

Finally, and what was also Fang Yuan's biggest problem, Hei Lou Lan knew the truth of Imperial Court blessed land. If he did not handle it appropriately, she would tell this truth to the world. By then, Fang Yuan would be hunted down by all the Gu Immortals in the world. The allure of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's inheritance would be so great that countless greedy Gu Immortals would charge at him like a tsunami, completely drowning him.

All in all, Hei Lou Lan was like a porcupine, if he was rash in dealing with her, not only might she be left unharmed, but he would also end up suffering major backlash.

"Hei Lou Lan, oh Hei Lou Lan, if not for the fact that you have the Great Strength True Martial physique which helps my cultivation, I would not want to target you." Fang Yuan sighed internally.

In the following days, Fang Yuan started his preparations on two aspects.

On one hand, he needed to think about an appropriate way to harm Hei Lou Lan.

On the other hand, he was refining star thought Immortal Gu while using letters to communicate with Fairy Li Shan on how to breach a contract.

But days went by, he was making very slow progress in all of them.

Ever since Hei Lou Lan realized her flaws, she made up her mind and focused on managing her blessed land. Since she could not hide inside Snowy Mountain blessed land anymore, she hid outside and went missing.

After Fang Yuan returned to Dark Flow Giant City, he took action to one again go to Earth Trench and collect star night mucus. After that, he used the star night mucus to refine star thought Immortal Gu, but he failed again.

Fairy Li Shan had cultivated earth path in the past, she later cultivated information path mainly alongside wood path, she had mountain pledge Immortal Gu, her information path attainment was definitely higher than that of Fang Yuan. Earlier, she had gone against the agreement to deal with Dong Fang tribe, but she was still alive and well now, this showed that not only was she skilled at making agreements, she was also able to break them.

Information path specialized in agreements. To make a comparison, they were like locks that restricted both parties.

Fairy Li Shan was like a locksmith, she was skilled at making locks, she was certain to be good at opening them.

Fang Yuan, Fairy Li Shan, and Hei Lou Lan, even though they had an agreement, the deadline was approaching, thus this agreement was not trouble.

The reason Fang Yuan gave Fairy Li Shan was — he needed to deal with the agreement for joining Zombie Alliance.

Fang Yuan had joined Zombie Alliance in Eastern Sea, he was restricted by the Zombie Alliance agreement.

"If I cannot get Hei Lou Lan, I can only lower my expectations and collect a large number of strength path immortal zombies. If that happens, I will need to break the Zombie Alliance agreement so that I can steal bodies inside the Zombie Alliance graveyard."

The careful Fang Yuan would naturally not put all of his eggs in one basket, he would make all kinds of preparations.

Therefore, these last days, Fang Yuan had been asking for information path methods from Fairy Li Shan often.

The results were minimal.

On one hand, Fairy Li Shan was guarding against Fang Yuan. He had developed too rapidly, it already made this third leader of Snowy Mountain blessed land feel threatened. Even though Fang Yuan offered a high price, she used the excuse of having to find immortal materials to reject him.

Secondly, Fang Yuan had little understanding in regards to information path, with such low attainment, it was hard for him to learn something in this short period of time.

Thirdly, was Zombie Alliance's agreement so easily broken? It was wishful thinking to expect Fang Yuan to be able to break it in such a short time!

Even though he did not make any progress in information path, after interacting with Fairy Li Shan, Fang Yuan had a clear understanding of the fight between Zombie Alliance and Snowy Mountain blessed land using his own knowledge from being inside Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's base.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' tactic was very smart.

These last days, she led the immortal zombies to attack the demonic path Gu Immortals of Snowy Mountain blessed land continuously.

Many of the demonic path Gu Immortals had low luck to begin with, it was hard to collect immortal materials, but now with the immortal zombies wreaking havoc, they faced even more problems, their gains were affected.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was helpless.

The reason was simple, even though he was a rank eight great expert, he was just one person.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had three rank eight immortal zombies.

If Blazing Heaven Demoness forcefully attacked Snowy Mountain blessed land, with Old Ancestor Xue Hu's battle strength, it was uncertain who would win.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness avoided that, she made use of Old Ancestor Xue Hu's weakness, this made Old Ancestor Xue Hu's life much more difficult.

If he attacked, he would not be around to guard Snowy Mountain blessed land.

The defending Gu Immortals only had rank seven cultivation level at the highest. Second leader Lady Wan Shou was skilled in refinement path, while third leader Fairy Li Shan cultivated information path, they both did not have high battle strength.

If Old Ancestor Xue Hu went out to attack and was held up by an expert of the same rank, and Snowy Mountain blessed land was ransacked by the other rank eight immortal zombies, then that would turn him into the biggest laughing stock in Northern Plains!

Especially that Blazing Heaven Demoness.

She did not have limits to her conduct, back then, she even burned a nine heavens fragment world, making it a lose-lose situation for everyone.

Snowy Mountain blessed land was only a blessed land that was pieced together, it had lower defense than normal blessed lands, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had to guard against her.

Thus, even though Old Ancestor Xue Hu had incredible battle strength, against Zombie Alliance, he was at a disadvantage, he could not turn the situation around.

Battle strength did not mean everything.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' experienced scheming made Old Ancestor Xue Hu suffer heavy losses, but he could not fight back effectively.

Fang Yuan had no other choice but to be patient and focus his attention on refining exert strength Gu and disappointment Gu.

The Fang Yuan stone nests that he built were already at quite the sizes.

Large numbers of hairy man slaves were working non-stop, the number of exert strength Gu and disappointment Gu grew, but they were still far from the desired quantity.

Even though Fang Yuan obtained those precious rank eight immortal materials, he did not sell them yet, he kept them for now.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was funding him in refining star thought Immortal Gu. Every month, Fang Yuan's profits were used for refining Gu worms, feeding Immortal Gu, as well as developing Star Form blessed land.

He purchased large amounts of cloud soil, ordering Star Form land spirit to arrange them.

He wanted to build a giant three dimensional river system, using the ample space to cultivate star fragment grass.

This had huge prospects.

If it succeeded, the profits would not be lower than guts Gu.

But the initial investment was huge, Fang Yuan could only develop it one step at a time.

He wanted to deal with Hei Lou Lan, but that might expose his crimes. It was too easy for Hei Lou Lan to expose the truth, even though there was an alliance, she had Fairy Li Shan's help if she wanted to breach the contract, she had a greater advantage than Fang Yuan.

All along, Fang Yuan had been feeling anxious.

The investigation of the Central Continent Gu Immortals could not be making zero progress.

Perhaps tomorrow, Central Continent Gu Immortals would come and attack Hu Immortal blessed land.

There was no way he could defend Hu Immortal blessed land, once it was lost, Star Form blessed land would be Fang Yuan's only place to retreat to.

As the saying goes, a sly rabbit makes three dens, not to mention the old demon Fang Yuan.

On this day, Fang Yuan was activating the refinement path Gu formation, processing a certain immortal material.

Inside his dead aperture, moving perspective cup Gu activated, bringing a letter from Fairy Li Shan.

Fang Yuan felt this was strange, this letter was actually Fairy Li Shan approaching him.

Opening it, it was a letter requesting for help.

As it turned out, Fairy Li Shan found traces of Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng was the father of Hei Lou Lan, she wanted to take revenge for her mother, he was someone she had to kill.

Fairy Li Shan's letter asked Fang Yuan to come along and kill Hei Cheng!

Hei Cheng's circumstances were not good.

As a person who held power in the super force, Hei tribe, he went missing for a long time (the hundred days battle), and by the time he reappeared, he was in a pathetic state, being hunted down secretly by Hei tribe itself.

In fact, in order to save his life, Hei Cheng sacrificed the rank six Immortal Gu House Dark Prison.

This was the symbol of strength in Hei tribe, it was also their trump card, he actually lost it.

Even though Hei Cheng had great authority, in this situation, he would still be punished according to the rules of the tribe!

The Immortal Gu House Dark Prison was not his, the core Immortal Gu that made up the Immortal Gu House came from the four supreme elders of Hei tribe. After the Central Continent Gu Immortals divided up Dark Prison, they brought the Immortal Gu back to their sects, one of the Immortal Gu had already been forcefully refined by a Central Continent Gu Immortal.

Thus, the Hei tribe supreme elders learned about it, Hei Cheng had committed a huge mistake, he needed to be punished!

Hei Cheng did not want to hand himself over.

Before he participated in Shadow Sect's activities, he had made an agreement with them, he could not expose any details regarding Shadow Sect.

This alliance agreement had a strong restriction!

Hei Cheng could not explain the matter to his tribe, he could only escape.

Hei tribe was unwilling to let him go, the Immortal Gu House was extremely important, it affected their deterrence capability and strength, it had to be taken back.

And Hei Cheng was the clue.

Thus, Hei tribe sent Gu Immortals to capture Hei Cheng.

After both sides fought several times, Hei Cheng narrowly escaped. As the commotion got larger, Fairy Li Shan learned about it. She and Hei Lou Lan discussed it, they felt that now was the best time to take revenge, after Hei Cheng had been abandoned by his tribe.

They needed to have greater numbers as assurance in killing a Gu Immortal.

Thus, Fairy Li Shan immediately contacted Fang Yuan, before the alliance expired, they now had an excellent chance to make use of him!

While it was true that the compensation that Fairy Li Shan gave was very profitable, Fang Yuan also had his own motives, this was a good opportunity.

Hei Lou Lan had been staying hidden all this time, only during a chaotic battle could Fang Yuan find a chance to take action.

Chapter 941: Third Battle With Hei Cheng

Escape! Escape! Escape!

A shadowy figure moved rapidly in the tall grass, like a flying snake.

A moment later, the shadow vanished with a soft sound, and the flying stopped. Hei Cheng crashed into the grass nearby.

A clear stream was flowing, right beside him.

Hei Cheng breathed roughly, he was sprawled on the ground, not even having the strength to turn his body over.

His current condition was terrible.

His entire body was covered in wounds, some were deep until bones could be seen, some were still bleeding. Intense pain was assaulting him, but Hei Cheng was already used to it.

These injuries were all created when he fought intensely with the pursuers from Hei tribe.

If Hei tribe was not trying to capture Hei Cheng alive, with his current ability, there was no way he could have escaped so many times.

"I am already at my limits, huh..." Hei Cheng felt grim internally, he gritted his teeth and tried to get up, seeing his reflection in the water, he smiled bitterly at himself.

Originally, he was handsome and charming, having a gentlemanly disposition, but now his face was pale and his lips were green, his body was covered in blood while he escaped for his life.

Suddenly, Hei Cheng's pupils shrunk to pinpricks in size as he curled up his body, like a venomous snake that felt threatened.

"Who is it?!" Hei Cheng's eyes shined with a sharp light, he shouted at a nearby bush.

At the next moment, with a loud bang, air currents burst out as the grass was uprooted, a large pathway was created.

Hei Lou Lan wore a mask as she stepped forward.

Her eerie and dark eyes were burning with flames of hatred that had been etched into her.

"It is you!" Hei Cheng was shocked, he tried to stand up but his head was dizzy, his body shook intensely as he fell down helplessly.

Thankfully, he did not collapse entirely, he managed to regain his balance but he was half squatting with tightened muscles, his expression was ruthless but he could not conceal the anxiety inside him.

If he was captured by the Hei tribe Gu Immortals, he might still be able to live, even though that was unlikely.

But if he ended up in the hands of Hei Lou Lan, Hei Cheng would be dead meat, his fate would be unthinkably miserable!

"Hei Cheng, to think that you would end up like this!" Hei Lou Lan walked towards him, her body was straight like a spear, across a small river, she looked down at him arrogantly.

Fate was unpredictable.

Who would have thought that Hei Cheng would end up in such a state?

Hei Lou Lan had never expected this!

Thus, when the perfect opportunity for revenge was right in front of her, other than hatred and anger deep inside her, she also felt a trace of pity.

The father and daughter stared at each other.

Hatred, grudges, all of their emotions were present.

For a moment, time seemed to have stopped.

"Don't look at me with that gaze!!!" Hei Cheng screamed, he struggled to get up.

He could accept Hei Lou Lan's anger and hatred, but he could not stand that trace of pity in her eyes.

I, the great Hei Cheng, do not need anyone's pity!

Whoosh!

A strong wind blew, the dark clouds in the sky moved as the surrounding grass swayed.

Ripples appeared in the stream, as Fairy Li Shan's voice was heard in the wind: "Nice wind, nice scenery, this nameless location is a good place for you to die, Hei Cheng."

Hei Cheng sneered, he could feel the hatred and killing intent in Fairy Li Shan's words.

He turned his head around with difficulty, looking at the surroundings: "A tiger without power gets bullied by dogs, isn't there someone else? Why are you not coming out?"

Fang Yuan quietly concealed himself nearby, he did not move and leaked no aura, as if he could not hear Hei Cheng's words.

"You, a tiger? You are just a dog who is struggling to survive on the verge of death. Thieving dog, prepare to lose your life!" Hei Lou Lan no longer concealed the anger inside her, she took a big step and sent out a punch.

In an instant, there was an explosion in the air as the air currents created from her punch burst out.

Fang Yuan's mood was stirred, he felt a strong desire: "This is only a mortal killer move, but with the amplification of the Great Strength True Martial Physique's strength path dao marks, its power could actually reach such a level."

Before this punch landed on Hei Cheng, the latter already felt an intense feeling of stiflement.

An immeasurable sense of danger filled him.

If this punch landed, Hei Cheng would die on the spot!

Escape!

Hei Cheng gritted his teeth, activating countless Gu worms.

With a swoosh, he turned into a dark shadowy snake again, escaping towards the left side.

Hei Lou Lan's punch missed, she quickly chased him.

But Hei Cheng was very fast, in a few breaths of time, Hei Lou Lan was already dozens of meters behind.

In fact, even though Hei Cheng lost the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison, he still had Immortal Gu Dark Arrow.

During the hundred days battle, in order to raise Hei Cheng's strength, Shadow Sect designed a set of immortal killer moves for him.

This set of immortal killer moves used dark arrow Immortal Gu as the core, right now, the dark snake that Hei Cheng had transformed into to escape was one of these immortal killer moves.

"Hei Cheng, stay here." Fairy Li Shan took action, the surrounding grass grew wildly as flowers grew out of nowhere.

Battlefield killer move — Pear Orchard!

Hei Cheng's body froze, but he immediately broke out of the pear orchard and moved west to escape.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

Countless strength path phantoms emerged from the tall grass, blocking Hei Cheng.

Fang Yuan had not exposed the identity of Xing Xiang Zi to Hei Lou Lan or Fairy Li Shan, right now he was using his strength path battle strength.

Fang Yuan secretly used his wisdom path techniques and deduced three possible escape paths, he quietly assigned his strength path phantoms to those areas in order to ambush him.

While escaping, Hei Cheng accidentally went towards one of them, and was stalled by Fang Yuan's strength path phantoms.

Even so, Hei Lou Lan was still a distance from Hei Cheng.

Seeing that Hei Cheng was about to escape, Fairy Li Shan transmitted to Fang Yuan anxiously: "Quickly stop him!"

Fang Yuan immediately showed his true form, using the true solid bat wings on his back to fly towards Hei Cheng.

Fairy Li Shan frowned deeply, she could tell, with Fang Yuan's speed, he could not obstruct Hei Cheng.

In truth, Fang Yuan was not planning to stop Hei Cheng either.

Earlier, he had fought with Hei Cheng, but times were different now.

Hei Cheng was Hei Lou Lan's weakness, as long as he was alive, he would be able to use Hei Cheng in order to scheme against Hei Lou Lan.

Fang Yuan had originally wanted to use this chance to see if he could capture Hei Lou Lan.

But after seeing Hei Cheng's severe injuries, he knew the chances were close to zero.

If it were possible, Fang Yuan would rather let Hei Cheng go and let him escape.

But because of the alliance agreement, he could not go overboard.

Hei Cheng got rid of the obstacles, he gave Fang Yuan a look as he sneered: "You finally came out? It is a pity you cannot catch me!"

Saying so, he was about to use his immortal killer move to escape from this place.

But right at this moment, the cry of an eagle resounded and almost tore his eardrums.

A giant iron crown eagle phantom appeared behind Fang Yuan!

His iron crown eagle strength activated, as Fang Yuan's speed rose, he flew at lightning speed, closing the gap between him and Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng was shocked, he did not dare to slow down, he quickly escaped.

Fang Yuan sighed internally.

Even though he had the rank six Immortal Gu recipe of all-out effort Gu, it was still a rank five mortal Gu now. Fang Yuan's iron crown eagle strength was obtained from an Immortal Gu, it could only be triggered with certain probabilities.

In the previous battles, it had never been triggered, but today, when he did not want it to activate, it did.

"It seems that it was inappropriate to use time assist luck right before this to raise my luck! If I had known that Hei Cheng would be in such a condition, I would have realized that it was impossible to execute my plan."

Fang Yuan sighed, his body was like an eagle, pouncing at Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng was slippery as a snake, he moved around in the grass as a dark snake, changing many directions, even though Fang Yuan attacked many times, he narrowly escaped each time.

But Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan were no longer anxious, they were excited.

With Fang Yuan's interference, Hei Cheng could no longer escape. In a few breaths of time, Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan got close to them.

Eventually, the three of them encircled Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng's expression was dark and ominous, he screamed with messy hair all over his face: "You want me dead? Don't think you will leave unscathed!"

An intense battle erupted.

Rumble...

Thunderous sounds exploded, darkness shot out, flowers were flying, strength qi rampaged, the soil on the ground was sent flying.

Without any doubt, Hei Cheng was heavily suppressed, Fang Yuan's group held the advantage.

"It is a pity that I can only hold back on ten to twenty percent of my strength, that is the limit. If I hold back any more, Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan would realize it, they would be suspicious towards me and lose trust."

Seeing that this excellent pawn in Hei Cheng was about to die, Fang Yuan felt some regret.

Including this time, Fang Yuan had already fought against Hei Cheng three times.

Fang Yuan and the others did not have much of an increase in battle strength compared to the previous time.

But Hei Cheng's condition was too terrible, he had experienced the hundred days battle and the immortal essence that he accumulated over all his life was expended. These last days, he had been escaping and fighting intensely with Hei tribe's Gu Immortals.

Thus at this moment, under the attacks of Fang Yuan and the rest, Hei Cheng suffered another severe injury, he spat out blood and was about to lose.

"Stop!"

Suddenly, an angry shout could be heard in the sky.

A blinding green light filled the entire battlefield.

Space tore open as a green hand grabbed at Hei Cheng imposingly.

Fang Yuan and the others reacted quickly, but the green hand could affect time, it grabbed Hei Cheng before anyone could react.

"Green City Rampage!" Hei Cheng could not move, he screamed while being captured.

Hei Lou Lan and the others rapidly retreated.

Green City Rampage was a powerful battle formation of the Olden Antiquity Era, at that time it was ranked at third in the world, only lower than Golden Heavenly Saint and Heavenly Giant Solor.

The fact that Hei tribe was in control of Green City Rampage was known to everyone in Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

At this moment, with the appearance of Green City Rampage, it meant that the four strongest supreme elders of the super force Hei tribe had arrived together.

"We of Hei tribe will deal with our own Hei tribe members, how can we allow you to kill him casually?"

"Hei Lou Lan, the tribe nurtured you, but you betrayed us and went to the demonic path, you are guilty of the most heinous crimes, surrender now!"

At the next moment, a green giant tore through space, standing on the ground.

A mysterious light shot out of its forehead, towards Hei Lou Lan.

At that moment, Hei Lou Lan was unable to move!

Strength path giant hand!

Fang Yuan rapidly retreated as he used his rank seven battle strength.

Boom!

With an intense collision, strength path giant hand collided with the green hand, and the strength path giant hand disintegrated immediately.

"Pitiful trick!" The green giant laughed coldly.

But at the next moment, a fire bird crashed into the green giant's chest out of nowhere.

Boom!

With an intense explosion, the green giant was sent back, almost falling onto the ground.

"Blazing Heaven Demoness?!" The four supreme elders of Hei tribe shouted with shock and anger on their faces inside the green giant.

Angry bird, this was a signature killer move of Blazing Heaven Demoness, it was widely known among Gu Immortals of Northern Plains.

At this time and place, why was Blazing Heaven Demoness here?

Be it the Hei tribe Gu Immortals or Fang Yuan, they were asking the same question.

Chapter 942: Little Aunt, Elder Aunt

Her rank eight aura was unconcealed, emanating freely.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was bathed in flames, she crossed her arms and stood arrogantly in the air.

Blazing Heaven Demoness shouted loudly: "Hei tribe elders, this ancient battle formation Green City Rampage of yours is so incomplete, you have the face to use it? A hundred years ago, in order to use this battle formation, you were forced to stay together at a distance of no more than three meters between each other. This time, you came here together, who is guarding the blessed land that is your main camp?"

The green giant gazed at Blazing Heaven Demoness.

An elderly voice came out of the green giant's body: "Blazing Heaven Demoness! Since you know that this is the ancient battle formation Green City Rampage, you should know that its power rivals that of rank eights. Hei Lou Lan and Hei Cheng are members of Hei tribe, this is an internal family matter of ours, as an outsider, you should not interfere. Don't forget that Zombie Alliance is in the righteous path. As the leader of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, you have significant responsibilities, do be careful."

Immediately after, another voice said: "Blazing Heaven Demoness, aren't you going to deal with Old Ancestor Xue Hu? Why are you here to join in the chaos?"

"Join in the chaos? Hahahahaha..." Blazing Heaven Demoness raised her head and laughed.

Fairy Li Shan spoke at this moment, she continued: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu's matter is none of your concern, elders of Hei tribe. Furthermore... you said this is your family matter, don't tell me it isn't our own family matter?"

"What do you mean?" Inside the green giant's body, the four elders of Hei tribe asked with shocked voices.

At this moment, Fang Yuan felt an intense feeling that something was not right.

"Big sister!" Fairy Li Shan called out.

There was tacit understanding between siblings, there was no need to communicate too much in words.

Blazing Heaven Demoness stopped laughed, her gaze was like lightning as she flew towards the green giant.

On the green giant's body, a lump of fire burned out of nowhere, in an instant, it turned into a blazing flame and engulfed the entire green giant.

Soon, the hill-like green giant became an orange pillar of fire.

Immortal killer move — Fire Prison!

In the burning flames, the green giant could barely move, it was as if it had fallen into a puddle of sticky black oil.

The four elders who assembled the green giant were shocked.

"When did we get hit by it?"

"This killer move's power is so immense! Even our Green City Rampage cannot break free for the time being."

"Most importantly, there were no hints of it being used, we cannot defend against it!"

But the four elders had rich battle experience, they were only shocked for a few breaths of time before they understood.

They remembered the attack earlier — angry bird had crashed into the green giant's chest.

Meanwhile, fire prison started burning at the green giant's chest.

This was a combo immortal killer move!

So-called combo immortal killer moves were the usage of two or more immortal killer moves one after another, they would have stronger power, having synergy between them.

Angry bird, fire prison, these two immortal killer moves formed a combo immortal killer move.

Blazing Heaven Demoness first used angry bird to attack the green giant, she next used fire prison to trap Green City Rampage with an incredibly powerful effect.

If a long time had passed, or if she had activated fire prison first, Blazing Heaven Demoness would have to spend time in activating the move, during that period, the four elders of Hei tribe would be able to dodge, fire prison's power would not be as great as now.

The reason was very simple.

It was due to dao marks.

Immortal killer moves used Immortal Gu as the core to activate powerful methods.

The power was great because they formed temporary dao marks.

When angry bird crashed into the green giant's chest, temporary fire path dao marks were left behind. Blazing Heaven Demoness used these fire path dao marks as the basis to unleash fire prison, elevating its power and temporarily trapping the green giant.

"To be able to design a combo immortal killer move, her attainment level must be great grandmaster! So Blazing Heaven Demoness' fire path attainment level has already reached such a level." Fang Yuan's heart was shaking.

Fire path great grandmaster!

This attainment level was not something ordinary Gu Immortals could reach.

Roar—!

The green giant roared loudly, large amounts of green fog spewed out of its body.

Wherever the green fog went, fire was put out.

Evidently, this mysterious green fog was a powerful immortal killer move.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' combo immortal killer move did not even last for ten breaths of time before it completely disintegrated.

But they still lost some precious time.

During this period, Fairy Li Shan had already finished preparing, she used her trump card.

Battlefield immortal killer move — Orchard Garden in Mountain!

The earth rumbled intensely.

Rumble...

In the blink of an eye, waves of terrifying tremors erupted deep underground.

The surface started to rise, the terrain changed swiftly.

The flat grassland had turned into a mound.

Soon, this mound rose rapidly, becoming taller. On the two sides of the mountain, there were evident ridges forming.

Eventually, the mountain stopped rising, a chain of mountains encircled the green giant in all directions.

The tremors of the earth finally stopped.

The terrain of over a thousand li had completely changed because of Fairy Li Shan's battlefield immortal killer move.

Achieving such incredible effects, it was truly breathtaking!

A chain of mountains surrounded the green giant in the center, it was like a giant bowl or a prison, blocking their escape route.

At this moment, the green giant was like trapped prey.

Fang Yuan's heart pounded, even though he knew that Fairy Li Shan had such a trump card, seeing this effect, he still felt some surprise.

In his previous life, when Fairy Li Shan used this move, the power was not as great. Why did it become so powerful now?

"Don't tell me, it is because of Miniscule Mountain?" Fang Yuan had a guess.

"That should be it. Fairy Li Shan's orchard garden in mountain is like myriad star fireflies, it has incredible power when used, but the price should be equally big. Each time it is used, dao marks in the Gu Immortal will be expended permanently. Thus, in records of history, Fairy Li Shan did not use this battlefield immortal killer move very often."

Or in other words, this was a last resort technique.

A forbidden move.

If it was used frequently, one's own foundation and cultivation level would fall drastically.

Miniscule Mountain was a secluded domain of heaven and earth, it was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, the mountain itself had a large number of dao marks. Fairy Li Shan placed it inside her own immortal aperture, the dao marks of Miniscule Mountain became her own foundation, she could use and expend them.

Thus, orchard garden in mountain's power became so terrifying, far beyond Fang Yuan's knowledge based on his previous life.

The four elders of Hei tribe were rank seven Gu Immortals, the ancient battle formation Green City Rampage that they created was ranked at third in the world. But using Miniscule Mountain, Fairy Li Shan used orchard garden in mountain and temporarily trapped the rank eight level green giant, controlling the situation.

Fang Yuan and the others were floating in the air, looking down.

The green giant was huge, but the mountains surrounding it were taller.

Fairy Li Shan had stopped her activation, she no longer controlled it.

But the transformation of orchard garden in mountain still continued.

In the valley of the mountains, vegetation grew rapidly, countless pear trees grew, the branches were like vines entangling with each other, extending rapidly.

At the same time, pear blossoms bloomed, they floated in the air, slowly descending like snow.

Behind the green giant, a pair of thick and huge green wings appeared.

One of the four Hei tribe elders was skilled in transformation path, thus, the green giant could have such a transformation.

This was the specialty of an ancient battle formation.

Once an Immortal Gu House was created, the methods would be fixed. But ancient battle formations had different abilities according to the Gu Immortals using it, as well as their various methods in fighting.

The four elders of Hei tribe wanted to fly out of the cage, but countless vines were coiled onto the legs of the green giant.

"Hmph!" The green giant snorted, the color of its body changed.

It was as if fire was burning deep inside its body. Its green color, like that of moss, had turned into a dark red color.

Dark path and fire path — dual immortal killer move — Dark Ember!

Boom!

An intense explosion resounded, it could cause eardrums to vibrate.

A dark red translucent shock wave burst out of the green giant's body, spreading rapidly.

Everywhere the shock wave went, the entangled vines burned like paper, becoming ash.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

With three shock waves emitted by the green giant, obstacles were swept away.

At once, dust rose like clouds, the earth trembled, countless rocks fell.

The powerful and terrifying aura made Fairy Li Shan take a small step back in reflex.

Hei Lou Lan was seemingly unaware of this, her eyes were staring at one of the green giant's hands. Inside this hand, her father, Hei Cheng, was held inside.

Fang Yuan's expression did not change, but his heart sank.

He was starting to understand the situation.

Evidently, Fairy Li Shan, Hei Lou Lan, and Blazing Heaven Demoness were in cahoots.

Today, this situation was created by them to kill Hei Cheng, but at the same time, they were targeting Fang Yuan.

"I was scheming against Hei Lou Lan, but to think they would move against me first!" Fang Yuan looked towards Blazing Heaven Demoness, before today, he had not expected the leader of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance to be so closely related to Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan.

Blazing Heaven Demoness sensed Fang Yuan's gaze and gave him a look that was seemingly smiling.

Fang Yuan snorted internally, he turned his gaze away.

He was in grave danger now!

If he wanted to escape, Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan would only bring him disturbance, but Blazing Heaven Demoness was a barrier that he could not pass!

Fang Yuan had Fixed Immortal Travel, Blazing Heaven Demoness surely knew about it.

"But now is not the time to act rashly. Since they have not attacked me yet, we can still talk it out. Even if I escape, it is pointless. I have joined Zombie Alliance, and Blazing Heaven Demoness is the leader of the Northern Plains Zombie Alliance branch. Furthermore, Fairy Li Shan is an information path Gu Immortal..."

It was laughable that previously, Fang Yuan was asking Fairy Li Shan for the method to leave Zombie Alliance.

"This means that my identity as Xing Xiang Zi has already been exposed. Hei Lou Lan is astute, since she knows I have star path cultivation, she would also know that I have already obtained Star Form blessed land!"

"Hei Lou Lan called Fairy Li Shan little aunt, I thought this was just an affectionate term, for example, little brother. To think that with a little aunt, she also had an elder aunt. And to think that Hei Lou Lan's elder aunt was such a formidable person!"

Chapter 943: Afraid of Death

Blazing Heaven Demoness was actually Hei Lou Lan's elder aunt, Fang Yuan did not expect this.

Fang Yuan's battle strength was rank seven at best.

Against Hei Lou Lan, he had an advantage, but the other party had the Great Strength True Martial Physique, he needed to be wary of her last resort attack.

Against Fairy Li Shan, he was at most only evenly matched. Fang Yuan would be in a disadvantage the moment she used her battlefield immortal killer move, he could not give her enough time to use it.

As for Blazing Heaven Demoness, he was extremely pitiful in comparison, it was despair-inducing. Even though Fang Yuan had many Immortal Gu, with his bottom tier rank six cultivation level, there was no way he could fight against a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Even a rank seven Gu Immortal could not match a rank eight Gu Immortal. Feng Jiu Ge was an exception, in the last thousand years of Central Continent's history, he was the only one.

It was virtually impossible for Fang Yuan to deal with Blazing Heaven Demoness.

The other party was simply too powerful, Fang Yuan was at a weaker position with an absolute disadvantage.

'Right now, the only thing that I can rely on is the alliance agreement I made with Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan previously. Allies are not allowed to kill each other.'

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly to himself internally.

Earlier, he was finding this agreement restricting to his actions, but now he had to rely on it to survive.

'However, Fairy Li Shan is an information path Gu Immortal, this agreement might not be reliable. Blazing Heaven Demoness can completely suppress me using battle strength, but she has not struck yet. If Fairy Li Shan wants to kill me, she would not create this situation either. Also, Blazing Heaven Demoness knows my true identity, why did she help me in refining star thought Immortal Gu? This means that they are not going after my life, they have other objectives.'

As for what their objectives were, Fang Yuan had a vague idea.

The conclusion was, right now, Fang Yuan was not in any mortal danger. This was also the reason why he was continuing to watch and not trying to escape.

Just as Fang Yuan was thinking over his own safety, the green giant that was trapped by orchard garden in mountain roared as it raised its head.

After several uses of the killer move dark ember, most of the pear trees in the valley were burned to ashes, but they continued to grow from the ground, extending towards the green giant even though it would take some time to trap it again.

Using this chance, two more pairs of giant green wings appeared on the green giant's back again.

At the same time, the green giant's appearance underwent a change, its large head turned into that of an eagle's, its entire body became slimmer and longer, its arms and legs turned into sharp five fingered claws.

Whoosh!

Its three pairs of wings flapped together, at the same time, the green giant's knees bent slightly, it jumped and burst into the sky.

The ground trembled, a huge crater was formed from the impact.

Dust clouds rose and mixed with the huge amounts of ashes.

This time, the green giant was not restricted by the vines, but the moment it flew into the sky, the four elders of Hei tribe felt a strong suction force, it was pulling onto the giant, preventing the green giant from flying far away from it.

"This is?" The four elders of Hei tribe showed stunned expressions one after another.

Every several meters the green giant rose into the sky, the strength of the huge pulling force increased by ten times as much!

Gradually, the green giant was unable to resist it anymore.

No matter how much the three wings flapped, the giant's speed became slower and slower, eventually, it slowed to a crawl, resembling a snail.

After reaching its limits, it was only thirty meters away from the ground.

Boom!

With another loud bang, the green giant crashed into the ground.

The four elders of Hei tribe were silent.

There was no need to say anything, anyone could guess the result, their faces were completely ashen now.

This was the true power of orchard garden in mountain.

Fairy Li Shan cultivated information path mainly, and secondarily in wood path and earth path. Orchard garden in mountain was a battlefield killer move that was formed by combining earth path and wood path, the pear blossoms were like snow, the vines coiled around the target, these were just wood path techniques. The force of gravity that pulled it down was the aspect of earth path.

Of course, this was also due to Fairy Li Shan using the power of Miniscule Mountain inside her.

Otherwise, if she used the original version of orchard garden in mountain that was based on her own strength, the green giant might have broken out of it already.

This was an ancient battle formation, Green City Rampage, even though it was incomplete, there were four rank seven Gu Immortals inside the battle formation, they could fight against a rank eight when unified.

The green giant could not break out, it landed on the ground. In the valley, countless vines coiled around it again like tough snakes, the green giant was restricted again.

At this time, there was a sharp sound of wind as explosions occurred in the air, the sound was so loud eardrums could almost burst.

Three angry birds fused in the air, turning into a fire phoenix that was neither big nor small.

The phoenix sang loudly, its wings flapped, it was extremely fast, it drew a beautiful rainbow arc in the sky, crashing into the green giant's arm and vanishing completely.

The green giant displayed an incredibly powerful defense, merely a deep hole was created from the explosion on its arm.

Next, waves of green fog circulated around it, as the deep hole closed up, it was like liquid metal, rapidly mending.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness' attacks did not stop for even a moment.

She stood arrogantly in the air, she slowly pointed her arm towards the green giant that was below her, her arm made a slashing motion from up to down!

Fire path killer move — Phoenix Feather Triple Wing Blade!

Three waves of flames formed instantly. They resembled the feathers of the phoenix, they were curved but extremely sharp like sickles.

Whoosh! Whoosh! Whoosh!

Three fire blades tore through the air, burning intensely as huge winds started blowing as a result of the movement.

Three blades launched one after another, hitting the same place consecutively.

Together with the angry bird earlier, this achieved another combo move effect, the green giant's arm was chopped off by these three blades.

The four elders of Hei tribe growled furiously, but it was too late for them to stop her.

The green giant's body was formed from the ancient battle formation, after the arm was detached from the body, it was as if the Gu formation itself had lost a portion of itself. Losing the immortal essence supply from the four elders, the arm quickly vanished into nothingness, as countless Gu worm flew out rapidly towards the green giant.

Hei Cheng who was captured earlier lost his restraint, he quickly fell.

The green giant tried to grab him, but Blazing Heaven Demoness stopped it.

Hei Cheng tried to escape, but times were different now, he was inside orchard garden in mountain, almost immediately, countless vines and roots tied him up tightly, sending him out into the hands of Fairy Li Shan.

"Let him go!" The four elders of Hei tribe flew into a rage.

Countless dark ember killer moves were used consecutively. Marks of dragons appeared on the green giant's chest and back, it was like they were emerging from a body of water, they turned into green dragons and flew around the area.

This was the signature killer move of Hei tribe's first supreme elder — Nine Dragon Body Protection!

It could both attack and defend, under the amplification of the ancient battle formation, it displayed incredibly terrifying power!

At once, nine dragons flew around, they were unstoppable.

Mountain ridges collapsed, pear blossoms wilted, plants and trees were sent flying.

Fairy Li Shan's expression changed: "Hurry up, I cannot hold on much longer!"

The green giant unleashed its full battle strength, it was already very difficult for orchard garden in mountain to trap it until now.

"Go!" Blazing Heaven Demoness moved without hesitation, she shot out a long chain of fire, grabbing onto Fairy Li Shan, Hei Lou Lan, Fang Yuan, and Hei Cheng.

Soon after, she used her killer move, turning into a rainbow, dragging everyone into the air along with her.

At the moment where he was trapped by the chain of fire, Fang Yuan subconsciously wanted to resist it, but he held in that instinct eventually.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' speed was extremely fast, in the blink of an eye, she vanished with everyone into the horizon.

Ten breaths of time later, orchard garden in mountain was completely destroyed, the terrifying collapse of mountains ravaged the battlefield.

The green giant successfully flew into the air, it roared and caused tremors in the sky and earth.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' movement killer move was extremely fast, it would take a lot of effort for the four elders of Hei tribe to catch up to her.

Even if they caught up, it would be hard to decide a winner among them.

But it was too late now, the four elders of Hei tribe had to chase her. Hei Cheng had been the representative of the four supreme elders, he had settled Hei tribe's affairs for so many years, he knew a lot of secrets.

Furthermore, as a super force, their own Gu Immortal was kidnapped by others, the four elders of Hei tribe had lost all of their face, if they did not stop Blazing Heaven Demoness, they would not be able to raise their heads in front of the other super forces, or even any of the righteous path or demonic path forces.

Hei tribe's Immortal Gu House Dark Prison was lost, and Hei Cheng got captured, Hei tribe's reputation was going to plummet.

As the saying goes, everyone kicks a man who is down, with Hei tribe being so weak now, all the other forces would try to suppress them, they would also be forced to give up a lot of the cultivation resources that they were holding onto in Northern Plains.

Green City Rampage was an ancient battle formation, the four supreme elders of Hei tribe had no lack of movement killer moves. Once they activated their moves together, their speed would be several times that of Blazing Heaven Demoness.

But just as the green giant was about to chase her, a latter for emergency support appeared beside the four elders of Hei tribe.

"What? Our blessed land base has been infiltrated by someone secretly and most of our resources were stolen, we have suffered great losses!"

"The Hei tribe Gu Immortals guarding the place are all heavily injured!"

"The invader is extremely powerful, they have undeniable rank eight aura!"

The four elders of Hei tribe were shocked and furious.

This was most definitely a plot.

"Right now, Northern Plains Zombie Alliance has three rank eights including Blazing Heaven Demoness."

"Damn it! Our base cannot be lost, the defense of a blessed land assembled with bits and pieces is not enough."

"We have all fallen into Blazing Heaven Demoness' scheme. Go! We have to go back and defend it."

The green giant roared loudly, both of its arms raised up and pulled, causing a gigantic dark hole to appear in the space in front of it.

The green giant flew into the dark hole and vanished, leaving behind only the ravaged battlefield which was completely in ruins.

"Hei tribe did not pursue us, we are safe now." Blazing Heaven Demoness landed on the ground with everyone.

The chain of fire that restricted everyone was collected by her.

Next, she waved her hand casually and the surrounding ten li were covered by a layer of dark red barriers.

The battle was now over, but Fang Yuan was more alert than before.

He moved his shoulders and arms, saying calmly to Fairy Li Shan: "So you are all family, you have truly kept me in the dark."

"The same goes for you." Fairy Li Shan smiled with deep meaning.

It was obvious that she had already known that Fang Yuan obtained Star Form blessed land and disguised himself as Xing Xiang Zi.

"Spare me! Spare my life! I am willing to become your subordinate, I am willing to serve you faithfully, it will be better for you if you keep me alive!" Hei Cheng struggled to get up, his face was filled with anxiety as he shouted continuously.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had taken away the parts of the chain of fire restricting everyone else, but Hei Cheng alone was still bound up tightly.

Not only did the situation develop beyond Fang Yuan's expectations, it was also completely out of Hei Cheng's expectations.

Fairy Li Shan stared with furious eyes as she pointed at Hei Cheng and scolded: "Dog thief, my little sister loved you so much, yet you took her life away. But that was not enough for you, you even wanted to lay your hands on your own daughter!"

Hei Cheng directly knelt on the ground, he raised his head and begged: "I am willing to be your dog or horse, I am willing to tell you all of the secrets of Hei tribe! Including the time path inheritance of our rank eight ancestor Hei Fan. Didn't Su Xian Er get close to me because of this inheritance? Don't you all want this inheritance! I will tell you everything that I know, I will not conceal any secrets!"

But Fairy Li Shan was completely unmoved, as Hei Cheng turned towards Blazing Heaven Demoness: "I did not have any intentions to offend you! Back then, if I had found out that you were behind Su Xian Er, I would not have taken her life! This is all a misunderstanding, this is all just a misunderstanding!!"

Hei tribe was a super force, they have an inheritance from long ago, their ancestor was obviously very powerful.

During the generation when Hei Fan was the one in power, Hei tribe had a rank eight Gu Immortal, they were one of the stronger super forces in Northern Plains.

But his lifespan was limited, after Hei Fan died, Hei tribe slowly became weaker, while some of the other super forces rose up.

This was normal in the world of Gu Immortals. The saying goes, upturns and downturns were just like the ebb and flow of tides, if one falls, another rises.

Hei Cheng continue to beg unceasingly.

He knew that this was the only way he could possibly survive.

Facing the rank eight Blazing Heaven Demoness, and Hei Lou Lan who bore a deep and unresolvable hatred towards him, he could not threaten them using Hei tribe itself. Thankfully, Hei Fan had an inheritance, and Hei tribe was unable to inherit it. The inheritance of a rank eight Gu Immortal was extremely attractive to any Gu Immortal out there.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness snickered, she looked at Hei Lou Lan and spoke with a gentle tone: "Your life is not mine, whether you can survive or not, only Little Lan can decide. Little Lan, go ahead, I have already restricted Hei Cheng, he is now as fragile as a mortal."

"Little Lan, Little Lan, listen to me!" Hei Cheng knelt on the ground, he rubbed his knees against the ground as he crawled towards Hei Lou Lan in a frenzy.

"You are my daughter, I am your father. you have the blood of Hei tribe flowing in you, you have a huge advantage in inheriting Hei Fan's inheritance. If your mother was alive, she would not want to see you and I in such conflict, right? If you mother was here, she would definitely be extremely happy to see you inherit Hei Fan's inheritance. Also, also! You have one of the ten extreme physiques, you were able to live until now because I asked Jiang Yu to protect your life, that is an undeniable fact!"

Hei Lou Lan looked at Hei Cheng, seeing his frightened and panicking face, she frowned, showing an expression of deep disgust and hatred.

Next, she kicked Hei Cheng away ruthlessly.

"I will only ask you one question!" Hei Lou Lan's expression was cold as ice.

"Ask, please ask! I will tell you everything that I know!" Hei Cheng could almost see a chance of survival.

Hei Lou Lan breathed in deeply, her eyes were red and her voice was trembling: "Mother loved you so much, she trusted you completely, actually, she knew that you were going to harm her long ago, but she believed that you would realize your mistake and stop your actions because of love. Facing someone who loved you so deeply, how could you have the heart to end her life?"

Hei Cheng was stunned.

He was originally tied up tightly on the ground, and was using his arm to prop his body, trying hard to sit up.

But he was completely stumped by Hei Lou Lan's question.

At this moment, he seemed to have turned into a statue.

A gust of wind blew, Hei Cheng's messy and muddy hair was blown up, his eyes were red as the loving memories of him and Su Xian Er surfaced in his mind.

Regret, pain, sadness, all sorts of emotions filled his heart.

He started choking, before wailing.

"I, of course I knew that your mother loved me... but, but, but I was afraid of dying... I was afraid of dying! Sob, sob, sob..."

After answering her question, Hei Cheng no longer had the strength to support his body, he collapsed on the ground.

He was like an old dog, or a rotting prawn, his body was curled up as he wept in the dirty mud.

His mucus and tears were mixed together, flowing down his face.

His silk robe was tattered beyond repair, his body was covered in blood.

His handsome face and former glory was like a dried up mask made of mud. When facing the prospects of death, this mask disintegrated and vanished.

Hei Lou Lan and the others fell into deep silence.

The scene was completely quiet.

Except for the wind that was blowing, and Hei Cheng's continuous soft weeping.

Hei Cheng's display made everyone around feel a deep sensation.

Death was truly a terrifying thing.

Facing death, even an invincible rank nine venerable was fragile beyond belief.

Eternal life.

Was it possible?

Fang Yuan only knew: From ancient times until the present, nobody had reached such a stage.

"Let him go." At this moment, a lump of emotion came out of Hei Lou Lan's body, turning into a translucent figure of a female immortal's body.

'Su Xian Er, the mother of Hei Lou Lan.' Fang Yuan's gaze flickered.

In the past, before Su Xian Er died, she had given Hei Lou Lan a sum of immortal essence, as well as this familial emotion.

It was because of the familial emotion and immortal essence that Hei Lou Lan could activate Immortal Gu while she was still a mortal.

"Little sister!" Seeing this familial emotion, Fairy Li Shan could not help but have tears fall from her eyes.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' eyes were turning red, she showed an extremely guilty expression full of regret.

Hei Lou Lan lowered her head, she looked at Hei Cheng calmly, seemingly in deep thought.

Su Xian Er's figure floated towards Hei Lou Lan, she stretched out her hand behind Hei Lou Lan, hugging her beloved daughter as she consoled her gently: "Let him go, you see how pitiful he is now. After killing me, he was already living a life of misery and regret, is he really happy to be alive now? No, he is barely scraping through life, he lives in terror, he lives in guilt, he is drifting without purpose, only living due to his fear, even though he is alive, he had already died long ago."

"Let him go, that is also the same as letting yourself off. Little Lan, do not live in a world of hatred, do not live in the past, you need to lead your own life. Don't bear the sin of killing your own father, it is a very heavy burden. Trust me, revenge will not lead you to salvation, but destruction instead. I want you to live a better life!"

"Mother, I know that you are saying that for my sake." Hei Lou Lan said as she walked towards Hei Cheng.

Suddenly, she raised her leg.

And she stomped!

Like what Blazing Heaven Demoness had said, Hei Cheng was currently as fragile as a mortal.

So under Hei Lou Lan's feet, his head was like a watermelon that burst, blood matter, blood, his skull, and teeth were all mixed together in a pile.

The high and mighty Hei Cheng, a rank seven Gu Immortal, a generation's hero, had died.

Su Xian Er's familial emotion was dazed.

Next, she saw that Hei Lou Lan turned around, facing her: "There is nothing I cannot bear, mother! It is like in the past, when you knew the situation but still let him have his way, I have my own resolution as well. Will this lead me on the path of destruction? Hmph, I am not so fragile."

"Little Lan." Fairy Li Shan took a step forward, holding Hei Lou Lan's hand with much worry.

"Little Lan..." Blazing Heaven Demoness muttered softly, she wanted to take a step towards Hei Lou Lan, but she did not do so eventually.

'So it's like this, I think I understand now.' Fang Yuan had been observing all of their expressions this entire time.

Chapter 944: The Greatest Fear is Fear Itself

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House.

Mountains stood tall, fog was thick, in a deep area of the bamboo forest, a waterfall resembled a clear veil as it hung in the air and fell downwards.

Feng Jin Huang sat silently on the branch of a pine tree, she quietly looked at the waterfall as her tears fell.

During this period of time, the Central Continent Gu Immortals who were sent to investigate Northern Plains had already returned.

But there was no news of Feng Jiu Ge.

From Feng Jin Huang's perspective, her father was missing without a trace in another region, it was likely that he had already died.

These last days, Feng Jin Huang did not have the appetite to eat or mood to cultivate, her face was drenched in tears as she became thinner.

Life and death.

These were heavy words, they attacked Feng Jin Huang's fragile heart at an unexpected timing.

It was not that Feng Jin Huang had never seen someone die.

But when it came to her own family, facing this situation, she lost all of the composure and calmness that she had.

But she was still hanging on staunchly.

The nightmare did not defeat her, she only cried secretly at a place without any other person.

On the surface, she was still cultivating as usual, but she had no idea what the content of her cultivation for the last few days was.

A figure appeared behind Feng Jin Huang silently, out of thin air.

"Daughter." She heard a familiar voice.

Feng Jin Huang turned around, the person was her mother, Fairy Bai Qing.

"Mother!" Feng Jin Huang could not hold it in anymore, she went into Fairy Bai Qing's embrace as she cried her lungs out.

Fairy Bai Qing consoled her for a long time before Feng Jin Huang stopped crying.

"Mother, father is so powerful, he must be alright now, am I right?" Feng Jin Huang raised her head as she looked at her mother with a hopeful expression.

But Fairy Bai Qing did not directly console her in this matter, she shook her head: "Even the invincible rank nine Gu Immortals die one day, not to mention your father. Peopleir must die eventually, Huang Er, stop crying, let mother tell you a story."

This was a story in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Legend says that Ren Zu tried to rely on the capabilities of the feathermen to save his daughter, who was still stuck inside ordinary abyss.

However, the feathermen wanted freedom, they did not want to be restricted.

Ren Zu thought of a scheme, but he failed, the feathermen would rather die than compromise their freedom.

Ren Zu fell into deep perplexity.

He could not find a better way to save his children.

The same situation applied to his eldest son, Verdant Great Sun, and also his daughter, Boundless Forest Samsara.

At this time, self Gu spoke in Ren Zu's heart: "Oh human, you want to save your son, Verdant Great Sun, I have a method."

Ren Zu thought that he had to save at least one of them, he quickly asked: "Oh? What method?"

Self Gu laughed: "All living beings in this world will die, this is because fate Gu entered the door of life and death, and left a trace behind when searching for fairness Gu. Oh human, you can enter the door of life and death, and walk on the road of life and death, as long as you do not walk on the traces of fate, you will step on a road that belongs to you solely. When you walk into the door of life and death and leave again, you will form a brand new road, that would be partway to success."

"Next, as long as you bring Verdant Great Sun onto the path that you walked on, and leave the door of life and death, you will be able to return to the human world where the sun shines. Your son, Verdant Great Sun, will be able to escape death and revive."

Ren Zu heard the method of self Gu and was very hesitant, but there was no better solution available.

Thus, he decided to let Boundless Forest Samsara stay inside ordinary abyss for a while longer, while he used the method taught by self Gu to save his eldest son, Verdant Great Sun.

Ren Zu set off towards the door of life and death, as he walked, one day, he met with a beastman.

This beastman was very muscular, his muscles were like rocks, the fangs in his mouth were sharper than blades. He took huge steps, sprinting in the wilderness as he shouted: "Don't get any closer, don't come here! I am afraid!"

Ren Zu was very curious, he asked: "Oh beastman, what are you afraid of?"

The beastman said: "I am afraid of my own shadow, it keeps following me, I cannot get rid of it. I am so afraid that I can only run around in all directions, I am tired, hungry, and thirsty, I am going to die!"

Ren Zu felt that this was funny: "Oh beastman, you have such a powerful body, yet you are afraid of a harmless shadow, do you have a cowardly heart? What is there to be afraid of?"

At this time, a Gu worm came out of the beastman's heart, it laughed at Ren Zu: "Oh human, do not speak so shamelessly. You do not feel afraid because you have not encountered me, fear Gu. Hehehehehe."

"Fear Gu?" Ren Zu took a step back, his expression changed.

Once fear Gu appeared, fear started to well up in Ren Zu's heart.

He was afraid.

Fear Gu laughed even more arrogantly now, it said to the beastman: "I will let you off now, little beastman, you pitiful worm."

The beastman was free now, it fell to the ground, weeping in extreme joy.

Fear Gu turned around, facing Ren Zu: "Oh human, you dared to look down on me, fear Gu, now I will torture you with endless fear!"

Saying this, fear Gu flew into Ren Zu's heart with a whooshing sound.

Ren Zu felt immense fear.

He was afraid of this, and afraid of that.

Fear Gu made him scared of the wind, every time the wind blew, Ren Zu screamed in horror.

Fear Gu made him afraid of sunlight, Ren Zu could only travel at night and often lost his way, during daytime he would enter caves or hide inside thick bushes.

Fear Gu also made Ren Zu afraid of tree leaves, thus Ren Zu ran away from the forests, every tree he saw made him shriek.

Fear Gu made Ren Zu afraid of snakes, in the end, Ren Zu even stopped using the grass ropes that he made himself.

After that, fear Gu made Ren Zu scared of rain.

Whenever it rained, Ren Zu would shrivel up and look at the sky that was raining continuously, feeling extreme fear.

Ren Zu wanted to go to the door of life and death, but after being struck by fear Gu, he could not move much, he could not make any progress.

When fear Gu understood Ren Zu's motive, it made Ren Zu scared of death.

Ren Zu no longer dared to walk towards the door of life and death.

Because once he entered the door of life and death, he would be walking from life towards death.

Ren Zu was afraid that he would die, he could only stay in place.

Self Gu sighed: "Oh human, actually death is not scary, the real scary thing is the fear in your heart."

"That is right!" Fear Gu heard this and said proudly: "The only thing worth being afraid of is fear!"

Fairy Bai Qing spoke this story as Feng Jin Huang was silent in her arms.

Fairy Bai Qing looked at her daughter lovingly, she said again: "Huang Er, no matter what, you have to become stronger, and face death head on! Death is not scary, everybody dies, not even a rank nine venerable is spared from it. Your father might be dead or alive. But one day, I will certainly die, and so will you. Never be defeated by the fear in your heart."

Feng Jin Huang's body shuddered.

She struggled lightly, freeing herself from her mother's warm hug.

Tears were still flickering in her eyes, but she showed determination and fortitude.

She looked at Fairy Bai Qing, gritting her teeth: "Mother, I understand! I will go cultivate now, there will be no fear in my heart, no matter how father is right now, I will not be fearful, I will face it directly, and face any possible outcome. I am Feng Jin Huang, how can I make father and mother lose face?"

"Hehehe, you are really a good child." Fairy Bai Qing concealed the worry in her eyes, her face was filled with a smile.

Actually, she was frantic internally.

Feng Jiu Ge's disappearance hugely influenced matters.

Spirit Affinity House recruited Feng Jiu Ge, allowing them to be at the lead of the ten ancient sects in this generation. The other nine sects faced some suppression in one way or another.

These were the characteristics of a society where one person could cultivate to have great strength.

The influence of one person was expanded hugely.

Right now, Feng Jiu Ge was not around, Spirit Affinity House's authority fell drastically, the other nine sects were ready to make trouble, Central Continent had deep undercurrents that could create huge tremors and drastic changes.

It was like this outside of the sect.

But within her own sect, Fairy Bai Qing also was not having an easy time.

Places with people will have competition for benefits.

Where there are sects, there is internal strife.

Feng Jiu Ge's disappearance made the ones who were had been suppressed to the lowest level able to suddenly raise their heads.

Feng Jiu Ge was too powerful, to the extent that Fairy Bai Qing had almost forgotten that there were many people in the sect who was against them.

These last days, those people had been gathering strength and ostracizing Fairy Bai Qing.

Fairy Bai Qing loved Feng Jiu Ge deeply, she wanted to go to Northern Plains and help him. But she had been controlling herself, holding down this impulse.

She had a daughter to care for, Feng Jiu Ge was so powerful but he still went missing, she could not move carelessly.

If even she was gone, what would Feng Jin Huang do?

"She is just a child!" This was Fairy Bai Qing's thoughts.

From the viewpoint of every parent, their children were always children.

Northern Plains.

Hei Cheng's headless corpse was still in the mud.

His soul was wailing, but he could not escape from Hei Lou Lan's hands.

Hei Lou Lan killed Hei Cheng and stomped on her father's head, but it was not enough. Now, Hei Cheng's soul had also been captured, he was surely going to be tortured and interrogated by Hei Lou Lan.

Meanwhile, Blazing Heaven Demoness squatted on the ground and used an immortal killer move.

A small hand of flames appeared out of nowhere, grabbing at Hei Cheng's stomach.

The small fire hand easily fused into Hei Cheng's corpse, after fiddling around for a while, it flew out while holding onto a pearl.

"This is Hei Cheng's immortal aperture, I have temporarily retrieved it. Little Lan, take it, it can only last for seven days and seven nights, once the time limit is up, my immortal killer move will stop and the immortal aperture will fuse with the outside world to form a blessed land. It is a pity that the Gu worms in the immortal aperture, be them mortal or immortal, have all been destroyed."

Blazing Heaven Demoness said as she passed the fire pearl into Hei Lou Lan's hands.

Hei Lou Lan received it silently.

Fairy Li Shan and Fang Yuan were inwardly shocked by Blazing Heaven Demoness' method.

Blazing Heaven Demoness laughed: "Don't look at me with such expressions. Hehehe, this method of taking an immortal aperture is not a skill devised originally by me. I obtained an inheritance of Immortal Kong Jue in Eastern Sea, I learned his method of retrieving apertures, and created this fire path immortal killer move."

Blazing Heaven Demoness was an extremely rare great grandmaster.

At this attainment level, it was easy to understand capabilities of other paths using their own as a foundation, her methods were very comprehensive in all aspects.

"Alright, now, we will talk about your matter, Fang Yuan." Fairy Li Shan looked towards Fang Yuan with a coldly smiling expression.

Chapter 945: Ceasefire

"Alright, now, we will talk about your matter, Fang Yuan." Fairy Li Shan looked towards Fang Yuan with a coldly smiling expression.

Fang Yuan's heart shook.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness said: "No need to rush, I am still waiting for someone."

"Oh? Who is it?" Fairy Li Shan asked in surprise.

"It is me." A voice suddenly came from nowhere.

Everyone's pupils shrunk, they turned around at lightning speed, facing the new arrival.

This person had immense capability, if he did not speak, none of them would have realized that he was so close to them.

But when they saw his appearance, everyone felt that such capability was to be expected.

"Old Ancestor Xue Hu!" Hei Lou Lan growled out.

"Lead, leader..." Fairy Li Shan's voice was hoarse and surprised.

The person's elderly face was very energetic, his snow-white beard was very thick, it extended to his toes.

Right now, all of his aura was concealed, not a trace of his might was felt, he looked like an ordinary old farmer.

But everyone was at full alertness.

Because he was the number one demonic path Gu Immortal in Northern Plains, in control of Snowy Mountain blessed land, after the battle of rank eights, some crowned him as the 'strongest rank eight Gu Immortal', Old Ancestor Xue Hu!

Facing Old Ancestor Xue Hu, only Blazing Heaven Demoness was calm and seemingly at ease: "Xue Hu, how was your harvest just now?"

Old Ancestor Xue Hu nodded, replying slowly: "Even though Hei tribe has gotten weaker over the years, it is still a super force, it has a deep foundation. This infiltration into Iron Eagle blessed land gave me great gains."

As it turned out, the four elders of Hei tribe directed the ancient battle formation Green City Rampage to chase after Hei Cheng, causing their base to be relatively unguarded.

In order to obtain more Gu refinement materials, Old Ancestor Xue Hu sneaked into Iron Eagle blessed land and looted it.

When the four elders of Hei tribe returned, he had already left with the profits.

"Snowy Mountain and Zombie Alliance are in a heated battle with constant conflicts. But just now, Blazing Heaven Demoness and Old Ancestor Xue Hu teamed up together to deal with Hei tribe?" Fang Yuan squinted, he couldn't help but raise his opinion of Blazing Heaven Demoness, seeing her in a different light.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was strong and overbearing, but what was truly fearsome were her wits.

If she did not ask Old Ancestor Xue Hu to take action, the four elders of Hei tribe would not have left, Blazing Heaven Demoness would not have been able to leave so easily.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu, who had the highest battle strength in Northern Plains, was willing to be used by Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Ultimately, the reason for this was that Blazing Heaven Demoness aimed at Old Ancestor Xue Hu's weakness. He needed lots of immortal material for Gu refinement, even though he knew he was being used, he was willing to do such a thing.

"Alright, this is the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie, and the other immortal zombies. Even though I used several of them, most are still around. I will return them to you." Old Ancestor Xue Hu waved his hand, dozens of immortal zombie bodies appeared on the ground, one of them was still sleeping, it was the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu looked at the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance physique immortal zombie with a regretful gaze.

He knew that the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance zombie had some Immortal Gu.

But these last days, even though he tried, he could not extract these Immortal Gu.

This Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie had many methods, he used an unknown immortal killer move and fell asleep. If Old Ancestor Xue Hu did something overboard, the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie would start self-detonating, and the Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture also showed signs of self-detonation.

Blazing Heaven Demoness collected and put away these immortal zombies as she said seriously: "Old Ancestor Xue Hu, you truly keep your words, then according to the agreement, Zombie Alliance will stop targeting Snowy Mountain, our battle will cease!"

Old Ancestor Xue Hu's eyes shined with light, he looked at Blazing Heaven Demoness as he said: "Blazing Heaven Demoness, it seems that you made great gains in Eastern Sea, your strength has increased tremendously. But the time path injury still plagues you, now that the four elders of Hei tribe are back in Iron Eagle blessed land, after this, they would not move out easily anymore. If you want to obtain Hei Fan's time path inheritance and settle your injury, it will be difficult. When you attack Iron Eagle blessed land in the future, I can lend a hand."

Blazing Heaven Demoness laughed heartily, she clapped: "Good! I am also looking forward to working together with you again."

Old Ancestor Xue Hu nodded, his figure slowly faded, in a few breaths' time, he vanished into thin air, like fog that dispersed under sunlight.

From start to finish, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had not taken a glance at Hei Cheng's headless corpse.

Earlier, Blazing Heaven Demoness and Old Ancestor Xue Hu had engaged in fierce combat, but now they were actually talking about future cooperation.

Having the power and capability to do anything they want, that was the power of rank eight great experts.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu was known as the strongest Gu Immortal in Northern Plains, his battle strength exceeded Blazing Heaven Demoness, but he actually gave in this time and handed over the immortal zombie captives and bodies.

He disregarded the reputation of the number one expert entirely.

But Fang Yuan felt no surprise.

Reputation was very much a secondary concern in reality, only one thing could move almost everybody in this world.

That was benefit.

Gu Immortals were humans too, they looked at benefits.

In fact, it was very common for Gu Immortals to work together.

Having cultivated to this stage, not at all an easy matter, what was the point of fighting to the death?

If there was no special reason, no Gu Immortals would do that.

All Gu Immortals want to develop themselves properly, because there was a sharp blade hanging above their heads.

This blade would descend once in a while, cutting at their necks.

If they could not endure it, they would die. If they survived it, they would still suffer a huge loss.

This blade naturally was calamities and tribulations.

The higher the Gu Immortal's cultivation level, the more terrifying the calamities and tribulations get, with greater difficulty in surviving, hope was bleak.

People like Old Ancestor Xue Hu and Blazing Heaven Demoness, these rank eight experts, were extremely cautious, they faced great danger. If they were careless, they would die under the tribulations.

Thus, rank eight Gu Immortals were all very vigilant.

Earlier, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang fought against Old Ancestor Xue Hu, but did they use all of their trump cards and full strength?

No.

Both sides were only probing each other.

In the end, Old Ancestor Xue Hu displayed methods that were superior to what they were willing to use.

That caused Yao Huang and Heavenly Lord Bai Zu to retreat. Because if they continued, the fight would escalate, and they would lose control of the situation, they would be in danger.

The fight between Zombie Alliance and Snowy Mountain blessed land was very heated, but there were few losses.

They were making a huge commotion but there were barely any consequences.

Because be it Old Ancestor Xue Hu or Blazing Heaven Demoness, they knew their limits.

Just now, both sides cooperated, it might seem abrupt, but that was not true.

Be it Blazing Heaven Demoness or Old Ancestor Xue Hu, they achieved their goals.

The former saved the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie and the other immortal zombie bodies, she completed the mission given by Zombie Alliance and successfully defended its reputation.

The latter gave in, but he plundered the base of Hei tribe, his gains were greater than the immortal zombies he lost!

The only party who had losses was the super force Hei tribe.

Hei tribe's losses were immense, but who cared?

One could say that Hei tribe was the innocent party, suffering due to the conflict between Zombie Alliance and Snowy Mountain.

But whose fault was it that the four elders of Hei tribe were schemed against?

In this world, be it Gu Immortals or mortals, it did not matter who was innocent, the only thing that mattered was who had greater strength and methods.

The strong prey on the weak, this was such a cruel and beautiful rule!

After confirming that Old Ancestor Xue Hu had left, Blazing Heaven Demoness turned around and faced Fang Yuan at long last.

"Now, we need to have a chat, Fang Yuan."

She smiled lightly, she called him Fang Yuan instead of Xing Xiang Zi.

Subconsciously, the pressure Fang Yuan felt internally intensified.

But Fang Yuan smiled confidently: "What do you have to say, I am listening."

Blazing Heaven Demoness could not help but frown.

She, Fairy Li Shan, and Hei Lou Lan had planned secretly for a long time to set up this situation, not only did they want Hei Lou Lan to fulfill her vengeance and kill Hei Cheng, they also schemed against Hei tribe and settled the battle between Zombie Alliance and Snowy Mountain. In addition, they also wanted to force Fang Yuan to relent so that they could get their way.

But now it seemed that Fang Yuan felt indifferent towards such force. He was like an eel, slipping out of their control.

Blazing Heaven Demoness did not speak, but Fairy Li Shan said in a heavy tone: "Fang Yuan, I admire you as a person, but please take a look at your situation. We can determine whether you live or die today!"

"So what?" Fang Yuan shrugged, he looked at Fairy Li Shan mockingly: "It's only death at worst. Do you think that I, the great Fang Yuan, would fear death?"

The air seemed frozen.

The scene became still.

Ever since Blazing Heaven Demoness, Fairy Li Shan, and Hei Lou Lan's relationship was exposed, Fang Yuan had been full of doubts.

What did they want to do with him?

Since Blazing Heaven Demoness knew the true identity of Xing Xiang Zi, why did she fund Fang Yuan to refine star thought Immortal Gu?

Using her rank eight battle strength, it was not hard for her to kill this bottom tier rank six immortal zombie. Why did she have to create this situation?

Next, Fang Yuan analyzed calmly, with his rich life experience, he could see the true relationship between Blazing Heaven Demoness, Fairy Li Shan, and Hei Lou Lan.

On the surface, these three seemed like a united family, very close to each other.

But in truth?

Hehehe, their relationship was quite peculiar, they were not united!

When Fang Yuan realized this, many questions that he had were answered at once.

Thus, he had some confidence just now to adopt a strong stance, negotiating with Blazing Heaven Demoness fearlessly.

Of course, he had split a portion of his focus on Spring Autumn Cicada at all times.

If this situation turned bad, he could only rely on this unreliable trump card.

But each time he used Spring Autumn Cicada, there was a chance of failure. Fang Yuan would not use it unless he had no other options.

The current situation was not so severe that he needed to use Spring Autumn Cicada.

While remaining silent, Blazing Heaven Demoness' frown became tighter.

Fang Yuan's attitude gave her a problem.

She understood that Fang Yuan had already realized her true motive.

That was self strength Immortal Gu!

Blazing Heaven Demoness was someone without limits, back then when she could not obtain the fragment world of the immemorial nine heavens, she directly destroyed it, resulting in nobody gaining anything.

She was afraid of Fang Yuan being just like that and destroying self strength Immortal Gu!

Self strength Immortal Gu was already refined by Fang Yuan, he could destroy it with a single thought.

Immortal Gu were hard to take away, if it were not for that, Blazing Heaven Demoness would not have created this situation, using a great deal of effort.

Chapter 946: Past Grudges and Hatred

In the past.

Blazing Heaven Demoness suffered from time path injuries, thus she had placed hope in Hei Fan's time path inheritance.

Thereupon, Blazing Heaven Demoness began to make arrangements, she took charge of Su tribe, changed her third sister's name to Su Xian Er and intentionally made her approach Hei Cheng to enter Hei tribe.

Hei Cheng and Su Xian Er were both in love with each other, becoming a Gu Immortal couple, and Su Xian's Night Elopement thus became a famous story.

Su Xian Er did not forget her task and tried to find out information of Hei Fan's inheritance, but she gradually exposed her traces in the process. Hei tribe began investigating and got knowledge of Fairy Li Shan, making them think this was Snowy Mountain's plot.

Su Xian Er, however, was truly in love with Hei Cheng, so she did not leave Hei tribe. Afterwards, Hei Cheng secretly killed Su Xian Er and prolonged his life.

After learning of their younger sister's sacrifice, Blazing Heaven Demoness and Fairy Li Shan felt incomparable grief.

Fairy Li Shan blamed Blazing Heaven Demoness and believed she was the reason for their sister's death. Later on, Fairy Li Shan completely fell out with Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Blazing Heaven Demoness felt ashamed and guilty, but she was heavily injured and could not take revenge. She had also taken position as the leader of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, she could not act independently easily, and could only go far away towards Eastern Sea.

When she passed the regional wall, it was a nearly fatal experience.

In Eastern Sea, she gradually had some fortuitous encounters from the clues she had gathered at Northern Plains. For instance, an inheritance left behind by Old Immortal Kong Jue allowed Blazing Heaven Demoness to have a method of seizing another person's immortal aperture.

These fortuitous encounters provided great help to Blazing Heaven Demoness and partially alleviated her injuries.

For a long time, Fairy Li Shan did not contact Blazing Heaven Demoness.

But when Fairy Li Shan took in Hei Lou Lan, instructed and helped her cultivate, and saw her growth, Fairy Li Shan gradually began to let go of her hatred.

She hoped Hei Lou Lan could receive better help and support.

Recently, Fairy Li Shan had completely calmed down and began to use information path methods to contact Blazing Heaven Demoness, both sides started to communicate with each other.

Blazing Heaven Demoness thus learned of Xing Xiang Zi's identity and began to scheme.

Because Fang Yuan just happened to need star thought Immortal Gu; Blazing Heaven Demoness was able to smoothly set an agreement with Fang Yuan.

When she made use of Zombie Alliance's power to return to Northern Plains, she wanted to resolve her countless years of shame and guilt to Hei Lou Lan.

She wanted to use all her strength to make it up to Hei Lou Lan, she wanted to make up for the mistakes she made in the past!

She viewed things through Hei Lou Lan's perspective and thought of ways to support her.

What was most important to Hei Lou Lan?

Without doubt, it was self strength Immortal Gu.

First of all, Hei Lou Lan possessed the Great Strength True Martial Physique and cultivated strength path, self strength Immortal Gu was a strength path Immortal Gu and was perfect for Hei Lou Lan.

Second, self strength Immortal Gu was an inheritance given to Hei Lou Lan by Su Xian Er; as far as Hei Lou Lan was concerned, it was not just a rank six Immortal Gu, it was an extremely important keepsake of her mother!

Thus, Blazing Heaven Demoness thought of every way possible to take self strength Immortal Gu back for Hei Lou Lan.

But she encountered a problem.

From the communication with Fairy Li Shan, Blazing Heaven Demoness got an understanding of Fang Yuan.

She was startled and wary of Fang Yuan's craftiness, and also saw her own image in him.

On one hand, Fang Yuan was very proficient in scheming, on the other hand, Fang Yuan could take life threatening risks and was not afraid of death.

In pleasant words, it was bravery. In ugly words, it was thuggish and unscrupulous behavior. If I can't get benefits, you also can stop dreaming about them. If you want to fight, then come, it is just death at worst.

This attitude was like that of Blazing Heaven Demoness, destroying a fragment world of the immemorial nine heavens.

As a result, Blazing Heaven Demoness had agreed to help Fang Yuan refine an Immortal Gu and set an agreement with him —

Blazing Heaven Demoness would help fund Fang Yuan with immortal materials, but Fang Yuan would be in debt to her. Whether he succeeded or not in refining the Immortal Gu, he would need to pay her back later. The longer he dragged this on, the more interest Blazing Heaven Demoness would receive. If Fang Yuan successfully refines the Immortal Gu but fails to return her the sum in a hundred years, then Blazing Heaven Demoness would be allowed to take any one Immortal Gu from Fang Yuan as compensation.

"Any one Immortal Gu" was the key.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was targeting the self strength Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan possessed..

Right now, as she saw Fang Yuan's attitude, Blazing Heaven Demoness raised her eyebrows and spoke frankly: "Right, I want self strength Immortal Gu. Return the Immortal Gu to Little Lan, it was hers after all."

If she could directly take it, Blazing Heaven Demoness would have already done so and absolutely would not have gone through such trouble.

But even if she was a fire path great grandmaster, she could not forcibly take Immortal Gu.

The Immortal Gu was already refined by Fang Yuan, and could be destroyed instantly with just a thought from him.

Like Old Ancestor Xue Hu who had extremely strong attainment in ice path, but had no way to take the mysterious Immortal Gu inside the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie.

Unless they were a wisdom path Gu Immortal who suppressed Fang Yuan and made sure he could not take action in thinking, or someone who had great accomplishment in theft path.

Theft path was created by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

His signature immortal killer move formless hand was feared by countless Gu Immortals.

Blazing Heaven Demoness, Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan did not have wisdom path methods and theft path was a not a mainstream path, despite it being created by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, besides him, other cultivators of theft path were generally not able to achieve anything significant.

If Blazing Heaven Demoness and the others had theft path methods, they could directly steal the Immortal Gu from Fang Yuan's aperture, given they had set this up, the possibility of this was very small.

Especially when Fang Yuan had wisdom path attainment, Blazing Heaven Demoness felt even more cautious regarding taking action.

Blazing Heaven Demoness directly demanded self strength Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan remained silent.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' reason was not very justifiable.

Fang Yuan had obtained self strength Immortal Gu fair and square, if he had not saved Hei Lou Lan, she would have already lost her life in the dream realm.

It could be said that Fang Yuan was Hei Lou Lan's benefactor.

However, Fang Yuan did not want to speak of this.

Such words were useless, why would there be discussion about benevolence with those of fierce character?

Moreover, back then when Fang Yuan helped Hei Lou Lan, he also did not hold any good intentions.

If he talked about this, Blazing Heaven Demoness and the others would instead look down on him.

'A bigger fist is the best and the strongest reason. If I were stronger, I would not need to fear Blazing Heaven Demoness' extortion. Unfortunately, I cannot even escape right now. My cultivation is stagnant, my strength is too low!'

Fang Yuan was self-aware.

He knew it was impossible for him to not hand over self strength Immortal Gu.

In the current situation, the enemy was strong while he was weak, like meat on the chopping block. But it was not that he did not have any cards in his hands.

'Firstly, there is the previous agreement. The agreement states allies cannot harm each other. But Fairy Li Shan is an information path Gu Immortal, she had openly violated the agreement when we invaded Dong Fang tribe's blessed land. The value of this is rather small.'

'Secondly, Immortal Gu are not easy to plunder. It is because of this that Blazing Heaven Demoness and the others had to make arrangements to trap me. But the value of this can only be at a middling level, I cannot overestimate its use. Blazing Heaven Demoness has the ability to capture me alive, if she put aside all considerations and decided to do so, wouldn't I be like that Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie that fell into Old Ancestor Xue Hu's hands?'

'Thirdly, there is Purple Mountain True Monarch. Hei Lou Lan and others don't know this is only a lie. Earlier, I used this lie to deceive Tai Bai Yun Sheng. But who could have thought it would instead become my greatest trump card at this moment.'

Fang Yuan was not wrong.

After Blazing Heaven Demoness knew of Purple Mountain True Monarch, she treated such information with great importance.

She was quite wary of this mysterious Purple Mountain True Monarch.

If Purple Mountain True Monarch was a rank eight Gu Immortal, and she captured his beloved disciple, the trouble stirred up in the future would not be small. Blazing Heaven Demoness had just approached Old Ancestor Xue Hu and sought to trouble him, she naturally did not want herself to fall into the same situation.

Even if Purple Mountain True Monarch was only rank seven, he still had many disciples. Fang Yuan claimed he was only a junior disciple and had senior disciples above him.

Especially when this Purple Mountain True Monarch was extremely resourceful, he could arrange his disciple to enter Immortal Crane Sect.

But did Purple Mountain True Monarch really exist?

Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan were completely in the dark, and Blazing Heaven Demoness, who obtained information from them, also was deceived by this.

Fang Yuan's silence made Blazing Heaven Demoness slightly impatient as she urged: "Fang Yuan, what requests do you have, say them, we can talk."

Fang Yuan let out a breath, he had already planned it all inwardly.

But he did not reply to Blazing Heaven Demoness' question, instead asking: "Those Gu refinement immortal materials you gave me to refine star thought Immortal Gu, did you tamper with them?"

Blazing Heaven Demoness smiled: "Of course."

She actually admitted it!

Moreover, she did not have even a trace of embarrassment on her face.

Fang Yuan frowned: "Actually, I had suspected this, but every time I refined Gu, I inspected the immortal materials carefully, why was I not able to find anything amiss?"

Blazing Heaven Demoness replied: "That is because your fire path attainment has not reached great grandmaster level. I added a trace of fire path dao marks on each fire path immortal material. The increase is very small, but it accumulates with every immortal material used, and takes substantial effect during the refinement process, ruining the Gu refinement."

Blazing Heaven Demoness naturally had to do this.

If Fang Yuan succeeded in refining, how could she coerce Fang Yuan?

Fang Yuan did not nag about this issue, he nodded and continued: "I can return self strength Immortal Gu, but I have some conditions."

Hearing this, Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan's hopes were raised.

Blazing Heaven Demoness looked at Fang Yuan with slight surprise, and clapped: "Now I can somewhat understand why little sister wanted to suppress you. Speak, what are your requests?"

"First of all, I want to form a new agreement."

This agreement was the assurance for his safety. Although Fairy Li Shan was an information path Gu Immortal and could have unknown methods to break the agreement, she would need to make preparations before doing so. At least during that period, Fang Yuan could escape safely.

"This is a must." Blazing Heaven Demoness agreed.

Fang Yuan continued: "Secondly, my debt of the immortal materials you lent to me before will be cleared."

"As long as you return self strength Immortal Gu, this won't be a problem." Blazing Heaven Demoness replied straightforwardly.

"I want to leave Zombie Alliance, and get rid of the alliance agreement with them."

"Okay."

"Finally, I want strength path immortal zombie corpses. You need to promise me that you will do your utmost to get me as many strength path immortal zombie corpses as possible." Fang Yuan's eyes shined brightly.

Chapter 947: Nirvana Fire

Hei Lou Lan had Blazing Heaven Demoness protecting her, Fang Yuan could no longer target her.

If he could not obtain a super grade blessed land, a high grade blessed land was still very good.

To achieve that, Fang Yuan needed a large number of ordinary strength path immortal zombie bodies. And in Northern Plains, who else could obtain more immortal zombie bodies than Blazing Heaven Demoness?

Of course, Fang Yuan gave a valid sounding excuse: "If I give self strength Immortal Gu to you, I will not have a useful strength path Immortal Gu with me. I need to refine a strength path Immortal Gu to replace it. The Immortal Gu recipe that I have needs a large number of strength path immortal zombie bodies."

This excuse perfectly concealed the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method, Blazing Heaven Demoness could not reject him either.

Blazing Heaven Demoness frowned deeply.

If she agreed, she would have a pay a huge price.

Earlier, Old Ancestor Xue Hu handed over some immortal zombies, a large number of strength path immortal zombies were among them. But if she gave them to Fang Yuan, Blazing Heaven Demoness' contribution to Zombie Alliance would be greatly diminished.

Immortal zombies were very particular about preserving their corpses after dying.

This was the last bit of pride they had.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu targeted the immortal zombie graveyard, that caused Zombie Alliance to mobilize their forces to deal with this rank eight expert, going into a state of frenzy disregarding the cost. That was because immortal zombie bodies were the bottom line of Zombie Alliance, anyone who targets them will face the vengeance of Zombie Alliance!

Old Ancestor Xue Hu understood this as well.

After the matter was exposed, even though he obtained a large number of immortal zombie bodies, he kept many of them without using them, leaving behind a way to settle the situation.

Blazing Heaven Demoness thought: "I can give the strength path immortal zombie bodies to Fang Yuan. This matter can be blamed on Old Ancestor Xue Hu, nobody will suspect me. But the problem is, Fang Yuan wants to use immortal zombie bodies to refine Immortal Gu!"

Immortal Gu were hard to refine, it was normal to fail.

Blazing Heaven Demoness shook her head, she said to Fang Yuan: "If you keep failing in your refinement, would I have to provide you immortal zombie bodies unceasingly? That is impossible! As the leader of the Zombie Alliance branch, I am stealing from the inside, if I get exposed, the consequences are severe. How about this, you can give me a number, if it is reasonable, I will consider it."

Fang Yuan thought about it and gave a number.

Blazing Heaven Demoness immediately rejected him, the number was too large, it was too risky for even her to obtain this many strength path immortal zombie bodies.

Next, both sides negotiated and eventually reached a consensus.

Fang Yuan obtained a number of strength path immortal zombies that greatly exceeded the requirements for a high grade blessed land. But on the surface, he pretended to be dissatisfied: "This is only enough for me to do three attempts at Gu refinement..."

Fairy Li Shan snorted coldly: "Fang Yuan, I urge you not to get an inch and ask for a mile."

Fang Yuan chuckled, he looked at Fairy Li Shan: "Back then, when Hei Lou Lan was trapped in the dream realm, why didn't you have this attitude?"

These words made Fairy Li Shan slightly awkward.

She was not as shameless as Blazing Heaven Demoness.

"Talking more is pointless, we can form the new agreement now. Once the agreement is created, I will return self strength Immortal Gu to you." Fang Yuan continued.

"Wait." Blazing Heaven Demoness waved her hand: "Earlier, you stated your conditions, now, it is my turn."

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly internally, he knew that Blazing Heaven Demoness was not so easy to deal with.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness' words made Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan extremely surprised.

"I am willing to fund you to refine star thought Immortal Gu, I will not do anything to the immortal materials this time."

Fang Yuan heard this and did not feel joy, he squinted as he went into high alert.

Seeing Fang Yuan's vigilant state, Blazing Heaven Demoness smiled, she said: "Fang Yuan, I know that you have been looking for a revival method to get rid of your immortal zombie state, look at this!"

Saying so, Blazing Heaven Demoness' body started to burn in raging flames.

Orange-yellow flames covered Blazing Heaven Demoness' entire body.

But the strange thing was, it was not hot, it was filled with life force and could give observers a feeling of warmth and hope.

It seemed harmless, but Fang Yuan took a few steps back vigilantly.

Next, his eyes opened wide as he witnessed an unbelievable sight.

In the burning flames, Blazing Heaven Demoness' immortal zombie body started to change.

First, her five meter tall zombie body shrunk rapidly, returning to a normal person's height.

Next, her skin which was rough and dark like tree bark vanished in the flames, white and tender skin appeared on her, like a freshly peeled egg.

Next, her immortal zombie hair, which looked like messy red wheat stalks, turned long and slim, the red color was vibrant and warm.

Finally, Blazing Heaven Demoness' entire figure went through a complete transformation.

From a scary giant zombie, she turned into a beautiful woman wearing a red dress, she had tender skin, sharp features, her gaze was energetic, and her lips were bright red.

Her chest was busty, it could be barely be contained, her legs were slim and long, yet they were also not thin.

Most strikingly, her hair extended to waist length, it was burning red, giving off a dream-like feeling, vibrant and overflowing with colors.

In this wondrous flame, Blazing Heaven Demoness had performed an amazing display in front of Fang Yuan.

She turned from an immortal zombie to a living person!

Her entire aura also became stronger. Like a gently burning flame, becoming larger and giving off loud noises, other than giving people a sense of liveliness, her aura was also more overbearing.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' face became more rosy, but Fairy Li Shan showed worry on her face: "Big sister, be careful of your injury!"

Blazing Heaven Demoness understood this of course, the price she paid for this was not small, but seeing Fang Yuan's shining eyes and intense desire, she felt that it was worth it.

Thus, she extinguished the flame on her body and used Gu worms, turning her body taller and transforming from a beauty into a monster, becoming an immortal zombie again.

Blazing Heaven Demoness said: "I have a time path injury on my body that causes my ageing to accelerate hundreds of times. Without any choice, I had to become an immortal zombie. But you saw earlier that I can revive easily, changing between the immortal zombie and living Gu Immortal states. This is because of the immortal killer move that I used earlier — Nirvana Fire!"

"Nirvana fire?" Fang Yuan felt some hope internally.

Earlier, he did not care about it, because he already had the best revival method there was.

But hearing Blazing Heaven Demoness' words, Fang Yuan still was greatly excited.

"Using the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method, I will turn into an ordinary Gu Immortal completely. My remaining lifespan will decrease accordingly. I cannot use wisdom Gu after that, since my lifespan would be consumed rapidly under the light of wisdom. Furthermore, each immortal aperture can only use the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method once, it cannot be repeated."

"If I can obtain this revival method and interchange between the states of immortal zombie and living Gu Immortal, that would be excellent! I would be able to use wisdom Gu more optimally!"

Blazing Heaven Demoness observed his expression, seeing that Fang Yuan was interested, she added chips to her side of the bargain.

She took out a mortal Gu, saying to Fang Yuan: "This is my third request, you have to accept this gift."

If it were an ordinary mortal Gu, Fang Yuan would not take even a glance at it.

But Fang Yuan could not look away from this mortal Gu that Blazing Heaven Demoness took out.

The reason was simple, this mortal Gu was so valuable even rank nine venerables looked for it painstakingly.

This was a lifespan Gu!

Blazing Heaven Demoness continued: "Fang Yuan, I know that you have little lifespan left, this lifespan Gu can give you sixty years of life, after you change back, you will not be old."

Fang Yuan sighed to himself deeply.

Blazing Heaven Demoness gave three conditions.

The first was to help Fang Yuan refine star thought Immortal Gu, and she promised that she would not tamper with the materials.

The second was to give Fang Yuan a revival method, most importantly, this revival method allowed Fang Yuan to turn into an immortal zombie freely and use wisdom Gu fully.

The third was a sixty year lifespan Gu, it was a treasure that Fang Yuan had been looking for.

Rather than saying these three requests were Blazing Heaven Demoness' conditions, they were more like bait that she was laying out in front of Fang Yuan.

Facing such huge temptation, Fang Yuan felt excited, at the same time, his mood was heavy.

He knew that Blazing Heaven Demoness was doing this for a reason.

Thus, he cupped his fists at Blazing Heaven Demoness, saying seriously: "I cannot reject Blazing Heaven Demoness' conditions. Please continue stating them."

Fang Yuan could not reject her.

Because he did not have the strength to do so.

"Hahaha." Blazing Heaven Demoness raised her head and laughed, Fang Yuan understood the situation he was in, she was very pleased and finally stated her true objectives.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had six true conditions.

First, she wanted Fang Yuan to give her all of his eerie fire dragon pythons.

Second, she wanted to enter into the guts Gu business, and become the largest buyer in the guts Gu trades.

Third, and the most important of them, she wanted Tai Bai Yun Sheng to cooperate with her using Man as Before and Landscape as Before, to try and heal the time path injury that she had.

Fourth, she wanted to be able to borrow Fang Yuan's Fixed Immortal Travel from now on to return to Eastern Sea.

Fifth, she wanted Fang Yuan to make a deduction for her each year for free. The content could be related to finding Immortal Gu, deducing incomplete Immortal Gu recipes, and others.

Sixth, if possible, she wanted to meet Fang Yuan's master, Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Fang Yuan thought about this thoroughly.

He could agree to the first request, eerie fire dragon pythons were related to fire path, they might be useful to Blazing Heaven Demoness, but Fang Yuan could do without them.

The second request was for Blazing Heaven Demoness to enter into the guts Gu trade and become a larger buyer than Immortal Crane Sect and Spirit Affinity House, Fang Yuan could accept this. With Blazing Heaven Demoness' funding, perhaps the guts Gu trade would expand even further.

For the third request, if Fang Yuan talked to Tai Bai Yun Sheng he would not reject it. But Man as Before and Landscape as Before could not fall into Blazing Heaven Demoness' hands.

The fourth request involving Fixed Immortal Travel was similar. Fang Yuan would not lend the Immortal Gu, at most, he would go along with Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Fang Yuan directly agreed to the fifth request.

The sixth request was nothing but Blazing Heaven Demoness trying to probe into Fang Yuan's background and the force behind him. This was impossible! Purple Mountain True Monarch did not exist, he was made up by Fang Yuan!

Chapter 948: Attitude Gu!

Central Continent, Heavenly Court.

The silver light in the sky seemed everlasting and indestructible. There were many halls on the ground, but there was silence, without any person around.

There was an old tower standing tall and proud among the halls.

This tower was covered in blemishes, it had over three million years of history.

It was very famous, the Immortal Gu House that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable created herself — Heaven Overseeing Tower!

There was a huge refinement path Gu formation around Heaven Overseeing Tower.

In the four cores of the Gu formation, there were four rank eight Gu Immortals respectively, three male and one female, one old looking and three young.

At this moment, seeing that the huge Gu formation was gradually coming to a halt, the four Heavenly Court Gu Immortals let out deep breaths, their tense minds calmed down.

Once they relaxed, Lian Jiu Sheng's body wavered, he could not stand upright, he sat down on the ground directly.

The others were not any better.

Bai Cang Shui's head was full of sweat, while Bi Chen Tian was pale. Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's aged face had even deeper wrinkles than before.

Any of these four people, if they went outside, would be huge characters in Central Continent, or famous experts even in the five regions.

But at this moment, they were all exhausted, it was as if they were extremely hungry, after having fought strong foes for three hundred days, without any rest or sleep.

After all, how could repairing the rank nine Immortal Gu Fate be so easy?

Thinking about the difficulties when activating the Gu formation, Bai Cang Shui and the others felt immensely glad.

One crucial step in repairing Fate was to draw in heaven's will.

Heaven's will was grand and vast, a human's will was small and insignificant compared to it. The four Gu Immortals endured much hardship to maintain their consciousness amidst the inflow of heaven's will, under this situation minutes felt like years, they lasted for several hundred days and eventually succeeded.

"Good! Just now was a great success for repairing fate Immortal Gu. Everyone has worked hard." Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord carried his walking stick as he slowly got up, he looked at the Gu formation in the center with much joy, as fate Immortal Gu floated above it.

This fate Immortal Gu was like a black and white spider. The red wound on its body had already shrunken by thirty percent.

"We finally succeeded." Bi Chen Tian sighed.

"Now that we succeeded, fate Gu can already use fifty percent of its strength. Even if it is outside of Heaven Overseeing Tower, it can start to show some effect!" Lian Jiu Sheng said excitedly.

"Oh? What effect?" Bai Cang Shui asked in puzzlement.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord was extremely tired, but he smiled and said: "The effect of fate Immortal Gu is fate itself. You have to know: All living beings in this world have certain paths in life that they follow, they cannot be allowed to change. After Red Lotus Demon Venerable harmed fate Immortal Gu, the world went into chaos! Right now, fate Immortal Gu has already recovered fifty percent of its strength, with its existence, the world is already starting to adjust itself. All of those who derailed from their original path before this, even if they took a huge detour, will start to move towards their original fate, and continue on that path!"

At this moment, in Northern Plains.

Blazing Heaven Demoness listed her true intentions.

After considering them, Fang Yuan replied to Blazing Heaven Demoness.

He did not directly reject the sixth request, he said he that he could not directly make the decision for such a thing. He would try to inform his master, Purple Mountain True Monarch, but whether he would show up or not was the master's decision.

Blazing Heaven Demoness expressed her understanding.

After both sides reached a consensus, the heavy atmosphere eased slightly.

After patiently negotiating, both sides set a new agreement.

This alliance agreement was hard to break. Fang Yuan used his previous life's experiences to avoid loopholes in the alliance agreement and increasing the difficulties of breaking it.

Fang Yuan estimated that even if Fairy Li Shan had information path great grandmaster attainment level, she would still need at least two to three years to break the agreement.

Moreover, Fairy Li Shan was not an information path great grandmaster.

After setting the alliance agreement, Fang Yuan's safety was assured, he followed the agreement and handed over self strength Immortal Gu to Hei Lou Lan.

Even though he lost self strength Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan was satisfied with the results.

In fact, Blazing Heaven Demoness was not overbearing in this negotiation.

Of course, if Fang Yuan refused to hand over self strength Immortal Gu, then that would be another story.

Fang Yuan made great gains this time.

All in all, this was a fair exchange of benefits.

Blazing Heaven Demoness did not try to lay her hands on Fang Yuan's Hu Immortal blessed land, Star Form blessed land, Dang Hun Mountain, or Fixed Immortal Travel. She did not even mention Fairy Li Shan's time luck Immortal Gu.

This showed that she was truly sincere in cooperating with Fang Yuan.

Be it his wisdom path attainment, Fixed Immortal Travel or other aspects, Fang Yuan had very great value if used.

After achieving a mutually beneficial result by cooperating, Blazing Heaven Demoness would not strike forcefully.

After all, in her mind, Fang Yuan was backed by Purple Mountain True Monarch.

After Hei Lou Lan received self strength Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan purposely let go of it, and she successfully refined it rapidly.

It had finally returned to her, Hei Lou Lan sighed as she used the Immortal Gu.

At once, her body shook as three strength path phantoms appeared.

These three phantoms were not burly and rough-looking men like before, they were similar to Hei Lou Lan's own appearance, they were all peerless beauties.

Fairy Li Shan was overjoyed at this: "Little Lan, you have finally unraveled the biggest obstacle in your heart, and found your true self!"

Hei Lou Lan nodded in joy.

When she killed Hei Cheng personally, she felt refreshed, her breathing became more relaxed, and she felt like she had started a new life.

The strength path phantoms in front of her were proof.

Hei Lou Lan smiled and laughed, she turned towards Blazing Heaven Demoness: "Elder aunt, don't you want Hei Fan's time path inheritance? I can help you."

Blazing Heaven Demoness heard Hei Lou Lan calling her 'elder aunt' and trembled from excitement.

She knew that Hei Lou Lan actually hated her.

After all, if it were not for her injury, Hei Lou Lan's mother would not have exposed herself during the course of events when undercover in Hei tribe.

In a way, Blazing Heaven Demoness could be considered the killer of Hei Lou Lan's mother.

Hei Lou Lan continued: "Next, I will return to Hei tribe by infiltrating it. I will find Hei Fan's inheritance, and obtain it afterwards."

"No!" Blazing Heaven Demoness and Fairy Li Shan shouted in disagreement.

Hei Lou Lan's words made them severely shocked.

Back then, Su Xian Er died because of this. Hei Lou Lan wanted to walk on Su Xian Er's former path, how could her two aunts allow tragedy to strike again?

"Don't worry, I have already planned this for a long time."

Hei Lou Lan expected their reactions, she placed her arms behind her as she walked slowly, analyzing calmly: "Times are different now. The four elders of Hei tribe would not leave their base easily after this battle. With Hei Cheng's death, Hei tribe's reputation has sunken, in the following days, many super forces will collaborate and deal with Hei tribe. With Hei tribe's current strength, they cannot hold onto so many resources anymore. This is a rare opportunity! I will get into Hei tribe and obtain the highest authority, it is time this super force had a new owner!"

Hei Lou Lan had great ambition, even Fang Yuan was shocked at her goals.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu only wanted to steal some resources, he even hid himself during the process, fearful of Hei tribe's revenge. But Hei Lou Lan actually wanted to take over all of Hei tribe.

"It is too dangerous!" Fairy Li Shan shook her head.

"I will not allow it." Blazing Heaven Demoness spoke plainly, but she showed off a stance that did not allow rebuking.

Hei Lou Lan looked at her aunts fearlessly, she smiled: "I know that you are concerned about me, but I'm afraid you have the wrong idea. This is my decision, I am not discussing it with you. You can refuse to cooperate with me, but you cannot interfere with my choice."

Fairy Li Shan and Blazing Heaven Demoness looked at each other speechlessly.

Hei Lou Lan knew that it was hard to accomplish this goal herself, but if she had the help of both her aunts, along with Fang Yuan's strength, it would be of huge help to her, the danger would be lower, and she would have a higher chance of succeeding.

"Fine, I will give you some assurance." Hei Lou Lan said, taking out a mask.

This mask was emanating with the aura of an Immortal Gu.

"Attitude Gu?" At once, Fairy Li Shan stared with wide opened eyes.

Fang Yuan's gaze was fixed onto this mask.

Attitude Gu was a legendary Immortal Gu, it was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, and also one of the Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan was searching for.

That was because attitude Gu was the core Immortal Gu of familiar face.

Fang Yuan had the modified immortal killer move vaguely familiar face, if he fused attitude Gu into it, his disguise would surely be at a higher level.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had a puzzled look: "This Gu was once in Hei Fan's hands, Hei Fan doted on his granddaughter, Hei Feng Yue, and gave attitude Gu to her. Hei Feng Yue was a spoiled brat, as a mortal, she brought the Immortal Gu to roam the icy plain. In the end, she was targeted by a mysterious Gu Immortal and vanished. Attitude Gu also disappeared as a result, and never showed up again."

Hei Lou Lan's lips curled up, she toyed around with attitude Gu: "That's right, I obtained this attitude Gu from the icy plain."

Fairy Li Shan was curious: "Little Lan, when did you go to the icy plain? Wait, unless..."

"That's right, I purposely went to the northern icy plain for my immortal ascension because I had clues of attitude Gu's whereabouts. That was the only way I could subdue attitude Gu, by borrowing the heavenly might of the tribulation. Haha, I will not talk about the specific details." Hei Lou Lan explained.

Fairy Li Shan was surprised.

She assessed Hei Lou Lan again, feeling complex emotions, she was both happy and dejected.

Nobody found out that Hei Lou Lan had obtained attitude Gu, and she did not tell anyone either. Even Fairy Li Shan was kept in the dark.

"This child has grown up after all." Blazing Heaven Demoness sighed internally.

Hei Lou Lan wore the mask, saying plainly: "From now onwards, I am Fairy Black Moon."

Blazing Heaven Demoness clapped and smiled: "Excellent! With attitude Gu as well as the genuine Hei tribe bloodline, this matter might very well succeed!"

Fang Yuan was shocked.

"Hei Lou Lan is Fairy Black Moon?!"

Chapter 949: Divine Concealment

Fang Yuan observed Hei Lou Lan closely.

Hei Lou Lan's appearance had changed greatly after wearing the mask.

Clad in black and gold armored martial attire, with short hair and bright eyes, a heroic and domineering aura radiated around her and gave an oppressive sensation to others.

She unexpectedly looked almost the same as Fairy Black Moon's appearance, which Fang Yuan had seen in the records from Central Continent back in his previous life.

'Attitude Gu influences not my eyes, but my mind. Right now, the person I am looking at is still Hei Lou Lan wearing attitude Gu, but my mind is perceiving her as a different person. This is far too huge of a coincidence, it seems Hei Lou Lan is undoubtedly Fairy Black Moon!'

Fang Yuan was convinced of this, understanding the hidden inside details of his previous life.

In his previous life, Hei Lou Lan had become the winner of the Imperial Court contest, according to history, she was a tyrant and was later assassinated.

But in fact, she had not died.

She joined Central Continent's Spirit Affinity House and became the next generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House. And later, she returned to Northern Plains, leading Central Continent's Gu Immortals, wrecking Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and destroying the spiritual pillar of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

If that was the case, how was Hei Lou Lan able to get in touch with Spirit Affinity House?

Fang Yuan immediately thought of Mo Yao's will.

Hei Lou Lan won in the Imperial Court contest, entered Imperial Court blessed land and obtained Mo Yao's will. And under the influence of Mo Yao's will, she joined Spirit Affinity House.

As for how big of an influence Mo Yao's will was, Fang Yuan was not sure.

His intuition told him that this guess should be the truth of history during his previous life.

It was only that in this life, because of Fang Yuan's interference, the whole situation was thrown into disorder. Mo Yao's will influenced Fang Yuan and almost caused him to die.

"So when I was in Northern Plains, I had already caused a huge influence to the future of Central Continent. Sure enough, the butterfly effect is beyond imagination. But now, Hei Lou Lan is still in Northern Plains, if so, who will Spirit Affinity House appoint as the next generation fairy? Will it be Feng Jin Huang?"

Fang Yuan let his thoughts wander.

He felt that since Hei Lou Lan was no longer involved, Feng Jin Huang was the most likely candidate to inherit the position of the next generation fairy.

...

"Zhao Lian Yun, you can be the next generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House — as long as you successfully obtain this inheritance!" Standing in front of the Thieving Heaven inheritance's entrance, a wisdom path Gu Immortal of Spirit Affinity House, Xu Hao, spoke to Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun gazed at the huge entrance of light with a resolute expression: "I don't care about being the next generation fairy, I only want to save brother Ma Hong Yun as quickly as possible!"

Illusory Fairy Li Jun Ying stood beside Xu Hao, revealing a slight smile as she heard this.

She softly stroked Zhao Lian Yun's cheek, revealing a bewitching smile: "Cute little sister, this is a Thieving Heaven inheritance. As long as you can successfully inherit it, you will be very likely to have the power to save your lover."

Zhao Lian Yun blushed, her eyes, however, were sober and calm.

She was an otherworldly demon, a transmigrator, she was not so easy to deceive.

Zhao Lian Yun persisted in asking: "I am only a mortal, can this inheritance immediately let me ascend and become a Gu Immortal?"

"Ah..." The female Gu Immortal, Li Jun Ying, did not have an answer to this, in fact, she also did not know the specific contents of the inheritance.

She glanced at the male Gu Immortal Xu Hao, before continuing: "Even if you can't immediately become a Gu Immortal, by obtaining Thieving Heaven's inheritance, you will become the strongest competitor for the position of the next generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House. Don't underestimate this position. As long as you succeed, you can borrow the sect's strength to save your lover. Our Spirit Affinity House is one of the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, only super forces like ours can match up to Old Ancestor Xue Hu and save your brother Ma Hong Yun."

"I understand." Zhao Lian Yun nodded and did not speak any further, taking a firm step forward into the entrance of light and disappearing within.

"Do you think she can succeed?" Illusory Fairy Li Jun Ying let out a sigh, and asked with a worried expression.

Xu Hao, however, was confident: "We have already confirmed that Zhao Lian Yun is an otherworldly demon, if even she can't succeed, who can?"

He continued: "I know you are worried the inheritance will have difficult tests, and Zhao Lian Yun might not be able to pass them since she is only a mortal. But you don't know much about this aspect. After these last years of research, I have already confirmed what the qualification for Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable inheritance tests are - as long as one is an otherworldly demon, they can easily obtain his inheritance, and there are no other dangerous tests. I just don't know how much Zhao Lian Yun can grow by inheriting this."

Li Jun Ying felt at ease at her husband's words: "I wouldn't be surprised even if Zhao Lian Yun were to immediately advance to a Gu Immortal. After all, this is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's arrangement."

"Hehe, compared to ascending to immortal, I want his formless hand more. Back then, if only I had a slightly stronger immortal killer move, I would not have been defeated by Feng Jiu Ge." Xu Hao's fists were clenched as he said this, his eyes flickering with a vague light of hatred.

No organization would lack internal strife, Spirit Affinity House naturally was not an exception.

After Feng Jiu Ge disappeared, many Gu Immortals of Spirit Affinity House tacitly agreed to trouble Fairy Bai Qing.

And Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying, this couple were the most important people in the 'anti-Feng' faction.

Li Jun Ying consoled her husband: "Heaven's Envy Manor had sent the news of the deaths of Ao Xue and Ling Mei. And Feng Jiu Ge has been missing for so long, he might already be dead as well. Why would you be bothered by a dead person?"

Xu Hao discontentedly gritted his teeth: "Hmph, in the past, Feng Jiu Ge had such might that almost anything he said in the sect was carried out automatically, suppressing us for so many years. I was dispatched to comprehend the Thieving Heaven inheritance, this was also him removing me from a seat of power. But it was fortunate, I became the person who has the most understanding of Thieving Heaven's inheritances, and have the highest authority regarding this matter. Otherwise, how could we have openly taken charge of Zhao Lian Yun?"

Li Jun Ying repeatedly nodded: "At present, Feng Jin Huang is the top candidate for the next generation's fairy, but Zhao Lian Yun's appearance is a new variable, becoming the competitor with the highest threat to Feng Jin Huang. If we could support her to rise to the status, we would not only be able to suppress that slut Bai Qing, but also can make use of it to regain authority."

Zhao Lian Yun was just newly arrived, but had already fallen into the power struggle within Spirit Affinity House, becoming a powerful weapon for Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying to fight for authority.

As the saying goes: In this world, people often had no control of the situation.

Xu Hao was just about to say something when his gaze suddenly focused, becoming very surprised: "Huh? She came out so quickly!"

In front of the two immortals, Zhao Lian Yun's figure gradually appeared from thin air.

Xu Hao hurriedly asked: "The Thieving Heaven inheritance has disappeared, this means she has succeeded! Is it really so simple?"

Even if he had done deep research and was mentally prepared, he could not avoid having an envious feeling right now.

Li Jun Ying had already moved ahead to welcome Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun was out of the inheritance space, and appeared somewhat clueless and dazed right now.

"How was it, did you succeed? What did you inherit?" Under the heat of the moment, Li Jun Ying grabbed Zhao Lian Yun's small, tender shoulder and shook it fiercely.

Zhao Lian Yun frowned from the pain: "I am also not too sure, there was a dazzling light after I entered, then a will appeared, he told me to accept the rank nine immortal killer move — Divine Concealment."

"Divine concealment?!" Hearing this term, Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying's eyes opened wide as they glanced at each other, both seeing the shock in each other's eyes.

Zhao Lian Yun, however, was disappointed, asking anxiously: "I did not become a Gu Immortal, and also didn't experience any changes, can I still save brother Ma Hong Yun?"

Xu Hao reacted at this moment, and started laughing heartily, replying firmly: "Of course! I did not think the true content of this inheritance was this. Being able to inherit divine concealment is a gargantuan fortune."

"Rank nine immortal killer move divine concealment..." Li Jun Ying also involuntarily let out a gasp, "In the past, when Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created theft path, he stole the treasures of the world with no one able to forecast or deduce his movements. Why was that the case? It was rumored that it was because of two defensive killer moves Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable possessed, one was 'divine concealment', the other was 'ghostly concealment'."

Zhao Lian Yun's eyes opened wide: "Divine concealment, ghostly concealment?"

Li Jun Ying nodded: "Right, divine concealment makes it so that no thoughts, wills or emotions can deduce your state or origins. Do you know what this means? The methods of probing and deducing of almost all wisdom path Gu Immortals in the world come from these three aspects: thought, will and emotion. And with divine concealment, you are immune to the deductions of almost all wisdom path Gu Immortals. Rank nine divine concealment... only a rank nine wisdom path Gu Immortal can have a chance to succeed in making deductions about you."

Xu Hao continued: "This is actually still not its most amazing aspect! You might not even believe it when I say it, but the most amazing thing is that divine concealment can make Gu Masters immune to heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities!"

Li Jun Ying's expression looked enchanted, while Zhao Lian Yun still looked uncomprehending.

Xu Hao could not help but laugh, he realized Zhao Lian Yun was only a mortal and not a Gu Immortal, thus she did not understand the significance of this.

He patiently explained: "Heaven's will is a kind of will. You have divine concealment, since heaven's will can't probe you, it can't send calamities and tribulations to you. You have already escaped the detection of heaven's will, when you ascend to immortal later, you won't attract any heavenly tribulation or earthly calamity. After Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created divine concealment, no calamities and tribulations befell him."

"But this has its disadvantages as well, calamities and tribulations are not entirely bad, they are a major way to increase the number of dao marks a Gu Immortal has. In the future, although you won't face calamities and tribulations, and will be incomparably safe, you won't be able to increase your quantity of dao marks through calamities and tribulations, and your accomplishments would be limited. Unless you have the other methods of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable to support your cultivation. In records of history, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could even steal dao marks."

Zhao Lian Yun's eyes moved round and round in puzzlement, as she probed: "Divine concealment is so powerful, then what about ghostly concealment?"

Xu Hao, who had been talking with confidence, did not have an answer for this, and Li Jun Ying also slowly shook her head.

"Divine concealment, ghostly concealment. The former is known by everyone, but the latter is extremely mysterious. There are many guesses and public opinions vary, but they are all unreliable and there has never been a publicly accepted answer." Xu Hao replied.

Li Jun Ying spoke faintly: "But since both are equally famous, it also must be extraordinary."

Zhao Lian Yun blinked, her tone one of astonishment: "Besides inheriting divine concealment, I also obtained a clue. Another Thieving Heaven inheritance is hidden in Luo Po valley, and that inheritance is about ghostly concealment!"

"What? A second Thieving Heaven inheritance!"

"And it is hidden in Luo Po valley?"

Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying was surprised and joyous, they glanced at each other with bright eyes.

Chapter 950: Unexpected Compensation

Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying were very perceptive.

Zhao Lian Yun's information was very important.

Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying immediately thought of Feng Jiu Ge rather than the Thieving Heaven inheritance!

Combined with the information from the Central Continent Gu Immortals who returned, they were almost certain: The reason why Feng Jiu Ge disappeared was because he was trapped inside the Thieving Heaven inheritance.

"The Thieving Heaven inheritance must have been used by the enemy to trap Feng Jiu Ge." Xu Hao was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he said this after deducing.

"Then what should we do now?" Li Jun Ying's words made them sink into silence.

Zhao Lian Yun looked around left to right and back, she did not speak.

The reason why said she mentioned this was because she wanted to return to Northern Plains, using Spirit Affinity House's power to save Ma Hong Yun.

But she did not know about the internal conflicts within Spirit Affinity House.

Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying looked at each other, they interacted with their gazes.

Both of their gazes gradually turned cold, they had chemistry and a close rapport built over the years, they quickly came to an agreement.

They decided to suppress this information and temporarily not report it.

They wanted Feng Jiu Ge to die.

If they reported it, Spirit Affinity House would definitely send people to save him, if Feng Jiu Ge was still alive, what would happen once he was saved?

After dragging it out for three days, both immortals reached the time limit and reported this information.

As expected, the higher ups in Spirit Affinity House were alarmed, they organized a group to save him. As for the otherworldly demon Zhao Lian Yun, she became the key person in this rescue mission, she was brought to Northern Plains.

Several days later.

Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, Dark Flow Giant City.

Boom!

A loud sound was heard as intense explosions occurred, the entirety of Giant City trembled.

"What is going on?"

"What is going on? Is someone attacking Dark Flow Giant City?"

In Dark Flow Giant City, people had fallen to the ground, shocked cries were heard.

Dark Flow Giant City was enormous, it had a total of seven layers. The lower five layers were the residences of mortal Gu Masters and were very bustling and clamorous. One layer above was where people with some connection to immortal zombies resided. The highest layer was reserved for immortals only.

At this moment, at the highest layer of Dark Flow Giant City, a thick smoke rose into the sky.

"Cough cough." Fang Yuan was covered in soot as he came out of the secret room, he was coughing non-stop.

He failed again when refining star thought Immortal Gu.

Ever since they made the new alliance agreement, Fang Yuan did not return to his blessed land, he came to Dark Flow Giant City and used Northern Plains Zombie Alliance's refinement path Gu formation.

He was not a refinement path Gu Immortal, he could not set up a refinement path Gu formation of such a level himself.

Fang Yuan tried to refine star thought Immortal Gu again.

Blazing Heaven Demoness had funded him a huge amount of immortal materials for Gu refinement in accordance with the agreement.

This time, the immortal materials were not tampered with at all.

Fang Yuan had an easy time during the refinement, but during the final few steps, the Gu refinement failed, and an intense explosion occurred.

Not only was the entire refinement path Gu formation blown to bits, the explosion also destroyed the secret room, alerting all of the Gu Immortals in Dark Flow Giant City, even the mortals in the lower layers felt it.

"At the final few steps, the dao marks will undergo a unique change that cannot be controlled. The interaction of dao marks would only stabilize under one condition, that is the successful refinement of star thought Immortal Gu. This step is purely dependent on luck." Fang Yuan sighed internally.

Man is the spirit of all beings, Gu are the essence of heaven and earth.

All living beings, including humans, could not directly manipulate dao marks. Be it Gu Masters, desolate beasts, desolate plants, even if they had dao marks in them, they could only make use of them through Gu worms.

Thus, when Gu Immortals refine Gu, they could not directly manipulate the dao marks, they could not control intense changes in the dao marks.

To make a rather crude comparison.

Refining a rank six Immortal Gu was like playing golf.

The Gu Immortal's preparations are all to ensure that the golf ball moves according to the path that they had planned.

But the long path that the ball needs to travel on is filled with over a hundred holes.

Only when the golf ball falls into the correct hole at the end of the path would the Gu refinement succeed.

Gu Immortals could only ensure that the golf ball would move according to their wishes during the first half of the route, by the second half, the ground would be uneven and filled with pits, the Gu Immortals would not be able to control how the ball moved anymore.

Thus, whether the ball could enter the proper hole depended on luck.

"Even though Blazing Heaven Demoness no longer tampered with the immortal materials, her funding is not without cost, I need to pay her back eventually. Refining Immortal Gu is simply too hard, the success rate is too low. Maybe I can seek help from Lang Ya land spirit, he should have a strong refinement path Immortal Gu, or a special refinement method to increase the rate of successfully refining Immortal Gu."

In history, Long Hair Ancestor was known as the 'number one refinement path immortal of all times', the number of Immortal Gu that he had refined in his life shocked countless people.

Even though Long Hair Ancestor had died, his land spirit was alive, and Lang Ya blessed land was still intact.

Fang Yuan's Gu refinement had failed again, he even suffered injuries.

He decided to seek help from Lang Ya land spirit and try to increase his chances, even if he had to pay a huge price!

"I'd suggest you to first try refining the strength path Immortal Gu." At this time, Fairy Li Shan came over and gave Fang Yuan a suggestion.

Fairy Li Shan could no longer stay in Snowy Mountain blessed land. Ever since they killed Hei Cheng, Fairy Li Shan had been staying inside Dark Flow Giant City.

Her relationship with Blazing Heaven Demoness was exposed, everyone knew about it.

Earlier, Blazing Heaven Demoness had led a band of immortal zombies to assault the Snowy Mountain blessed land demonic path Gu Immortals, with high rates of success.

In actual fact, it was because Fairy Li Shan was the traitor exposing intelligence to Blazing Heaven Demoness.

Fairy Li Shan was an information path quasi-great grandmaster, even though she had was restricted by the alliance agreement of the forces of Snowy Mountain blessed land, she could skirt around the restrictions and aid Blazing Heaven Demoness while only suffering mild injuries from violating it.

How could Old Ancestor Xue Hu keep such a traitor?

After meeting with Blazing Heaven Demoness, he publicly announced the expulsion of Fairy Li Shan, and declared her to be an enemy of Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Fairy Li Shan had offended the biggest demonic path force in Northern Plains, but she was welcomed by Zombie Alliance. Her relationship with Blazing Heaven Demoness made her one of them. Furthermore, she was the key person in forcing Old Ancestor Xue Hu to give in just now, in Dark Flow Giant City, Fairy Li Shan was very well respected by the immortal zombies.

Fang Yuan heard Fairy Li Shan's words and frowned: "Please explain."

Fairy Li Shan sighed: "There is a change in the situation, my sister's funding for your refinement of star thought Immortal Gu might have to be delayed."

"Why is that the case?" Fang Yuan could not understand, they had just set the agreement, was Blazing Heaven Demoness going to break the agreement so quickly?

That did not make sense.

Because funding Fang Yuan's refinement of star thought Immortal Gu was Blazing Heaven Demoness' idea.

Fairy Li Shan explained the reason and Fang Yuan soon understood why.

The reason was that the cooperation between Blazing Heaven Demoness and Old Ancestor Xue Hu had a huge impact on Northern Plains after Snowy Mountain and Zombie Alliance went into a ceasefire.

The conflict between both forces received much attention, some of the other regions even looked into the matter.

But Blazing Heaven Demoness and Old Ancestor Xue Hu knew their limits, they cooperated and settled this conflict rapidly and peacefully.

The righteous path forces in Northern Plains were excitedly watching this as they wanted to see a conflict between them.

Suddenly, there was a turn of events.

As the conflict ended, Zombie Alliance's headquarters sent out a mandatory mission in addition to the contribution points.

All the members of Northern Plains Zombie Alliance had to work together, using all their resources to refine a giant Gu formation.

This Gu formation's sole use was to protect the immortal zombie graveyard.

If a situation like Old Ancestor Xue Hu stealing bodies happened again, the Gu formation would activate and defend the place. If it could not defend the place, the power of the Gu formation would teleport these immortal zombie bodies out of Northern Plains.

"Right now, Zombie Alliance is putting in a huge sum! Not just the Northern Plains Zombie Alliance branch, but the other three branches and even the headquarters are building this giant Immortal Gu formation together. Just here alone, we are using thirteen Immortal Gu, and countless supplementary mortal Gu."

"Most of the Immortal Gu are sent here from the headquarters, but we also have to refine a number of them. Thus, Dark Flow Giant City is recalling all the immortal zombies back to refine Gu. There will definitely be insufficient storage in Dark Flow Giant City, the immortal zombies will have to use their personal resources." Fairy Li Shan explained in detail.

Of course, the immortal zombies would be compensated for contributing their personal resources.

The Zombie Alliance headquarters was giving out huge amounts of contribution points, much higher than ordinary times, to compensate the members.

This was among the biggest actions taken by Zombie Alliance in the last thousand years.

An immense amount of contribution points made the immortal zombie members feel enthusiastic about refining Gu. As long as they participated and expended immortal materials, regardless of whether they failed or succeeded, they would be able to obtain a huge sum of contribution points, this was a benefit rarely seen in a thousand years!

Furthermore, after setting up this Gu formation, the Zombie Alliance graveyard would be safe without any future worries.

The immortal zombies in Zombie Alliance were also delighted to see the creation of this giant Immortal Gu formation.

The immortal zombies from Eastern Sea were temporarily unable to return to Eastern Sea, they stayed and refined Immortal Gu, and a huge number of supplementary mortal Gu.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was in the same place, she could no longer fund Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's plan to refine star thought Immortal Gu was obstructed, he could not even continue using the Gu refinement secret room.

He had already rescinded the Zombie Alliance agreement that had been placed on him.

Blazing Heaven Demoness, who was the branch leader, had the authority to do this.

In Dark Flow Giant City, Fang Yuan and Fairy Li Shan were both outsiders. Except that Fairy Li Shan was much more popular and well regarded than Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan frowned as he thought: "In the five hundred years of my previous life, Zombie Alliance had this plan too, and they even succeeded. But the reason was not because Old Ancestor Xue Hu stole immortal zombies from the graveyard. It seems that the course of history will not alter easily, in this life, Zombie Alliance is building this giant Immortal Gu formation again."

Fang Yuan could not stop them, of course.

Zombie Alliance was a huge force, Blazing Heaven Demoness, who was just the leader of a branch, was already able to suppress him firmly.

If not for Fang Yuan's immense value which interested Blazing Heaven Demoness, choosing to cooperate with him, Fang Yuan might have been dead already.

But no matter how strong Blazing Heaven Demoness was, Fang Yuan would not let go of the compensation that he was entitled to.

"Blazing Heaven Demoness' action is going against our alliance agreement, right?" Fang Yuan asked as he looked at Fairy Li Shan.

Fairy Li Shan smiled bitterly.

This was indeed Blazing Heaven Demoness violating the agreement.

According to their alliance agreement, Blazing Heaven Demoness had to give Fang Yuan quite a sum of compensation.

Unless Fang Yuan was willing to forgo the compensation claim, Blazing Heaven Demoness would have to pay him, otherwise the backlash of the agreement would heavily injure her.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was feeling regret towards this as well.

If she had known this, why would she fund Fang Yuan? Wasn't a different condition better? Even if she wanted to fund him, she could do so in a different way that did not break the agreement.

The plan of Zombie Alliance caught Blazing Heaven Demoness off guard, since Fang Yuan refused to let go, she could only compensate him.

Chapter 951: Genius of a Generation, Feng Jiu Ge!

Fang Yuan returned to Hu Immortal blessed land.

Blazing Heaven Demoness' compensation was very satisfactory.

Firstly, Blazing Heaven Demoness' recently funded immortal materials were all waived, Fang Yuan did not need to pay her back. Secondly, Blazing Heaven Demoness lent Fang Yuan three fire path Immortal Gu and gave him a large number of mortal Gu.

These three fire path Immortal Gu along with the countless mortal Gu could create the fire path immortal killer move — Nirvana Fire.

Speaking of which, Blazing Heaven Demoness was quite unlucky.

She had funded Fang Yuan in refining star thought Immortal Gu, and provided him a huge amount of precious immortal materials. In the end, all of it went to waste and Fang Yuan did not need to pay her back.

Even though Blazing Heaven Demoness had tampered with the immortal materials earlier, Fang Yuan had gained a lot of experience from it, he was very familiar with the refinement process of star thought Immortal Gu.

Because of the alliance agreement, Fang Yuan obtained the details of the immortal killer move nirvana fire.

Which Immortal Gu were the cores, how many supplementary mortal Gu were needed, what was the order of the Gu worms, Fang Yuan knew all of these clearly.

But to use this killer move, there was a prerequisite — fire path dao marks needed to be expended from the Gu Immortal's body!

Blazing Heaven Demoness had cleverly concealed this fact, it was a small trap in the agreement.

She wanted to increase her control over Fang Yuan using this.

Since Fang Yuan did not have any fire path dao marks, if he wanted to revive using nirvana fire, he would need Blazing Heaven Demoness to use nirvana fire for him.

Fang Yuan planned to modify the immortal killer move nirvana fire, using other Immortal Gu as the cores to achieve the same or similar results.

And it would be best of these new core Immortal Gu were Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan possessed.

This modification was very difficult, typical wisdom path Gu Immortals would not have any confidence in this, but Fang Yuan had high hopes for it.

The reason was because wisdom Gu was inside Hu Immortal blessed land.

The power of the rank nine wisdom Gu was simply brilliant, it could not be expressed with words!

It was important for Fang Yuan to do this.

The life-and-death immortal aperture revival method could allow him to revive, but it could only be used once on each immortal aperture. After revival, he would not be able to use wisdom Gu.

If Fang Yuan could modify nirvana fire and freely change between being an immortal zombie and a living person, wisdom Gu would continue to assist him in unimaginable ways.

"Blazing Heaven Demoness is tight on funds now, she needs to spend her own resources to refine Immortal Gu and complete the mandatory mission by Zombie Alliance. Thus, she had to lend out these three fire path Immortal Gu. If not for this situation, even if I requested it, she would not lend them to me so easily. With these three fire path Immortal Gu, my modification and deduction will be much easier!"

Fang Yuan felt very pleased about this.

The Gu formation plan of Zombie Alliance unexpectedly made him a beneficiary.

In the following days, Fang Yuan was bathed in the light of wisdom, he deduced with all his energy, concentrating on modifying the killer move nirvana fire.

Speaking of which, he had already gathered enough strength path immortal zombies and refined enough exert strength Gu, he even had a sixty year lifespan Gu.

He had all three, he could activate the life-and-death immortal aperture revival method now to become a living Gu Immortal and obtain a high grade blessed land.

But after obtaining nirvana fire, Fang Yuan was no longer satisfied with just this.

Even though with Blazing Heaven Demoness' interference, Fang Yuan was prevented from plotting against Hei Lou Lan and obtaining a super grade blessed land, because of this opportunity, he obtained nirvana fire and if he used it well, he would be able to continue using wisdom Gu.

Summing up his gains and losses, Fang Yuan was uncertain if he had overall made a gain or a loss.

Just as Fang Yuan was modifying the immortal killer move, Zhao Lian Yun had already stepped into Luo Po valley.

She was the key to rescuing Feng Jiu Ge.

There was only one person who came along with her as the rescue team from Spirit Affinity House.

Prince Feng Xian!

His rank eight cultivation could face any challenges.

On the surface, he was a Northern Plains righteous path Gu Immortal, and was an external supreme elder of a super force, Gong tribe. He did not have the Huang Jin bloodline in him, and because he had some grievances with Gong tribe, he had been living outside for many years.

The truth was, he was a disciple of Spirit Affinity House. The Central Continent force had spent a huge effort and price to send him into Northern Plains as their highest level spy, his main task being in regards to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Normally, Prince Feng Xian could not be used easily. If any traces were exposed, Prince Feng Xian's secret status, which had been hidden for hundreds of years, would be wasted.

But it was different now because of Feng Jiu Ge. He was the face of Spirit Affinity House, currently, he already could suppress the rest of Central Continent, if he advanced to rank eight, with his talent and ability, in time, he would be an expert even among rank eights. His existence meant more benefits. His life and death would tilt the balance between the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, and even change the situation of the entire Central Continent Gu Immortal world.

Thus, Spirit Affinity House took a risk in using the hidden agent Prince Feng Xian, to try and save him as soon as possible!

Prince Feng Xian and Zhao Lian Yun, a mortal and an immortal, moved forward in Luo Po valley.

"Lord, I would like to ask a question. If I can save Lord Feng Jiu Ge, will I be able to become the next generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House?" While traveling, Zhao Lian Yun asked this.

Prince Feng Xian wore a mask, his figure was blurry, he was shrouded in fog, his true appearance was concealed.

He said softly with a smile: "It is not so easy to become Spirit Affinity House's next generation fairy. But if you can save Feng Jiu Ge, then it would almost be guaranteed that you succeed. I heard that his daughter Feng Jin Huang is the top competitor for this title. If you become the savior of her father's life, she would step down from this contest for sure."

"So that's it..." Zhao Lian Yun's eyes shined with the light of hope.

Even though she had the soul of an adult, after she went to Spirit Affinity House, she was very cooperative, she did not conceal anything and acted obediently.

Because she had understood what world she was in.

Without strength, no matter how intelligent you was, you were like a loose strand of grass, once the wind blew, you would be blown away and sent into danger.

She understood that she needed to rely on Spirit Affinity House to save Ma Hong Yun.

But it was unrealistic to get Spirit Affinity House to attack Snowy Mountain.

Zhao Lian Yun had understood the rules of Spirit Affinity House, all the generations of fairies were fully nurtured by the sect. In Spirit Affinity House's long history, all of these fairies had become Gu Immortals, they had immense strength and had significant authority in the sect.

"To save brother Hong Yun, I need to rely on myself. Brother Hong Yun, you must hang in there!" Zhao Lian Yun prayed for Ma Hong Yun internally.

Prince Feng Xian suddenly stopped moving: "Found it, it is here."

Using the Immortal Gu from Spirit Affinity House, Prince Feng Xian obtained an immortal killer move that was specialized in finding the Thieving Heaven inheritance.

To use this killer move, they had to move slowly.

Prince Feng Xian brought Zhao Lian Yun and walked for over two hours before they located the Thieving Heaven inheritance in the giant Luo Po valley.

Prince Feng Xian activated his Immortal Gu, and in a few minutes, an entrance of light opened.

Whoosh!

The entrance of light had just opened when an intense wind blew.

Prince Feng Xian was shocked: "How can the winds of assimilation be here?!"

He quickly activated his Immortal Gu, using a killer move and grabbing with his hand.

The winds of assimilation were condensed into a ball, grabbed tightly by Prince Feng Xian in his hand.

But soon, Prince Feng Xian's hand started trembling as his expression turned pale: "Quickly go in, I can only control it for a moment!"

Zhao Lian Yun swiftly acknowledged his words, even though she could not see his face, she could hear how anxious he was from his voice.

Zhao Lian Yun stepped in and saw a familiar sight.

Like the previous inheritance space, this place was empty. The only thing here were over a dozen tornadoes of the winds of assimilation, moving slowly in the space like tall pillars.

Zhao Lian Yun's heart was pounding.

Even though she did not know what the winds of assimilation were, from the actions of Prince Feng Xian, she knew that they were incredibly powerful.

"You are finally here, quickly come to me." A voice was transmitted into her ears.

Zhao Lian Yun was shocked, she took a step back: "Who are you?"

"I am Feng Jiu Ge, hurry, come here now." The voice was extremely weak, it sounded like a dying old man who was holding onto his last breath.

Zhao Lian Yun hesitated.

She could hear that the voice came from within one of the tornadoes of the winds of assimilation.

Zhao Lian Yun also realized that the tornadoes were all gathering towards the most central one, they were moving slowly, like a group of lions stalking and eyeing up on their food.

"Don't worry, you are an otherworldly demon, you have received the acceptance of Thieving Heaven's will, the winds of assimilation are harmless to you."

Feng Jiu Ge paused before speaking with difficulty: "Didn't you come to save me? If I stay here, you will not be able to inherit this Thieving Heaven inheritance."

Zhao Lian Yun licked her dry lips.

She knew that she had to make a decision now.

Time waits for no one.

Zhao Lian Yun carefully got closer to a tornado of the winds of assimilation, the tornado's power was very concentrated, Zhao Lian Yun could only feel a light breeze when she was beside it.

She stretched out her trembling hand as she placed it into the tornado.

If any Gu Immortal saw this, they would cry out in shock. But Zhao Lian Yun's ignorance made her less fearful, she did not know the power of the winds of assimilation, and she chose to believe in Feng Jiu Ge.

Like what Feng Jiu Ge had said, the winds of assimilation that even Prince Feng Xian could not deal with were harmless towards Zhao Lian Yun. After Zhao Lian Yun placed her hand into it, the tornado shrunk at an observable rate, in a few breaths' time, it vanished.

Feng Jiu Ge's voice was transmitted again: "See, wasn't I correct? This inheritance space has a power greater than the winds of assimilation, thus it cannot be destroyed. You are an otherworldly demon accepted by this space, with it protecting you, you are in no danger."

Zhao Lian Yun was overjoyed: "Lord Feng Jiu Ge, I will save you now!"

She rushed into the tornadoes, charging her way in, as the winds of assimilation vanished wherever she went.

Eventually, she reached the center, and the largest wind pillar trapping Feng Jiu Ge dispersed.

Next, she saw that Feng Jiu Ge was sitting cross-legged in the air, three meters from the ground. His face was rosy and his robe was clean, but his eyes were shut tight.

"Lord Feng Jiu Ge..." Zhao Lian Yun called out lightly.

Feng Jiu Ge slowly opened his eyes, his expression was clear as jade.

He did not speak, he opened his right hand and showed it to Zhao Lian Yun.

There were two words written with blood on his palm.

Zhao Lian Yun looked at it in confusion, turning her gaze towards Feng Jiu Ge again.

Feng Jiu Ge smiled lightly at her, next, his entire body scattered with the wind, it disintegrated and vanished on the spot.

Zhao Lian Yun was left staring blankly.

The greatest genius of a generation, Feng Jiu Ge, had passed away!

Chapter 952: Fang Yuan's First Entry into Luo Po Valley

Hu Immortal blessed land.

Because the rate of time was different, half a month had already passed here.

In the underground cave, Fang Yuan was bathed in the light of wisdom as he deduced quietly as usual.

In here, he did not need to use the killer move vaguely familiar face, he was in his original zombie appearance.

He did not move, he sat still like a rock.

But in his mind, countless starlight specks were shining, as thoughts clashed endlessly within.

"Puff..." A long while later, he let out a breath, he opened his eyes and showed an extremely tired expression.

He stood up with difficulty, after undergoing such a long period of intense thinking, his mind was hurting and he felt waves of dizziness.

Even though he was a wisdom path grandmaster, his fire path attainment level was too low, he could only maintain each deduction for seven days and nights.

After seven days and nights, he would need to rest, unable to continue further.

His mind was like a simmering cauldron, it needed time to cool down frequently. If not, his mind would suffer considerable damage.

"After so many days, I have only completed twenty percent of nirvana fire's modification. And this was with the effect of the light of wisdom. If I did it alone, I would need countless years to reach my current progress."

Immortal killer move were very hard to create.

The killer move nirvana fire was even more profound. Using fire path to display the mysteries of life and death, if Blazing Heaven Demoness was not a fire path great grandmaster, she might not have successfully created this move.

Fang Yuan left the underground cave and returned to Dang Hun palace to rest.

After sleeping for half a day, his mind was refreshed, but according to his experience, Fang Yuan still needed to rest for an entire night before he could recover fully.

Hu Immortal blessed land did not have day and night, there were no changes in the sky.

But if it did, then there were would still be six hours until night time.

Fang Yuan was unwilling to waste his time, he activated connecting heaven Gu and his consciousness entered treasure yellow heaven. During this period of time, he selectively put some rank eight immortal materials up for sale, to exchange for a large amount of food to feed his Immortal Gu.

Of course, the more precious quasi rank nine immortal materials were kept in his possession.

The rank eight immortal materials that he sold were the lowest quality among his inventory.

Even so, waves of commotion were created in treasure yellow heaven as a result.

The attraction of rank eight immortal materials was huge. This allowed Fang Yuan to easily complete the current goal of feeding his Immortal Gu.

"If not for these rank eight immortal materials, I would be troubled by this for a long time." Fang Yuan was feeling the burden of feeding Immortal Gu now.

He had simply too many Immortal Gu on him right now.

Very few Gu Immortals had so many Immortal Gu in their possession.

The burden of feeding these Immortal Gu was huge.

Actually, quality was more important than quantity for Immortal Gu. Like Xue Song Zi, he only had one Immortal Gu, but after Shadow Sect gave him a set of immortal killer moves, he fought without any clear weaknesses. In this situation, he was making full use of his Immortal Gu.

"The most common situation is to feed a small number of Immortal Gu and use them as the cores to create many different immortal killer move to deal with different situations."

Fang Yuan knew this, but he had no choice.

He could not sell these Immortal Gu easily.

Transactions of Immortal Gu were very rare, even if there occurred, they traded Immortal Gu for Immortal Gu.

After settling the final deal in treasure yellow heaven, Fang Yuan's Immortal Gu feeding session ended for the time being.

As for the refinement of star thought Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan had set it aside.

He still had the rank six Immortal Gu recipe of all-out effort Gu, but he did not plan to refine it. Even though he lost self strength Immortal Gu and his battle strength fell drastically.

The success rate of refining Immortal Gu was too low, in order to refine star thought Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan suffered huge losses.

Right now, he felt sick every time he heard about refining Immortal Gu. He felt some pity and sympathy towards the immortal zombies who were refining Immortal Gu collectively right now.

He did not lack immortal essence stones currently, but his funds were all spent on the building of Star Form blessed land.

During this period, Fang Yuan had been multitasking.

Star Form land spirit had been working laboriously, following the design plans of Fang Yuan in building the new structures. Right now, Star Form blessed land was already forty percent done with the new development.

But with the revival method, Fang Yuan no longer felt such urgency towards Star Form blessed land.

Fang Yuan also did not plan to move Hu Immortal blessed land's resources into Star Form blessed land.

During this period, Fang Yuan's time in Hu Immortal blessed land was fulfilling and peaceful.

His main effort was on modifying the killer move nirvana fire.

Everything was prepared now, he only lacked the final critical elements!

Once nirvana fire was completed, Fang Yuan would revive and obtain a high grade blessed land. Next, he will move all of the blessed lands' resources into his own immortal aperture.

This was the safest and fastest way.

Undoubtedly, once this plan succeeds, Fang Yuan's future would be bright.

Fang Yuan waited patiently.

He was not anxious, even though he had been seeking this goal for a long time.

His experiences in the five hundred years of his previous life trained his incredible level of patience.

But just when he was preparing to rest for the night before continuing his killer move modification, Hei Lou Lan requested help from him.

"You will never imagine what I found in Hei Cheng's soul!" Using a stargate, Hei Lou Lan arrived in front of Fang Yuan excitedly.

After Hei Cheng died, his soul was captured by Hei Lou Lan.

These last days, Hei Lou Lan had obtained lots of shocking information from Hei Cheng's soul. What moved her the most was the hundred days battle in Luo Po valley!

"Fang Yuan, you have the ability to move mountains, I need you to retrieve Luo Po valley for me! Don't worry, I will give you enough compensation! We have to move quickly before complications arise!" Hei Lou Lan acted rapidly.

Luo Po valley...

Fang Yuan did not speak, he thought of the open door Gu and close door Gu in his possession.

He had the clue to Luo Po valley long ago, but he was bothered with other matters and did not head there.

Now, after receiving Hei Lou Lan's information, he was internally glad about his vigilance and careful decision.

Luo Po valley was under the control of Shadow Sect long ago, it was their base. If Fang Yuan headed there abruptly, without enough strength, he would be easily captured by the other party. Even if he struggled while risking his life, his enemies would be too powerful, there would be little hope of escaping.

"But now is a chance!" Hei Lou Lan's eyes shined brightly.

Fang Yuan nodded, agreeing: "Shadow Sect failed and Luo Po valley is controlled by the Central Continent Gu Immortals now. But they are from another region after all, they cannot stay for long. We just need to leak some information to force them to escape."

Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan did not know that the Central Continent Gu Immortals had already left Northern Plains, returning to Central Continent.

Fang Yuan had always been weak in collecting information. In terms of Northern Plains, he relied on Fairy Li Shan. In terms of Central Continent, Immortal Crane Sect would never reveal such secrets to him.

"This group of people should be trying to investigate the culprit behind the fall of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, they are after us. But for some reason, their investigation led to Shadow Sect." Hei Lou Lan chuckled.

Fang Yuan pondered: "Compared to this, I am more concerned about the Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance immortal zombie. He is a member of Shadow Sect, why was he saved by Zombie Alliance?"

When the mysterious Gu Immortal revealed his identity as a ten extreme immortal zombie, Hei Cheng was there as well, thus this precious information was leaked.

"Sigh, there are many secretive Gu Immortals and Gu Master forces. Zombie Alliance has a loose structure, many of the members have their own forces, this is nothing strange, right?" Hei Lou Lan said nonchalantly.

"Shadow Sect is not to be underestimated!" Fang Yuan had a heavy expression: "Shadow Sect members are not afraid of sacrifice, the unity of this mysterious force is simply too high."

This was not the first time Fang Yuan had heard of Shadow Sect.

Back in Southern Border, he had heard about it from Chou Jiu.

Fang Yuan even knew that the door of life and death was inside Shadow Sect's blessed land. But he did not make any plans regarding it.

The reason was that his strength was too low, and there was no good opportunity.

It was very difficult to attack a blessed land and not attract attention. Shadow Sect was mysterious and stretched across Southern Border and Northern Plains, they were not to be trifled with.

"Alright, enough of that. Luo Po valley is right in front of us, I am inviting you and my aunts to explore it. We will split the gains according to our alliance agreement." Hei Lou Lan said anxiously.

Fang Yuan understood why she was in a rush.

This was truly an incredibly rare opportunity.

Fang Yuan was excited too.

He still had open door Gu and close door Gu in his possession, he wanted to know if these two Gu worms could grant him any different treatment in Luo Po valley.

But before going, some things had to be said.

"You want to take Luo Po valley completely, I do not agree with that." Fang Yuan said firmly.

Hei Lou Lan stared with furious eyes, her gaze shined with a ruthless light: "What do you mean? I found the information on Luo Po valley!"

Fang Yuan laughed, he said the location of Luo Po valley.

Hei Lou Lan was shocked, she was staring at Fang Yuan with much suspicion.

She had withheld some information earlier, she did not tell Fang Yuan this piece of important information!

Fang Yuan took out open door Gu and close door Gu. Like how Hei Lou Lan exposed attitude Gu to them, since these Gu worms were going to be used anyway and could not be concealed, he openly explained it.

Hei Lou Lan snorted, looking at Fang Yuan disdainfully: "Without my information, would you dare to go? By the time you are willing to go, the chance would have been lost."

Fang Yuan smiled: "Don't be so agitated, I am just saying your information is not as important as you think."

But Hei Lou Lan acted very agitated.

Next, they went into an intense verbal fight.

Both sides were breathing roughly with exertion written on their faces, their demeanor as Gu Immortals was disregarded, but they came to an agreement.

The ownership of Luo Po valley was divided up.

Blazing Heaven Demoness would take fifty percent, Fairy Li Shan would take twenty, while Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan would take ten percent each.

Hei Lou Lan was very crafty, she used her two aunts to force Fang Yuan to give in.

Ten percent of the ownership might be little, but it achieved Fang Yuan's goal.

He just needed the rights to use it.

Fang Yuan had never thought of taking Luo Po valley for himself. After all, Hei Lou Lan had Blazing Heaven Demoness backing her.

However, Blazing Heaven Demoness was busy refining Gu, and as a rank eight, her every action would garner great attention. She transmitted to them: Since Fang Yuan had Fixed Immortal Travel anyway, if they were in any danger, she would be able to save them.

In the end, only Fang Yuan, Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan went.

"Oh no, some people have entered Luo Po valley!" Hui Feng Zi, who was hidden outside guarding the entrance, saw Fang Yuan and the others and quickly reported it.

Soon, Prince Feng Xian was informed of it!

Chapter 953: Late By One Step

After Hui Feng Zi surrendered in battle, he was subdued by Central Continent's ten great ancient sects. The Central Continent Gu Immortals returned while leaving him behind to keep watch over Luo Po valley.

He had just sided with Central Continent and had originally been unwilling, and was only a temporary hired hand, so naturally he did not have the qualifications to know of Prince Feng Xian's true identity.

He only knew an immortal and a mortal had entered Luo Po valley, while he was keeping watch for them.

He was at the mercy of others and had no choice but to slog for Central Continent; the moment he saw Hei Lou Lan and the rest of the group, he quickly used information path methods to inform Prince Feng Xian who was inside Luo Po valley.

Prince Feng Xian quickly obtained the information. At this moment, his hand was still slightly shaking.

Clearing up the winds of assimilation was truly not easy.

Just from this, Prince Feng Xian could not help but admire Feng Jiu Ge. The latter was actually able to last for so long under the winds of assimilation. He truly did not know how Feng Jiu Ge was able to do this.

Unfortunately, Feng Jiu Ge was already dead!

The process of inheriting the Thieving Heaven true inheritance was extremely fast.

Only the identity needed to be checked and if one was indeed an otherworldly demon, the Thieving Heaven inheritance would go to them.

After Feng Jiu Ge died, the inheritance space only had Zhao Lian Yun remaining. So, she quickly obtained this inheritance — Ghostly Concealment.

Right at this moment, she returned to Prince Feng Xian's side and reported the news of Feng Jiu Ge's death.

"Sigh, we were late." Prince Feng Xian sighed inwardly.

He then grabbed Zhao Lian Yun's shoulder and flew away.

An immortal and a mortal were soon away of the scene.

At present, Fairy Li Shan and Blazing Heaven Demoness' relation was already known by everyone.

Prince Feng Xian did not want to get in a fight.

The social circle of rank eight Gu Immortals was very small.

In the whole of Northern Plains, the number of rank eight Gu Immortals on the surface was only five.

Old Ancestor Xue Hu, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu, Yao Huang, Prince Feng Xian and Five Elements Grandmaster.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was a rank eight immortal zombie who was barely able to join in this circle.

One could say all six of them were very familiar with each other, and had fought and sparred with each other many times. To exaggerate it, if someone farted, they would know who it was, and they would recognize someone even if they turned into ashes.

Were Prince Feng Xian to attack Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan, Blazing Heaven Demoness would definitely come out.

In Prince Feng Xian's opinion, Blazing Heaven Demoness might already be secretly lurking in the surroundings.

Prince Feng Xian's identity was very special, he could not rashly make a move. If he made a move and Blazing Heaven Demoness recognized his identity, that would truly mess up the situation.

Why would Prince Feng Xian appear in Luo Po valley?

Gu Immortals were not idiots, they would easily guess Prince Feng Xian had a secret link with Shadow Sect or perhaps Central Continent forces.

One should not forget the existence of wisdom path Gu Immortals in this world!

Prince Feng Xian was looking at the overall situation and in caution, he took the initiative to retreat, avoiding leaving behind any clues or evidence that could be deduced by wisdom path Gu Immortals.

Hei Lou Lan and the others still did not know they had already forced a rank eight great expert to 'retreat'.

They broke the concealment seal outside and entered inside Luo Po valley, inspecting their surroundings.

Luo Po valley was a scene of ruins, this valley of legend had experienced the hundred days battle and was already half-ruined. Moreover, the remains of the valley was already beyond recognition, as almost everywhere were Gu formations arranged by Gu Immortals.

Some of these Gu formations were the works of Shadow Sect while some were arranged by Central Continent's Hong Chi Ming.

These Gu formations had no doubt an extremely bad influence to Luo Po valley's environment. It was to the extent that the bewilderment fog which blew all year round in Luo Po valley, and Luo Po wind, were nowhere to be seen.

The group of three began to roughly search Luo Po valley.

Fang Yuan found some remains of white lotus giant silkworm Gu.

He sighed, feeling some regret.

He had learned from Hei Lou Lan that there had been large numbers of white lotus giant silkworm Gu in Luo Po valley, but the hundred days battle caused the death of most of them, and when the Central Continent Gu Immortals swept through the battlefield later, they did not leave behind any living ones.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan had already obtained enough white lotus giant silkworm Gu in treasure yellow heaven, and fed cleanse soul Immortal Gu.

This proved that the accumulation of those old senior Gu Immortals could not be looked down upon. Naturally, the prior condition was you needed to have something enticing enough to make them act and carry out the transaction.

Under Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan's attentive gazes, Fang Yuan used open door Gu and close door Gu.

No response!

Open door Gu and close door Gu were the inheritances of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, but this place was already occupied by Shadow Sect and there were Gu formations everywhere, turning Luo Po valley into a stronghold or a fortress.

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh, he realized the Thieving Heaven inheritance was already taken by someone else. Most probably it was Shadow Sect.

But his guess was wrong.

The true beneficiary of the Thieving Heaven true inheritance was Zhao Lian Yun and Central Continent's forces.

What's more, she had inherited it just a short while ago.

Prince Feng Xian was late in saving Feng Jiu Ge, and Fang Yuan was also late by a step to arrive at Luo Po valley.

"Even if Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had left behind an inheritance, so many years have gone by, it is normal for it to be taken by others. The true treasure is still Luo Po valley!" Hei Lou Lan patted Fang Yuan's shoulder and said with a smile.

Fang Yuan knew she was urging him to hurry up and get to work.

Fang Yuan nodded, and activated Immortal Gu to slowly lift the whole of Luo Po valley.

Fairy Li Shan closely cooperated from another side, countless Gu worms flying all around.

"They are actually going to take Luo Po valley!" Hui Feng Zi had been spying from outside and was shocked at this sight.

Prince Feng Xian was also surprised.

He had not expected Hei Lou Lan's side actually had such an unorthodox method!

This truly caught Prince Feng Xian unprepared. He hesitated, but finally decided to restrain himself and do nothing.

After spending an hour, Fang Yuan succeeded in storing Luo Po valley in his immortal aperture.

"There are still blessed lands here, but just to be safe, we better leave now." Ever since Hei Lou Lan failed in passing the calamity, she had become more self-controlled and had lost almost all her rashness.

Although Luo Po valley was extremely ruined, but with Tai Bai Yun Sheng's Landscape as Before, it could definitely be restored.

Compared to the blessed lands, Luo Po valley's value was extremely difficult to replace.

Many Gu Immortals had fallen here in the hundred days battle. After they died, their immortal apertures should have become blessed lands hidden in space within this place.

Fang Yuan could take away Luo Po valley, but he could not bring these blessed lands.

However, now was not a good time to search for them.

After taking Luo Po valley, Fang Yuan and the group quickly made their retreat.

"They left really quickly, they know their situation." Far away, Prince Feng Xian quietly looked at the receding figures of the three people, his gaze dark and cold.

Although he could not make a move, he had the two female Gu Immortals, Swordmaster You Lan and Le Yao, under him, and he also had other secret forces.

Prince Feng Xian had hidden in Northern Plains for hundreds of years, naturally, he would have accumulated quite a bit of strength.

He had still been wanting to find trouble for Fang Yuan and the others, but they left too quickly, so he was unable to chase them.

Prince Feng Xian glanced at the battlefield of the hundred days battle, Luo Po valley was already gone, this place had now become an empty desolate land.

Although the auras of Immortal Gu were removed as much as possible, an expert could still sense some clues.

So many Gu Immortals had died here, these blessed lands themselves were rich resources.

Prince Feng Xian naturally would not give them up.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals behind him also would not give them up and would definitely move to retrieve these blessed lands.

As for the Immortal Gu, he did not have to even think about it, they were certainly already destroyed.

Retrieving blessed lands, especially ones that fell in foreign regions, was a difficult and troublesome matter.

"I hope this troublesome matter doesn't fall upon me, it is better if those other nine ancient sects take up the trouble. Feng Jiu Ge died from the winds of assimilation, he left behind nothing except two words in blood. I should first send back Zhao Lian Yun and this important information to the sect!"

Prince Feng Xian did not remain any longer and immediately left with Zhao Lian Yun.

As for Hui Feng Zi, he was still left behind to watch over the blessed lands.

"This is Xiao Hun blessed land." Hei Lou Lan brought Fang Yuan and Fairy Li Shan to the blessed land left by Hei Cheng.

This blessed land was clearly dominated by dark path and soul path dao marks, the whole of the blessed land was dim and gloomy, giving an oppressive feeling.

In the central area of the blessed land was a large and dense forest.

The trees were in all kinds of postures resembling female bodies. This was a special resource Hei Cheng had raised in his immortal aperture.

This kind of tree was not found in the nature, Hei Cheng could be considered its creator.

Thus these female-shaped trees were also one of a kind.

Hei Lou Lan had already thought of the place for Luo Po valley, calling out the land spirit.

Xiao Hun blessed land's land spirit looked rather peculiar, it was a jade-green vine. The vine was like a cloth, attaching itself onto that familial emotion left behind by Su Xian Er to Hei Lou Lan.

Fairy Li Shan introduced to Fang Yuan with a sigh: "Xiao Hun land spirit's ownership condition was to stay together forever with Su Xian Er. So after Little Lan took out sister's familial emotion, she easily became the master of this blessed land."

Fang Yuan was also slightly surprised.

Who could have thought that Hei Cheng's final obsession before his death was actually Su Xian Er.

It could be seen he truly loved Su Xian Er and even during the moments of his death, what he thought of was still her.

Humans were truly complicated creatures.

Turbulent events occurred over time, most people did not understand themselves fully even until their deaths.

"Little Lan, you have returned." Su Xian Er's familial emotion looked at Hei Lou Lan with love.

"Mother." Su Xian Er softly called out, then ordered the land spirit.

The land spirit brought the three to another part of the blessed land in an instant.

The land spirit's movement ability signified this blessed land had a lot of space path dao marks. Fang Yuan's Star Form blessed land had few space path dao marks, so Star Form land spirit did not have the ability to teleport.

Boom, Fang Yuan placed down Luo Po valley.

Fairy Li Shan could not help but smile at the completion of this task: "Fang Yuan, you have Dang Hun Mountain, I have Miniscule Mountain, and Little Lan has Luo Po valley. Haha, this is interesting, we actually have possession of three secluded domains of heaven and earth!"

Gazing at the Luo Po valley below him, Fang Yuan also could not help but reveal some look of expectation.

Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po valley were proclaimed by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable as the two treasures of soul path cultivation. Fang Yuan was already gaining endless profits from Dang Hun Mountain. He wondered how this Luo Po valley would make him grow.

Chapter 954: Blue

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House, discussion hall.

There were fifteen Gu Immortals in the sect, more than half of them had come in person.

This was a rare sight.

There were meetings held in the sect quite often, Gu Immortals only needed to participate with their will or emotion.

But now, there were eight Gu Immortals who came in person, including the only two rank eight Gu Immortals in Spirit Affinity House.

The reason for this situation was Feng Jiu Ge's disappearance.

Spirit Affinity House's Gu Immortals felt uneasy and uncertain towards the future.

"This time, we gathered everyone here to declare important information." Spirit Affinity House's first supreme elder sat at the main seat as she looked around, speaking solemnly.

Spirit Affinity House was very different from the other nine sects in one aspect.

They had a high proportion of female immortals.

Spirit Affinity House had ten female Gu Immortals, but only five male Gu Immortals.

Spirit Affinity House's first supreme elder and second supreme elder were both female rank eight immortals.

At this moment, everyone's attentions were focused on first supreme elder.

First supreme elder was expressionless, but second supreme elder beside her had a grim expression.

The Gu Immortals observed their reactions and had a very bad feeling.

As expected, first supreme elder's following words were like a huge rock crashing into their hearts.

"It has been confirmed, Feng Jiu Ge has died in Northern Plains. He died inside the winds of assimilation, he did not leave behind anything but two words written in blood."

All of the immortals' hearts sank.

Fairy Bai Qing, who attended the meeting personally, felt her head spinning as her expression paled.

Even though they were mentally prepared, when they heard the news, everything still found it unbelievable.

Feng Jiu Ge, who was so strong, actually died in Northern Plains. In contrast, the Gu Immortals who were weaker than him were alive and returned to their sects.

Honestly speaking, when Feng Jiu Ge went to Northern Plains, nobody expected this ending.

Since long ago, Feng Jiu Ge's strength was ingrained into everyone's minds. He was the face of Spirit Affinity House, he had even become a symbol.

Now that he was dead, the immortals felt dejected and empty inside.

Even those who were against him, Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying, had the same feelings.

First supreme elder continued: "Look at the information path Gu worms in front of you, the details are recorded inside, take a look."

The Gu Immortals looked into the Gu worms.

"Sigh, Lord Feng Jiu Ge died in the winds of assimilation, it was not an unworthy death." Long after, a Gu Immortal broke the silence in the hall.

Fairy Bai Qing's eyes were shut, her body was trembling slightly, the intense pain and grief engulfed her like a tsunami.

She loved Feng Jiu Ge so deeply, and Feng Jiu Ge loved her just as much.

Her mind was filled with the scene before he left. To think that it was the last time she would see him!

People were often played by destiny.

Right now, she was alive while he was dead, she was in Central Continent while he perished in Northern Plains!

Fairy Bai Qing did not dare to open her eyes, she was afraid that her tears would flow out uncontrollably if she did.

She tried to think of her daughter and said to herself internally: "Bai Qing, oh Bai Qing, you must stay strong. At this time, you cannot let others see your weakness!"

She took a few deep breaths, slowly opening her eyes. Her eyes were watery and had redness in them.

At this moment, the immortals in the hall were discussing Feng Jiu Ge's final action.

"Before Feng Jiu Ge died, he wrote 'Bo Qing' on his palm, what was he trying to say?"

"In my opinion, this lead is very important. Feng Jiu Ge must have understood something while under the immense pressure of death. It is a pity that he was already beyond saving when he met Zhao Lian Yun, he did not have the strength to speak anymore, he only left this clue for us."

"Feng Jiu Ge was investigating the truth behind the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, what does that have to do with Bo Qing?"

"Feng Jiu Ge and Bo Qing are very similar people. Of course, Bo Qing was much stronger than him, he was at the peak of Central Continent, even Heavenly Court Gu Immortals had to bow to him. At that time, Spirit Affinity House was at its most glorious period! Back then, many people thought highly of him, that he would become a sword path Immortal Venerable. It was a pity that he failed in the end."

"We all know about Bo Qing's information. What I want to know is, why did Feng Jiu Ge write his name before dying? What was he trying to tell us?"

The hall became silent, a Gu Immortal opened their mouth: "Did everyone forget? In the information returned, Feng Jiu Ge had fought against Qin Bai Sheng who used five finger fist heart sword. This killer move was created by Bo Qing, it was his signature killer move."

"Feng Jiu Ge was trying to say that the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was related to Bo Qing?"

"According to my deduction, he should have thought that since the other party had five finger fist heart sword, they must be related to Bo Qing in some way. Bo Qing was a Gu Immortal of Spirit Affinity House, we will have an advantage in investigating it, this is an important lead."

"That is indeed the case, back then, Bo Qing died under the tribulation, not even his ashes were left. How can his killer move be used by a Northern Plains Gu Immortal?"

The Gu Immortal talked about it for a while, they had all sorts of ideas, but none were reliable.

First supreme elder raised her hand, her action made the hall turn quiet.

"No matter what, we have to investigate Bo Qing's matter. I will pass this mission to you, Bai Qing."

Hearing first supreme elder call her name, Fairy Bai Qing turned around and looked at first supreme elder, agreeing.

These was her husband's final words before dying!

Fairy Bai Qing would exert all her efforts to investigate this lead, and find the truth.

"Only we will know about Feng Jiu Ge's death, conceal it as much as possible. Whoever leaks this information will be come under trial as a traitor of the sect!" First supreme elder called out coldly: "Next, we will talk about the forces that are under our sect's control in Central Continent."

Feng Jiu Ge's death created many problems for Spirit Affinity House.

Even though the sect had two rank eight Gu Immortals, unless they were in a perilous situation, these two Gu Immortals would not move easily.

There were many reasons.

Firstly, rank eight cultivation level was like treading on thin ice, the Gu Immortals would be very careful, and spend all their efforts on the tribulations. If they were careless, and lost their battle strength from fighting, they would die under the terrifying might of the tribulations.

Secondly, the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent had a sole origin, that was Heavenly Court. With Heavenly Court around, the conflicts of the ten great ancient sects would never escalate, they did not require rank eight Gu Immortals to intervene.

Thus, in the world of Central Continent's Gu Immortals, or even in all five regions, the most active ones were rank seven Gu Immortals and rank six Gu Immortals.

And among rank sevens, the invincible Feng Jiu Ge was important beyond words for the sect.

Because of his existence, Spirit Affinity House could expand to such a size, and occupy countless precious resource points.

With Feng Jiu Ge's demise, Spirit Affinity House was much less of a threat towards the other sects. The resources that they controlled were like pieces of delicious meat that attracted countless greedy gazes.

"Xuanwu mountain range has rich resources, it is a treasury of immortal materials, at least one rank seven Gu Immortal needs to guard it."

"The mining inside the golden sand cave has reached a critical moment, we have already invested a huge amount of time and resources into it, now is the time we reap our harvest, we should not give it up."

"Reincarnation Battlefield is most important..."

The Gu Immortals felt headaches, they had too large of a sphere of influence but too few Gu Immortals. Even if they were split their forces up to defend everywhere, they still had insufficient numbers.

At this time, they finally realized that Feng Jiu Ge's reputation was such a huge deterrence to the outside world.

Fairy Bai Qing was silent.

The Gu Immortals were talking about immortal materials or other resources constantly, nobody talked about Feng Jiu Ge anymore.

It was as if Feng Jiu Ge's existence ended with the discussion of the two words 'Bo Qing'.

Fairy Bai Qing felt some sadness towards this, "Husband, oh husband, you made so many contributions to the sect, yet in the end, these people forget about you in an instant."

In the entire process of the discussion, Fairy Bai Qing's mind was not focused on it.

The immortals could tell and understood why, even the strict first supreme elder did not criticize her.

Only when the immortals mentioned Zhao Lian Yun did Fairy Bai Qing's eyes light up, showing deep concern.

If Feng Jiu Ge was still around, Feng Jiu Ge would almost certainly become Spirit Affinity House's next generation fairy. But now that Feng Jiu Ge was gone, and Zhao Lian Yun appeared out of nowhere, she became Feng Jin Huang's greatest threat.

Fairy Bai Qing doted on her daughter, of course, thus she was very concerned about Zhao Lian Yun's matters.

She heard the Gu Immortals discuss:

"Zhao Lian Yun inherited two Thieving Heaven true inheritances, did anything change in her?"

"Otherworldly demons cannot be trusted!"

"Divine concealment, ghostly concealment, these two are top tier defensive immortal killer moves, we are still researching on them... with our current progress, it is profound and unfathomable! These two immortal killer moves have formed two layers of dao marks cloaking Zhao Lian Yun's soul, I have never seen such a unique usage of dao marks!"

"These two layers of dao marks will always protect Zhao Lian Yun. We tried many methods to deduce her, but there is no effect. We as Gu Immortals are deducing a mortal, but we failed to get anything. If I did not experience it myself, I would not believe it."

"Did you all notice? Divine concealment and ghostly concealment are top tier defensive killer moves that do not expend immortal essence. They are like fortune rivalling heaven Gu, the power of venerables are truly hard to comprehend."

"Hiding from the deductions of thoughts, wills, and emotions, this is the defensive effect of divine concealment. Then what about ghostly concealment?"

"That is still unclear, we have tried many methods. Oh, Zhao Lian Yun was very cooperative during the entire process. I feel that even though she is an otherworldly demon, she knows how to behave properly, she can be nurtured."

"This little fellow wants to save her lover. Hehe, but sadly, according to our intelligence, Old Ancestor Xue Hu has already gathered enough immortal materials, he will start the refinement soon."

Finally, first supreme elder concluded this meeting: "Continue researching, and also increase Zhao Lian Yun's attachment to our sect. I am looking forward to her future!"

At the same time, in a nameless forest.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie looked at a mirror to communicate with someone.

There was a vague elderly figure in the mirror.

He spoke slowly: "All the preparations are in place. But Heavenly Court has already completed their last process of repairing fate Gu, you have to act in advance now."

"Understood." Seven Star Child immortal zombie said solemnly.

"Be careful, Vice Envoy Blue." The figure in the mirror spoke again.

Seven Star Child did not speak, he stopped activating this information path immortal killer move and the mirror vanished.

Next, he turned around and entered deep into the forest without looking back.

Chapter 955: Swords Traverse Central Continent

The scene was quiet and dark.

Under the hazy moonlight, shadows of trees seemed to be dancing.

The occasional breeze, the cries of birds and the growls of beasts felt like the sleep talking of this mountain range.

Lanterns were lit in a cabin in the mountain valley, giving off a dim light.

Feng Jin Huang lay on the bed, weak and pale without a trace of rosiness on her face.

She looked at Fairy Bai Qing who was sitting at the edge of the bed, and apologized: "Mother, I made a mistake, I will not do it again..."

Fairy Bai Qing was grave: "Huang Er, I know what you are thinking about. You are cultivating so desperately that you have already injured yourself five or six times over these last dozens of days. I have warned you when you began cultivating, you need to be act according to what is natural and be in control. But what you are doing is going for more haste, which is instead causing you to progress slowly, you might even collapse and endanger your life as well!"

Feng Jin Huang lowered her eyelids, speaking quietly: "Mother, I am sorry."

"I have already placed Gu in your body, as punishment, you cannot cultivate for seven days and seven nights and you can only move around this mountain valley. If you are hungry, you can pick up wild fruits, if you are thirsty, you can go drink from the mountain spring. Think properly over these days." Fairy Bai Qing said in a heavy voice.

"Mother, don't!" Feng Jin Huang was very anxious.

However, Fairy Bai Qing brushed her sleeves at Feng Jin Huang's cheek.

Immediately, an intense sleepiness attacked Feng Jin Huang's mind.

Her eyelids were extremely heavy and she felt so exhausted that she was not able to say anything.

In the blink of an eye, she fell into a deep sleep.

Seeing her daughter in a deep sleep but still frowning slightly, Fairy Bai Qing was sad and worried.

Fairy Bai Qing had not informed Feng Jin Huang of Feng Jiu Ge's death.

On one hand, Spirit Affinity House wanted to conceal the news for as long as possible to make arrangements more easily. Feng Jin Huang, a mortal, was not qualified to know. After all, prying information from mortals were much easier than prying information from Gu Immortals.

Secondly, Fairy Bai Qing did not know how she could inform her.

Why was Feng Jin Huang cultivating so desperately? She was working hard to advance further, to become stronger so that she could look for her father and save him.

How could Fairy Bai Qing tell the cruel truth to Feng Jin Huang?

She could not bear to.

"Sigh..." As she looked at her daughter's face, Fairy Bai Qing heaved a long sigh.

Her normally upright posture and dignified white robe, in this dim light, looked weak and dull.

She was truly tired.

Only now did she remove the disguise and revealed her true emotions.

Fairy Bai Qing softly caressed Feng Jin Huang's cheek. The love and affection in her gaze could even melt iron.

Feng Jin Huang's appearance combined the good features of Feng Jiu Ge and Fairy Bai Qing.

In her face, Fairy Bai Qing could vaguely see Feng Jiu Ge's image.

Feng Jiu Ge was dead, Feng Jin Huang was now her only sustenance to keep on living.

In such a silent gaze, time passed and light was already shining in from outside the cabin.

The light of dawn made Fairy Bai Qing realize the passing of time, she had to set out now.

She stood up slowly, taking slow steps towards the outside, and closed the door carefully.

She looked at the cabin in the valley deeply, murmuring to herself: "Huang Er, wait seven days for mother, you need to take care of yourself during this period and calm your mind."

Fairy Bai Qing was not worried about Feng Jin Huang's safety.

After all, this was Spirit Affinity House's central region.

Even if there were internal fights in the sect, they were limited and a move would not be made against Feng Jin Huang.

Fairy Bai Qing stepped on the clouds and mist, flying towards the north-west direction.

Her destination was the source of Falling Heavenly River.

Why was she going there?

She had received the sect mission to investigate Bo Qing, the clue left behind by Feng Jiu Ge.

Bo Qing had been a Gu Immortal of Spirit Affinity House and the sect had large amounts of records on him which Fairy Bai Qing had looked through.

In her investigation, Fairy Bai Qing discovered Bo Qing's experiences were actually extremely similar to Feng Jiu Ge's. What made her even more interested was Bo Qing's lover, Mo Yao.

Mo Yao had been the fairy of that generation of Spirit Affinity House, and unlike those of other generations, she was an inkman and not a human.

But even so, Bo Qing and Mo Yao had fallen in love with each other at first sight.

"Bo Qing might not have entered Northern Plains, but Mo Yao went to Northern Plains, even entering Imperial Court blessed land. Could Mo Yao be involved in the plan of destroying Eighty-Eight True Yang Building?"

Fairy Bai Qing knew the reason that Mo Yao risked entering Imperial Court blessed land was to help her husband, Bo Qing, pass his tribulation.

Back then, the peak rank eight Bo Qing was about to face tribulation to breakthrough to the rank nine level. Such a huge event had not only attracted the attention of Central Continent, but also the other four regions.

Unfortunately, at the end, Bo Qing died, perishing in the terrifying tribulation. And Mo Yao also perished with him.

In fact, all the Gu Immortals of Central Continent knew of this.

Fairy Bai Qing had also heard of this many times in the past.

But now, as she recalled, she got a different feeling, as if they were in the same boat.

She even envied Mo Yao, even in death, she had died together with her husband. Both had not let each other down, they were a couple who were greatly in love with each other and had died worthy deaths.

Fairy Bai Qing repeatedly investigated and racked her brains, but was not able to make much progress. She discovered some clues in the records of the sect, all pointing towards the same place — the source of the Falling Heavenly River.

As there was no breakthrough in other aspects, Fairy Bai Qing decisively moved towards Falling Heavenly River to search for more clues.

The source of Falling Heavenly River was the place where Bo Qing had perished in the past.

Spirit Affinity House was quite far away from the source of Falling Heavenly River.

If Fairy Bai Qing relied on her own methods, she would take up to a year to reach there.

She naturally would not do so and had already made sufficient preparations before leaving.

She flew rapidly, using Spirit Affinity House's Gu formations constantly on the way to transport her, in one use, she could travel over a hundred thousand li, saving a large amount of time.

She did not directly move towards the direction of the source of Falling Heavenly River, instead moving towards Myriad Dragon Dock.

In the range of Myriad Dragon Dock's force, she used their transportation Gu formations to speed up her journey. She had already communicated with Myriad Dragon Dock's Gu Immortals, and although she paid a high price, she was able to further save a large amount of time.

She moved smoothly towards Falling Heavenly River, after Myriad Dragon Dock's territory, Fairy Bai Qing stepped into the territory of Combat Immortal Sect.

Just like before, she used their transportation Gu formations to speed up her journey.

A day and a night later, the fatigued Fairy Bai Qing was finally only a thousand li away from the source of Falling Heavenly River.

In front of her was an enormous waterfall that fell from an endless height.

A boundless expanse of water heavily crashed at the riverbed.

The rumbling noise of the waterfall was like the continuous crackling of thunder.

Endless water vapor formed dense fog that shrouded a vast range of the surroundings.

Why was it called Falling Heavenly River?

Falling Heavenly River, a giant river that fell from the heavens.

Compared to this enormous river, Fairy Bai Qing was minute like an ant.

Fairy Bai Qing had already seen Falling Heavenly River when she had traveled with Feng Jiu Ge in the past.

Right now, as she looked at this enormous river again, she could not avoid thinking about Feng Jiu Ge, feeling distressed.

She still remembered what Feng Jiu Ge said to her at that time.

It was about the reason for the formation of Falling Heavenly River.

Feng Jiu Ge had confidently told Fairy Bai Qing that there were two opinions about this.

One was that Falling Heavenly River itself was a form of calamity or tribulation, while the second said that when Bo Qing had resisted his tribulation, his sword light was so sharp that it instantly pierced through white heaven to black heaven.

And Bo Qing had faced his tribulation during daytime.

Thus this sword light had pierced a huge hole in white heaven, continuing on to black heaven, where it formed a small hole in the bottom layer of black heaven.

It just so happened that above these two holes was a majestic heavenly river.

The heavenly river followed the path between these two holes and crashed down to Central Continent, forming an inland sea; at the same time, the river surged and opened a path, forming the first river that traversed through Central Continent's mainland.

Fairy Bai Qing had asked, which was more reasonable between these two opinions?

Feng Jiu Ge had answered with a smile: "I am also not too sure. But the second opinion can explain the change in the water flow. During daytime, the Falling Heavenly River flows with extremely strong momentum, even rank eight Gu Immortals are unable to resist this momentum. And during night, the flow of Falling Heavenly River slows down to the extent rank seven Gu Immortals can just barely resist it."

Nature's might was boundless and peerless. Even Gu Immortals appeared insignificant when compared to it.

Ending her recollection, Fairy Bai Qing's gaze focused.

She had borrowed many water path Immortal Gu for this trip, to help her enter Falling Heavenly River.

However, it was clearly impossible to do that during the day, Fairy Bai Qing was a rank seven Gu Immortal, her only opportunity was to enter during night and search for clues.

It was still daytime right now, Fairy Bai Qing reduced her speed and slowly neared Falling Heavenly River.

She intended to wait for nightfall before she entered the riverbed.

Time passed, the sun gradually set in the west, red streaks of colors overlapped in the horizon and the radiance of the setting sun shone on Fairy Bai Qing's face.

Suddenly, she opened her eyes, looking at the distant Falling Heavenly River with astonishment.

Roar!

Water gurgled as a giant beast stretched out its head from under the river, revealing the tips of its horns.

This was an enormous bull head, the horns were curved.

"Immemorial desolate beast myriad eyes clear bull!" Fairy Bai Qing was pale as she recognized this fierce beast's identity.

Falling Heavenly River was not safe.

Besides the majestic waterfall, there were also large amounts of ancient desolate beasts and immemorial desolate beasts living inside.

The myriad eyes clear bull was an immemorial desolate beast and one of the overlords that lived at the riverbed of Falling Heavenly River.

"Doesn't it normally stay at the riverbed and patrol its territory? Why has it suddenly come out of the river?" Fairy Bai Qing was puzzled, but she quickly retreated, maintaining some distance with this myriad eyes clear bull.

Immemorial desolate beasts had rank eight battle strength.

Fairy Bai Qing could not defeat this giant bull.

Moreover, her main objective here was not to hunt.

Fairy Bai Qing was cautious while sighing at her bad luck. With the myriad eyes clear bull's appearance, she had an ominous feeling.

Right as she was about to distance herself further from the myriad eyes clear bull, a sword light suddenly came out from the riverbed.

Like a thunderbolt, it pierced through the myriad eyes clear bull.

This sturdy and tough immemorial desolate beast was instantly cut into two by the sword light.

Endless blood and internal organs splattered out, dying the nearby river blood red.

Whoosh!

Before Fairy Bai Qing was able to react, another sword light flew out, slashing at the river bank.

The next moment, a long gash was slashed open on the ground, like it was a delicate tofu, and large amounts of water flowed towards the space rapidly.

The river water overflowed, all of the surroundings were covered with water.

Fairy Bai Qing was extremely shocked.

What was going on?

What was this situation?

The sword light had such power that its terrifying might had reached an extreme. The immemorial desolate beast had been cut down as easily as a vegetable.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Countless sword lights shot out from below the Falling Heavenly River.

Like fireworks, the sword lights flew everywhere, leaving Falling Heavenly River before rapidly disappearing from Fairy Bai Qing's sight.

Swords traverse Central Continent!

Chapter 956: World Shaking Might

Central Continent, centipede valley.

A terrifying chase was happening in the narrow ravine on the mountain road.

"Quickly run, quickly run!" A miniman laid down on Hong Yi's head as it shouted anxiously.

"It hurts, it hurts! Don't pull my hair." Hong Yi screamed in pain.

The miniman did not pay attention to what he said, it subconsciously grabbed onto Hong Yi's hair and turned back to look.

"Damn it! It is already here, quickly leave, if you are not fast enough, we will be eaten by it." The miniman called out frantically.

"I also want to move faster..." Hong Yi gritted his teeth, exerting all his effort to use his movement Gu. Unfortunately, his cultivation level was too low, at only rank two upper stage.

Of course, this cultivation level was already very rare at Hong Yi's age.

Ever since the Refinement Path Convention, Hong Yi had obtained some lucky opportunities and his cultivation speed far surpassed others.

But in this current moment of danger, rank two upper stage cultivation level was useless against the wild rank five golden horn centipede chasing behind him.

This centipede had a huge body, it was like a large python. It had a sharp horn on its head, when it moved on the ground, its hundreds of legs stomped, its body twisted as it moved rapidly.

"We're finished! It is already right behind you." The miniman was pale from shock, it was terror-stricken.

"I'll risk it!!" Hong Yi could also feel the golden horn centipede getting closer, the hair over his body was standing on end from fear, he had no choice but to use his only killer move.

This killer move was a movement killer move.

But Hong Yi had only obtained it recently, he had not practiced with it for long enough.

When he used it, the success rate and failure rate was fifty percent each.

Killer moves required at least two Gu worms to activate. The more Gu worms there were, the more complicated the steps involved, and the greater difficulty in activating it, but the power of the move also normally increased.

Hong Yi's new movement killer move was formed by nearly ten mortal Gu.

It was not comparable to a Gu Immortal, but for Gu Masters, this was a relatively huge number of Gu.

Killer moves were not so easy to practice.

When the activation of the killer move fails, the Gu Master or the Gu worms might receive damage.

Thus, normally, Hong Yi was very careful every time he practiced this killer move.

But at this time, his life was in critical danger, he could not care anymore.

His original speed was not enough for him to break free from the golden horn centipede, he was sure to die.

Right now, there was only one way left, he had to risk it!

"Activate, I must succeed!" Hong Yi screamed in his mind.

But wishes were wonderful, reality was cruel.

Activating killer moves required intense concentration, some killer moves needed special environments and could not be disturbed.

Fang Yuan could easily use his killer moves because he had a huge amount of experience in the five hundred years of his previous life, but Hong Yi was a newbie.

At this time, he was in danger, he had to pay attention to the path in front of him as the mountain was full of rocks and pitfalls, he was running rapidly, if he fell, his life would be over.

On the other hand, Hong Yi was chased by the golden horn centipede. The intense commotion behind him was ringing in his ears, he was engulfed in the aura of death, how could Hong Yi be unaffected by it?

Under this situation, those who could remain calm and absolutely focused were experienced experts who had already undergone countless battles and had disregarded the fear of death. Hong Yi could reach this stage eventually, but he was too young now.

"It's catching up, it's catching up!" The miniman on top of his head screamed in fear as it looked at the golden horn centipede, shortening the gap between them with a fierce demeanor.

The centipede was heavy and had a huge body, it had hundreds of legs and a huge mouth, saliva splattered everywhere as it bit at Hong Yi.

The miniman screamed tragically, it shut its eyes in fear.

Even though it had wings, they were broken already, it could not fly.

It had succeeded in stealing the rank five Gu material hundred flower dew during this exploration into the cave. But there was a price to pay for this, it had attracted the animosity of the golden horn centipede which was guarding the dew. Thus, the miniman could only escape with Hong Yi, trying to get away using his superior speed.

However, the miniman did not feel any pain.

It opened its eyes, showing disbelief.

For some reason, Hong Yi had escaped from the golden horn centipede's bite.

But at the next moment, the golden horn centipede chased them again.

The miniman was scared, but it could see clearly now.

The reason was, whenever the golden horn centipede tried to bite Hong Yi, it would subconsciously raise its head first.

This action would cause its head to go dozens of meters above the ground, half of its body would be elevated from the ground as well, before it landed heavily.

When the centipede raised its head, many of its legs would leave the ground, its speed would fall.

But at this time, Hong Yi was still running without lowering his speed.

Thus, Hong Yi could evade the golden horn centipede every time it attacked.

"This fool!" The miniman laughed heartily, it felt an intense joy in escaping from mortal danger.

Man is the spirit of all beings, wild Gu worms had limited intelligence, their movements were decided by instincts.

"I was kind enough to escape with you, but you call me a fool!" Hong Yi was displeased.

"I am not scolding you, I am talking about this golden horn centipede, you fool!" The miniman shouted.

Hong Yi was still nursing displeasure: "You are the fool, I said the centipede was sleeping, you should not have been afraid and simply should have stolen the hundred flower dew and escaped, but you had to scream for no reason!"

The miniman's cheeks puffed up, guilt flashed across its eyes as it showed an embarrassed expression.

It wanted to rebuke him, but at the next moment, its eyes opened wide in shock.

It turned out, the golden horn centipede behind saw that it could not bite Hong Yi, it changed its attack method, using its golden horn.

Of course, it had not become smarter.

The reason was, during its long life, the golden horn centipede had encountered some large prey that it could not swallow, in that situation, the golden horn centipede would use its horn to slice the prey up into pieces.

Opening its mouth to bite was the golden horn centipede's instinct, using the golden horn was also an instinct.

The golden horn centipede pounced harshly, lowering its head and stabbing its horn forward, soon approaching... Hong Yi's butt.

This was unavoidable because of its size.

"Fool, run!" The miniman saw this dangerous situation and shuddered in fear, it could not even grab onto the hair firmly.

"You still are calling me a fool — oh!" Hong Yi shouted, but suddenly, his pitch became higher, like a rooster who was grabbed by the neck. There was shock, unpreparedness, and intense pain in his voice.

The golden horn had already stabbed into Hong Yi's buttocks.

The miniman was full of despair, it thought that this was it!

But at this moment, Hong Yi's speed suddenly rose by a huge amount.

He shot out like a cannonball!

The reason was, when he was screaming, the intense pain gave him a moment of inspiration and he successfully used the killer move in an instant.

Hong Yi escaped as a result.

"Bleeding, you are bleeding." The miniman screamed loudly to Hong Yi.

It turned out that the golden horn centipede had already stabbed Hong Yi's buttocks, but because Hong Yi burst out in an instant, the two sides had been separated by a distance again.

It was as if a dagger was pulled out of Hong Yi's buttocks, the wound was unstopped and started bleeding.

"My butt hurts! Ahhhh, its so painful!!" At this moment, Hong Yi's mind was filled with an intense thought.

He subconsciously grabbed his butt, applying pressure on the wound.

However, naturally because he was feeling pain from his injury, his mind was distracted again.

The killer move that he had activated earlier fell apart, and his speed dropped again.

But the golden horn centipede was still chasing him.

The golden horn stabbed into his other buttcheek.

"Ah!" Hong Yi screamed again.

But the same thing happened again.

The powerful attack, the sudden pain, Hong Yi's focus reached another peak, he used the killer move again.

He sprinted again.

"You're bleeding, you're bleeding!" The miniman screamed.

There was no choice, the two wounds were very deep, because of Hong Yi's intense movement, it was no wonder that blood spewed out!

Hong Yi grabbed his buttocks as the golden horn centipede chased relentlessly, he was in such a helpless situation.

"Oh no, my primeval essence is running out!" Suddenly, Hong Yi's expression paled.

Gu Masters had little primeval essence in the first place, it was easily used up. Activating killer moves meant using many Gu worms, the expenditure was great. After running for such a long time, Hong Yi reached his limits.

Death was approaching, Hong Yi was forced into a desperate situation, there was no way to live.

"Are we going to die? Are we going to die? Lord centipede, don't eat me. I am so small, I have little meat, eat him, eat that fool." The miniman was muttering senselessly while grabbing Hong Yi's hair.

At this moment, Hong Yi was feeling empty inside, he did not bother to respond to this miniman.

But suddenly, sword light that shook the world flashed!

In an instant, the world turned white, everything turned silent.

The sudden change did not make Hong Yi stop running, he kept running for a while before he realized something amiss.

Looking back, he was shocked.

The rank five golden horn centipede Gu was no longer present, it had vanished completely.

Along with it, half of centipede valley had vanished!

What was in front of him was a huge and deep trench. The sides of the trench were extremely smooth, like a mirror.

"This, what is going on?" Hong Yi was lost for words, he could not believe it.

"Just, just that sword light..." The miniman was completely stunned.

Central Continent, east coast.

Waves crashed, rumbling non-stop, frost energy oozed out in the surrounding area.

"Youngsters, we are here. This is profound ice island, the place where Flying Frost Sect is located. This will be where you live from now on, the place where you change your destiny." The leading Gu Master pointed at the ice island and proudly introduced this.

The youngsters raised their heads, looking forward.

Some had shining eyes, some were extremely excited.

Even though Flying Frost Sect did not have any Gu Immortals and was not a super force, within a huge surrounding area, it was the supreme overlord, the only force that could contest it was Five Virtues Sect.

Not long ago, when the Central Continent Refinement Path Convention was held, Flying Frost Sect was one of the venues for participation.

Because of this, the reputation of Flying Frost Sect had spread widely.

"This time, the children here have the highest aptitude for the last ten years. They are the future of the sect, nurture them well, they will make us stronger." The leading Gu Master saw these children and felt very excited.

The leading Gu Master said loudly: "Youngsters, it is your fortune to be able to become Flying Frost Sect's disciples. Now, let me tell you..."

Swoosh!

At this time, sword light flashed, everyone was blinded momentarily, they all shut their eyes.

When they opened their eyes, everyone was stunned, their opened their mouths and were still like statues with exaggerated expressions.

The huge profound ice island was gone, in its place, there was a deep trench that appeared in their vision.

Even the sea water was split apart!

On the surface of the sea, a path of five to six li in length had been completely emptied of water, the lingering sword path dao marks were extremely overbearing, blocking the water path dao marks and preventing the water from filling up the gap.

At once, a weird but domineering scene was formed!

Heavenly Court.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord held his walking stick as he stood below Heaven Overseeing Tower shakily.

His other hand was holding fate Gu, his old wrinkled hand was gently rubbing fate Gu.

This time, fate Gu was successfully repaired to a great extent, Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord was extremely excited and happy.

The ones who had repaired it with him, Bai Cang Shui, Lian Jiu Sheng, and Bi Chen Tian had already left Heavenly Court, going to the mortal world.

The Gu Immortals in Heavenly Court mostly used sleeping as their lifespan extension method. After waking up, they had to make good use of their time, going to their sects and settling some private matters, or to take care of their blood related descendants in the sect.

Heavenly Court controlled the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, but at the same time, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were also chosen from the ten great ancient sects.

In the structure of sects, Heavenly Court was like the upper level sect, and the ten great ancient sects were the lower level sects.

Not all Gu Immortals had the chance to join Heavenly Court.

Other than having deep attainment in their paths, great battle strength and reaching rank eight cultivation level, there was also additional important criteria to join Heavenly Court.

That was their values!

Heavenly Court.

What was Heavenly Court?

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable had described it three million years ago, it was —

Following the will of heaven, and upholding justice for heaven!

"After this restoration, fate Gu can use half of its might. Using Heaven Overseeing Tower, we can find more people who escaped from fate. Eliminating these people will help in repairing fate Gu, this can allow more people to be found and result in a beneficial cycle, as long as this progresses, Heaven Overseeing Tower will regain its former glory!"

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord was filled with anticipation, he was about to step into Heaven Overseeing Tower again.

Rumble!

A sword light shot over like a flash of lightning. In no time, it sliced through Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's mouth was opened wide, his pupils shrunk to pin size.

His body was extremely stiff, he saw that the upper half of Heaven Overseeing Tower slowly tilted and crashed onto the jade floor.

"Heaven Overseeing Tower!!" After being stunned momentarily, Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord screamed loudly.

Chapter 957: Rising Commotion

"It finally stopped." Fairy Bai Qing looked at the tranquil river surface, her face pale with lingering fear.

When the sword lights rampaged, she was nearest to the source and had personally witnessed this heaven shaking scene.

Right now, Falling Heavenly River was filled with corpses.

Large quantities of mutilated body parts of ancient desolate beasts and immemorial desolate beasts bobbed up and down in the river.

The surging white heavenly river water was now dyed blood red.

Although Falling Heavenly River came from the heavens, the river water was filled with vitality. Countless ferocious beasts lived within and propagated, large numbers of aquatic plants grew within and there were also countless hidden currents, whirlpools and other natural traps which even a Gu Immortal could die from.

Fairy Bai Qing waited for some moments, no more sword lights appeared.

She ran to the river and picked up the corpses of the beasts, and the branches and roots of ancient desolate plants and immemorial desolate plants.

She had truly earned a fortune!

The fortune was so huge even she could not help being joyous.

But the happiness did not last long, many ancient desolate beasts began to show up, Fairy Bai Qing could even vaguely see some faint images of ancient desolate beasts through the river water.

These beasts' ferocity was stimulated by the bloodied water.

The flesh and bones cut apart by the sword light were excellent delicacies to these beasts.

More and more beasts were attracted over by the blood and flesh, leading to a fierce battle.

They tore at each other as they battled for food, raising frightening waves.

Fairy Bai Qing had no choice but to retreat, over half the original quantity of corpses remained, she looked at them with much regret. These were all excellent Gu refinement materials!

"The sword lights shot out so suddenly, what happened in Falling Heavenly River? Should I enter to explore and find the reasons or not?"

Fairy Bai Qing was held back by the thought of Feng Jin Huang, thus she hesitated.

However, she had a feeling that Bo Qing's clues should be in the riverbed of Falling Heavenly River.

Fairy Bai Qing gritted her teeth, turning into a white light, shooting straight into Falling Heavenly River.

From Falling Heavenly River's source, unrivaled sword lights had shot out everywhere, their range covering the whole of Central Continent.

Whether it was the centipede valley in Central Continent's central region, or Flying Frost Sect in the east, or even Heavenly Court which was high above, they were all affected by the sword lights.

The whole of Central Continent was in a commotion.

Heavenly Court.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's face was ashen, his hand moved without stopping, he had immediately started restoring Heaven Overseeing Tower when he had gotten out of his shocked state.

He had already sent a message to Bi Chen Tian, Bai Cang Shui and Lian Jiu Sheng, urgently recalling them.

Right now, they were already on their way.

The damage created by the sword light was extremely troublesome, its sword path dao marks seemed to contain a corrosive nature. The remaining parts of Heaven Overseeing Tower might be standing upright, but it would not last for long.

If the sword path dao marks were left to continue corroding, it would definitely lead to even more disastrous damage.

"We succeeded in our last attempt at restoring fate Immortal Gu, but when I was just about to use it, Heaven Overseeing Tower was split apart. Is this a coincidence? Or...."

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord had a bad premonition.

After a while, Bi Chen Tian was the first to return, then Bai Cang Shui and finally Lian Jiu Sheng arrived.

Lian Jiu Sheng had stopped partway through, but was thus able to bring concrete information: "I have investigated it, the sword light came from the source of Falling Heavenly River. Right now, the whole of Central Continent is in a ruckus."

"Falling Heavenly River's source, isn't that where Bo Qing died?" Bai Cang Shui exclaimed in shock.

Speaking of Bo Qing, Heavenly Court's four immortals had complicated feelings on him.

Back then, it was not that they did not try to recruit Bo Qing, but unfortunately, Bo Qing's ideals did not conform to theirs, and he did not join Heavenly Court.

"Bo Qing..." Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's gaze was dark, "Investigate, we must investigate this clearly. Fairy Cang Shui, you are specialized in water path, I will have to trouble you to make a trip. The three of us will stay here to restore Heaven Overseeing Tower. For some reason, I am having a very bad feeling about this."

The other three immortals' expressions turned serious, Bi Chen Tian spoke: "Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord, you are in charge of Heaven Overseeing Tower and fate Gu, if you are uneasy, we cannot disregard it, we need to move quickly!"

Central Continent, Combat Immortal Sect.

"Falling Heavenly River's source has changed all of a sudden, I suspect Bo Qing's sword path inheritance has appeared! Jin Lie Yang, you will go to investigate the truth. You can bring two rank six Gu Immortals, choose whoever you want." Combat Immortal Sect's first supreme elder's will floated in mid-air.

Gu Immortal Jin Lie Yang was sitting within fire. He was tall and well-built, with golden hair and fiery eyes, and a vigorous rank seven aura.

Hearing what was said, he instead snorted, not giving any face to the first supreme elder: "You should go find Shi Lei for this matter, he is the Immortal Monkey King, with Feng Jiu Ge no longer alive, he is now the strongest among Central Continent's rank seven Gu Immortals!"

First supreme elder's will smiled: "Jin Lie Yang, Shi Lei might be strong, but he is not the only person in Combat Immortal Sect. He has already made more than enough contributions in the exploration of Starry Sky grotto-heaven, could it be that you want him to make more contributions?"

An idea came to Jin Lie Yang and he suddenly became convinced.

He leaped out of the fire, and cupped his fists: "Heh! First supreme elder is correct. I had thought of growing another seventeen or eighteen fire path dao marks, but since that is the case, I will immediately move out!"

First supreme elder's will nodded, instructing: "Go and return quickly."

Wind Cloud Manor.

"First senior brother, you came out of seclusion?" Gu Immortal Hong Chi Ming immediately greeted the person in front of him with great joy.

This person was clothed in a white robe and was wearing a jade belt. He was tall and thin, elegance and harmoniousness seemed to be expressed in him. He smiled and nodded: "I came out because of the change in Falling Heavenly River. Junior brother, you participated in the hundred days battle and personally witness five finger fist heart sword. I have been asked to go investigate the truth of Falling Heavenly River, please lend me a hand."

Hong Chi Ming took a deep breath and said sincerely: "First senior brother, you are treating me like an outsider. Back then, were it not for your help, I would not be around today. I will offer my full efforts!"

Spirit Affinity House, discussion hall.

"Should we send someone to investigate the strange change in Falling Heavenly River's source?" First supreme elder was not present, so the discussion hall was managed by second supreme elder.

"Second supreme elder, you may not be aware but Fairy Bai Qing has already gone to explore Falling Heavenly River's source a few days ago." Li Jun Ying's will spoke.

"Oh? Did she discover some clues?" A Gu Immortal unavoidably recalled the matters discussed.

Second supreme elder frowned: "Fairy Bai Qing only has peak rank six cultivation, it is not enough to cope with this situation. But the sect is limited on available personnel right now, who should I send to reinforce Bai Qing at this time?"

Xu Hao's will laughed: "Reporting to second supreme elder, Fairy Bai Qing has actually already advanced to rank seven, it is just that she concealed it and did not report it."

"Oh? Is that the case? I remember there was still some time before the tribulation for her advancement to rank seven."

Xu Hao calmly replied: "This matter has been confirmed. Before Feng Jiu Ge left for Northern Plains, he borrowed time path Immortal Gu to secretly help Fairy Bai Qing advance her cultivation."

"So it was like that." Second supreme elder mumbled before saying, "Fairy Bai Qing advancing to rank seven is a blessing for our Spirit Affinity House. When she returns, she shall be rewarded heavily. Also, open the storage and let her choose a rank seven Immortal Gu. As for this matter of Falling Heavenly River, there is no need to send reinforcements anymore, just message her regarding the sect's intentions."

"Yes, we will follow second supreme elder's command."

Tian Ti mountain.

"This sword light, Bo Qing, Bo Qing... the pseudo-Immortal Venerable who split the five regions with his sword, it was fortunate for the people in the world that love changed him... maybe this is the appearance of his sword path true inheritance!"

Sword path Gu Immortal Jian Yi Sheng gazed into the horizon with excitement and yearning.

"Such a huge change, Falling Heavenly River will definitely be a gathering point for Gu Immortals, maybe there will be an opportunity to fish for profits in this commotion. Central Continent's ten great ancient sects are strong and can eat the meat, but I should be able to drink some soup, right?"

As he thought of this, Jian Yi Sheng hardened his mind and flew out of Tian Ti Mountain towards the northwest.

Whether it was the righteous path led by the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, or the demonic path or lone cultivators like Jian Yi Sheng, they all started making their moves.

Countless gazes pierced through space and gathered at the source of Falling Heavenly River.

Bo Qing, a pseudo-Immortal Venerable, at the pinnacle below the venerables, this reputation that had been covered in dust resurfaced once again.

The countless sword lights that wreaked havoc throughout the whole of Central Continent reminded the world of Bo Qing's power.

A rumor, who knows from where, started spreading and kept on getting bigger, affecting everyone's mental states.

"The sword lights are the arrangements left behind by Bo Qing before he perished. He is reminding the world that his sword path true inheritance has appeared, and although he perished, he did not want his true inheritance to be obtained by the wrong person. He is using this chance to select the most suitable inheritor!"

Thereafter, the shock created from the sword lights' might, gradually turned into greed and desire.

Central Continent's Gu Immortal world was in a commotion!

Countless Gu Immortals, even the hidden old monsters, started to move towards Falling Heavenly River.

A commotion occurred in Central Continent, a huge dispute that covered the whole of Central Continent was going to unfold at Falling Heavenly River.

But in Southern Border, it was calm and tranquil.

The trees swayed in the lush green hills.

On a mountain peak, in a stone pavilion.

Old Man Yan Shi was sitting inside the pavilion, playing chess.

A giant rock was in front of him, on the smooth surface of the rock were star path dao marks that formed either horizontal cuts, vertical cuts or diagonal cuts, forming a dazzling diagram.

Below Old Man Yan Shi was actually the famous astrolabe chessboard from history.

A figure descended down from the sky, and the stone pavilion instantly filled with cold air.

"Why did you call me?" Bai Ning Bing coldly stared at the back of Old Man Yan Shi.

Old Man Yan Shi slowly turned around and faced Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing continued to speak in an icy tone: "Although you helped me in becoming a Gu Immortal, I am not a subordinate of yours who is at your beck and call."

Old Man Yan Shi smiled, speaking softly: "Do you know that Fang Yuan will be returning?"

Fang Yuan!

Bai Ning Bing's gaze turned bright, he then squinted, hiding the sharp light in his eyes.

With a cold snort, he said: "Explain it clearly."

Chapter 958: Pawn Bai Ning Bing

Looking at Old Man Yan Shi, Bai Ning Bing was very vigilant.

Ever since he had advanced to Gu Immortal, while in the process conveniently getting rid of his female body which had been troubling him for a long time, he thoroughly realized how unfathomable Old Man Yan Shi was.

Bai Ning Bing's nature was to be indifferent. But his firm attitude towards Old Man Yan Shi was only a type of probe.

Even his strong desire of wanting to fight Fang Yuan and take vicious revenge was also a disguise for himself as well as a probe towards Old Man Yan Shi.

Although only a few years had passed, Bai Ning Bing was no longer so concerned about Fang Yuan.

Being at the Gu Immortal level had broadened his horizons, he saw many more things and experienced many more wonders.

What he minded was Old Man Yan Shi in front of him, it was not that he had not secretly investigated, but Shadow Sect was still deeply concealed, not revealing a trace.

He did not know why Old Man Yan Shi was helping him, but at the same time, he was also discontent at being controlled like this.

He had thought of walking away from all of this. But Shadow Sect had spent so much effort on him, they certainly would not let him leave easily. In addition, Bai Ning Bing cared about excitement and brilliance more than his own life, when the enemy was stronger, the process was dangerous, resistance became more difficult, it instead made him feel like he had not lived in vain, taking it as a pleasure of life.

Competing against heaven, competing against earth, competing against humans, the joy was endless!

There was one thing that Bai Ning Bing had never done in his life, that was — retreating in the face of danger!

Facing Bai Ning Bing's query, Old Man Yan Shi leisurely took out an Immortal Gu and said: "You only need to do as I say and I can guarantee Fang Yuan will return to Southern Border."

Bai Ning Bing's eyes shined with coldness: "You seem to know Fang Yuan's whereabouts clearly. But in the past, when I was advancing to Gu Immortal, and I asked you the same question, you said you did not know."

Old Man Yan Shi chuckled.

He did not respond to Bai Ning Bing's query, instead continuing: "To the south of Namei peak, east of Li Qiu, not far away from rock dragon cave, there is a nameless mountain peak. The mountain is tall and there is a long river that passes by it, the trees on the mountain are green and lush, it is a lone mountain with no other branch peaks. Go to the top of that mountain and activate this Gu. Once you succeed, leave quickly. This mountain will become a forbidden zone for immortals, any Gu Immortals that enter this area will be met with fatal killing intent."

Bai Ning Bing did not accept this Immortal Gu, his eyes still staring at Old Man Yan Shi as he coldly said: "You still haven't answered my question."

"I don't need to answer your question. You only need to know that when this is done, Fang Yuan will return. Back then, you signed an agreement with Shadow Sect, wasn't the agreement that only after Fang Yuan is dead, you can be free from the agreement and regain your freedom?" Old Man Yan Shi smiled faintly.

Bai Ning Bing was silent for a while, before taking the Immortal Gu.

He then gave a cold snort, and flew away, disappearing into the horizon.

He made haste when traveling, two days later, he found the mountain Old Man Yan Shi spoke of.

"This mountain is ordinary and there is nothing strange, why did he choose this place?" Bai Ning Bing was puzzled.

Actually, he had many guesses, even thinking of the possibility that Old Man Yan Shi was trying to harm him.

"But, he has spent a huge price to raise me to Gu Immortal, why would he kill me now? The chance of this is very low."

Bai Ning Bing shook his head, there was another uncertainty which he had for a long time: "Why did Old Man Yan Shi help me to become a Gu Immortal? Among so many people, why did he choose me? Is it simply because of my Northern Dark Ice Soul physique?"

Previously, Bai Ning Bing had such thoughts, but now he was increasingly feeling the truth was not as simple as that.

Bai Ning Bing started to carefully investigate this nameless mountain peak, but he did not find any traces of Gu formations.

He was filled with doubts and hesitation.

If this was truly a trap, then he would be stupidly sending himself to death, wouldn't he be humiliating himself?

Bai Ning Bing suddenly had a thought: "Old Man Yan Shi would not make me come here in particular and activate Immortal Gu for no reason. His motive is veiled in mystery, but there is no time limit, I might as well delay and probe him."

If the matter was urgent, Old Man Yan Shi would be very anxious and naturally would urge him. At that time, with the Immortal Gu, Bai Ning Bing could obtain the initiative.

Bai Ning Bing bided his time and made no move, sure enough, someone on Shadow Sect's side became anxious.

A black robed Gu Immortal appeared inside the stone pavilion, and spoke with a rough voice: "Yan Shi, Bai Ning Bing has already gone for close to half a month, but there has been no word or action from him. Could it be that he ran away with the Gu, or maybe encountered a problem?"

Old Man Yan Shi was at ease, looking at the astrolabe chessboard.

The astrolabe chessboard in front of him was filled with dao marks but compared to before, when Bai Ning Bing had appeared, the numerous and disorderly lines had already reduced by a little less than half.

Old Man Yan Shi was pinching his fingers as he tried to deduce the chess moves, while saying to the black robed Gu Immortal: "Bai Ning Bing is still there, just not making a move. He already had doubts, doubts that this trip is harmful to him, so it is normal for him to have this reaction."

The black robed Gu Immortal could not help but speak urgently when he saw the leisurely attitude of Old Man Yan Shi: "But we can no longer delay the matter in Central Continent! Now, not just the Gu Immortals from the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, but even a lot of lone cultivators and demonic cultivators have entered to explore the riverbed of Falling Heavenly River. Vice Envoy Blue and the others can only hold on for three days at most. After three days, Heavenly Court will realize this is an arrangement and it might disrupt our true plan."

Old Man Yan Shi nodded, agreeing: "What you say makes sense. In fact, the present state has already diverged from the original plan, the progress is really too slow."

"How about you send a letter to urge Bai Ning Bing to make a move quickly. If he doesn't submit, we can take away his immortal level and make him fall down back to a mortal! He became a Gu Immortal with our help, but he is only a false immortal, there is no need for us to continue letting him be so arrogant! We can take action first and remove his Gu Immortal strength, making him a mortal again, restoring his female body. Such a junior with his head high above the clouds, if we don't make him know his place, we won't be able to use him." The black robed Gu Immortal suggested.

"Hehehe, why do you think I am using him?" Old Man Yan Shi chuckled, he lightly flicked his wide sleeve, immediately, a star mark was removed from the astrolabe chessboard.

If Fang Yuan was to see this sight, he would definitely be very shocked.

Doing this with such ease, Old Man Yan Shi's wisdom path attainment level was definitely great grandmaster!

The black robed Gu Immortal was wearing a large hood that covered his expression, but his tone was filled with heavy doubts: "Yan Shi, didn't you choose Bai Ning Bing because you saw his ten extreme physique battle strength?"

"No, no, that is not the case." Old Man Yan Shi laughed, "This is only what makes him special on the surface. His true special characteristic is that he is also someone who has escaped fate!"

"What? He is also one?" The black robed Gu Immortal was shocked.

Old Man Yan Shi explained further: "Our crucial plan has been devised for a hundred thousand years! Our true enemy is not the Central Continent's Heavenly Court, or the other four regions, but heaven. So I am handing this final crucial step to Bai Ning Bing. He is an escapee of fate, from a certain perspective, he could be said to have escaped the grasp of heaven's will as well. Only this kind of person is qualified to become our pawn."

"So it was like that." The black robed Gu Immortal came to a realization and had no more doubts.

Old Man Yan Shi continued: "Bai Ning Bing is a fate escapee, heaven's will is unable to control him completely, making him a potent weapon for us. We will first let him spearhead the attack, and what we will do is build up our energy, using all of our strength to cope with the fury of heaven's will. After Bai Ning Bing left, I did not contact him and let him move freely, but you can rest assured, with his nature, he will not wait for much longer."

"Since that is the case, then I will continue sleeping." The black robed Gu Immortal cupped his fists, and took his leave.

Bai Ning Bing waited another two days on the nameless mountain peak, occasionally looking at the direction of Old Man Yan Shi's stone pavilion.

"So many days have passed by, but Old Man Yan Shi has not urged me yet. It seems he is not in a hurry about this matter. That makes sense! If he was hurried, he would emphasize the time limit for completing the task when he handed it to me."

Bai Ning Bing could not help but feel somewhat dejected.

The probing just now was undoubtedly a failure.

He looked at the mountain below him, and pondered: "I have checked this mountain time and time again over these last days, but I could not find traces of any Gu formations. Sigh! If this is is truly harmful to me, I can only admit defeat, I could not find out anything, I can only blame my inadequate ability!"

Bai Ning Bing sighed and hovered in the air, looking at this ordinary mountain.

"Go." With a shift of his mind, his immortal essence started to be consumed as he activated the mysterious Immortal Gu.

The Immortal Gu let out some radiance but it still lay on his palm, showing no movement.

Bai Ning Bing was slightly surprised: "So this Immortal Gu requires a lot of immortal essence."

He continued to send beads of green grape immortal essence to it, the radiance of the Immortal Gu grew brighter and brighter, and the exquisite body of the Immortal Gu started to slightly tremble.

After a while, Bai Ning Bing's forehead was dripping with sweat, and he was feeling worried: "I have already used up hundreds of beads of immortal essence, why does it still not activating? So the difficulty in this task was in this!"

Just when he was getting very puzzled, the Immortal Gu in his hand suddenly buzzed, it turned into a ray of light that shot towards the sky.

The light continued to grow bigger, its speed however was becoming slower. When it reached a peak in height, it charged down to the nameless mountain.

Boom!

It crashed onto the mountain peak, the clash produced incomparably dazzling radiance.

Bai Ning Bing quickly covered his eyes and retreated.

He no longer needed to use his immortal essence.

But whether the Immortal Gu succeeded in its activation, he still needed to check to be certain.

Thus, he flew to a distance of five li away, before stopping in the air.

He then saw an unbelievable and marvelous scene!

Within the intense radiance, the nameless mountain peak suffered no damage, phantom images started to appear over the woods on the mountain.

This was a section of a long river, the river water billowed, rising and falling, filled with a mystical and natural wondrousness that would be difficult to portray, there was endless profundity that could not be described with words or expressed.

"This scene... could it be the river of time?!"

Bai Ning Bing's eyes suddenly enlarged, filled with extreme surprise.

Afterwards, he saw the river of time's phantom image gradually dissipate, becoming dimmer and dimmer. Two human-shaped figures seemed to jump out of the river, their appearances and clothes gradually becoming clearer.

These two people were fighting!

Both sides exchanged moves one after the other, the battle's intensity shocked Bai Ning Bing to the core.

Among them, one was enormous with bulging muscles, he was like a mythical creature that rampaged around with an extremely fierce momentum. He was a rank eight Gu Immortal!

The other person was rank seven. But he seemed to be using a killer move to disguise himself, his whole body was covered in a layer of fog that made others unable to distinguish his face or stature. The only thing that could be clearly seen was a red lotus that was drawn on his forehead.

Chapter 959: Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage

The battle between the two shook the scenery in the image, boulders shattered and the river roared.

Even if the change in the phantom image did not affect reality, it was an extremely moving scene.

The battle gradually heated to the climax, the burly rank eight Gu Immortal held the upper hand, he raised his head and laughed wildly: "I have rank eight cultivation and also possess the Great Strength True Martial Physique, a mere rank seven dreams of challenging me?!"

That mysterious Gu Immortal with a red lotus mark on his forehead chuckled and said with a plain voice: "Martial Duel Heavenly King, your defeat is certain. Take this move!"

Right after he finished speaking, the rank seven Gu Immortal flung his right hand and a high platform flew out.

The next moment, the contempt on the face of the rank eight Gu Immortal, Martial Duel Heavenly King, was completely gone, replaced by shock: "This is an Immortal Gu House! What Immortal Gu House is this?"

The rank seven Gu Immortal proudly smiled: "Let me teach you, this is my original creation — Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage!"

"Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage?" Bai Ning Bing frowned, as far as he knew, the present Southern Border Gu Immortal world did not have any such Immortal Gu House.

Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage's might was extremely mysterious.

No matter what kind of attacks Martial Duel Heavenly King sent, they were all absorbed and sealed.

That was not all.

After the attacks were sealed, they could still be used by the rank seven Gu Immortal to strike back!

Martial Duel Heavenly King's attacks were mighty, but in the end, he had to bear most of his attacks himself.

The images transformed continuously, and the battle situation kept on getting more heated.

Finally, with the help of Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, the mysterious rank seven Gu Immortal won against Martial Duel Heavenly King, accomplishing an extraordinary feat of rank seven defeating rank eight!

However, the rank seven Gu Immortal also had to pay a heavy price.

As a final stand, Martial Duel Heavenly King did not hesitate to turn into a rank eight immortal zombie, almost possessing an unkillable body. The mysterious rank seven Gu Immortal was not able to take his life, and could only let go of this Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, using it to suppress Martial Duel Heavenly King deep under the earth.

To win against Martial Duel Heavenly King, the unknown rank seven Gu Immortal had to give up an Immortal Gu House.

After the battle was over, he sighed as he gazed down, at his Immortal Gu House that was under the earth, before flying away.

There were no more images of the Gu Immortals, but the phantom image still kept on transforming.

The battlefield where the Gu Immortals fought returned to tranquility. With good weather, grass and trees started to grow. Then there were lightning strikes and flood. Meteors crashed down and inferno raged. The plain terrain gradually began to rise, growing slowly. At first, it was a mound, then it continued to increase until it became a mountain.

There were occasionally scenes of humans moving in the mountain, the movements were extremely quick, whether it was natural phenomenon or the movements of humans and beasts, they were shown like a sped-up video.

This mountain also began to change rapidly, it occasionally had landslides and occasionally changed in shape. Finally, in the phantom image, this mountain gradually turned into the appearance of the nameless mountain.

When the phantom image had completely disappeared, the world regained its original appearance.

Bai Ning Bing's eyes shone strangely, he understood that the Immortal Gu Old Man Yan Shi gave him was a time path investigative Immortal Gu!

It drilled into the crevices of time and transported the scene of the 'past' at a certain segment of the river of time towards the 'present'.

The scene of a huge battle between the two Gu Immortals was now this ordinary and inconspicuous mountain.

"This means there is an Immortal Gu House buried here!" Bai Ning Bing fixed his gaze under the mountain, his heart thumping in excitement.

He naturally knew the value of an Immortal Gu House.

Only forces with Gu Immortals could be considered super forces. But even among these super forces, only the powerful ones could possess one or more Immortal Gu Houses!

"If I can get hold of this Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, it will definitely be a huge help to me and I can more easily deal with Shadow Sect and leave! But this is bad, the Immortal Gu's aura has leaked everywhere, the disturbance when I activated the Immortal Gu was also not small, it will definitely attract other Gu Immortals. Time does not wait for anyone, I must hurry up!"

Bai Ning Bing had just thought of flying down, piercing deep into the earth and taking the Immortal Gu House, when he hesitated.

He thought of Old Man Yan Shi.

If he went down, would it be messing up Old Man Yan Shi's plan?

Maybe Old Man Yan Shi already calculated his reaction and wanted him to go deep into the earth, explore the depths of the earth and take Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage.

"If it is like this, he must have something up his sleeve... the mantis stalks a cicada, unaware of the oriole behind, if I blindly move, all my efforts will be in vain and I will be used by others!"

Bai Ning Bing's gaze was deep, he decided to first probe the surrounding environment before deciding to move.

However, what he had not expected was when he had just approached the nameless mountain by some distance, he felt an intense weakness, his Gu Immortal aura started to quickly weaken, he could not even exert his thoughts.

Bai Ning Bing retreated in shock, he recalled Old Man Yan Shi's words.

"Go to the top of that mountain and activate this Gu. Once you succeed, leave quickly. This mountain will become a forbidden zone for immortals, any Gu Immortals that enter this area will be met with fatal killing intent."

Bai Ning Bing thought with a frown, could this be the forbidden zone for immortals?

If this had truly become a forbidden zone, then how could he seize Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage?

At this moment, the phantom image on the mountain peak changed again, turning into the previous scenes.

Bai Ning Bing patiently observed, and could not help having a thought: could it be that there was a clue to take the Immortal Gu House hidden in the transformations of these phantom images?

However, after the phantom image finished showing the scenes, it disappeared again, Bai Ning Bing was not able to find out any clues.

He then discovered: the phantom image would reappear once in a while.

Every time the phantom image played, it would show the same contents with no difference.

He also discovered: the forbidden zone was expanding.

At first, he could still approach within three li of the nameless mountain. Now, however, he was ten li away from the mountain peak, but still felt exhausted and weak. He had a sense of warning deep within telling him that were he to forcefully charge in, he would definitely die.

Looking at the huge fortune moving farther and farther away from him, Bai Ning Bing was naturally uneasy.

He had stayed here for three days, trying to hide this constantly appearing phantom image.

He had already erased the Immortal Gu aura, but he was not able to hide these images.

Although Old Man Yan Shi helped him ascend to immortal, he did not give him any Immortal Gu.

This phenomenon in front of him was created by a time path investigative Immortal Gu, Bai Ning Bing naturally could not cover it using mortal Gu.

Of course, if he used superior mortal killer moves, there was a possibility of covering the images temporarily. But his foundation was shallow, and he did not have such methods.

"If Fang Yuan was here, what would he do?" In the worrisome moment, Bai Ning Bing recalled Fang Yuan's image.

Despite him no longer being concerned with Fang Yuan, he could not deny that Fang Yuan's ruthlessness and craftiness had made a deep impression and subconsciously influenced him.

He thought and thought, before he stopped in terror.

He suddenly realized: this Immortal Gu was given by Old Man Yan Shi, this should be a plan of Shadow Sect.

What was Shadow Sect trying to do?

They did not try to seize Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage secretly and silently earn a fortune, instead they were proclaiming this as if they wanted the whole world to know...

"Involving an ancient battle and the Immortal Gu House Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, probably the whole of Southern Border will be in an uproar. Be it righteous path Gu Immortals or demonic path or lone immortals, they will all go crazy for it. None of them would yield a step for the Immortal Gu House, this will definitely cause great turbulence and incite bloodshed. Is Shadow Sect's objective to bring a calamity to Southern Border? But how would this benefit them?"

Bai Ning Bing fiercely slapped his forehead, as his anxious expression vanished, clarity returned to his gaze.

"What was I doing these last days?! I actually let myself be blinded by greed. This is not something I can obtain, this nameless mountain will soon become the center of a storm in Southern Border, luring almost all the Gu Immortals of Southern Border. I am only a rank six Gu Immortal with limited methods. I can't stay here for long, I better leave early. Right, I should return and try to probe Old Man Yan Shi on what he is thinking of doing. Does he want to use this to lure Fang Yuan?"

Bai Ning Bing hurriedly returned, but Old Man Yan Shi was no longer in the stone pavilion.

He hurried to Shadow Sect's blessed land, but he was unable to summon the blessed land's entrance to appear, he also could not contact them using information path mortal Gu, it was almost like the entirety of Shadow Sect, including Old Man Yan Shi, had completely disappeared in an instant.

The wave of doubts in Bai Ning Bing's mind intensified, there was a sensation of being discarded, he vaguely felt that the last series of events was anything but a reassuring omen.

Central Continent, Falling Heavenly River.

Right now, the bottom of the riverbed of the source of Falling Heavenly River was filled with light.

Countless Gu Immortals of Central Continent fixed their gazes at the riverbed's only light source, their hearts filled with fervent desire.

An immortal zombie with eyes closed was floating in this light. His appearance was just like before when he was alive, seemingly filled with vitality. Sharp brows, high nose, jade green hair, upright back, it was Bo Qing!

"Who could have thought Bo Qing would have turned into an immortal zombie."

"Back then, the fairy of Spirit Affinity House at that time, Mo Yao, had also faced the tribulation with him. But there is only Bo Qing here, it seems Mo Yao had completely died."

"According to the sect records, that heavenly tribulation had such terrifying might that it shook the whole of Central Continent. It really is inconceivable that Bo Qing could preserve his life, how strong was he actually?"

The immortals discussed with each other.

"The corpse has been maintained for so long, who knows how many secrets it contains. As long as we can obtain it, we can decipher the profound mysteries of Bo Qing's cultivation back then. Even if there is no sword path true inheritance, just this research alone would be an enormous gain. Maybe it can even add to a true inheritance in the sect?"

Most of these thoughts were from the Gu Immortals of the ten great ancient sects. They were looking at long term prospects, considering for the situation of their sect.

While the lone immortals and demonic cultivators like Jian Yi Sheng were paying attention to the Immortal Gu carried by the immortal zombie Bo Qing.

"There are still auras of so many Immortal Gu on his body. This is really unimaginable for them to exist until now! These are all sword path Immortal Gu of the pseudo-Immortal Venerable, I will be satisfied with even just one!"

Central Continent's righteous path was very prosperous, and the demonic cultivators were fiercely suppressed, to the extent that their situation was the most miserable among the demonic cultivators in the entirety of the five regions.

These demonic cultivators and lone cultivators did not dare to have any idea of taking Bo Qing's immortal zombie body, and only wanted to make a profit and run away quickly.

In fact, before this, in the process of entering Falling Heavenly River, almost all the immortals had made some gains.

The remains of beasts and plants cut down by the sword lights were not few. As long as one looked for them carefully, they could find them.

However, Bo Qing's assets was truly too attractive.

Humans die for wealth and birds die for food. Since they personally witnessing it, who would want to leave now?

Chapter 960: Bo Qing Awakens

At this time, there were at least thirty Gu Immortals at the bottom of Falling Heavenly River's source.

The immortals had heated gazes, they were staring at the light lump that enveloped the immortal zombie, Bo Qing, they looked around secretly, they were very alert towards their competitors.

Among these competitors, the strongest ones were the Gu Immortals from Central Continent's ten great ancient sects.

Jin Lie Yang, Hong Chi Ming, Qi Yun Tian and others.

And among the people from the ten great ancient sects, the most threatening one was Fairy Bai Qing.

Seeing this stalemate, Qi Yun Tian said slowly: "Fairy Bai Qing, this situation is very clear. Bo Qing has his immortal zombie remains, but his soul was decimated by the tribulation. However, there are some wills and emotions left in his mind, he can defend himself."

"Thus, whenever we get close, he will use his Immortal Gu and shoot out extremely sharp sword lights, attacking everywhere. To weaken his animosity, we need something that contains Bo Qing's aura, or a Gu worm that he refined in the past, we can also use the wills and emotions left behind by Bo Qing, as long as we take these out, we can get close to Bo Qing and gain the upper hand."

Fairy Bai Qing smiled bitterly: "Why would I have these things, if I did, I would have taken action long ago, right?"

She indeed did not.

Because she had not expected to find Bo Qing's immortal zombie body.

Qi Yun Tian smiled lightly: "Fairy Bai Qing, why are you lying to us? You are the first person here, why did you come here alone secretly? Is all this a coincidence?"

Fairy Bai Qing's smile became more bitter: "You say I came here secretly, that is wrong. I had used the path through Myriad Dragon Dock and Combat Immortal Sect, I came here openly, what do you mean by secretly?"

She had come to investigate Falling Heavenly River because of Feng Jiu Ge's last words.

But she could not expose this truth.

Spirit Affinity House needed to stall the information regarding Feng Jiu Ge's death as much as possible, so that they could have more time to prepare.

Jin Lie Yang frowned more deeply now, his voice became more shrill: "Why is Fairy Bai Qing hiding it from us? The current situation will only draw in more Gu Immortals. As time passes, accidents might occur! We of the ten great ancient sects should work together to jointly control situation in Central Continent. Otherwise, if those lone cultivators obtain Sword Immortal Bo Qing's sword path Immortal Gu, Central Continent would undergo huge turbulence. Is your sect going to ignore Central Continent's wellbeing just for your own greed?"

Qi Yun Tian's attitude was warm, he continued urging: "We of the ten great ancient sects are of the same origin. We should work together and obtain immortal zombie Bo Qing. I can represent Wind Cloud Manor and sign an alliance agreement with your sect, we will ensure you get your benefits in this matter."

Fairy Bai Qing was silent.

She sneered internally, Jin Lie Yang and Qi Yun Tian were working together to coerce and coax her, how could she not know that.

She was secretly anxious.

This had happened too suddenly, and Spirit Affinity House did not send Gu Immortals to reinforce her.

Even though she was rank seven, facing these immortals, she could not do much.

No matter what immortal zombie Bo Qing's situation was, it was very important to take back his body and sword path Immortal Gu for Spirit Affinity House.

The other nine sects knew this.

Right now, in their opinion, Feng Jiu Ge was missing, he was likely dead, Spirit Affinity House was weakened now, they could not let them obtain this immortal zombie Bo Qing.

If they nurtured another Bo Qing who was as strong as Feng Jiu Ge, what would the nine sects do?

The situation in Falling Heavenly River was extremely dangerous.

Immortal zombie Bo Qing's sword lights were extremely sharp, they shot through the entirety of Central Continent.

Large numbers of demonic and lone cultivators came because of it. They desired conflict, they wanted to obtain huge gains from it.

As for the immortals from Central Continent's ten great ancient sects, they want to stabilize the situation and not give these outsiders a chance.

But at the same time, the immortals of the ten great ancient sects were not united, thus, the nine sects were resisting Spirit Affinity House together.

Fairy Bai Qing was thought to have possession of a crucial method, she could not explain her innocence now.

Just as the immortals were in a deadlock, a vast rank eight aura surged.

"All of the immortals stand back, we of Heavenly Court are taking charge."

Everyone gasped, they looked at the source of the sound and saw a female immortal descending.

It was the rank eight water path Gu Immortal Bai Cang Shui.

The situation changed at once!

Central Continent, Heavenly Court.

Light shone on Heaven Overseeing Tower, it had been rebuilt again, standing in front of the three immortals.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord, Bi Chen Tian, and Lian Jiu Sheng felt the weight on their hearts easing, they sighed in relief.

Ever since Heaven Overseeing Tower was slashed by the sword light, they had not rested.

To prevent the sword path dao marks from corroding it further and destroying more Gu worms, they had worked day and night to repair it without rest, they had finally succeeded.

Thankfully, the three immortals rapidly replaced the destroyed Gu worms using the huge amount of immortal materials in Heavenly Court's storage, saving it in time.

There was something important to note, Heaven Overseeing Tower was a rank nine Immortal Gu House, it had incredible defense. Even though it was split in half by the sword light, what it truly lost was only the Gu worms near the damage caused by the sword, in fact, Heaven Overseeing Tower was not gravely damaged.

After looking at it for a while, Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord took a deep breath and supported himself on his walking stick as he held fate Gu, walking towards the tower.

Lian Jiu Sheng could not help but ask: "Tower Lord, are you not going to rest, why are you in a rush to activate Heaven Overseeing Tower?"

"Thank you for your concern, it is alright." Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord smiled, rejecting the suggestion.

For some reason, ever since the sword light attacked Heaven Overseeing Tower, he had been having an ominous sensation.

As time passed, this ominous sensation intensified.

Even after seeing the repaired Heaven Overseeing Tower, he did not feel this ominous sensation going away.

"Go." He willed, in his hand, fate Gu turned into a mystical light, entering the top of the tower, towards the formation core.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord moved his aged body as he slowly walked up the stairs.

Every step he took expended rank eight immortal essence.

The tower walls were shining in bright light, they appeared to be in a mess and did not give any hints or advice.

But Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord did not mind it.

Fate Immortal Gu could only use half of its might, half of the images displayed were blurry or dark.

After walking for sixty steps, the image on the wall became clear.

On the nameless peak of Southern Border, the scene was depicted vividly in front of Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord.

In the image, Martial Duel Heavenly King and the mysterious rank seven Gu Immortal's fight entered Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's vision.

This old man frowned unconsciously.

"Rank eight Great Strength True Martial immortal zombie... Immortal Gu House Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage... and this!"

On the mysterious rank seven Gu Immortal's forehead, the red lotus mark was very bright red and striking.

"An inheritor of Red Lotus' true inheritance!"

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's eyes flashed with sharpness.

The pain that Red Lotus Demon Venerable brought to Heavenly Court and the damage he dealt to fate Immortal Gu, had tormented generations after generations of Heavenly Court Gu Immortals for over a million years!

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord stopped on this step, thinking deeply.

"Red Lotus' true inheritance, it has to be destroyed! No traces must be left behind!"

"The Great Strength True Martial immortal zombie is less of a concern... but that Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage should belong to Heavenly Court ideally. Even if Southern Border has the regional wall, Heavenly Court has to make an attempt now."

Just that mystical Immortal Gu House, Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, was worth the intervention of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals.

Even though rank eight Gu Immortals faced much difficulty in passing the five regions' regional walls, and had to pay a huge price.

"Without concealing such a scene, Southern Border's Gu Immortal world would definitely be stirred up, countless immortals would come forward to fight for it. If Heavenly Court wants to traverse regions and compete, we have to choose appropriate people, and the number has to be precise."

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord thought more deeply and soon shook his head, placing these troublesome thoughts aside.

He continued to go up.

Sixty steps, seventy steps, eighty steps...

When he got to the eighty-third step, the image changed again.

This time, it was the scene of Central Continent.

In Falling Heavenly River, immortal zombie Bo Qing's eyes were shut as the Heavenly Court Gu Immortal Bai Cang Shui led the immortals and controlled the situation singlehandedly.

In the image, Bai Cang Shui smiled and spoke to Fairy Bai Qing.

But after Fairy Bai Qing replied to her, Bai Cang Shui's expression became one of deep disappointment.

Soon, she concealed her expression and became calm again.

She moved her fingers, setting up a Gu formation, planning to seal this place.

But at this moment, starlight shot over, it penetrated the incomplete Gu formation and shot towards immortal zombie Bo Qing.

As starlight shined brightly, immortal zombie Bo Qing opened his eyes!

In an instant, countless flashes of sword light burst out, turning the world white.

Even Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord shut his eyes in response.

At the next moment, he opened his eyes.

What he saw was a bloody scene.

There were bits and pieces of Gu Immortal corpses everywhere, the head of the Heavenly Court Gu Immortal, Bai Cang Shui, was rolling away with streams of blood.

Her eyes were opened wide, she had died!

"How can this be?" Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord, who saw this, was anguished.

Three figures landed immediately.

Seven Star Child was in front, followed by Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun.

"Azure, you are finally awake." Seven Star Child laughed loudly, his body was emitting a powerful rank eight aura.

He walked forward, getting close to immortal zombie Bo Qing.

Bo Qing's eyes shined with ruthlessness, sword light shot out.

Seven Star Child was shocked, he did not expect Bo Qing to attack him!

The sword light was peerlessly sharp, he was sliced in half, even his immortal zombie body was useless against it.

Seven Star Child's pitiful death stunned Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun.

"What is going on? Envoy Azure killed Vice Envoy Blue!"

"No, he is not Envoy Azure, his mind is filled with heaven's will, and there is another person's remnant soul living inside his body!"

At once, Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun were shocked and furious.

Immortal zombie Bo Qing was expressionless, he turned around to look at them.

Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun felt a strong chill, they sank into despair.

They did not see any killing intent from immortal zombie Bo Qing's eyes.

They only saw the unfeeling and impartial nature of the way of heaven!

They were people who escaped from fate, they were targets of elimination of the way of heaven.

An intense aura of death engulfed them, against the famous pseudo-Immortal Venerable, Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun could not escape or dodge, they could only await their deaths.

Chapter 961: Unprecedented Contest

"Hahaha, I finally succeeded!"

Coming out of the underground cave, Fang Yuan's face was filled with joy.

During this period, he had exerted all of his effort into deducing this immortal killer move, he had finally obtained some results today.

This new killer move used eat strength Immortal Gu, pulling mountain Immortal Gu and pulling water Immortal Gu as the cores, with three hundred and thirty thousand supplementary mortal Gu, he formed an extravagant combination that would stun another person.

To activate this killer move, Fang Yuan had to focus wholeheartedly for two hours, activating this set of Gu worms.

Then, going through three days and nights without rest, he could gradually transform his living body into an immortal zombie body, or transform his immortal zombie body into a living body.

Even though it was not as convenient as nirvana fire, Fang Yuan had reached his limits by getting such progress.

Fang Yuan was very satisfied with this result.

After all, Fang Yuan only had so many strength path Immortal Gu. He could use all of them here thanks to the light of wisdom.

Of course, it was because he had nirvana fire as the blueprint.

If he did not have nirvana fire, or the set of Gu worms to research that were lent by Blazing Heaven Demoness, Fang Yuan would not have been able to obtain a strength path version in such a short time.

Also, Fang Yuan had wisdom path grandmaster attainment level.

Because of all these reasons, a minor miracle was created.

"Next, I have to use those strength path immortal zombies and exert strength Gu to form my high grade life-and-death blessed land, to revive." Fang Yuan sighed internally.

After searching for so long, he had finally reached this stage.

As for Luo Po valley, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had repaired it not long ago.

Fang Yuan gave it a try, cultivating inside Luo Po valley.

It was indeed the soul cultivation sacred land that was on par with Dang Hun Mountain!

Paired with Dang Hun Mountain's guts Gu, Fang Yuan's soul cultivation was advancing by leaps and bounds.

But now, Fang Yuan knew that the most important thing was to revive. His soul cultivation could be placed aside now, he did not need to engage in it.

Fang Yuan could almost not hold in his urge.

But just as he was about to start, he received Blazing Heaven Demoness' letter.

The contents caused his revival plan to pause.

"Rank eight Great Strength True Martial immortal zombie?" When Fang Yuan saw this line, his heart pounded.

The information that Blazing Heaven Demoness gave him was regarding the nameless mountain in Southern Border.

This matter was too big now, it concerned an Immortal Gu House, it had spread throughout the entirety of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world.

In Southern Border, there was a Zombie Alliance branch as well.

Thus, as the leader of the Northern Plains Zombie Alliance branch, Blazing Heaven Demoness quickly got hold of the news.

"Blazing Heaven Demoness has great ambitions, she knows that I have Fixed Immortal Travel, thus she observed the events over all five regions. As a higher up of Zombie Alliance, she could collect information more easily than Fairy Li Shan."

Fang Yuan felt his weakness in intelligence gathering once again.

In his previous life, he had an organization and network, his developed blood path Gu worm techniques could replace the use of most information path methods.

But in this life, Fang Yuan used his previous life's memories together with intelligence mainly from people like Fairy Li Shan and Lang Ya land spirit.

As more and more unexpected surprises occurred, Fang Yuan was starting to feel that his previous life's memories were beginning to become unreliable.

The truth of history was often hidden in deep fog, what Fang Yuan saw in his previous life was only what had been exposed and was seemingly true on the surface.

Even for matters that he had experienced personally, they might not have been as simple as he thought.

The reasons for the occurrence of many events were complicated.

"In my previous life, I had a tough time, I slowly climbed up from the bottom, my network and resources were accumulated slowly, thus I had no obvious weaknesses. But after rebirth, I have obtained opportunities one after another, my strength rose rapidly, or rather, explosively. Thus, in many aspects, I could not keep up."

"It seems that I have to use more information path methods to collect intelligence. For the time being, I can rely on outsiders like Blazing Heaven Demoness, but in the long run, I need to rely on myself!"

Fang Yuan contemplated.

Lack of information meant losing many opportunities.

Like just now, Fang Yuan did not know the situation, he was kept in the dark, he almost missed this fortuitous encounter completely.

Three days later, Fang Yuan went alone to Southern Border, approaching the nameless mountain.

Blazing Heaven Demoness was still in Dark Flow Giant City, she had told Fang Yuan in the letter that she was busy refining Gu and setting up the Immortal Gu formation, she could not leave. But when necessary, she would come to take action.

As for Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan, they were in Northern Plains, using Luo Po valley to cultivate their souls, and increase their foundation. They had an intense interest towards the Immortal Gu House, but their Northern Plains aura made it difficult for them to roam Southern Border.

Fang Yuan came here to obtain intelligence.

Even though he had become a Gu Immortal in Northern Plains, he had the concealment of vaguely familiar face, ordinary Gu Immortals could not expose him.

On the nameless mountain, once in a while, phantom images would reappear.

Bai Ning Bing was nowhere to be found.

Fang Yuan watched it three times over and pondered over it before moving, getting close to the nameless mountain.

As expected, like what Blazing Heaven Demoness said in the letter, this place was a forbidden zone for immortals. The deeper Fang Yuan went, the more he felt his limbs going weak, he felt that his immortal aperture was being pressured by a formless force.

Fang Yuan had to stop in his tracks, he knew that if this continued, his immortal aperture would be destroyed before he took fifty or sixty steps.

That would not do.

He had to use his strength path immortal aperture to create the life-and-death immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan had to retreat.

At this time, he heard a tender laughter from behind him.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, he immediately turned around.

Only to see a beautiful woman, dressed in pink and red, her hair was tied up and her skin was white like snow, her eyes were alluring and watery, she was standing nearby, looking at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not dare to be careless.

This woman was oozing with Gu Immortal aura, she was a rank six Gu Immortal.

Seeing Fang Yuan's gaze, this beautiful woman introduced herself: "I am Li Mei Hua, people call me Granny Mei Hua. Handsome lad, you look very unfamiliar, where do you cultivate?"

Fang Yuan smiled, he thought: "So she is Granny Mei Hua."

Even though Fang Yuan had never seen Granny Mei Hua personally, he had seen her granddaughter, that demonic path female Gu Master, Hu Mei Er.

To care for beauty was natural for women.

There was no relation between the age and appearance of Gu Immortals.

Right now, Fang Yuan wore a green robe and his sleeves were large and wide, the wind blew and his robe fluttered, moving like a war banner.

In Fang Yuan's disguise, he had a rank six Gu Immortal aura, he was tall and skinny, having a middle aged appearance with a tall nose bridge, slim eyes, and his pupils radiated with faint traces of jade green light. He gave off an eerie aura, as if he was not to be trifled with, even though he was not good looking, he had quite a disposition.

"Granny Mei Hua, I have long since heard of you. I am Sheng Ying, I am just a simple wanderer." Fang Yuan replied.

"Sheng Ying..." Li Mei Hua memorized this name, she could not remember such a person in Southern Border.

However, she did not find it strange.

Hearing Fang Yuan's introduction, she knew that he was a lone cultivator.

Southern Border had many mountains, countless experts were in seclusion. Many lone cultivators never showed themselves, nobody knew about them.

But because of the Immortal Gu House, Gu Immortals one after another were attracted and had come over.

Fang Yuan, who was disguised as Sheng Ying, was just one of them.

These last days, Li Mei Hua had contacted many Gu Immortals similar to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was slightly suspicious towards Li Mei Hua's warm attitude in approaching him.

Fang Yuan was about to ask, when Li Mei Hua told him the reason.

Fang Yuan realized at once.

Li Mei Hua invited Fang Yuan to travel together, after thinking about it, he agreed.

He followed Li Mei Hua and moved out, settling down at Headless Mountain which was a thousand li away. When Fang Yuan got there, there were already many demonic path or lone immortals on the mountain.

Seeing Fang Yuan, many cast curious gazes, while some has grim or ruthless expressions.

Because they did not know Fang Yuan's background, no Gu Immortals spoke to him yet.

But Granny Mei Hua was quite popular, the moment she returned, someone smiled: "Li Mei Hua, you brought another one?"

"Hahaha, this time, we demonic and lone cultivators have gathered to negotiate with the righteous path, Granny Mei Hua has made the most contribution towards it."

"Oh no, I am flattered, I am just doing my best to help." Li Mei Hua smiled as she greeted and interacted with the people around here one after another, she managed the individual relationships with great ease.

"Let me introduce you, this is brother Sheng Ying, he is a lone immortal." After talking to everyone, Li Mei Hua introduced Fang Yuan to them.

"So you are brother Sheng." Immediately, a demonic path Gu Immortal cupped his fists.

"I am Zhong He Zi."

"I see that sir cultivates transformation path, oh, my name is Lan Tian Hong, I am also a lone cultivator."

...

Fang Yuan showed a look of being poor at socializing, barely interacting with them.

After some short talks, Headless Mountain returned to being peaceful like before Fang Yuan arrived.

Li Mei Hua did not stay on the mountain for long, she had to return to the nameless mountain and wait for more people, she pointed at a mountain before leaving, telling Fang Yuan: "That Pine Tail Mountain is the base camp of the righteous path Gu Immortals."

Even without her pointing it out, the intense Gu Immortal aura on that mountain had already informed Fang Yuan.

After separating from Li Mei Hua, Fang Yuan stayed on Headless Mountain.

He did not go out often, most of his time was spent in his cave, after all, Fang Yuan was disguised now, and vaguely familiar face was not an invincible disguise.

He stayed and waited for more than ten days, during this period, Headless Mountain and Pine Tail Mountain welcomed Gu Immortals from both righteous and demonic paths.

Most of them were rank six, whenever a rank seven Gu Immortal came, a commotion would be created, eventually, even rank eight Gu Immortals arrived, a total of four!

One demonic path, one lone cultivator, and two of the righteous path.

It formed a balance of power on both sides.

The rank eight Gu Immortals did not involve themselves, every day, the Gu Immortals on both sides recommended one person each to engage in a difficult negotiation.

After seven days and nights of negotiation, they finally came to an agreement.

The righteous and demonic paths, dozens of Gu Immortals set an agreement together, all around the nameless mountain, they were engaging in a grand contest that was rare even in a thousand years!

The winner of the contest would obtain the opportunity on the nameless mountain. As for the other Gu Immortals, they were not to attack the victor for the next three years.

Chapter 962: Xiao Shan, Xiao Mang

At the bottom of Falling Heavenly River, immortal zombie Bo Qing's eyes moved around, looking emotionlessly at Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun.

At this moment, Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun's hearts were jumping, they were facing immense pressure, they were drenched in sweat.

Bo Qing was known as a pseudo-Immortal Venerable, during his time, he was publicly recognized as the strongest person under rank nine venerables in the five regions!

Even though he had become an immortal zombie after the tribulation and his immortal aperture was completely destroyed, he still had ample rank eight immortal essence on him, especially his sword path dao marks, they were not destroyed.

Thus, his battle strength was terrifying.

The most crucial point were the dao marks!

The higher the Gu Immortal's cultivation level, the more dao marks they had. Even if two people were using the same Immortal Gu, the difference in dao marks would cause different outcomes when the Immortal Gu's power was amplified.

Consider Qin Bai Sheng, a soul path Gu Immortal who also cultivated metal path, he did not have a single sword path dao mark on him, but when he used five finger fist heart sword, he could fight Feng Jiu Ge on equal grounds.

Right now, none of Bo Qing's Immortal Gu were damaged, together with his vast number of sword path dao marks, he could display unimaginable might, he could almost replicate the glory that he had when he was alive.

Thus, Bai Cang Shui, Seven Star Child, and the others had no chance to resist him.

Not to mention Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun.

The higher the rank of the Gu Immortal, the greater the difference, between rank seven and eight, the difference in dao marks was like heaven and earth. Between rank six and seven, there might be those who are evenly matched occasionally. But when rank eight fought against rank seven, it was almost always a one-sided fight. When rank nine fought rank eight, it would be as simple as stepping on an ant.

Facing immortal zombie Bo Qing, Song Zi Xing and Yu Mu Chun had no way to retaliate!

"Am I going to die today?"

"What will we do? What will we do!"

The two of them felt their bodies going cold, countless thoughts were churning in their minds, looking at this situation, they had almost no hope.

Bo Qing raised his finger, pointing at Song Zi Xing.

A thin sword light flashed.

Song Zi Xing did not even try to escape, he faced death with a bitter smile.

Because he knew that in front of Bo Qing, escaping was completely futile.

Bo Qing pointed at Yu Mu Chun.

"No—! I am unresigned, I cannot die!" Yu Mu Chun shouted loudly, in the moment between life and death, he took out an Immortal Gu.

Immortal zombie Bo Qing's movements froze.

His face started to show a struggling expression.

Yu Mu Chun's heart was pounding loudly, he started at Bo Qing's changing face anxiously.

Immortal zombie Bo Qing's expression turned from impassive to confused, he showed pain, hatred, and sadness, he was like a traffic light that was rapidly changing in color.

Eventually, his expression turned lively, there was some intelligence shining in his eyes, it was like a person with dementia suddenly recovering his senses.

He looked at his hand, and looked around at the brutal bloody scene, in the end, he looked towards Yu Mu Chun, asking hesitantly: "You are..."

Yu Mu Chun's body was full of cold sweat, he replied weakly like he had lost all his strength: "You are finally awake, Mo Yao, it seems that I made the right gamble. It was so close, so close."

It turned out that the remnant soul inside immortal zombie Bo Qing's body was Mo Yao's remnant soul.

Yu Mu Chun's Immortal Gu awakened Mo Yao's remnant soul, it caused the heaven's will which was inside the immortal zombie's mind to be pushed out.

Without the manipulation of heaven's will, immortal zombie Bo Qing stopped attacking.

Yu Mu Chun took several deep breaths as he continued: "Remember our conversation back then, in order to revive Bo Qing..."

"Bo Qing!"

Hearing her lover's name, Mo Yao's remnant soul shook.

She manipulated the immortal zombie body, nodding as she interrupted Yu Mu Chun: "Then what should I do now?"

Yu Mu Chun looked at Seven Star Child and Song Zi Xing's corpses, sighing.

If they were still alive, together with Yu Mu Chun, the three of them could use an immortal killer move and teleport all of the immortals to Central Continent's north-east area.

Heavenly Lotus Sect was in control of that area.

But now that Seven Star Child and Song Zi Xing were dead, Yu Mu Chun could only settle for dealing with Combat Immortal Sect, giving up on attacking Heavenly Lotus Sect.

"I hope that they can be stalled!" Yu Mu Chun took a glance in Heavenly Court's direction, feeling deeply worried.

Heavenly Court, Heaven Overseeing Tower.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's expression was dark, he was filled with anger.

He looked at the image, Yu Mu Chun cooperated with immortal zombie Bo Qing and was going to attack one of the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, Combat Immortal Sect, he could no longer watch idly.

Even though he was a Gu Immortal from Heavenly Lotus Sect, Combat Immortal Sect was still a sect underneath Heavenly Court.

Right now, immortal zombie Bo Qing had awakened, Combat Immortal Sect was in danger. Only Heavenly Court Gu Immortals could save them!

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord flew out of Heaven Overseeing Tower, summoning Lian Jiu Sheng and Bi Chen Tian: "An issue has occurred in Falling Heavenly River, Bai Cang Shui is dead, Bo Qing revived as an immortal zombie and is attacking Combat Immortal Sect. We have to reinforce them now!"

The two immortals were extremely shocked, Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord's words contained information that was simply too hard to believe.

"Go!"

The two immortals were only stunned momentarily.

Immediately after, they reacted and the three immortals used Heavenly Court's teleportation Gu formation and appeared at Combat Immortal Sect's base in a moment.

Looking at the north-west direction, the sky was clear as a grand sword light flew over rapidly.

A battle of rank eights was right before their eyes.

Southern Border, Light Mountain.

Light Mountain was more than two and a half kilometers tall, the light path Gu worms produced on the mountain were well-known over the whole of Southern Border.

This mountain had been in the control of a single force for the last thousand years.

Xiao clan.

Rumors had it that Southern Border's Xiao clan and Western Desert's Xiao clan were of the same origin. A thousand years ago, there was an internal conflict within Western Desert's Xiao clan, resulting in the losing side leaving and moving to Southern Border.

Southern Border's Xiao clan was once a super force. But its final remaining Gu Immortal, Xiao clan's supreme elder, had not appeared for the last hundred years, it caused Xiao clan to fall from a super force to a large scale force.

Xiao clan's current leader, Xiao Shan, stood on a mountain slope, he looked at Xiao clan's main base partway up the mountain as he showed dejection and hatred in his eyes.

A figure ran up the mountain rapidly, landing beside Xiao Shan, paying respects to him: "Xiao Zi Feng greets lord clan leader."

"That Wu Hui, is he still causing trouble?" Xiao Shan asked in a low voice.

Clan elder Xiao Zi Feng lowered his head: "Reporting to clan leader, Wu Hui is still screaming in the hall, requesting us to hand over the culprit that killed his son. The other elders are still holding the ground, don't worry clan leader."

Xiao Shan snorted coldly, he gritted his fists: "Wu Hui's son was the one with ill intentions, trying to target Xiao Cui Er, my daughter was just defending herself. This Wu Hui is actually using Wu clan to cause a ruckus in Xiao clan's discussion hall!"

"Clan leader, all will be fine if we endure this. Wu Hui is not a problem, but Wu clan is very powerful, we cannot resist them." Xiao Zi Feng quickly urged.

Xiao Shan's clenched fists loosened, he sighed deeply, his face was full of fatigue and bitterness.

He waved to Xiao Zi Feng: "Forget it, I will hide at the back of the mountain for the time being."

Xiao Zi Feng took his leave, vanishing into the forest below.

Xiao Shan sighed at the sky again, his mind was filled with gloominess and anger, he could not calm himself.

But at this moment, he suddenly heard a voice resounding in his mind.

"Come here, my descendant!"

"Who is it?" Xiao Shan was suspicious and uncertain.

This voice spoke again — come here, my descendant!

This voice was very familiar to Xiao Shan. He followed the voice's direction, entering deep into the region at the back of the mountain, until he reached Xiao clan's forbidden area.

"This is Xiao clan's forbidden area, even as the leader of Xiao clan, I have no authority to enter it!" Xiao Shan stopped moving, he was very troubled.

That voice rang in his mind again: "My descendant, you inherited my bloodline, why are you so timid? I am Xiao clan's ancestor, a Gu Immortal of Xiao clan, quickly come and receive my inheritance, the mission to strengthen our clan is yours to bear."

Xiao Shan's eyes shined, his body was trembling in agitation.

Gu Immortal!

Xiao clan's ancestor!

"Were the rumors true? My Xiao clan has had a Gu Immortal before? This voice is so familiar to me. I am a rank five peak stage Gu Master, other than Gu Immortals, who in this world can transmit their voices into my mind directly?"

"But this is forbidden area in the clan. Anyone who steps into this place will be exiled from the clan, even as the leader, I am no exception!" Xiao Shan thought of this and clenched his fists tightly.

He was engaged in an intense internal struggle.

"No, I must get the ancestor's inheritance! Wu Hui has caused our Xiao clan to lose face, if Wu clan voices out their support of Wu Hui, will I be able to protect my daughter? Wu clan is so overbearing and forceful, rumors says that they have Wu clan's Gu Immortals backing them! If I can receive the inheritance and become a Gu Immortal, I will definitely be able to raise Xiao clan's reputation and change everything!"

Xiao Shan's face shined with determination.

He hesitated no longer, he walked into the forbidden area.

Under the guidance of the voice, he reached a cave, seeing an Immortal Gu inside the cave.

Before he reacted, the Immortal Gu turned into a mystical light and fused into his body.

"This Gu worm's aura is preventing me from moving at all through power alone. Is this a legendary Immortal Gu?" Xiao Shan was surprised and joyful.

But when he inspected his body, the Immortal Gu was nowhere to be seen.

He could not find it anywhere.

And at this time, the voice in his head vanished completely.

Xiao Shan felt trepidation and deep suspicion as he walked out of the mountain's forbidden area.

"Brother, right now, Wu clan's elder is here to cause trouble, but you as the leader violated our rules and sneaked into our clan's forbidden area! You are not fit to be the clan leader!" Xiao Mang suddenly appeared, bringing with him a larger number of Xiao clan elders.

Xiao Shan realized the situation was turning bad.

He knew that his twin brother had great ambitions, he had been coveting his position as clan leader.

"This is not what you think!" Xiao Shan wanted to explain himself, but he could not explain himself clearly.

He was unwilling to casually mention the Gu Immortal inheritance, he was afraid that other forces or experts would try to take it away by force.

"Your explanations are just excuses! According to the clan rules, you are no longer a member of Xiao clan! The position of clan leader is mine!" Xiao Mang shouted, his expression was ruthless and furious, excitement and ambition was hidden deep inside his eyes.

Chapter 963: Yi Tian Mountain!

The speed of the sword light was beyond belief, as it cut through the air.

However, Heavenly Pool, the location of Heavenly Lotus Sect, was still far away beyond the horizon.

"Hmm?" The sword light dissipated, revealing Bo Qing's immortal zombie body and Yu Mu Chun.

The immortal zombie Bo Qing, which was controlled by Mo Yao's remnant soul, was now frowning with a sharp gaze, as he used sword light to sweep the surroundings.

The sword light was incomparably sharp, everywhere it went, space rippled and illusions shattered, revealing the true scene.

However, a breath of time later, the true scenery was covered by layers and layers of illusions again.

"This is Heavenly Lotus Sect's Immortal Gu House, Illusion Garden, which is built on the foundation of illusion path and was created over three hundred years ago by Illusion Demon Immortal Huang Xiao." Yu Mu Chun immediately explained.

Bo Qing's immortal zombie body nodded, sighing: "Every age brings forth new geniuses. It seems many geniuses have appeared in Central Continent after my main body's death."

Yu Mu Chun spoke: "Illusion Demon Immortal has already died, this Immortal Gu House could beguile and trap us so stealthily that we were only able to realize now, the person who is controlling it should have a very high cultivation!"

Just as he said this, Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord, Bi Chen Tian and Lian Jiu Sheng appeared.

"Escaping fate is already a great sin. Now, you are thinking of attacking the sects under Heavenly Court, this is unpardonable!" Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord immediately shouted.

"You talk too much!" Immortal zombie Bo Qing was furious, he waved his arm, a terrifying sword light quickly slashed.

Heaven Overseeing Tower Lord, Bi Chen Tian and Lian Jiu Sheng cried out as they activated their immortal killer moves.

The sword light was unstoppable, it broke all the killer moves of the three immortals, its might had decreased for the most part in doing this but it still was able to charge towards them.

The three immortals disappeared without a trace, evading this strike.

"Cowards!" Immortal zombie Bo Qing snorted, extremely displeased.

Yu Mu Chun's eyes shined with sharp radiance, but he let out a sigh of relief inwardly.

The three Heavenly Court immortals were controlling the Immortal Gu House Illusion Garden, combining the strength of three rank eights, using this to be able to trap Bo Qing's immortal zombie body and Yu Mu Chun in it.

Time passed, several days later.

Southern Border, on the nameless mountain.

Bam bam bam!

Three explosions resounded, and bright light blossomed.

Xiao Mang was sent flying, blood spurted out from his mouth while in the air.

Bam.

A muffled sound echoed.

He did not crash on the ground, but was instead caught by the elders behind him with some difficulty.

Defeated!

Xiao Mang's face was pale as paper, he opened his eyes wide, staring fixedly at Xiao Shan with hatred and anger.

Behind Xiao Shan stood two demonic path Gu Masters, both rank five experts, one tall and fat, another short and thin.

Several days ago, Xiao Shan had set foot in the forbidden area at the back of Light Mountain, breaking Xiao clan's rules, and had to be punished. Xiao Mang took this chance to seize authority and kill Xiao Shan.

Xiao Shan ran as quickly as he could, while Xiao Mang hunted him down with the elders.

Their chase had brought them to this nameless mountain peak, Xiao Shan was in a hopeless situation with no way out, just as he was about to be killed by Xiao Mang, two demonic path Gu Masters descended from the sky and saved him.

Xiao Mang was filled with anger at having all his efforts go to waste at the last moment, he pushed away the hands of the elders supporting him as he stood up, shouting at Xiao Shan: "Xiao Shan, sure enough, you were harboring evil intentions! As a clan leader of the righteous path, you were secretly colluding with demonic path Gu Masters!!"

Xiao Shan threw his head back and laughed loudly, his laughter filled with grief and indignation: "I really misjudged you, for power, you were actually willing to kill me! You have such a vicious heart, it is so funny that I always treated you as my only close relative in the world. You can distort the facts as you like, but I believe that others will easily be able to discern the truth."

"Lord Xiao Mang, the enemy's strength is great, we should retreat."

"Right, we have enough time."

"Xiao Shan is heavily injured and near death, but the two rank five demonic path Gu Masters behind him are in good condition."

The elders tried to quietly persuade him.

"Hmph!" Xiao Mang spat out some blood and said with disdain, "Those two are also nothing but stray dogs, their cultivation might be high but they don't have many Gu worms, what are you afraid of?"

Although he said this, Xiao Mang also knew that he would be unable to kill his own elder brother, Xiao Shan, today.

The dark light in his eyes flickered as he internally pondered: "Right now, I already hold the upper hand and also have the basis of righteousness on my side. There is no need to go all-out, after returning to Light Mountain, I can inherit the position of clan leader! At that time, I can use my identity in the righteous path to issue a warrant and bounty for Xiao Shan's head. Xiao Shan is without a clan now, and with the righteous path's warrant, he can only live as a fugitive with his strength decreasing constantly. It will be wiser if I bide my time and kill him in the future."

With these thoughts, Xiao Mang did not stubbornly persist.

"Xiao Shan, you traitor of the righteous path, you will surely die like a dog. For now, I will spare your life, just you wait, I will come to take it in the future! Let's go!"

After leaving behind these vicious words, Xiao Mang and the elders cautiously retreated.

He was also injured but he still had ample strength left.

The two demonic path Gu Masters did not have many Gu worms and so did not dare to go on a reckless chase, letting them leave.

"Brother Xiao, we meet again!" The tall and fat rank five demonic path Gu Master was called Sun Pang Hu, after he saw Xiao Mang had left, he looked at Xiao Shan with tears in his eyes.

The short and thin rank five Gu Master was called Zhou Xing Xing, he was supporting Xiao Shan's shoulder while activating a healing Gu worm: "Talk about the past later, heal brother Xiao's injuries first!"

Xiao Shan's heavy injuries were quickly stabilized under the efforts of these two Gu Masters.

Xiao Shan had an ashen expression as he heaved a deep sigh: "It is fortunate the two of you were here to help, otherwise I would have died here! But my younger brother is ruthless, he will definitely try to come after me again. He won't rest until he kills me, I can heal these injuries myself, both of you leave, I don't want to implicate you two!"

"What are you talking about, back then I was saved by you. My life is yours, brother Xiao!"

"Right! In the past, I had slaughtered an enemy's family for revenge, but was caught by brother Xiao. When you heard my story, you let me go that very night. This kindness has always been engraved in my mind."

Sun Pang Hu and Zhou Xing Xing spoke fervently and sincerely.

"Neither of us will leave you."

"If Xiao Mang wants to battle, he can come, I will fight him to the end!"

Sun Pang Hu and Zhou Xing Xing were extremely firm in their attitude.

Xiao Shan was very moved, his eyes started getting moist with tears: "Sigh, over these years, I have understood this. Who says demonic path Gu Masters are all ungrateful and unkind? Instead, the hypocrites who put on false pretences of kindness can be seen everywhere in the righteous path."

"Brother Xiao is correct! Many of us in the demonic path stay true to our nature, and the righteous path go through all possible means to kill us. Since the righteous path won't accept you, we will be a team from now on, and roam the world as part of the demonic path!" Sun Pang Hu spoke boldly.

Xiao Shan fell into silence.

He still had the mindset and ideals of the righteous path embedded in him, and he did not want to join the demonic path.

He knew there was an Immortal Gu hidden in him, he still wanted to restore his position in Xiao clan.

Zhou Xing Xing was observing his expression: "Brother, you may not understand. When people hear how you were expelled out of your clan and are being hunted by an insidious relative, many good people will come to help you. Brother, you have been just, upright and have aided people in need over these years, saving others from disasters without consideration for whether they belonged in the righteous or demonic path. Everyone will be willing to help you, willing to fight for you!"

Xiao Shan frowned, but did not respond.

At this moment, the voice appeared in his mind again: "Fool! Why do you need to rigidly mind the difference between righteous and demonic? Since you inherited my Immortal Gu, you have the ability to create your own Xiao clan and lead it to prosperity! i will give you a task now, listen carefully..."

Xiao Shan was excited, and listened carefully.

The voice in his mind told him that only by passing this test, he could truly earn the inheritance, getting the Immortal Gu and obtaining the method to become a Gu Immortal.

"Gather Gu Masters at this mountain and create a fortified village, and fight off any invading righteous path enemies. As long as it can be maintained for a hundred days, I can pass the test, obtaining the Immortal Gu and becoming a Gu Immortal!"

Xiao Shan's excitement was hard to describe, he clenched his fists and his eyes shined brightly.

"Good, then let's go all out! Let these so-called righteous path people look at our might!!" Xiao Shan suddenly spoke boldly.

Sun Pang Hu and Zhou Xing Xing were very happy.

After discussing for a while more, they felt a close affinity with each other, talking and drinking harmoniously.

Xiao Shan saw the timing was right and suggested becoming sworn brothers.

Sun Pang Hu and Zhou Xing Xing exclaimed that this was a wonderful thing!

Immediately, they chopped off a chicken's head, put drops of the blood into a single bowl of wine, before they all drank and used Gu to make an oath...

After they became sworn brothers, Xiao Shan's face also regained some rosiness, he stood up and faced the breeze of the mountain as he looked at the scenery in front of him.

He sighed: "The Xiao Shan of the righteous path from yesterday is dead, today, the one standing here is Xiao Shan of the demonic path. This place and I have a fated connection, it allowed me to run into the two of you, this is an arrangement of heaven! I want to build a new village on this mountain, we will welcome any demonic path Gu Masters. Let's work together and band up to resist the righteous path clans!"

Sun Pang Hu's face flushed with excitement, giving a thumbs-up as he praised: "Brother, you are truly a great hero with high morals, this is such a grand course of action!"

Zhou Xing Xing spat out saliva, speaking with a dark and ruthless look: "Screw it, I have been hunted everywhere by the righteous path over these years, living a life of a fugitive, I have been dissatisfied with this for a long time. Brother, I support you, we will do it like that!"

"My good brothers!" Xiao Shan grabbed the arms of Sun Pang Hu and Zhou Xing Xing, saying, "The demonic path is filled with mutual suspicion, if we are to accomplish this, we need to set aside our prejudices and doubts, and believe others, abiding by a spirit of loyalty and brotherhood. Our village shall be called Yi Tian Village! This mountain shall be called Yi Tian Mountain!"

Far away, Fang Yuan sighed as he observed all these events.

Indeed, this nameless mountain that hid the Immortal Gu House, Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, and the rank eight Great Strength True Martial immortal zombie was Yi Tian Mountain.

He had already recognized it the moment he saw this mountain.

It was just that he had not expected the true reason for the battle of Yi Tian Mountain in his previous life to be this.

"My status was too low back then, my vision was only limited to the mortal world. There are so many hidden details to history, who obtained the Immortal Gu House in my previous life?"

Fang Yuan was filled with the desire to explore this.

His gaze moved down again, piercing through the soil, inspecting the Immortal Gu House deep under the earth.

Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage was suppressing the Great Strength True Martial immortal zombie, it was extremely strong and the forbidden zone for immortals was caused by its strength seeping to the outside. Clearly, it contained the mysteries of food path, the Gu worms that formed the Immortal Gu House were full and in excellent condition.

And that rank eight immortal zombie, although possessing the Great Strength True Martial Physique, its main cultivation was wisdom path.

He naturally was not willing to be suppressed, and used a certain killer move, attempting to use his battle will to refine the Immortal Gu House.

He did not succeed.

His soul thoroughly died, only leaving behind an empty shell of a body.

But he did not completely fail either.

There were large quantities of his battle will in the Immortal Gu House, these battle wills were already purified by the Immortal Gu House's strength, becoming pure and ownerless battle will.

When battles occurred on Yi Tian Mountain, the intentions of Gu Masters to fight would form battle will, and resonate with the battle will in the Immortal Gu House, the pure battle will would then gradually turn into the Gu Master's individual battle will.

If someone turned all the battle will in the Immortal Gu House into their own battle will, they would complete the unfinished last step of the rank eight immortal zombie, that is, refining the Immortal Gu House and becoming the true owner of the Immortal Gu House!

The gambling contest agreed to by the Southern Border Gu Immortals revolved around this point.

First of all, the forbidden zone for immortals had already expanded to ten thousand li. Gu Immortals were unable to personally make a move, so they could only select mortals as their representatives.

Afterwards, they would form a battlefield, only continuous fierce battles could stimulate the battle will of mortal Gu Masters.

Then, the bodies of mortal Gu Masters would be tampered with via a simple wisdom path technique.

Finally, the pure battle will in the Immortal Gu House would convert into the Gu Immortal's personal battle will.

In conclusion: Gu Immortals would choose certain mortals and turn these mortals into tools, which the Gu Immortal would use to indirectly refine Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage.

Xiao Shan was the person selected by the supreme elder of Xiao clan.

On his body was not only the Immortal Gu of Xiao clan's supreme elder, there was also immortal essence and large amounts of the supreme elder's battle will.

It was just that Xiao Shan was only a mortal, only able to see the vague image of an Immortal Gu, and had no awareness of the truth.

Naturally, besides Xiao Shan, Xiao Mang was similarly a pawn of Xiao clan's supreme elder.

If it were not arranged by Xiao clan's supreme elder, how could Xiao Mang coincidentally run into Xiao Shan when he stepped foot in the forbidden area?

These two rank five Gu Masters, standing at the peak of the world of Gu Masters, were both in the dark, both being played in the hands of Xiao clan's supreme elder.

Chapter 964: Gua Lao Borrows Money

Xiao Shan forced Xiao clan's reinforcements into retreat, and after naming this mountain Yi Tian Mountain, he began to invite demonic path members from all over, building up his forces.

Before he was expelled from the clan, he was known for his grand morals, his social network was extremely large and he had been popular in both the righteous and demonic path.

Xiao Shan's nature was straightforward, he clearly separated kindness and hatred, and emphasized close connections and loyalty.

On the other side, Xiao clan was weakening, suppressed and pressured by Wu clan and other forces from all sides. Sometimes, even demonic path Gu Masters could not be offended, especially those lone warriors with rank four and rank five cultivation.

These demonic path experts were different from the righteous path experts.

Demonic path experts were loners, acting without scruples, but righteous path experts were bound by morals, family, reputation and so on.

Xiao clan had established a caravan years ago to strengthen themselves. These wandering demonic path experts were treated with even more caution compared to other clans.

Over these last years, Xiao Shan let these demonic path Gu Masters go, or roped them in if he could, but if it came down to killing, he would do it with all his strength and as fast as possible. Occasionally, he even aided some lone cultivators or demonic cultivators financially. Thus, although he was a righteous path clan leader, he had obtained the approval of many Gu Masters of the demonic path.

All these gave Xiao Shan a strong rallying force.

When the news of him creating a fortified village was spread, there were many immediate responses.

A few days later, several demonic path experts traveled from far away to join Xiao Shan.

Moreover, the Gu Immortal of Southern Border intensified the situation in secret, so as to easily put their own pawns in the battlefield.

Thus, more and more demonic path Gu Masters and lone cultivators started joining Yi Tian Village.

In just six to seven days, Yi Tian Village already had over thirty members. Such a speed made even Xiao Shan shocked and surprised.

As the number of people grew, they formed an organization.

Any organization needed to have distinctions in status.

In the world of Gu Masters, the strong were always revered.

Among all these people, Xiao Shan not only had the highest strength, he also had the highest reputation, he was chosen by everyone as Yi Tian Village's leader, stably placed at the highest ranking.

His two sworn brothers, Sun Pang Hu and Zhou Xing Xing, respectively were placed at the second and third ranks. After all, they were rank five experts, having the highest strength among others.

As for the other people, the vast majority were rank two and rank three, with few at rank four. Their statuses were arranged simply according to their cultivation and strength.

In a mountain cave, Fang Yuan was drinking wine with a Gu Immortal.

This demonic path rank six Gu Immortal was short but had a large head, he was an old man and his name was Gua Lao.

"Here, brother Sheng Ying, give it a sip, how is the taste of my melon wine?" Gua Lao enthusiastically urged Fang Yuan to drink.

Fang Yuan knew Gua Lao's intention in coming, without saying anything, he drank a mouthful and nodded, critiquing: "Not bad, not bad."

Although he said 'not bad', but Fang Yuan's expression was impassive and it was clear he had spoken only half-heartedly.

Gua Lao was observing him, he chuckled and pointed outside: "I wonder what opinion brother Sheng Ying has towards this grand contest of Southern Border?"

Fang Yuan calmly replied: "Given that it concerns who Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage will belong to, no one will yield a step. Since everyone is participating in this contest and has joined the agreement, putting forth their wagers, there should not be anyone who will cause trouble."

In the past, it was always the righteous path who suppressed the demonic path.

Whether it be in the mortal Gu Master world or the Gu Immortal world.

But right now was an exception.

The appearance of the Immortal Gu House completely shook the world of Southern Border's Gu Immortals. To seize the Immortal Gu House, demonic and lone immortals emerged, forming a huge force that gave the righteous path no choice but to compromise and set up this large gambling contest.

The content of the wager was to select mortals as pawns who would participate in the battle between the righteous and demonic paths in Yi Tian Mountain, helping the Gu Immortal behind them to refine the Immortal Gu House.

But to participate in this huge contest, there were some conditions.

Any Gu Immortal that wanted to participate in this gambling contest had to make a wager. Those who made larger wagers could arrange pawns with higher cultivation and enter the battle earlier.

Finally, when the gambling contest ends, all the wagers would be redistributed.

Each Gu Immortal would be ranked according to the amount of battle will they refined. Whoever had higher quantities of battle will in the Immortal Gu House would accordingly have higher returns.

Naturally, one that refined over fifty percent of the battle will would be the winner who could activate the Immortal Gu House, obtaining the highest returns from their bet.

But other Gu Immortals would also be able to get some profits, they might even be able to get great returns from small bets, earning a huge fortune.

This condition could be considered to be superb!

It was because of this that all the Gu Immortals participating in the gambling contest, be it righteous path, demonic path or lone cultivators, whether they had enmity or resentment, they all subconsciously worked together to maintain this unrivaled gambling contest.

Anyone who attempted to play dirty tricks or acted shamelessly would have their wagers completely confiscated.

Gu Immortals who arrived later could also join in, but they had to take part in the gambling.

And as the gambling contest progressed, if Gu Immortals wanted to raise their bets, they could do so.

And this demonic immortal Gua Lao in front of Fang Yuan was a person who wanted to raise his bet.

But he lacked the capital to do so.

Over these last days, he went around borrowing money, so everyone knew of it. This time, he intentionally came to find Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was giving him the cold shoulder, Gua Lao had no choice but to take the initiative to mention the gambling contest.

Fang Yuan had only given a casual analysis, but Gua Lao squinted and gave a thumbs-up, exaggeratedly smiling: "Brother Sheng Ying, you are right, you have hit the nail on the head. The rules of this contest cannot be broken by anyone. If anyone breaks them, it will be akin to making Gu Immortals of the whole of Southern Border their enemies! So they need to earn capital and participate honestly in the contest."

"Just look at it, the contest has just started, but Xiao clan's supreme elder is already at the lead. Xiao Shan is his pawn and from the previous battle of Xiao Shan and Xiao Mang, Xiao clan's supreme elder has become the first to refine the battle will in the Immortal Gu House. As long as Xiao Shan doesn't die, his lead will continue increasing."

Fang Yuan glanced at Gua Lao: "Xiao Shan is a rank five Gu Master and was the first to enter the mountain, Xiao clan's supreme elder naturally will have a huge advantage. But, he has also paid a large price for this, although he is only a rank seven Gu Immortal, his wagers are the highest, to the extent that even rank eight Gu Immortals cannot match it."

Gua Lao nodded repeatedly, and grinned, revealing his yellow teeth: "Yes, the earlier we can place our pawns in Yi Tian Mountain, the more beneficial it would be. Of course, the cultivation of these pawns need to be ensured, they should at least be rank four, otherwise they will likely die there and we will just suffer losses. Brother Sheng Ying, I won't conceal it from you, I really hate not being able to put myself as a wager! I am a bit short on funds right now, brother Sheng Ying, could you lend me some immortal materials? Wait till this is over, and I will return double the amount!"

Fang Yuan smiled: "Sure."

Gua Lao was joyous, and was just about to say his thanks, when Fang Yuan said: "But we need to set a vow."

"This is natural, and it is a must as well." Gua Lao nodded quickly.

Fang Yuan continued: "Also, take out an Immortal Gu as collateral."

Gua Lao's joyful expression immediately stiffened: "Brother Sheng Ying, is this a joke? If I had an Immortal Gu, why would I go for this Immortal Gu House?"

Fang Yuan's expression also changed, with a face filled with coldness, he glared violently and spoke: "Gua Lao, you don't even have one Immortal Gu, but are actually scheming for this Immortal Gu House? Don't you think you are indulging in a wild fantasy? Aren't you too greedy?!"

"Sheng Ying, you..." Gua Lao was just about to flare up, but suddenly he sensed an aura of Immortal Gu from Fang Yuan's body, no longer concealed.

"He actually has Immortal Gu!" Gua Lao's heart immediately sank.

Many rank six Gu Immortals did not have even one Immortal Gu.

But Fang Yuan did.

This surpassed Gua Lao's expectations. As far as he was concerned, any Gu Immortal with Immortal Gu would have some reputation.

But Sheng Ying clearly did not.

He had taken Fang Yuan to be a weak lone immortal, cultivating bitterly in some unvisited area of the world.

But Fang Yuan had Immortal Gu, this caused fear to emerge in Gua Lao's heart.

With an Immortal Gu, the Gu Immortal's battle strength would often rise by a large extent. Sheng Ying, with Immortal Gu, was not someone Gua Lao could handle.

Thus, he did not vent his anger and finally forced a smile as he cupped his fists towards Fang Yuan: "I was too abrupt and rude, brother Sheng Ying, please don't mind it!"

Fang Yuan gave a cold snort: "You can leave."

"I am leaving, leaving now, farewell!" Gua Lao smiled as he retreated a few steps, before turning around and leaving, not daring to linger.

When he walked out of the cave, the smile on his face disappeared, replaced by shame and anger.

His gaze was cold, as he roared in his mind: "Hmph! Having Immortal Gu is indeed amazing! I shall remember this humiliation. Wait for the day I have an Immortal Gu, I will return this humiliation back to you!!"

Inside the cave, Fang Yuan was thinking.

Gua Lao's matter made him aware of the gambling mentality of many bottom tier Gu Immortals.

Most of these people did not have Immortal Gu, so they had an extreme thirst for the Immortal Gu House. They all knew that success could not be built on small efforts, but when it concerned themselves, who did not want to soar to the sky with a step and get rich overnight?

The gambling contest in front of them gave these Gu Immortals an extremely favorable environment to compete in.

If it were a normal situation, for instance, finding wild Immortal Gu, the Gu Immortals would engage in fighting each other. These bottom tier Gu Immortals with no Immortal Gu had low battle strength, how could they compete with other Gu Immortals?

But what this gambling contest examined were other aspects, not the Gu Immortal's own battle strength.

This gave hopes of success to the bottom tier Gu Immortals.

Examples like Gua Lao were not few in number.

Fang Yuan then thought of Xiao clan's supreme elder.

According to the news, this rank seven Gu Immortal was facing a huge problem. He had barely gotten past extreme danger in his previous tribulation, and his strength had yet to recover. The next tribulation, which would be even more powerful, was already approaching.

Xiao clan only had one Gu Immortal remaining, that was him. Without another Gu Immortal's support, he would not be able to face this tribulation by himself, and his death was almost certain.

However, this gamble gave him hope of surviving.

If he obtained the Immortal Gu House, he would have huge assurance in getting through this tribulation.

Thus, he brought out all he had and went all in on this gamble, placing the highest wagers. These wagers gave him the qualifications to select two pawns.

Moreover, both the pawns had rank five cultivation. Among them, Xiao Shan was the first to enter the area of the contest, the other, Xiao Mang, would enter the stage after some more time.

Xiao Shan belonged to the demonic path and Xiao Mang belonged to the righteous path, no matter what the result between the righteous and demonic paths was, or how the process went, Xiao clan's supreme elder was well-prepared with having these two arranged. The two rank five pawns had a low likelihood of death, as time passed, the advantage of Xiao clan's supreme elder would continue growing larger.

"This time, I intentionally leaked out an Immortal Gu's aura so as to let other Gu Immortals feel sufficiently cautious and not take me as a weakling."

"I need to properly participate in this gambling contest. The information exposed from the gambling contest is extremely valuable, it is a most precious opportunity for me to get close to the world of Southern Border's Gu Immortals and understand their structure!"

"As for this gamble, maybe I can personally take action..." A sharp light flashed past Fang Yuan's eyes.